* [](javascript:void(0);)
    
    Global
    
    * Africa

    * Asia Pacific

    * Europe

    * Latin America

    * Middle East

    * North America

* |
* [BUSINESSES](javascript:void(0);)
    
    BUSINESSES

* |
* |

* Close

* [Industries](javascript:void(0);)
    
    Industries

* [Company](javascript:void(0);)
    
    Company

        OT Cybersecurity

* [News & Media](javascript:void(0);)
    
    News & Media

* [](javascript:void(0);)
    
    Global
    
    * Africa

    * Asia Pacific

    * Europe

    * Latin America

    * Middle East

    * North America

* |
* [BUSINESSES](javascript:void(0);)
    
    BUSINESSES

* |
* |

Search

You are browsing the product catalog for

/content/honeywellbt/us/en/search.html

title

subtitle

Language

**Last updated April 29, 2024**

**Introduction**

Honeywell International Inc. (“**Honeywell**”, “**our**”, “**us**”, or “**we**”), is the "data controller" of the personal information we collect about you when you visit or use any of our websites, or use products, services and applications that are linked to this Privacy Statement (collectively, our “**Sites**”).  This Privacy Statement explains how we collect, share and use your personal information collected in this way and how you can exercise your privacy rights.

When we interact with you, we may also provide you with additional privacy notices about specific processing activities or offer you additional choices about how Honeywell processes your personal information at that particular point in time.   

 Click on one of the links below to jump to the section that interests you:

**Our collection of information**

* **Information collected directly from you**. We may ask you for personal information to provide a service or carry out a transaction that you have requested. You may also provide personal information to us when you contact or engage with us (e.g., with a comment, inquiry or customer support request, site visitors) or register for an account to use our Sites. This personal information may include:
    * **Identity data,** such as your name, title, company/organization name, e-mail address, telephone numbers and physical address (including street, city, state, postal or zip code, and/or country);           
    * **Registration data,** provided by you when you register for an account to use our Sites, including usernames and passwords;  
        
    * **Recruitment data,** including information submitted in connection with a job application or inquiry (as described below); 
    * **Business contact data**, such as information related to other employees, owners, directors, officers, or contractors of a third-party organization (e.g., business, company, partnership, sole proprietorship, non-profit, or government agency);
    * **Biometric data**, such as facial recognition scanning, for health, safety, and security screening and other administrative functions;
    * **Marketing and communications data,** including your marketing preferences and your subscriptions to our publications;  
        
    * **Financial information,** including credit card or other financial account information for the purpose of enabling us to facilitate your purchase of Company products and services that may be available on our Sites;  
        
    * **Export control information,** such as your nationality, citizenship and country of residence, that allows us to determine your eligibility under export control regulations to receive information about certain technologies;  
        
    * **Transaction data,** including inquiries about and orders for our products and services and details of payments to and from you, including purchase order history and information needed to facilitate payment transactions;  
        
    * **Event registration information,** including information you provide when filling in e-registration forms; and  
        
    * **Your feedback,** including surveys, recommendations, or other feedback from you about our Sites as well as our products and services generally.

When you do not provide requested information, we may not be able to provide you the requested service or complete your transaction.

* **Information we collect automatically about you**. We collect certain information about your visit to our Sites using cookies and similar tracking technologies. We will always respect any legal rights you may have to prevent us doing this. Data collected in this way includes:
    * **Usage data,** including information about how you use our Sites, what pages you view, the number of bytes transferred, the links you click, the materials you access, the date and time you access the Site, the website from which you linked to one of our Sites and other actions taken within the Sites; and  
        
    * **Technical data,** such as your Internet Protocol (IP) address, your browser type and capabilities and language and your operating system.

For information about the cookies and other similar tracking technologies we use on our Sites, please refer to our [Cookie Notice](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice).

* **Geo-location information.** For certain Sites, with your consent, we may collect the precise, real-time location (i.e., geo-location) of your mobile device. This information will be used only for purposes of facilitating your use of the Sites including by our service providers who may process this information in connection with providing services on our behalf. If given, you may adjust this consent by managing your Location Services preferences through the settings of your mobile device.
* **Information collected from third parties.** In accordance with applicable law, we may collect personal information about you from third parties, such as social media websites and applications and combine it with information we already hold, to help us improve and customize our Sites to your preferences and for other purposes set forth in this Privacy Statement. We may also collect your business contact information from your employer or other third parties to facilitate or otherwise engage in traditional business activities and similar administrative matters.

**Our use of information**

We may use the personal information collected via our Sites or when you contact us for purposes that include:

* **Business Contact Data**. Honeywell collects and uses business contact data to engage in communications or transactions, including for conducting due diligence regarding, or providing or receiving, a product or service. For example, Honeywell may collect and use this business contact data in order to facilitate and manage orders, contracts, warranties, maintenance, and similar business functions, for credit analysis and collection purposes, to assist with our own internal compliance and legal requirements, and (if necessary) to defend our interests and claims.
* **Services and transactions.** We may use your personal information to deliver services to you or carry out transactions you have requested, including, but not limited to, providing information on Company products or services you have purchased or otherwise use, registering purchased products, processing product orders, handling warranty claims, replacing product manuals, answering customer service requests and facilitating the use of our Sites.
* **Administering and protecting our business and Sites.** We may use your personal information to administer and protect our business and our Sites, including troubleshooting, system maintenance, support, reporting and hosting of data.
* **Improving our business, Sites, products and services.** We may use your personal information to perform business analyses or for other purposes that help us to develop and improve the quality of our business, Sites, products and services (including new products and services), for example, by customizing our Sites to your particular preferences or interests.
* **Marketing.** In accordance with applicable laws and regulations, we may use your personal information to inform you of products or services which may be of interest to you, and to otherwise communicate with you about offerings, events and news, surveys, special offers, and related topics. You are able to opt-out from marketing communications sent via e-mail at any time, free of charge by using the “unsubscribe” link in any e-mail marketing materials you receive from us, or by contacting us using the contact information listed in this Privacy Statement. Depending on your country of residence, you may also be able to opt out of other types of marketing communications; please contact us using the contact information listed in the Privacy Statement for more information. Some jurisdictions provide individuals (e.g., California residents) with the right to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for the third party’s direct marketing purposes.  For more information on our data disclosure practices for marketing purposes, please contact us in accordance with the instructions listed below.
* **Interest-Based Advertising.** We collect data about your online activities and identify your interests so that we can provide advertising that is most relevant to you. You can opt out of receiving interest-based advertising from Honeywell as described in our [Cookie Notice](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice).
* **Financial Incentive and Loyalty Programs**. We collect and use personal information to maintain and administer our financial incentive and loyalty programs. We use the personal information you provide in these programs to offer unique rewards, track your program status, and to facilitate the exchange of program points for products, promotional materials, training workshops, and other items. To the extent permitted by law, we may also use any personal information that you provide in the context of a financial incentive program for any other purpose set forth in this Privacy Statement. Please review the terms and conditions of each financial incentive program in which you would like to register or participate as such terms and conditions may be narrowly tailored to the applicable program. If you consent to participate in these programs, you may withdrawal that consent at any time by contacting us using the contact details at the end of this Privacy Statement or in accordance with the instructions set forth in the applicable program’s terms and conditions.
* **Employment applications.** In connection with a job application or inquiry, you may provide us with information about yourself, such as a resume/curriculum vitae, professional references, information about education and job background, and information about professional training and certifications. We and members of our group may use this information for the purpose of employment consideration, background checks and employment eligibility, and as otherwise set forth in any separate privacy statement or other notice made available to in connection with your application. We may use a third party (e.g., job recruiter) or social media platform to solicit, collect, and retain employment applications. For more information, please read our [Applicant Privacy Notice](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/applicant-privacy-notice).
* **Research and analysis.** We may use your personal information to conduct research and analysis to help us analyse your purchasing preferences, identify the products and services that best meet your requirements and measure the effectiveness of the advertising we serve you.
* **Enforcement:** We may use the personal information we collect in order to detect, prevent and respond to fraud, intellectual property infringement, violations of our terms and conditions, violations of law or other misuse of our Sites.

Where permitted by law, we may combine the information that we collect via our Sites with other information we hold about you (such as information about your use of our products and services) in order to offer you an improved and consistent customer experience when interacting with us or for other purposes set forth in this Privacy Statement.

**The legal basis on which we process information**

Where required by law, we will ensure there is a legal basis for the processing of your personal information. In most cases our legal basis will depend on the personal information concerned and the specific context in which we collect it.

* **Contract**: the processing is necessary for the performance of the services we provide to you, or in order to take steps (at your request) prior to, and anticipation of, performing, such services;
* **Legal obligation**: the processing is necessary to comply with our legal obligations, including compliance with applicable laws, regulations, governmental and quasi-governmental requests, court orders or subpoenas;
* **Consent**: the processing is based on your consent to the processing of your personal information for one or more specified purposes (e.g. marketing);
* **Legitimate interests:** the processing is necessary to meet our legitimate interests, for example to develop and improve our Sites, products and/or services for the benefit of our customers; or
* **Vital interests**: the processing is necessary to protect your vital interests (for example, health and safety reasons if you attend a meeting at a Honeywell location).

If you have any questions about or need further information concerning the legal basis on which we collect and use your personal information, please send an email to [HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com).

**Anonymizing information**

In accordance with applicable law, we may anonymize your personal information so that it can no longer be used to identify you. Anonymized information is not considered personal information and is therefore not subject to this Privacy Statement. We may collect, use, aggregate and share anonymized information for any purpose.

**How long we keep information**

The period during which we store your personal information varies depending on the purpose for the processing. For example, we store personal information needed to provide you with products and services, or to facilitate transactions you have requested, for so long as you are a customer of Honeywell or if you submit an employment application via our Sites, we will retain details of your application as set forth in the privacy notice made available to you in connection with your application or as otherwise required by law. In all other cases, we store your personal information for as long as is needed to fulfil the purposes outlined in this Privacy Statement, following which time it is either anonymized (where permitted by applicable law), deleted or destroyed.

**Disclosure of information**

We may share your personal information with selected third parties in accordance with applicable law, including as set out below:

* **Our group companies.** We may share your personal information with our affiliates and group companies as reasonably necessary for the purposes set out in this Privacy Statement.
* **Service providers.** We may share your personal information with companies with which we have contracted to provide services on our behalf, such as hosting websites, conducting surveys, processing transactions, analyzing our Sites and performing analyses to improve the quality of our business, Sites, products and services. We require these service providers to protect the confidentiality of your personal information.
* **Distributors and other trusted business partners.** We may share your personal information with third parties that distribute our products and other trusted business partners for purposes that include allowing those third parties to send marketing communications to you. Such sharing of personal information for marketing purposes will be performed in accordance with applicable laws and regulations.
* **Disclosure in connection with transactions.** In connection with certain transactions, we may disclose some or all of your personal information to financial institutions, government entities and shipping companies or postal services involved in fulfilment of the transaction.
* **Disclosures in connection with acquisitions or divestitures.** Circumstances may arise where for strategic or other business reasons Honeywell decides to sell, buy, divest, merge or otherwise reorganize businesses in some countries. We may disclose information we maintain about you to the extent reasonably necessary to proceed with the negotiation or completion of a merger, acquisition, divestiture or sale of all or a portion of Honeywell’s assets.
* **Disclosure for other reasons.** We may disclose personal information if required or authorized to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with legal requirements or with legal process served on us, to protect and defend our rights or property or, in urgent circumstances, to protect the personal safety of any individual.

**International transfers**

Honeywell is a global organization and your personal information may be transferred to, held, stored or used across various locations worldwide such as the US, Mexico and India in accordance with applicable law. This means that when we collect your personal information it may be processed in countries that may have data protection laws that are different to the laws of your country. However, Honeywell will always take reasonable steps to protect your privacy and to provide a level of protection of personal information that is comparable to that of your country of residence which include implementing the European Commission's Standard Contractual Clauses. For more information on the appropriate safeguards in place to protect your personal information, please contact us at [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com).

**Biometric Data Policy (Illinois Residents Only)**

Honeywell may collect and use biometric data for health, safety, security, and other administrative functions, such as for performing wellness and health screening at our facilities, implementing timekeeping programs, implementing authentication and access controls with respect to Honeywell computers and other technology resources, and undertaking security measures, such as video surveillance with biometric-enabled features. Notwithstanding anything to the contrary in this Privacy Statement, it is Honeywell policy to retain biometric data for no longer than one (1) year following the last interaction between the applicable individual and us, provided however, we may retain such biometric data beyond this retention timeframe when permitted or otherwise required to comply with an applicable law, or a valid warrant, subpoena, or order issued by a court of competent jurisdiction, or for Honeywell to establish, exercise, or defend against, legal claims so long as we retain such biometric data for the minimum time necessary in order to satisfy the same. Honeywell has implemented and maintains commercially reasonable protocols for permanently destroying, or disposing of, biometric data in a manner that will not intentionally compromise its confidentiality. For the avoidance of doubt, this paragraph does not, and is not intended to, abrogate the confidential nature of any internal Honeywell policy, procedure, or record related to the processing of biometric data or other personal data concerning a Honeywell employee, contractor, or temporary worker. This paragraph only applies to individuals who reside in Illinois, United States and furnish their biometric data to Honeywell.

**Washington Residents Only**

Please read [the Washington State Consumer Health Data Privacy Policy](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/washington-consumer-health-data-privacy-policy) for additional information about the processing of your personal data and your privacy rights. 

**Security**

We are committed to protecting the security of your personal information. We use technical and organisational measures to provide a level of security appropriate to the risk of processing your personal information. For more information on how Honeywell protects your personal information please contact us at [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com).

**Your rights**

Depending on applicable law, you may have certain rights with respect to your personal information.

* You may have the right to **access, correct, update** or **request deletion** of your personal information.
* You can **object** to the processing of your personal information, ask us to **restrict** processing of your personal information or request **portability** of your personal information.
* You may have the right **not to have a decision made about you that is based solely on automated processing, including profiling** if that decision produces legal effects about you or significantly affects you.
* Similarly, if we have collected and process your personal information with your consent, then **you can withdraw your consent at any time**. Withdrawing your consent will not affect the lawfulness of any processing we conducted prior to your withdrawal, nor will it affect processing of your personal information conducted in reliance on lawful processing grounds other than consent.
* You may have the right to **opt-out of the sale of your personal information**. Honeywell does not sell your personal information to third parties for profit. However, we do share or otherwise disclose your personal information to third parties in accordance with this Privacy Statement and our [Cookie Notice](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice). For example, we engage with third parties to distribute our products, provide you with technical assistance, operate website analytical tools and features, and engage in marketing and sales of our products and services. Such activities may involve the disclosure of your personal information to third parties and may be considered a “sale” of data under certain (but not all) data protection laws.
* You have the right to **complain** to a data protection authority responsible for overseeing compliance with data protection law in your jurisdiction about our collection and use of your personal information if you believe our processing of your personal information does not comply with data protection law. For example, individuals in the EEA have the right to lodge a complaint with the competent Data Protection Authority, a list of which can be accessed at: [https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/board/members\_en](https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/board/members_en).  We would however appreciate the chance to address your concerns, so please feel free to contact us regarding any complaint you may have.  We will not discriminate against individuals for exercising their data privacy rights.

We will facilitate your exercise of the rights that apply to you in accordance with applicable law. However, even if your personal information is not afforded protection under, or otherwise subject to, a data protection law, we may seek to accommodate any request or inquiry you may have with regard to our data processing activities. If you have questions about your rights or wish to exercise your rights, you can contact us at [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com) or submit privacy questions via our interactive webform at the following link:  

**Children's information**

Our Sites are not directed to, and should not be used by, children under the age of sixteen (16) and we do not knowingly collect, use or sell information from such individuals. If you are a minor as understood by laws of your country, please do not submit any personal information through our Sites.

**Links to other websites**

Our Sites may contain links to third-party websites, products and services. We have no liability or responsibility for those websites, products and services, their policies, or their collection or other processing of your personal information. The practices of those third parties is governed by their own privacy policies. We encourage you to learn about the privacy policies of those third parties.

**Contact us**

If you have questions regarding this Privacy Statement or our handling of your personal information, would like to lodge a complaint, or wish to contact our Data Protection Officer, please contact us using the contact information listed below. We will promptly address your concern and strive to reach a satisfactory resolution. 

Interactive Webform:   
  
Email:   
  
Mailing Address:   
Honeywell Privacy   
4D5   
115 Tabor Road   
Morris Plains, NJ 07950  
  
Toll-Free Number:   

**Changes to this Privacy Statement**

We may occasionally update this Privacy Statement. When we do, we will revise the "last updated" date at the top of the Privacy Statement and take such additional steps as may be required by law.

**Last updated April 29, 2024**

**آخر تحديث بتاريخ 11 يونيو 2021**

**مقدّمة**

تُعدّ شركة Honeywell International Inc. (المشار إليها باسم **"Honeywell"**، أو**"خاصتنا"،** أو**"الخاصة بنا"،** أو **"نحن**")، هي "المتحكم في البيانات" المتعلقة بالمعلومات الشخصية التي نجمعها عنك عندما تزور أيًّا من مواقعنا الإلكترونية أو تستخدمها، أو عندما تستخدم المنتجات، والخدمات، والتطبيقات المرتبطة ببيان الخصوصية هذا (ويشار إليها إجمالًا باسم **"المواقع").** يوضح بيان الخصوصية هذا كيفية جمعنا لمعلوماتك الشخصية المجمّعة بهذه الطريقة، وكيفية مشاركتها، واستخدامها، كما يوضّح كيفية ممارستك لحقوق الخصوصية الخاصة بك.

وعندما نتفاعل معك، فسيمكننا كذلك تزويدك بإشعارات إضافيةٍ تتعلق بالخصوصية حول أنشطة معالجةٍ معيّنةٍ أو نعرض عليك خياراتٍ إضافيةً حول طريقة معالجة Honeywell لمعلوماتك الشخصية في ذلك التوقيت الزمني المحدد.

انقر فوق أحد الروابط أدناه للانتقال إلى القسم الذي يلفت انتباهك:

**تجميعنا للمعلومات**

* **معلوماتٌ يتم تجميعُها منك بشكلٍ مباشر**. قد نطلب منك معلوماتٍ شخصيّة لتقديم خدمةٍ أو تنفيذ معاملةٍ قمت طلبتها. كما يمكنك تقديم معلوماتٍ شخصيةٍ إلينا عندما تتصل بنا أو تتواصل معنا (لذكر تعليقٍ -مثلًا- أو استفسارٍ ما، أو لطلب دعم العملاء، أو بخصوص زوار الموقع) أو التسجيل للحصول على حساب لاستخدام مواقعنا. وقد تتضمّن هذه المعلومات الشخصية ما يلي:  
    * **بيانات الهوية،** مثل الاسم، والمسمى الوظيفي، واسم الشركة/المؤسسة، وعنوان البريد الإلكتروني، وأرقام الهواتف، والعنوان الفعلي (وهذا يتضمّن اسم الشارع، و/أو المدينة، و/أو الولاية، و/أو الرمز البريدي، و/أو البلد)؛
    * **بيانات التسجيل،** والتّي تزوّدنا بها عند التسجيل للحصول على حسابٍ لاستخدام مواقعنا، بما في ذلك أسماء المستخدمين وكلمات المرور؛
    * **بيانات التوظيف،** بما في ذلك المعلومات المقدّمة حول التقدّم لوظيفة أو الاستفسار عنها (كما هو موضح أدناه)؛
    * **بيانات الاتصال الخاصة بالأعمال التجارية،** مثل المعلومات المتعلقة بالموظفين الآخرين، أو أصحاب العمل، أو المديرين، أو المسؤولين، أو المقاولين التابعين لمؤسسةٍ خارجية (على سبيل المثال: عمل تجاري، أو شركة، أو شراكة، أو ملكية فردية، أو جهة غير ربحية أو حكومية).
    * **بيانات التسويق والاتصالات،** بما في ذلك تفضيلاتك التسويقية واشتراكاتك في المنشورات الخاصة بنا؛
    * **المعلومات المالية،** بما في ذلك معلومات بطاقة الائتمان، أو معلومات الحسابات المالية الأخرى؛ لتمكيننا من تسهيل شرائك لمنتجات الشركة وخدماتها التي قد تكون متاحةً على مواقعنا؛
    * **معلومات مراقبة الصادرات،** مثل الجنسية، والمواطنة، وبلد الإقامة، ما يسمح لنا بتحديد أهليّتك لتلقّي معلوماتٍ حول تقنياتٍ معينةٍ بموجب لوائح مراقبة الصادرات؛
    * **بيانات المعاملات،** بما في ذلك الاستفسارات والأوامر ذات الصلة بمنتجاتنا وخدماتنا وتفاصيل المدفوعات الصادرة منك والواردة إليك، وهذا يشمل محفوظات أوامر الشراء والمعلومات اللازمة لتسهيل معاملات الدفع؛
    * **معلومات تسجيل الأحداث،** ويشمل ذلك المعلومات التي تقدّمها عند ملء استمارات التسجيل الإلكتروني؛ و
    * **ملاحظاتك،** بما في ذلك الاستطلاعات، أو التوصيات، أو ملاحظاتك الأخرى حول مواقعنا، وكذلك حول منتجاتنا، وخدماتنا بشكلٍ عام.

في حال لم تقم بتقديم المعلومات المطلوبة، فقد لا نتمكن إذًا من تزويدك بالخدمة المطلوبة أو من إكمال معاملتك.

* **معلوماتٌ حولك نجمعها تلقائيًا.** نعمل على جمع معلوماتٍ معينةٍ حول زيارتك لمواقعنا باستخدام ملفات تعريف الارتباط وتقنيات التتبع المماثلة. وسنراعي دائمًا أي حقوق قانونية يمكنك استخدامها لمنعنا من القيام بذلك. وتتضمن البيانات التي يتم جمعها بهذه الطريقة ما يلي:
    * **بيانات الاستخدام،** بما في ذلك المعلومات المتعلّقة بكيفية استخدامك لمواقعنا، والصفحات التي تشاهدها، وعدد وحدات البايت المنقولة، والروابط التي تنقر فوقها، والمواد التي تصل إليها، وتاريخ وصولك إلى الموقع ووقت وصولك إليه، والموقع الإلكتروني الذي قمت بربطه بأحد مواقعنا، وغير ذلك من الإجراءات المتَّخذة داخل المواقع؛ إلى جانب
    * **المعلومات الفنّية،** مثل عنوان بروتوكول الإنترنت (IP)، ونوع المتصفّح الخاص بك وإمكانياته واللغة المستخدمة فيه، ونظام التشغيل الخاص بك.

للحصول على معلوماتٍ حول ملفات تعريف الارتباط وتقنيات التتبع المماثلة الأخرى التي نستخدمها على مواقعنا، يُرجى الرجوع [إلى إشعار ملفات تعريف الارتباط لدينا](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#arabic).

* **معلومات الموقع الجغرافي.** بالنسبة لبعض المواقع، يمكننا -بموافقتك- جمع البيانات الدقيقة للموقع الفعليّ (أي الموقع الجغرافي) لجهازك المحمول. وسيكون الغرض الوحيد من استخدام هذه المعلومات هو تسهيل استخدامك للمواقع، وهذا يشمل استخدامها من قِبل مزودي الخدمة لدينا الذين قد يعالجون هذه المعلومات في سياق تقديم الخدمات نيابةً عنا. وفي حال موافقتك، يمكنك تعديل هذه الموافقة بإدارة تفضيلات خدمات الموقع من خلال الإعدادات الموجودة بجهازك المحمول.
* **المعلومات المُجمّعة من جهاتٍ خارجية.** طبقًا للقانون المعمول به، يُسمح لنا بجمع معلوماتٍ شخصيةٍ عنك من جهاتٍ خارجية -مثل المواقع والتطبيقات الخاصة بوسائل التواصل الاجتماعي- ودمجها مع المعلومات التي نحتفظ بها بالفعل؛ لمساعدتنا على تحسين مواقعنا وتخصيصها وفقًا لتفضيلاتك، وكذلك لأغراضٍ محددةٍ أخرى في بيان الخصوصية هذا. كما يُسمح لنا بجمع معلومات الاتصال التجارية الخاصة بك من صاحب العمل لديك أو من جهاتٍ خارجيةٍ أخرى؛ لتسهيل أنشطة الأعمال التقليدية والمسائل الإدارية المماثلة أو المشاركة فيها بطرقٍ أخرى.

**استخدامنا للمعلومات**

يُسمح لنا باستخدام المعلومات الشخصية التي يتم جمعها عبر مواقعنا أو أثناء اتصالك بنا لأغراضٍ تشمل ما يلي:

* بيانات الاتصال التجارية. تعمل شركة Honeywell على جمع **بيانات الاتصال التجارية** واستخدامها للمشاركة في الاتصالات أو المعاملات، بما في ذلك إجراء العناية الواجبة فيما يتعلق بمنتجٍ معيّنٍ أو خدمةٍ معيّنةٍ، أو توفيرها، أو الحصول عليها. فمثلًا، قد تقوم شركة Honeywell بجمع بيانات الاتصال التجارية هذه واستخدامها لتسهيل الأوامر، والعقود، والضمانات، والصيانة، والوظائف التجارية المشابهة وإدارتها، تحقيقًا لأغراض تحليل الائتمان والتّحصيل؛ للمساعدة في الامتثال الداخلي وتحقيق المتطلبات القانونية الخاصة بنا، وللدفاع عن مصالحنا ومطالباتنا (إذا لزم الأمر).
* **الخدمات والمعاملات.** يُسمح لنا باستخدام معلوماتك الشخصية لتزويدك بالخدمات أو تنفيذ المعاملات التي طلبتها، ومن ذلك -على سبيل المثال لا الحصر- تقديم معلوماتٍ عن منتجات الشركة أو خدماتها التي اشتريتها أو استخدمتها بأي طريقةٍ أخرى، إلى جانب تسجيل المنتجات التي اشتريتها، ومعالجة أوامر الشراء، والتعامل مع مطالبات الضمانات، واستبدال أدلّة استخدام المنتجات، والرد على طلبات خدمة العملاء، وتسهيل استخدام مواقعنا.
* **إدارة أعمالنا التجارية ومواقعنا وحمايتها.** يمكن أن نستخدم معلوماتك الشخصية لإدارة أعمالنا ومواقعنا وحمايتها، بما في ذلك استكشاف الأخطاء وإصلاحها، وصيانة النظام، والدعم، وإعداد التقارير، واستضافة البيانات.
* **تحسين أعمالنا التجارية، ومواقعنا، ومنتجاتنا، وخدماتنا.** قد نستخدم معلوماتك الشخصية لتحليل الأعمال، أو لأغراضٍ أخرى تساعدنا على تطوير جودة أعمالنا التجارية، ومواقعنا، ومنتجاتنا، وخدماتنا، وتحسينها (بما في ذلك المنتجات والخدمات الجديدة)، ويكون ذلك -على سبيل المثال- بتخصيص مواقعنا لتناسب تفضيلاتك الخاصة واهتماماتك.
* **التسويق.** طبقًا للقوانين واللوائح المعمول بها، قد نستخدم معلوماتك الشخصية لإبلاغك بالمنتجات أو الخدمات التي قد تهمك، أو للتواصل معك بشأن العروض، والأحداث، والأخبار، والاستطلاعات، والعروض الخاصة، والموضوعات ذات الصلة. ويمكنك إلغاء الاشتراك في المراسلات التسويقية المرسلة عبر البريد الإلكتروني في أي وقت، مجانًا، وذلك باستخدام رابط "إلغاء الاشتراك" في أي مواد تسويقية تتلقاها منا عبر البريد الإلكتروني، أو عن طريق الاتصال بنا باستخدام معلومات الاتصال المدرجة في بيان الخصوصية هذا. وحسب بلد إقامتك، قد تتمكن كذلك من إلغاء الاشتراك في أنواعٍ أخرى من المراسلات التسويقية؛ ولمزيدٍ من المعلومات، يُرجى الاتصال بنا باستخدام معلومات الاتصال المدرجة في بيان الخصوصية. كما تمنحُ بعض السلطات الحقَّ للأفراد (على سبيل المثال، سكان كاليفورنيا) في طلب معلوماتٍ معينةٍ بخصوص إفصاحنا عن المعلومات الشخصية لجهاتٍ خارجيةٍ لأغراض التسويق المباشر من جانب تلك الجهات. ولمزيدٍ من المعلومات حول ممارسات الإفصاح عن البيانات لأغراض التسويق لدينا، يُرجى الاتصال بنا وفقًا للتعليمات المذكورة أدناه.
* **الإعلانات القائمة على الاهتمامات.** نقوم بجمع بياناتٍ حول أنشطتك عبر الإنترنت ونحدّد اهتماماتك لنتمكن من أن نقدّم إليك الإعلانات الأكثر صلةً بك. يمكنك إلغاء الاشتراك في تلقي الإعلانات القائمة على الاهتمامات من شركة Honeywell كما هو موضّحٌ في [إشعار ملفات تعريف الارتباط الخاص بنا](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#arabic).
* **برامج الحوافز المالية والولاء.** نقوم بجمع المعلومات الشخصية واستخدامها للحفاظ على برامج الحوافز المالية والولاء وإدارتها. فنحن نستخدم المعلومات الشخصية التي تقدّمُها لنا في هذه البرامج لتقديم مكافآت فريدة، وتتبُّع حالة البرنامج لديك، وتسهيل تبديل نقاط البرنامج للمنتجات، والمواد الترويجية، وورش العمل التدريبية، وغيرها من العناصر. كما يُسمح لنا باستخدام أي معلومات شخصية تقدمها -بالحد الذي يسمح به القانون- في سياق برنامج الحوافز المالية لأي غرض آخر من الأغراض المنصوص عليها في بيان الخصوصية هذا. يُرجى مراجعة الشروط والأحكام الخاصة بكل برنامج من برامج الحوافز المالية التي ترغب في التسجيل فيها أو المشاركة فيها، فقد تكون هذه الشروط والأحكام موضوعةً بشكل حازمٍ حسب البرنامج المعمول به. في حال وافقت على المشاركة في هذه البرامج، يمكنك سحب هذه الموافقة في أي وقتٍ عن طريق الاتصال بنا باستخدام تفاصيل جهات الاتصال المدرجة في نهاية بيان الخصوصية هذا أو وفقًا للتعليمات المنصوص عليها في الشروط والأحكام الخاصة بالبرنامج المعمول به.
* **طلبات التوظيف.** فيما يتعلق بالتقدّم بطلبٍ لوظيفةٍ ما أو الاستفسار عنها، يمكنك تزويدنا بمعلوماتٍ عن نفسك، مثل بيان السيرة/السيرة الذاتية، والمراجع المهنية، ومعلوماتٍ حول مؤهلاتك التعليمية وخلفيتك الوظيفية، ومعلوماتٍ حول التدريب والشهادات المهنية. ويُسمح لنا ولأعضاء مجموعتنا باستخدام هذه المعلومات لغرض النّظر في طلبات التوظيف، والتحقق من الخلفية ومن الأهلية لشغل الوظيفة، كما يُسمح لنا باستخدامها على النحو المنصوص عليه بخلاف ذلك في أي بيان خصوصيةٍ منفصلٍ أو أي إشعارٍ آخر تتم إتاحته فيما يتعلق بطلبك الذي تقدّمه. قد نلجأ إلى استخدام جهةٍ خارجيةٍ (على سبيل المثال: مسؤول توظيف) أو استخدام منصةٍ من منصات وسائل التواصل الاجتماعي لاجتذاب طلبات التوظيف، وتجميعها، والاحتفاظ بها. لمزيدٍ من المعلومات، يُرجى قراءة إشعار [خصوصية مقدّم الطلب الخاص](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/applicant-privacy-notice) بنا.
* **البحث والتحليل.** يمكن أن نستخدم معلوماتك الشخصية لإجراء البحث والتحليل، وذلك لمساعدتنا في تحليل تفضيلات الشراء الخاصة بك، وتحديد المنتجات والخدمات التي تلبي متطلباتك على أفضل وجهٍ، وقياسِ فعالية الإعلانات التي نعرضها لك.
* **الاستخدام الإلزامي:** يمكن أن نستخدم المعلومات الشخصية التي نجمعها من أجل اكتشاف محاولات الاحتيال، أو انتهاكات الملكية الفكرية، أو انتهاكات الشروط والأحكام الخاصة بنا، أو انتهاكات القانون، أو أي إساءة استخدام أخرى لمواقعنا، إلى جانب منعها، والاستجابة لها.

قد نقوم بدمج المعلومات التي نجمعها عبر مواقعنا مع المعلومات الأخرى التي نحتفظ بها حولك (مثل المعلومات المتعلقة باستخدامك لمنتجاتنا وخدماتنا) -أينما سمح القانون بذلك- من أجل أن نقدم لك تجربة عملاءٍ محسّنةٍ ومتّسقةٍ عند التفاعل معنا أو لأغراض أخرى من المنصوص عليها في بيان الخصوصية هذا.

**الأساس القانوني الذي نستند إليه في معالجة المعلومات**

سنضمن وجود أساس قانوني لمعالجة معلوماتك الشخصية حيثما يقتضي القانون ذلك. يعتمد أساسنا القانوني -في معظم الحالات- على المعلومات الشخصية المعنيّة وعلى السياق المحدد الذي نجمعها فيه.

* **اتفاق:** تُعد المعالجة أمرًا ضروريًا لأداء الخدمات التي نقدمها لك، أو لاتخاذ خطوات (بناءً على طلبك) قبل تنفيذ هذه الخدمات، بالإضافة إلى توقّعها؛
* **الالتزام القانوني:** تُعد المعالجة أمرًا ضروريًا امتثالًا لالتزاماتنا القانونية، بما في ذلك الامتثال للقوانين واللوائح المعمول بها، أو الطلبات الحكومية، أو شبه الحكومية، أو الأحكام القضائية، أو مذكرات الإحضار؛
* **الموافقة:** تعتمد المعالجة على موافقتك على معالجة معلوماتك الشخصية لغرضٍ واحدٍ محددٍ أو أكثر من غرض (مثل التسويق)؛
* **المصالح المشروعة:** تُعد المعالجة أمرًا ضروريًا لتلبية مصالحنا المشروعة، ومن ذلك -على سبيل المثال- تطوير مواقعنا و/أو منتجاتنا و/أو خدماتنا وتحسينها لصالح عملائنا؛ أو
* **المصالح الحيوية:** تُعد المعالجة أمرًا ضروريًا لحماية مصالحك الحيوية (ومن ذلك على سبيل المثال: الأسباب المتعلّقة بالصحة والسلامة إذا كنت ستحضر اجتماعًا في موقع شركة Honeywell).

إذا كانت لديك أي أسئلةٍ أو كنت بحاجةٍ إلى مزيدٍ من المعلومات بشأن الأساس القانوني الذي نستند إليه في جمع معلوماتك الشخصية واستخدامها، فيُرجى إرسال رسالة إلكترونية عبر [HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com)

**إخفاء مصادر المعلومات**

يُسمح لنا -طبقًا للقانون المعمول به- بإخفاء مصادر معلوماتك الشخصية، بحيث لا يمكن استخدامها فيما بعد لتحديد هويتك. لا تُعدُّ المعلومات مجهولة المصدر معلوماتٍ شخصية، ومن ثمّ فهي لا تخضع لبيان الخصوصية هذا. يُسمح لنا بجمع المعلومات مجهولة المصدر، واستخدامها، وتجميعها، ومشاركتها لأي غرضٍ كان.

**مدّة احتفاظنا بالمعلومات**

تختلف الفترة التي نحتفظ فيها بمعلوماتك الشخصية باختلاف الغرض من المعالجة. فمثلًا، نحتفظ بالمعلومات الشخصية اللازمة لتزويدك بالمنتجات والخدمات، أو لتسهيل المعاملات التي طلبتها، طالما أنك عميلٌ لشركة Honeywell أو في حال تقدّمت بطلب توظيفٍ عبر مواقعنا، فسنحتفظ بتفاصيل طلبك على النحو المنصوص عليه في إشعار الخصوصية المتاح لك فيما يتعلق بهذا الطلب أو حسبما يقتضيه القانون. أمّا في جميع الحالات الأخرى، فإننا نحتفظ بمعلوماتك الشخصية طالما كانت ضروريةً لتحقيق الأغراض الموضّحة في بيان الخصوصية هذا، وبعد ذلك الوقت تكون هذه المعلومات مجهولة المصدر (حيثما يسمح القانون المعمول به) أو محذوفةً، أو تالفة.

**الإفصاح عن المعلومات**

يُسمح لنا بمشاركة معلوماتك الشخصية مع جهاتٍ خارجيةٍ محددةٍ طبقًا للقانون المعمول به، بما في ذلك مشاركتها على النحو الموضّح أدناه:

* **مجموعة شركاتنا.** يمكن أن نشارك معلوماتك الشخصية مع الشركات التابعة لنا ومجموعة الشركات حسبما تقتضيه الضرورة -بشكلٍ معقولٍ- تحقيقًا للأغراض المنصوص عليها في بيان الخصوصية هذا.
* **مقدمو الخدمة.** يمكن أن نشارك معلوماتك الشخصية مع الشركات التي تعاقدنا معها لتقديم الخدمات بالنيابة عنا، مثل استضافة مواقع الويب وإجراء الاستطلاعات، ومعالجة المعاملات، وتحليل مواقعنا، وإجراء التحليلات لتحسين جودة أعمالنا التجارية ومواقعنا، ومنتجاتنا وخدماتنا. ونحن نطلب من مزودي الخدمة هؤلاء حماية سرية معلوماتك الشخصية.
* **الموزعون والشركاء التجاريون الآخرون الموثوق بهم.** قد نشارك معلوماتك الشخصية مع جهاتٍ خارجيةٍ توزع منتجاتنا، ومع شركاء تجاريين موثوقين آخرين لأغراضٍ تشمل السماح لتلك الجهات الخارجية بإرسال مراسلاتٍ تسويقيةٍ إليك. وستتم مشاركة المعلومات الشخصية لأغراض التسويق على هذا النحو طبقًا للقوانين واللوائح المعمول بها.
* **الإفصاح المتعلق بالمعاملات.** قد نكشف عن بعض معلوماتك الشخصية أو كلها -فيما يتعلق بمعاملاتٍ معينةٍ- للمؤسسات المالية، أو الهيئات الحكومية، أو شركات الشحن، أو الخدمات البريدية، المتعلقة بتنفيذ المعاملة.
* **الإفصاحات المتعلقة بعمليات الاستحواذ أو التصفية.** قد تنشأ ظروف عندما تقرر شركة Honeywell -لأسبابٍ إستراتيجيةٍ أو لأسبابٍ تجاريةٍ أخرى- بيع الأعمال التجارية، أو شراءها، أو تجريدها، أو دمجها، أو إعادة تنظيمها بطريقةٍ أخرى في بعض البلدان. وقد نكشف عن المعلومات التي نحتفظ بها عنك بالقدر الضروري -وبشكلٍ معقول- للمضي قدمًا في التفاوض أو إكمال عملية الدمج لجميع أصول شركة Honeywell أو جزءٍ منها، أو الاستحواذ عليها، أو سحبها أو بيعها.
* **الإفصاح لأسبابٍ أخرى.** يُسمح لنا بالإفصاح عن المعلومات الشخصية إذا اقتضى الأمر ذلك بموجب القانون، أو عند الاعتقاد -بحسن نيةٍ- أن هذا الإجراء ضروري للامتثال للمتطلبات القانونية أو للإجراءات القانونية التي نخضع لها، وذلك بهدف حماية حقوقنا، أو ممتلكاتنا، والدفاع عنها، أو لحماية السلامة الشخصية -في حالات الطوارئ- لأي فردٍ.

**عمليات النقل الدولية**

شركة Honeywell هي مؤسسةٌ عالمية، ويمكن من خلالها نقل معلوماتك الشخصية، أو الاحتفاظ بها، أو تخزينها، أو استخدامها عبر مواقع مختلفةٍ في جميع أنحاء العالم، مثل الولايات المتحدة، والمكسيك، والهند، ويكون ذلك طبقًا للقانون المعمول به. ما يعني أنه حين نجمع معلوماتك الشخصية، فمن المحتمل أن تتم معالجتها في البلدان التي تُطبّق فيها قوانين مختلفةٌ عن قوانين بلدك فيما يخُصّ حماية البيانات. ومع ذلك، ستتخذ شركة Honeywell دائمًا خطواتٍ مقبولةٍ لحماية خصوصيتك، ولتوفير مستوى من الحماية للمعلومات الشخصية يمكن مقارنته بمستوى بلد إقامتك، والذي يتضمن تنفيذ البنود التعاقدية القياسية للمفوضية الأوروبية. لمزيدٍ من المعلومات حول الضمانات المناسبة المعمول بها لحماية معلوماتك الشخصية، يُرجى التواصل معنا عبر [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com).

**الأمان**

نحن ملتزمون بحماية أمان معلوماتك الشخصية. نستخدم التدابير الفنية والتنظيمية لتوفير مستوى من الأمان يتناسب مع المخاطر المتعلّقة بمعالجة معلوماتك الشخصية. ولمزيدٍ من المعلومات حول كيفية حماية شركة Honeywell لمعلوماتك الشخصية، يُرجى التواصل معنا عبر [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com)

**حقوقك**

طبقًا للقانون المعمول به، فإنك قد تتمتّع بحقوقٍ معينةٍ فيما يتعلق بمعلوماتك الشخصية.

* فقد يكون لك الحق في **الوصول إلى معلوماتك الشخصية أو تصحيحها، أو تحديثها، أو** طلب حذفها.
* ويمكنك **الاعتراض** على معالجة معلوماتك الشخصية، كما يمكنك أن تطلب منا **تقييد** عملية معالجة معلوماتك الشخصية أو أن تطلب **قابلية نقل** معلوماتك الشخصية.
* قد يكون لديك الحق **في عدم الالتزام بقرارٍ اتُّخذ بشأنك ويستند بالكامل إلى المعالجة الآلية، بما في ذلك جمع المعلومات** إذا كان هذا القرار تنتج عنه آثار قانونية تتعلق بك أو يؤثر عليك بشكلٍ كبير.
* وبالمثل، إذا قمنا بجمع معلوماتك الشخصية ومعالجتها بموافقتك، يمكنك حينها **سحب موافقتك في أي وقت.** لن يؤثر سحب موافقتك على شرعية أي معالجة أجريناها قبل انسحابك، ولن يؤثر على معالجة معلوماتك الشخصية التي تتم وفقًا لأسس معالجةٍ قانونيةٍ بخلاف الموافقة.
* قد يكون لك الحق في **اختيار عدم بيع معلوماتك الشخصية.** لا تبيع شركة Honeywell معلوماتك الشخصية لجهاتٍ خارجيةٍ بغرض الربح. ومع ذلك، فإننا نشارك معلوماتك الشخصية أو نكشف عنها بطريقةٍ أخرى لجهاتٍ خارجية بما يتوافق مع بيان الخصوصية هذا ومع [إشعار ملفات تعريف الارتباط](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#arabic) الخاص بنا. فنحن نتشارك -على سبيل المثال- مع جهاتٍ خارجيةٍ لتوزيع منتجاتنا، ونوفر لك المساعدة الفنية، ونقوم بتشغيل الأدوات التحليلية والمزايا لمواقع الويب، ونشارك في تسويق منتجاتنا، وخدماتنا، وبيعها. وقد تتضمّن هذه الأنشطة الكشف عن معلوماتك الشخصية لجهاتٍ خارجية، وقد تعتبر "عملية بيعٍ" للبيانات بموجب بعض القوانين المعنيّة بحماية البيانات (وليس كلّها).
* لديك الحق في **رفع شكوى** إلى سلطة حماية البيانات المسؤولة عن الإشراف على الامتثال لقانون حماية البيانات في ولايتك القضائية بشأن جمعنا لمعلوماتك الشخصية واستخدامها إذا كنت تعتقد أن معالجتنا لمعلوماتك الشخصية لا تتوافق مع قانون حماية البيانات. فيحقّ -على سبيل المثال- للأفراد في المنطقة الاقتصادية الأوروبية التقدّم بشكوى إلى هيئة حماية البيانات المختصة، والتي يمكن الوصول إلى قائمتها عبر: [https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/board/members\_en](https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/board/members_en). ومع ذلك، فإننا نقدّر منحك الفرصة لمواجهة مخاوفك، لذلك لا تتردد في الاتصال بنا بخصوص أي شكوى قد ترغب في التقدّم بها. ولن يصدر منّا أي شكل من أشكال التمييز ضد أي فردٍ من الأفراد لممارستهم حقوق خصوصية البيانات الخاصة بهم.

وسنعمل على تسهيل ممارسة الحقوق التي تنطبق عليك وفقًا للقانون المعمول به. وعلى أي حالٍ، فحتى إذا كانت معلوماتك الشخصية غير متاحةٍ للحماية بموجب قانون حماية البيانات، أو كانت لا تخضع له بأي شكلٍ آخر، فقد نسعى إلى تلبية أي طلبٍ أو استفسارٍ قد يكون لديك فيما يتعلق بأنشطة معالجة البيانات الخاصة بنا. وإذا كانت لديك أسئلةٌ حول حقوقك أو كنت ترغب في ممارستها، يمكنك التواصل معنا عبر [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com) أو إرسال أسئلة الخصوصية عبر نموذج الويب التفاعلي الخاص بنا من خلال الرابط التالي:

**المعلومات الخاصة بالأطفال**

لا تُوجَه مواقعنا إلى الأطفال الذين تقل أعمارهم عن ستة عشر (16) عامًا ولا ينبغي عليهم استخدامها، ونحن لا نقوم بجمع أي معلوماتٍ من هؤلاء الأفراد، أو بيعها، أو استخدامها عن قصد. وإذا كنت قاصرًا حسب ما تنصّ عليه قوانين بلدك، فيُرجى عدم إرسال أي معلوماتٍ شخصيةٍ عبر مواقعنا.

**روابط لمواقع ويب أخرى**

قد تحتوي مواقعنا على روابط لمواقع ويب، ومنتجاتٍ، وخدماتٍ تابعةٍ لجهات خارجية. نحن لا نتحمل أي التزامٍ أو مسؤوليةٍ تجاه تلك المواقع، أو المنتجات، أو الخدمات أو سياساتها، أو تجميعها لمعلوماتك الشخصية، أو سبل معالجتها الأخرى لمعلوماتك الشخصية. وتخضع ممارسات تلك الجهات الخارجية لسياسات الخصوصية الخاصة بها. ونحن نحثّك على التعرف على سياسات الخصوصية لتلك الجهات الخارجية.

**تواصل معنا**

إذا كانت لديك أي أسئلةٍ فيما يتعلق ببيان الخصوصية هذا أو بطريقة تعاملنا مع معلوماتك الشخصية، أو كنت ترغب في التقّدم بشكوى، أو في الاتصال بمسؤول حماية البيانات لدينا، فيُرجى الاتصال بنا باستخدام معلومات الاتصال المدرجة أدناه. سنتعامل مع مخاوفك على الفور وسنسعى للتوصل إلى حلٍّ مرضٍ.

نموذج الويب التفاعلي :  

البريد الإلكتروني :  

العنوان :  
Honeywell Privacy  
4D5  
115 Tabor Road  
Morris Plains, NJ 07950

رقم المكالمات المجانية :  

**التغييرات في بيان الخصوصية هذا**

قد نقوم بتحديث بيان الخصوصية هذا من حينٍ لآخر. وعندما نقوم بذلك، سنحرص على مراجعة تاريخ "آخر تحديث" في الجزء العلوي من بيان الخصوصية وسنراعي اتّخاذ الخطوات الإضافية التي قد يقتضيها القانون.

**آخر تحديث بتاريخ 11 يونيو 2021**

**上次更新日期 2021年 12 月 02 日**

**简介**

当您访问或使用我们涉及隐私声明的任何网站、产品、服务和应用程序（统称为我们的“站点”）时，Honeywell International Inc.（**“霍尼韦尔”**或**“我们”**）会收集您的个人信息，并且是所收集信息的数据控制者。 本隐私声明说明了我们如何收集、共享和使用借此收集的您的个人信息，以及您可以如何行使您的隐私权。

当我们与您互动时，可能还会向您发布有关特定处理活动的其他隐私通知，或为您提供关于霍尼韦尔在该特定时间点如何处理您个人信息的其他选择。

单击下方的链接之一，跳转到您感兴趣的部分：

**信息的收集**

* **直接向您收集的信息**。为了按照您的请求提供服务或进行交易，我们可能会请您提供个人信息。 与我们联系或合作（例如提供意见、查询事宜、有客户支持请求或访问站点），或者为使用我们的站点而注册帐户时，也可能需要您向我们提供个人信息。 这些个人信息包括：
    * **身份数据，**例如您的姓名、职务、公司/组织名称、电子邮件地址、电话号码和实际地址（包括国家/地区、省/自治区/直辖市、市、街道和邮政编码）；
    * **注册数据，**您为使用我们的站点而注册帐户时提供的信息，包括用户名和密码；
    * **招聘数据，**包括在申请工作或查询时提交的信息（如下所述）；
    * **业务联系数据，**例如与第三方组织（如企业、公司、合伙企业、独资企业、非营利组织或政府机构）的其他员工、所有者、董事、高级职员或承包商相关的信息。
    * **营销和通讯数据，**包括您的购买偏好，以及您对我们出版物的订阅；
    * **财务信息，**包括信用卡或其他财务帐户信息，旨在方便您购买我们的站点上可能提供的公司产品和服务；
    * **出口管制信息，**例如您的国籍、公民身份以及所在国家/地区，以便我们可依据出口管制法规确定您是否有资格获知关于某些技术的信息；
    * **交易数据，**包括与我们的产品和服务相关的查询和订单，以及您的收付款详细信息，包括购买订单历史记录和促进付款交易所需的信息；
    * **活动注册信息，**包括您在填写电子注册表单时提供的信息；以及
    * **您的反馈，**包括您对我们的站点以及产品和服务整体上的调查结果、建议或其他反馈。

如果您没有提供请求的信息，我们可能无法为您提供请求的服务或完成您的交易。

* **我们自动收集的与您相关的信息**。我们会使用 Cookie 和类似跟踪技术来收集有关您访问我们站点的某些信息。 您有阻止我们收集这些信息的合法权利，我们将一直尊重您的此等权利。 以此方式收集的数据包括：
    * **使用数据，**包括以下相关信息：您如何使用我们的站点、查看的页面、传送的字节数、单击的链接、访问的资料、访问站点的日期和时间、您从哪个网站链接到我们的某个站点，以及在站点内执行的其他操作；以及
    * **技术数据，**例如 Internet 协议 (IP) 地址、浏览器类型、功能和语言，以及操作系统。

有关我们在霍尼韦尔站点上使用的 Cookie 和其他类似跟踪技术，请参阅我们的 [Cookie 声明](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#language3)。

* **地理位置信息**。对于某些站点，经您同意后，我们可能会收集您移动设备的准确、实时位置（即地理位置）。 此信息将仅用于方便您使用站点，包括我们的服务提供商可能会出于代表我们提供服务而处理此信息。 您给予同意后，也可以更改此同意，方法是在您移动设备的设置中，管理“定位服务”首选项。
* **从第三方收集的信息**。依据适用的法律，我们可能会从第三方（例如社交媒体网站和应用程序）处收集与您相关的个人信息，并将此类信息与我们已有的信息结合使用，来帮助我们根据您的偏好并出于本隐私声明中所列的其他目的，改进和定制我们的站点。我们还可能会从您的雇主或其他第三方处收集您的业务联系信息，以促进或参与传统业务活动和类似的管理事项。
* **敏感个人信息**。根据适用法律，我们收集的有关您的一些个人信息可能被视为“敏感”信息，视情况而定，**其中可能包括财务信息、交易信息和跟踪信息**。

**信息的使用**

通过霍尼韦尔站点或您联系我们时收集的个人信息，可能会用于以下目的，包括：

* **业务联系数据**。 霍尼韦尔将收集和使用业务联系数据进行沟通或交易，包括就产品或服务开展尽职调查，或者提供或接收产品或服务。 例如，霍尼韦尔可能会收集和使用此类业务联系数据来促进和管理订单、合同、保修、维护和类似业务职能；用于信用分析和收集；帮助达成我们自己内部的合规性和法律要求；以及（如有必要）捍卫我们的利益和主张。
* **服务和交易**。我们可能会使用您的个人信息按您的请求提供服务或进行交易，包括但不限于提供有关您已购买或以其他方式使用的公司产品或服务的信息、注册所购买的产品、处理产品订单、处理保修索赔、更换产品手册、回应客户服务请求以及方便使用我们的站点。
* **管理和保护我们的业务与站点**。我们可能会使用您的个人信息管理和保护我们的业务和站点，包括疑难解答、系统维护、支持以及数据的报告和托管。
* **改进我们的业务、站点、产品和服务**。我们可能会使用您的个人信息执行业务分析，或将其用于其他目的，来帮助我们发展业务、站点、产品和服务（包括新产品和服务）和改进其质量，例如根据您的特定偏好或兴趣定制我们的站点。
* **营销**。依据适用的法律和法规，我们可能会使用您的个人信息向您告知您可能感兴趣的产品或服务，或以其他方式向您告知产品和服务、活动和新闻、调查、特惠以及相关主题。 您可以随时选择不接收通过电子邮件发送的营销资讯，而无需承担任何费用，方法是使用我们发送给您的任何电子邮件营销资料中的“取消订阅”链接，或者使用本隐私声明中所列的联系信息联系我们。 根据您所在的国家/地区，您还可以选择不接收其他类型的营销资讯；有关详情，请使用本隐私声明中所列的联系信息联系我们。在某些司法管辖区，个人（如加利福尼亚州居民）有权请求有关我们向第三方披露个人信息以用于第三方直接营销的特定信息。 想了解更多我们出于营销目的而采取的数据披露做法，请按照下文的说明与我们联系。
* **根据兴趣推送广告**。 我们收集您的在线活动数据并明确您的兴趣所在，从而提供您最兴趣的广告。 您可以按照我们的 [Cookie 声明](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#language3)所述，选择不接收霍尼韦尔根据兴趣提供的广告。
* **财务激励和忠诚度计划**。 我们收集和使用个人信息来维护和管理我们的财务激励与忠诚度计划。 我们使用您在这些计划中提供的个人信息来提供特殊奖励、跟踪您的计划状态，并促进用计划积分兑换产品、促销材料、培训研讨会和其他项目。 在法律允许的范围内，我们还可能会出于本隐私声明中所列的任何其他目的，将您提供的任何个人信息用于财务激励计划。 请查看您要注册或参与的每个财务激励计划的条款和条件，因为这些条款和条件可能严格限于适用计划。 如果您同意参与此类计划，您可以随时撤销此项同意，方法是使用本隐私声明在末尾提供的详细联系信息或根据适用计划的条款和条件中所列的说明与我们联系。
* **就职申请**。在工作申请或查询中，您可能会向我们提供有关您自己的信息，例如简历、职业推荐信、有关教育和工作背景的信息以及有关职业培训和证书的信息。我们和我们集团的成员可能会将此类信息用于雇佣考虑、背景调查和就业资格认定，以及与您的申请相关的任何单独隐私声明或其他适用通知中所列的其他目的。 我们可能会使用第三方（例如招聘机构）或社交媒体平台来征集、收集和保留就职申请。 有关更多信息，请查看我们[的求职者隐私声明](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/applicant-privacy-notice#chinese)。
* **调查和分析**。我们可能会使用您的个人信息进行研究和分析，来帮助我们分析您的购买偏好、确定最能满足您要求的产品和服务，并衡量我们向您提供的广告的效果。
* **强制实施：**我们可能会将收集的个人信息用于检测、阻止和应对欺诈、知识产权侵犯、违反我们的条款和条件、违反法律或其他滥用我们站点的行为。

在法律允许的范围内，我们可能会将通过我们的站点收集的信息与我们拥有的与您相关的其他信息（例如与您使用我们的产品和服务相关的信息）结合使用，以在您与我们交互时为您提供改进的一致客户体验，或将其用于本隐私声明中所列的其他目的。

**我们处理信息的法律依据**

在法律要求的情况下，我们将会确保根据法律依据处理您的个人信息。 在大多数情况下，我们的法律依据取决于相关个人信息以及我们收集个人信息所在的特定环境。

* **合同：** 要正常使用我们为您提供的服务，或者在提供此类服务之前（应您请求）采取措施或预计将提供此类服务，则必需处理您的个人信息；
* **法律义务：** 我们出于履行法律义务（包括遵循适用的法律、法规、政府和准政府请求、法院命令或传票）而必需处理您的个人信息；
* **同意：** 处理建立在您同意出于一个或多个指定目的（例如营销）处理您的个人信息的基础之上；
* **合法利益：** 处理对于行使我们的合法利益是必需的，例如为了我们客户的利益，开发和改进我们的站点、产品和/或服务；或者
* **重要利益：** 处理对于保护您的重要利益是必需的（例如，如果您在霍尼韦尔地点参加会议，则我们可能出于保护您的健康和安全的原因来处理您的个人信息）。

如果您对我们收集和使用您的个人信息的法律依据有任何疑问或需要进一步的信息，请发送电子邮件至 [HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com)

**对信息进行匿名化处理**

依据适用的法律，我们可能会匿名处理您的个人信息，以便该信息不再能够用于识别您的身份。 匿名信息不属于个人信息，因此不受本隐私声明的制约。 我们可能会出于任何目的收集、使用、整合和共享匿名信息。

**我们保留信息的时长**

我们存储您的个人信息的时长因处理目的而异。 例如，在您作为霍尼韦尔客户的时间内，我们会一直存储您的个人信息，以便为您提供产品和服务，或为您请求的交易提供便利；或者如果您通过我们的站点提交求职申请，除非法律另有要求，否则我们将根据提供的与您的申请相关的隐私声明中的规定，保留您的申请详细信息。 在其他所有情况下，根据适用法律，我们会按照实现本隐私声明中所列的目的所需的时长存储您的个人信息，此后将匿名保存（在适用法律允许的范围内）、删除或销毁该信息。

**信息的披露**

我们可能会依据适用的法律与包括以下方在内的所选第三方共享您的个人信息：

* **我们的集团公司**。出于本隐私声明中所述的目的，我们可能会根据合理需要，与我们的关联公司和集团公司共享您的个人信息。
* **服务提供商**。我们可能会与签订了合同代表我们提供服务（例如托管网站、开展调查、处理交易、分析我们的站点和执行分析）的公司共享您的个人信息，以便提高我们的业务、站点、产品和服务的质量。 我们要求这些服务提供商保护您的个人信息的机密性。
* **分销商和其他可靠业务合作伙伴**。我们可能会与分销我们的产品的第三方以及其他可靠业务合作伙伴共享您的个人信息，以用于允许这些第三方向您发送营销资讯等目的。 出于营销目的进行的此类个人信息共享，将依据适用的法律和法规执行。
* **执行交易时披露**。在执行某些交易时，我们可能会向执行交易过程中涉及的金融机构、政府部门和运输公司或邮政机关披露您的部分或全部个人信息。
* **收购或资产剥离时披露**。出于战略原因或其他商业原因，可能会出现霍尼韦尔决定出售、购买、资产剥离、合并或以其他方式重组某些国家/地区内的企业的情况。 我们仅会披露我们所保留的有关您的合理必要信息，以便继续磋商或完成霍尼韦尔全部或部分资产的合并、收购、资产剥离或出售。
* **出于其他原因披露**。在以下情况下，我们可能会披露个人信息：法律规定或许可这么做；确信必须这么做才符合适用的法律规定或法律程序；保护和捍卫我们的权利或财产；在紧急情况下保护任何人的人身安全。

**跨国转移**

霍尼韦尔是一家全球性组织，因此可能会根据适用法律，将您的个人信息转移到世界各地或在这些地方保存、存储或使用您的个人信息，例如美国、墨西哥和印度等其他国家。 这意味着，当我们收集您的个人信息时，它可能会在其数据保护法律与您所在国家/地区的法律不同的国家/地区进行处理。 但是，霍尼韦尔将始终根据适用法律采取合理的措施来转移或处理您的个人信息，以保护您的隐私，并提供与您所在国家/地区同等水平的个人信息保护，其中包括执行相关监管部门批准的标准合同条款。

有关为保护您的个人信息所采取的相应安全保障措施的更多信息，请通过 [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com) 联系我们。

**安全性**

我们致力于保护您的个人信息的安全。 我们使用技术和组织措施来提供与处理您的个人信息的风险相适应的安全级别。有关霍尼韦尔如何保护您的个人信息的更多信息，请通过 [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com) 联系我们。

**您的权利**

根据适用法律，您对您的个人信息可能享有某些权利。

* 在适用及实际可行的情况下，您有权**访问、要求一份复印本、更正、更新**或要求**删除**您的个人信息。
* 您可以**反对**处理您的个人信息，要求我们**限制**处理您的个人信息或请求您的个人信息的**可移植性**。
* 您有权要求解释，并且要求**不完全基于自动化处理（包括分析）来做出有关您的、**会对您产生法律影响或对您有重大影响的决定。
* 同样，如果我们在征得您同意的情况下收集并处理了您的个人信息，**您可以随时撤销同意**。 撤销同意不会影响我们在您撤销之前进行的任何处理的合法性，也不会影响根据同意以外的合法处理理由对您个人信息的处理。
* 您有权**选择不出售您的个人信息**。 霍尼韦尔不会将您的个人信息出售给第三方以获取利润。 但是，我们会根据本隐私声明和我们的 [Cookie 声明](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#language3)，与第三方共享或以其他方式向第三方披露您的个人信息。 例如，我们会与第三方合作来分销我们的产品、向您提供技术帮助、运行网站分析工具和功能以及从事我们的产品和服务的营销与销售。 此类活动可能涉及向第三方披露您的个人信息，这些活动在某些（而非全部）数据保护法律下可能会被视为“出售”数据。
* 如果您认为我们在处理您的个人信息时未遵循数据保护法，您有权向您所在司法管辖区内负责监督数据保护法遵循情况的数据保护机构就我们收集和使用您的个人信息提出投诉。 例如，欧洲经济区的个人有权向主管的数据保护机构提出投诉，相关机构的列表可在以下位置访问： [https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/board/members\_en](https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/board/members_en)。 无论如何，我们都感谢您让我们有机会为您排忧解难，因此，敬请随时与我们联系，告知您可能提出的任何投诉。 我们不会因个人行使其数据隐私权而歧视他们。

我们将根据适用法律帮助您行使适用于您的权利。 不过，即使您的个人信息没有受到数据保护法的保护，我们也可能会力求满足您对我们的数据处理活动提出的任何请求或查询。 如果您对您的权利有疑问或希望行使您的权利，可以通过 [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com) 联系我们，或通过以下链接提供的交互式表单提交隐私问题：

**儿童的信息**

我们的站点不面向十六 (16) 周岁以下的儿童，也不应由他们使用，我们不会有意收集、使用或出售此类个人的信息。 如果您是您所在国家/地区的法律所理解的未成年人，请勿通过我们的站点提交任何个人信息。

**与其他网站的链接**

我们的站点可能包含指向第三方网站、产品和服务的链接。 对于这些网站、产品和服务及其政策，或它们对于您的个人信息的收集或以其他方式的处理，我们不负有任何义务或责任。 这些第三方的做法受其自己的隐私政策约束。 我们建议您了解这些第三方的隐私政策。

**联系我们**

如果您对本隐私声明或我们处理您的个人信息的方式有任何疑问，想要提出投诉，或希望联系我们的数据保护专员，请使用下面列出的联系信息与我们联系。 我们将立即着手解决您的问题并力争提供令您满意的解决方案。

交互式表单：  

电子邮件：  

邮寄地址：  
Honeywell Privacy  
4D5  
115 Tabor Road  
Morris Plains, NJ 07950

免费电话：  

**本隐私声明的变更**

我们有时可能会更新本隐私声明。 在更新时，我们将会修订本隐私声明顶部“上次更新”日期，并根据法律可能的要求采取此类其他措施。

**上次更新日期 2021 年 12月 02日**

**Naposledy aktualizováno 11. června 2021**

**Úvod**

Společnost Honeywell International Inc. (dále „**Honeywell**“, „**my**“, „**nás**“ nebo „**náš**“), je správcem údajů ve vztahu k osobním údajům, které o vás shromažďujeme, když navštívíte nebo používáte některý z našich webů, používáte naše produkty, služby a aplikace, jež jsou propojeny s tímto Prohlášením o ochraně soukromí (souhrnně dále „**weby**“). Toto Prohlášení o ochraně soukromí vysvětluje, jak shromažďujeme, sdílíme a používáme vaše osobní údaje, jež byly takto shromážděny, a jak můžete uplatnit svá práva z oblasti ochrany osobních údajů.

Při interakci s vámi vám můžeme poskytnout ještě další prohlášení o ochraně soukromí, jež se týkají konkrétních činností zpracování údajů, případně vám nabídnout další možnosti ohledně toho, jak bude společnost Honeywell v daném konkrétním čase zpracovávat vaše osobní údaje.

Kliknutím na některý z následujících odkazů přejdete na oddíl, který vás zajímá:

**Shromažďování údajů**

* **Údaje shromažďované přímo od vás**. Můžeme vás požádat o vaše osobní údaje, abychom mohli poskytnout službu nebo provést požadovanou transakci. Osobní údaje nám také můžete poskytnout, když nás kontaktujete nebo jste s námi v jiné interakci (např. nám pošlete komentář, dotaz, žádost o podporu, případně navštívíte náš web) nebo si zaregistrujete účet, abyste mohli používat naše weby. Mezi tyto osobní údaje se mohou řadit:
    * **údaje o identitě,** jako je vaše jméno, titul, název společnosti nebo organizace, e-mailová adresa, telefonní a faxové číslo a poštovní adresa (včetně ulice, obce, kraje, poštovního směrovacího čísla nebo země);
    * **registrační údaje,** které zadáte při registraci účtu, abyste mohli používat naše webové stránky, včetně uživatelských jmen a hesel;
    * **náborové údaje,** včetně údajů poskytnutých v souvislosti s žádostí o zaměstnání nebo dotazem na zaměstnání (viz níže);
    * **obchodní kontaktní údaje,** například údaje týkající se dalších zaměstnanců, vlastníků, ředitelů, představitelů nebo smluvních partnerů organizace, jež je třetí stranou (např. firmy, společnosti, partnerství, podniku s jediným majitelem, neziskové organizace nebo vládní agentury);
    * **marketingové a komunikační údaje,** včetně vašich marketingových předvoleb a přihlášení k odběru našich publikací;
    * **finanční údaje,** včetně informací o účtu platební karty nebo o jiném peněžním účtu pro účely nákupu produktů a služeb naší společnosti, které jsou dostupné na našich webových stránkách;
    * **údaje pro kontrolu vývozu,** například vaše národnost, občanství a země trvalého pobytu, které nám umožní rozhodnout, zda podle nařízení o kontrole vývozu smíte dostávat informace o určitých technologiích;
    * **údaje o transakcích,** včetně dotazů a objednávek našich produktů a služeb a podrobností o platbách vám a od vás, včetně historie objednávek a informací potřebných k provádění platebních transakcí;
    * **údaje o registraci na akce,** včetně informací, které poskytujete při vyplňování elektronických registračních formulářů; a
    * **vaše připomínky a názory,** včetně průzkumů, doporučení nebo jiných názorů na naše weby, případně obecných názorů a připomínek k našim produktům a službám.

Pokud nám požadované údaje neposkytnete, můžete se stát, že vám nebudeme moci poskytnout požadovanou službu nebo dokončit transakci.

* **Údaje, které o vás shromažďujeme automaticky**. Můžeme od vás automaticky shromažďovat určité informace o vaší návštěvě našich webů. K tomu slouží soubory cookie a dalších podobné sledovací technologie. Budeme vždy respektovat veškerá zákonná práva, jež nám v tomto počínání mohou bránit. Mezi údaje takto shromážděné se řadí:
    * **údaje o použití,** včetně údajů o způsobu použití našich webů, o prohlížených stránkách, o počtu přenesených bajtů, o odkazech, na které kliknete, o otevřených materiálech, o datu a času přístupu k webu, o webu s odkazem na náš web a o dalších akcích prováděných na našich webech; a
    * **technické údaje,** jako je IP adresa, typ a možnosti prohlížeče, váš jazyk a operační systém.

Informace o souborech cookie a dalších podobných sledovacích technologiích, které používáme na našich webech, najdete v [Prohlášení o používání souborů cookie](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#czech).

* **Údaje o zeměpisné poloze**. U některých webových stránek můžeme s vaším výslovným souhlasem shromažďovat údaje o přesné aktuální poloze (tzv. geografické poloze) vašeho mobilního zařízení. Tyto údaje využijeme pouze k tomu, abychom vám usnadnili používání webů, mj. prostřednictvím našich poskytovatelů služeb, kteří mohou tyto informace zpracovávat v souvislosti s poskytováním předmětných služeb naším jménem. Pokud takový souhlas udělíte, můžete jej spravovat spolu s předvolbami služeb zjišťování polohy v nastavení mobilního zařízení.
* **Informace shromážděné od třetích stran**. V souladu s platnou legislativou můžeme shromažďovat osobní údaje od třetích stran, jež se vás týkají, například z webů a aplikací sociálních médií, a spojovat je s informacemi, které již máme. Tento postup může sloužit vylepšení a přizpůsobení našich webů vašim předvolbám a dalším účelům stanoveným v tomto Prohlášení o ochraně soukromí. Můžeme také shromažďovat vaše obchodní kontaktní údaje od vašeho zaměstnavatele nebo jiných třetích stran, abychom mohli provádět běžné obchodní aktivity a podobné administrativní záležitosti nebo se do nich jiným způsobem zapojili.

**Používání údajů**

Osobní údaje shromážděné prostřednictvím našich webů nebo v případě, že nás kontaktujete, můžeme použít pro tyto účely:

* **Obchodní kontaktní údaje**. Společnost Honeywell shromažďuje a používá obchodní kontaktní údaje ke komunikaci nebo transakcím, včetně provádění due diligence ohledně produktů či služeb, případně poskytování nebo přijímání produktů či služeb. Společnost Honeywell může například shromažďovat a používat obchodní kontaktní údaje za účelem usnadnění a správy objednávek, smluv, záruk, údržby a podobných obchodních funkcí, za účelem posouzení úvěryschopnosti a pro účely inkasování prostředků, za účelem pomoci při vyřizování našich vlastních interních požadavků a právních požadavků a (pokud by to bylo nutné) k obraně našich zájmů a nároků.
* **Služby a transakce**. Vaše osobní údaje používáme k poskytování služeb nebo provádění požadovaných transakcí. Může se jednat například (ale nikoli výlučně) o poskytnutí informací o zakoupených nebo jinak používaných produktech či službách naší společnosti, registraci zakoupených produktů, zpracování objednávek produktů, vyřizování reklamací, poskytování náhradních příruček k produktům, vyřizování vašich požadavků v rámci služeb zákazníkům nebo o používání našich webů.
* **Správa a ochrana našeho podnikání a webů**. Vaše osobní údaje můžeme používat ke správě a ochraně naší obchodní činnosti a našich webů, včetně řešení potíží, údržby systémů, podpory, přípravy hlášení a hostování dat.
* **Zlepšování našeho podnikání, webů, produktů a služeb**. Vaše osobní údaje můžeme používat k obchodním analýzám a jiným účelům, které nám pomáhají rozvíjet naši obchodní činnost a zvyšovat její kvalitu, jakož i kvalitu našich webů, produktů a služeb (včetně nových produktů a služeb), například tím, že naše weby přizpůsobíme určitým preferencím nebo zájmům.
* **Marketing**. Podle platné legislativy a předpisů smíme používat vaše osobní údaje, abychom vás informovali o produktech nebo službách, které vás mohou zajímat, nebo s vámi jiným způsobem komunikovali o našich nabídkách, událostech a novinkách, průzkumech, speciálních nabídkách a souvisejících tématech. Marketingovou komunikaci zasílanou e-mailem můžete kdykoli bezplatně zrušit, když použijete odkaz pro zrušení odběru v kterémkoli z e-mailových marketingových materiálů, které od nás dostáváte, nebo když se na nás obrátíte prostřednictvím kontaktních údajů uvedených v tomto prohlášení. S ohledem na zemi vašeho pobytu můžete mít možnost odhlásit se z jiných typů marketingové komunikace. Máte-li zájem o více informací, kontaktujte nás s využitím kontaktních údajů uvedených v tomto Prohlášení o ochraně soukromí. V některých jurisdikcích náleží fyzickým osobám (např. obyvatelům Kalifornie) právo požadovat určité informace týkající se toho, jak sdělujeme osobní údaje třetím stranám pro účely přímého marketingu třetích stran. Chcete-li získat další informace o našich praktikách při poskytování údajů pro marketingové účely, kontaktujte nás v souladu s níže uvedenými pokyny.
* **Zájmově orientovaná reklama**. Shromažďujeme údaje o vašich online aktivitách a identifikujeme vaše zájmy, abychom vám mohli poskytovat nejrelevantnější reklamu. Přijímání zájmově orientované reklamy od společnosti Honeywell můžete odhlásit způsobem popsaným v našem [Prohlášení o používání souborů cookie](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#czech).
* **Finanční pobídkové a věrnostní programy**. Shromažďujeme a používáme osobní údaje k udržování a správě finančních pobídkových a věrnostních programů. Osobní údaje, které poskytujete v rámci těchto programů, využíváme k tomu, abychom vám nabízeli jedinečné odměny, sledovali váš stav v programu a umožnili výměnu programových bodů za produkty, propagační materiály, školicí semináře a další položky. V míře, do jaké to připouští zákon, můžeme také využít jakékoli osobní údaje, které nám poskytnete ve spojitosti s programem finančních pobídek, k jakémukoli jinému účelu uvedenému v tomto Prohlášení o ochraně soukromí. Prostudujte si podmínky každého finančního pobídkového programu, do něhož se chcete zaregistrovat nebo jehož se chcete účastnit, protože takové podmínky mohou být speciálně přizpůsobeny příslušnému programu. Pokud poskytnete souhlas s účastí v těchto programech, můžete jej kdykoli zrušit tak, že nás kontaktujete s využitím kontaktních údajů uvedených na konci tohoto Prohlášení o ochraně soukromí, případně v souladu s pokyny stanovenými v podmínkách příslušného programu.
* **Žádosti o zaměstnání**. V souvislosti s žádostí o zaměstnání nebo souvisejícími dotazy nám můžete poskytnout informace o sobě, například ve formě CV či životopisu, profesních referencí, informací o vzdělání a praxi, informací o odborných školeních a certifikacích. My a další členové naší skupiny můžeme tyto informace použít za účelem zvážení uzavření pracovního poměru, ověření vaší spolehlivosti či způsobilosti k výkonu práce, případně jak se uvádí jinak v jakémkoli samostatném prohlášení o ochraně soukromí nebo v jiném prohlášení, jež vám bude poskytnuto v souvislosti s vaší žádostí. K získávání, shromažďování a uchovávání žádostí o zaměstnání můžeme využívat třetí stranu (např. firmu zabývající se náborem pracovníků) nebo platformu sociálních médií. Další informace najdete v našem [Prohlášení o ochraně soukromí uchazečů o zaměstnání](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/applicant-privacy-notice#czech).
* **Průzkumy a analýzy**. Vaše osobní údaje můžeme používat k průzkumům a analýzám, které nám pomáhají analyzovat vaše nákupní preference, identifikovat produkty a služby, které nejlépe vyhovují vašim požadavkům, a měřit účinnost zobrazované reklamy.
* **Vynucování práva**. Shromažďované osobní údaje můžeme používat k odhalování, prevenci a řešení podvodů, porušování duševního vlastnictví, našich podmínek a ujednání, porušování zákona nebo jiného zneužití našich webů.

Pokud to zákon dovoluje, můžeme údaje shromažďované prostřednictvím našich webů spojovat s ostatními údaji, které o vás evidujeme (například s údaji o používání našich produktů a služeb), abychom vám nabídli dokonalejší a jednotnější prostředí určené ke spolupráci se zákazníky nebo k jiným účelům uvedeným v tomto prohlášení.

**Právní základ zpracování vašich údajů**

Pokud to vyžaduje zákon, zajistíme, aby zpracování vašich osobních údajů mělo právní základ. Ve většině případů bude právní základ záviset na příslušných osobních údajích a konkrétním kontextu, v němž je shromažďujeme.

* **Smlouva**: zpracování je nezbytné pro provádění služeb, jež vám poskytujeme, nebo za účelem realizace kroků (na vaši žádost) před provedením těchto služeb nebo v jejich očekávání.
* **Zákonná povinnost**: zpracování musíme provádět, abychom dostáli svým právním povinnostem, včetně dodržování platné legislativy, předpisů, státních a jiných obdobných požadavků, soudních rozhodnutí nebo předvolání.
* **Souhlas**: zpracování vychází z vašeho souhlasu se zpracováním osobních údajů k jednomu nebo více konkrétním účelům (např. marketing).
* **Oprávněné zájmy**: zpracování je nutné, protože na něm máme oprávněný zájem, například kvůli vývoji a zdokonalování našich webů, produktů nebo služeb k prospěchu našich zákazníků.
* **Životně důležité zájmy**: zpracování je nezbytné kvůli ochraně vašich životně důležitých zájmů (například ze zdravotních a bezpečnostních důvodů, pokud se zúčastníte schůzky na pracovišti společnosti Honeywell).

Pokud máte jakékoli dotazy nebo potřebujete další informace týkající se právního základu pro shromažďování a používání vašich osobních údajů, zašlete e-mail na adresu [HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com)

**Anonymizace údajů**

V souladu s platnou legislativou můžeme vaše osobní údaje anonymizovat, aby nebylo možné vás podle nich identifikovat. Anonymizované údaje se nepovažují za osobní údaje, a proto se na ně toto prohlášení nevztahuje. Anonymizované údaje můžeme shromažďovat, používat, agregovat a sdílet k jakýmkoli účelům.

**Jak dlouho údaje uchováváme**

Doba uložení vašich osobních údajů se liší podle účelu jejich zpracování. Například uchováváme osobní údaje potřebné k tomu, abychom vám mohli poskytovat produkty a služby nebo abychom mohli realizovat vámi požadované transakce, jste-li zákazníkem společnosti Honeywell nebo žádáte-li o zaměstnání prostřednictvím našich webů. V takovém případě budeme údaje z vaší žádosti uchovávat po takovou dobu, jak se uvádí v prohlášení o ochraně soukromí, jež vám je poskytnuto ve spojení s žádostí, případně jak to vyžaduje zákon. V ostatních případech uchováváme vaše osobní údaje tak dlouho, dokud jsou potřeba ke splnění účelu uvedeného v tomto prohlášení. Po uplynutí takové doby budou údaje anonymizovány (pokud to vyžaduje platná legislativa), odstraněny nebo zničeny.

**Sdělování údajů**

Podle platné legislativy smíme vaše osobní údaje sdílet s vybranými třetími stranami. Týká se to těchto třetích stran:

* **Společnosti naší skupiny**. Vaše osobní údaje můžeme sdílet s našimi přidruženými společnostmi a společnostmi naší skupiny, pokud k tomu existují přiměřené důvody, které jsou uvedeny v tomto prohlášení.
* **Poskytovatelé služeb**. Vaše osobní údaje můžeme sdílet se společnostmi, se kterými máme uzavřenou smlouvu o poskytování služeb naším jménem, jako je například hostování webů, provádění průzkumů, zpracování transakcí, analýza našich webů a další analýzy, které zvyšují kvalitu naší obchodní činnosti, webů, produktů a služeb. Od poskytovatelů služeb vyžadujeme, aby vaše osobní údaje chránili jako důvěrné.
* **Distributoři a jiní důvěryhodní obchodní partneři**. Vaše osobní údaje můžeme sdílet s třetími stranami, které distribuují naše produkty, a s dalšími důvěryhodnými obchodními partnery, abychom jim umožnili například posílat vám marketingové materiály. Sdílení osobních údajů k marketingovým účelům probíhá podle platné legislativy a předpisů.
* **Sdělování údajů ve spojitosti s transakcemi**. V souvislosti s určitými transakcemi můžeme sdělit některé nebo všechny vaše osobní údaje finančním institucím, státním úřadům a přepravním nebo poštovním společnostem, které se podílejí na uskutečnění transakce.
* **Sdělení údajů ve spojitosti s akvizicemi nebo odprodejem**. Mohou nastat okolnosti, kdy se společnost Honeywell ze strategických nebo jiných obchodních důvodů rozhodne v některých zemích prodat, koupit, odprodat, sloučit nebo jinak reorganizovat své podniky. Informace, které si o vás udržujeme, můžeme zpřístupnit do míry přiměřeně nezbytné k vyjednávání nebo provedení fúze, akvizice, odprodeje či prodeje části nebo veškerého majetku společnosti Honeywell.
* **Sdělení údajů z jiných důvodů**. Osobní údaje můžeme sdělit jiné straně, pokud to vyžaduje zákon (nebo nás k tomu opravňuje) nebo tak učiníme v dobré víře, že je to nutné ke splnění zákonných požadavků nebo kvůli dodržení právního procesu uplatňovaného vůči nám, dále k ochraně a obraně našich práv nebo majetku, v naléhavých případech a kvůli ochraně bezpečí osob.

**Mezinárodní přenosy**

Společnost Honeywell je globální organizace a vaše osobní údaje mohou být v souladu s platnou legislativou přenášeny, drženy, uchovávány nebo používány na různých místech po celém světě, například v USA, Mexiku a Indii. To znamená, že když shromažďujeme vaše osobní údaje, mohou být zpracovány v zemích, kde platí zákony na ochranu údajů, které se liší od zákonů vaší země. Společnost Honeywell však vždy přijme přiměřená opatření k ochraně vašeho soukromí a k zajištění úrovně ochrany osobních údajů, která je srovnatelná s úrovní vaší země pobytu, včetně implementace standardních smluvních doložek Evropské komise. Máte-li zájem o další informace o příslušných opatřeních na ochranu vašich osobních údajů, kontaktujte nás na adrese [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com).

**Zabezpečení**

Zavazujeme se chránit vaše osobní údaje, aby byly v bezpečí. Využíváme technická a organizační opatření k zajištění úrovně zabezpečení odpovídající riziku plynoucímu ze zpracování vašich osobních údajů. Máte-li zájem o další informace o postupech ochrany osobních údajů využívaných společností Honeywell, kontaktujte nás na adrese [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com)

**Vaše práva**

S ohledem na příslušnou legislativu můžete mít v souvislosti se svými osobními údaji určitá práva.

* Můžete mít právo na **přístup, opravu, aktualizaci** nebo **požádání o výmaz** svých osobních údajů.
* Můžete **vznést námitku** vůči zpracování svých osobních údajů, požádat nás o **omezení** zpracování osobních údajů nebo žádat o **přenositelnost** osobních údajů.
* Můžete mít právo požadovat, **aby se o vás nerozhodovalo pouze na základě automatického zpracování, včetně profilování**, pokud má takové rozhodnutí na vás právní dopady nebo se vás významně dotýká.
* Pokud shromažďujeme a zpracováváme vaše osobní údaje na základě uděleného souhlasu, **můžete svůj souhlas kdykoli odvolat**. Odvolání souhlasu nebude mít vliv na zákonnost jakéhokoli zpracování, které jsme provedli před odvoláním, ani to nebude mít vliv na zpracování vašich osobních údajů prováděné na základě jiných zákonných důvodů zpracování, než je souhlas.
* Můžete mít právo **odhlásit se z prodeje osobních údajů**. Společnost Honeywell neprodává vaše osobní údaje třetím stranám za účelem zisku. Vaše osobní údaje však sdílíme nebo jinak poskytujeme třetím stranám v souladu s tímto Prohlášením o ochraně soukromí a s naším [Prohlášením o používání souborů cookie](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#czech). Spolupracujeme například s třetími stranami při distribuci našich produktů, poskytování technické pomoci, používání analytických nástrojů a funkcí webů a při marketingových aktivitách a prodeji našich produktů a služeb. Takové aktivity mohou zahrnovat poskytnutí osobních údajů třetím stranám a podle některých (nikoli však všech) zákonů na ochranu osobních údajů mohou být považovány za „prodej“ údajů.
* Máte právo **vznést stížnost** úřadu pro ochranu údajů odpovědnému za dohled nad dodržováním zákonů o ochraně údajů ve vaší jurisdikci s ohledem na shromažďování a využívání vašich osobních údajů z naší strany, pokud se domníváte, že naše zpracování vašich osobních údajů není v souladu s právními předpisy o ochraně osobních údajů. Například fyzické osoby v EHP mají právo stěžovat si příslušnému úřadu pro ochranu údajů, jejichž seznam je k dispozici na adrese: [https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/board/members\_en](https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/board/members_en). Velice bychom ocenili, kdybyste nám dali příležitost problém vyřešit, a proto nás prosím v případě jakýchkoli stížností neváhejte kontaktovat. Nebudeme žádné fyzické osoby diskriminovat za to, že uplatňují svá práva na ochranu osobních údajů.

Uplatňování vašich práv zajistíme podle platné legislativy. I v případě, že vaše osobní údaje nejsou chráněny podle zákona o ochraně osobních údajů nebo se na ně tyto zákony jinak nevztahují, můžeme se pokusit vyhovět jakýmkoli požadavkům nebo dotazům, které můžete mít v souvislosti s našimi činnostmi v oblasti zpracování údajů. Pokud máte dotazy týkající se práv nebo si přejete svá práva uplatnit, můžete nás kontaktovat na adrese [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com) nebo můžete posílat dotazy týkající se ochrany osobních údajů prostřednictvím interaktivního webového formuláře na odkazu:

**Údaje dětí**

Naše weby nejsou zaměřeny na děti mladší šestnácti let (16) a neměly by být takovými dětmi používány. Vědomě neshromažďujeme, nepoužíváme ani neprodáváme informace od takových osob. Pokud jste nezletilí ve smyslu právních předpisů vaší země, žádné osobní údaje nám prostřednictvím našich webů neposkytujte.

**Odkazy na jiné weby**

Naše weby mohou obsahovat odkazy na webové stránky, produkty a služby třetích stran. Za jejich webové stránky, produkty a služby, zásady, shromažďování ani za jiné zpracování vašich osobních údajů neneseme žádnou odpovědnost. Postupy uplatňované těmito třetími stranami se řídí jejich vlastními zásadami ochrany osobních údajů. Proto vám doporučujeme, abyste se s těmito zásadami ochrany osobních údajů třetích stran seznámili.

**Kontaktujte nás**

Máte-li dotazy týkající se tohoto prohlášení nebo našeho zpracování vašich osobních údajů, chcete podat stížnost nebo se chcete obrátit na pověřence pro ochranu osobních údajů, použijte kontaktní údaje uvedené níže. Na váš dotaz budeme neprodleně reagovat a pokusíme se najít uspokojivé řešení.

Interaktivní webový formulář:  

E-mail:  

Poštovní adresa:  
Honeywell Privacy  
4D5  
115 Tabor Road  
Morris Plains, NJ 07950

Bezplatné telefonní číslo:  

**Změny tohoto prohlášení o ochraně soukromí**

Toto prohlášení o ochraně soukromí můžeme příležitostně aktualizovat. Pokud tak učiníme, opravíme datum poslední aktualizace uvedené nahoře v tomto prohlášení a případně podnikneme další kroky vyžadované zákonem.

**Naposledy aktualizováno 11. června 2021**

**Sidst opdateret den 11. juni 2021**

**Introduktion**

Honeywell International Inc. (»**Honeywell**«, »**vores**«, »**os**« eller »**vi**«), er »dataansvarlig« for de personlige oplysninger, vi indsamler om dig, når du besøger eller bruger enhver af vores hjemmesider, eller bruger produkter, tjenester og applikationer, der er knyttet til denne databeskyttelseserklæring (samlet vores »**sider**«). Denne databeskyttelseserklæring forklarer, hvordan vi indsamler, deler og bruger dine personlige oplysninger, der indsamles på denne måde, og hvordan du kan gøre brug af dine databeskyttelsesrettigheder.

Når vi interagerer med dig, kan vi også give dig yderligere databeskyttelseserklæringer om specifikke behandlingsaktiviteter eller tilbyde dig yderligere valg om, hvordan Honeywell behandler dine personlige oplysninger på det pågældende tidspunkt.

Klik på et af nedenstående links for at gå til den sektion, der interesserer dig:

**Vores indsamling af oplysninger**

* **Oplysninger, der indsamles direkte fra dig**. Vi kan bede dig om personlige oplysninger for at levere en tjeneste eller udføre en transaktion, som du har anmodet om. Du kan også give os personlige oplysninger, når du kontakter eller engagerer dig med os (f.eks. gennem en kommentar, forespørgsel eller kundesupportanmodning eller som besøgende på siden) eller når du tilmelder dig en konto for at bruge vores sider. Disse personlige oplysninger kan omfatte:
    * **Identitetsdata,** f.eks. dit navn, din titel, dit virksomhedsnavn/organisationsnavn, din e-mailadresse, dine telefonnumre og din fysiske adresse (herunder gade, by, stat, postnummer og/eller land);
    * **Tilmeldingsdata,** som du oplyser, når du tilmelder dig en konto for at bruge vores sider, herunder brugernavne og adgangskoder;
    * **Rekrutteringsdata,** herunder oplysninger, der er indsendt i forbindelse med en jobansøgning eller en forespørgsel (som beskrevet nedenfor);
    * **Virksomhedskontaktdata,** såsom oplysninger om andre medarbejdere, ejere, direktører, embedsmænd eller kontrahenter i en tredjepartsorganisation (f.eks. firma, virksomhed, partnerskab, enkeltmandsvirksomhed, nonprofitorganisation eller et statsligt agentur).
    * **Markedsførings- og kommunikationsdata,** herunder dine markedsføringsindstillinger og dine abonnementer på vores udgivelser;
    * **Finansielle oplysninger,** herunder kreditkortoplysninger eller andre finansielle kontooplysninger, som vi indsamler med henblik på at gøre det muligt for os at gennemføre dit køb af virksomhedens produkter og tjenester, der kan være tilgængelige på vores sider;
    * **Oplysninger om eksportkontrol,** såsom din nationalitet, dit statsborgerskab og dit bopælsland, der giver os mulighed for at afgøre din berettigelse til at modtage oplysninger om visse teknologier i henhold til eksportkontrolbestemmelser;
    * **Transaktionsdata,** herunder forespørgsler om og bestillinger af vores produkter og tjenester og oplysninger om betalinger til og fra dig, herunder købsordrehistorik og oplysninger, der er nødvendige for at udføre betalingstransaktioner;
    * **Tilmeldingsoplysninger for begivenheder,** herunder oplysninger, som du giver, når du udfylder tilmeldingsformularer online; og
    * **Din feedback,** herunder undersøgelser, anbefalinger eller anden feedback fra dig om vores sider samt vores produkter og tjenester generelt.

Når du ikke giver os de ønskede oplysninger, kan vi muligvis ikke levere den anmodede tjeneste eller gennemføre din transaktion.

* **Oplysninger, vi indsamler om dig automatisk**. Vi indsamler visse oplysninger om dit besøg på vores sider ved hjælp af cookies og lignende sporingsteknologier. Vi vil altid respektere de juridiske rettigheder, du måtte have for at forhindre os i at gøre dette. Data, der indsamles på denne måde omfatter:
    * **Brugsdata,** herunder oplysninger om, hvordan du bruger vores sider, hvilke websider du ser, antallet af overførte byte, de links, du klikker på, de materialer, du tilgår, datoen og tidspunktet for, hvornår du tilgår siden, hjemmesiden, hvorfra du blev forbundet til en af vores sider, og andre handlinger, der er foretaget inden for siderne; og
    * **Tekniske data,** såsom din internetprotokoladresse (IP), din browsertype og dine tilvalg og dit sprog samt dit operativsystem.

Find oplysninger om cookies og andre lignende sporingsteknologier, som vi bruger på vores sider i vores [cookieeklæring](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#danish).

* **Geo-placeringsoplysninger**. For visse sider, med dit samtykke, kan vi indsamle den præcise placering i realtid (dvs. geo-placering) for din mobile enhed. Disse oplysninger vil kun blive brugt til din brug af siderne, herunder af vores tjenesteleverandører, der kan behandle disse oplysninger i forbindelse med leveringen af tjenester på vegne af os. Hvis disse oplysninger gives, kan du ændre dette samtykke ved at administrere dine indstillinger for placeringstjenester via indstillingerne på din mobile enhed.
* **Oplysninger, der indsamles af tredjeparter**. I overensstemmelse med gældende lovgivning kan vi indsamle personlige oplysninger om dig fra tredjeparter, såsom sociale medier og applikationer, og kombinere dem med oplysninger, vi allerede har, for at hjælpe os med at forbedre og tilpasse vores sider til dine indstillinger og til andre formål, der er angivet i denne databeskyttelseserklæring. Vi kan også indsamle dine forretningskontaktoplysninger fra din arbejdsgiver eller andre tredjeparter for at muliggøre eller på anden måde engagere os i traditionelle forretningsaktiviteter og lignende administrative anliggender.

**Vores brug af oplysninger**

Vi kan bruge de personlige oplysninger, der indsamles via vores sider, eller når du kontakter os, til formål, der omfatter:

* **Forretningskontaktdata**. Honeywell indsamler og bruger forretningskontaktdata til at udføre kommunikation eller transaktioner, herunder til at udføre due diligence vedrørende, eller ved levering eller modtagelse af, et produkt eller en tjeneste. Honeywell kan for eksempel indsamle og bruge disse forretningskontaktoplysninger til at muliggøre og administrere ordrer, kontrakter, garantier, vedligeholdelse og lignende forretningsfunktioner med henblik på kreditanalyse og opkrævning, for at hjælpe vores egen interne overholdelse og juridiske krav og (om nødvendigt) til at forsvare vores interesser og krav.
* **Tjenester og transaktioner**. Vi kan bruge dine personlige oplysninger til at levere tjenester til dig eller udføre transaktioner, du har anmodet om, herunder, men ikke begrænset til, at levere oplysninger om virksomhedens produkter eller tjenester, som du har købt eller på anden måde bruger, registrere købte produkter, behandle produktordrer, håndtere garantikrav, udskifte produktmanualer, besvare kundeserviceanmodninger og muliggøre brugen af vores sider.
* **Administration og beskyttelse af vores forretning og sider**. Vi kan bruge dine personlige oplysninger til at administrere og beskytte vores virksomhed og vores sider, herunder til fejlfinding, systemvedligeholdelse, support, rapportering og datahosting.
* **Forbedring af vores forretning, sider, produkter og tjenester**. Vi kan bruge dine personlige oplysninger til at udføre forretningsanalyser eller til andre formål, der hjælper os med at udvikle og forbedre kvaliteten af vores forretning, sider, produkter og tjenester (herunder nye produkter og tjenester), f.eks. ved at tilpasse vores sider til dine specifikke indstillinger eller interesser.
* **Markedsføring**. I overensstemmelse med gældende love og bestemmelser kan vi bruge dine personlige oplysninger til at informere dig om produkter eller tjenester, der kan være af interesse for dig, og til på anden måde at kommunikere med dig om tilbud, begivenheder og nyheder, undersøgelser, særtilbud og relaterede emner. Du kan til enhver tid framelde dig markedsføringskommunikation, der sendes via e-mail gratis ved brug af linket »frameld« i det e-mailmarkedsføringsmateriale, du modtager fra os, eller ved at kontakte os gennem de kontaktoplysninger, der er angivet i denne databeskyttelseserklæring. Afhængigt af dit bopælsland kan du også fravælge andre former for markedsføringskommunikation; kontakt os ved hjælp af kontaktoplysningerne i databeskyttelseserklæringen for flere oplysninger. Nogle jurisdiktioner giver enkeltpersoner (f.eks. beboere i Californien) ret til at anmode om visse oplysninger vedrørende vores videregivelse af personoplysninger til tredjeparter, der bruges til tredjepartens direkte markedsføringsformål. Du kan få flere oplysninger om vores praksis for videregivelse af data til markedsføringsformål ved at kontakte os i overensstemmelse med instruktionerne nedenfor.
* **Interessebaseret annoncering**. Vi indsamler data om dine onlineaktiviteter og identificerer dine interesser, så vi kan levere de annoncer, der er mest relevante for dig. Du kan fravælge at modtage interessebaseret annoncering fra Honeywell i henhold til beskrivelsen i vores [cookieerklæring](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#danish).
* **Finansielle incitamenter og loyalitetsprogrammer**. Vi indsamler og bruger personlige oplysninger til at vedligeholde og administrere vores økonomiske incitaments- og loyalitetsprogrammer. Vi bruger de personlige oplysninger, du giver i disse programmer, til at tilbyde unikke belønninger, spore din programstatus og til at muliggøre udvekslingen af programpoint for produkter, reklamemateriale, træningsworkshops og andre ting. I det omfang loven tillader det, kan vi også bruge personlige oplysninger, som du giver i forbindelse med et økonomisk incitamentsprogram, til andre formål, der er angivet i denne databeskyttelseserklæring. Gennemgå vilkårene og betingelserne for hvert økonomisk incitamentsprogram, som du ønsker at tilmelde dig eller deltage i, da sådanne vilkår og betingelser kan være svært skræddersyede til det relevante program. Hvis du accepterer at deltage i disse programmer, kan du til enhver tid trække samtykket tilbage ved at kontakte os ved hjælp af kontaktoplysningerne i bunden af denne databeskyttelseserklæring eller i overensstemmelse med instruktionerne i de gældende vilkår og betingelser for programmet.
* **Jobansøgninger**. I forbindelse med en jobansøgning eller forespørgsel kan du give os oplysninger om dig selv, såsom et CV/curriculum vitae, faglige referencer, oplysninger om uddannelse og jobbaggrund, samt oplysninger om faglig uddannelse og certificeringer. Vi og medlemmer af vores koncern kan bruge disse oplysninger med henblik på ansættelsesovervejelser, baggrundstjek og ansættelsesberettigelse, og som ellers angivet i en separat databeskyttelseserklæring eller anden erklæring, der stilles til rådighed i forbindelse med din ansøgning. Vi kan bruge en tredjepart (f.eks. en rekrutteringsagent) eller en social medieplatform til at anmode om, indsamle og opbevare ansættelsesansøgninger. Du kan få flere oplysninger ved at læse vores [databeskyttelseserklæring for ansøgere](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/applicant-privacy-notice#danish).
* **Forskning og analyse**. Vi kan bruge dine personlige oplysninger til at udføre forskning og analyse for at hjælpe os med at analysere dine købspræferencer, identificere de produkter og tjenester, der bedst opfylder dine krav, og til at måle effektiviteten af den annoncering, vi viser for dig.
* **Håndhævelse**: Vi kan bruge de personlige oplysninger, vi indsamler, til at detektere, forhindre og reagere på svindel, brud på intellektuel ejendomsret, brud på vores vilkår og betingelser, brud på loven eller anden misbrug af vores sider.

Når det er tilladt ved lov, kan vi kombinere de oplysninger, vi indsamler via vores sider, med andre oplysninger, vi har om dig (såsom oplysninger om din brug af vores produkter og tjenester) for at tilbyde dig en forbedret og konsekvent kundeoplevelse, når du interagerer med os eller til andre formål, der er angivet i denne databeskyttelseserklæring.

**Det juridiske grundlag, hvorpå vi behandler oplysninger**

Når loven kræver det, vil vi sikre, at der er et retsgrundlag for behandlingen af dine personlige oplysninger. I de fleste tilfælde vil vores retsgrundlag afhænge af de pågældende personlige oplysninger og den specifikke kontekst, hvortil vi indsamler dem.

* **Kontrakt**: behandlingen er nødvendig for udførelsen af de tjenester, vi leverer til dig, eller for at tage skridt (efter din anmodning) forud for og i forventning om udførelsen af sådanne tjenester;
* **Juridisk forpligtelse**: behandlingen er nødvendig for at overholde vores juridiske forpligtelser, herunder overholdelse af gældende love, bestemmelser, statslige og kvasi-statslige anmodninger, retskendelser eller stævninger;
* **Samtykke**: behandlingen er baseret på dit samtykke til behandlingen af dine personlige oplysninger til et eller flere specifikke formål (f.eks. markedsføring);
* **Legitime interesser**: behandlingen er nødvendig for at opfylde vores legitime interesser, for eksempel for at udvikle og forbedre vores sider, produkter og/eller tjenester til gavn for vores kunder; eller
* **Vitale interesser**: behandlingen er nødvendig for at beskytte dine vitale interesser (f.eks. af sundheds- og sikkerhedsmæssige årsager, hvis du deltager i et møde på en Honeywell-lokation).

Hvis du har spørgsmål eller brug for yderligere oplysninger vedrørende det retsgrundlag, hvorpå vi indsamler og bruger dine personlige oplysninger, bedes du sende en e-mail til [HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com)

**Anonymisering af oplysninger**

I overensstemmelse med gældende lovgivning kan vi anonymisere dine personlige oplysninger, så de ikke længere kan bruges til at identificere dig. Anonymiserede oplysninger betragtes ikke som personlige oplysninger og er derfor ikke underlagt denne databeskyttelseserklæring. Vi kan indsamle, bruge, sammenlægge og dele anonymiserede oplysninger til ethvert formål.

**Opbevaringstiden for oplysninger**

Den periode, hvor vi gemmer dine personlige oplysninger, varierer afhængigt af formålet med behandlingen. For eksempel gemmer vi personlige oplysninger, der er nødvendige for at levere produkter og tjenester til dig, eller for at muliggøre transaktioner, du har anmodet om, så længe du er kunde hos Honeywell; eller hvis du indsender en jobansøgning via vores sider, vil vi opbevare oplysninger om din ansøgning som angivet i den databeskyttelseserklæring, der er gjort tilgængelig for dig i forbindelse med din ansøgning, eller som på anden måde krævet af loven. I alle andre tilfælde gemmer vi dine personlige oplysninger, så længe det er nødvendigt for at opfylde de formål, der er beskrevet i denne databeskyttelseserklæring, hvorefter de enten anonymiseres (hvor det er tilladt i henhold til gældende lovgivning), slettes eller destrueres.

**Videregivelse af oplysninger**

Vi kan dele dine personlige oplysninger med udvalgte tredjeparter i overensstemmelse med gældende lovgivning, herunder som angivet nedenfor:

* **Vores koncernselskaber**. Vi kan dele dine personlige oplysninger med vores datterselskaber og koncernselskaber, hvis det med rimelighed er nødvendigt til de formål, der er angivet i denne databeskyttelseserklæring.
* **Tjenesteleverandører**. Vi kan dele dine personlige oplysninger med virksomheder, som vi har indgået kontrakt med omkring levering tjenester på vegne af os, såsom hosting af hjemmesider, udførelse af undersøgelser, behandling af transaktioner, analyse af vores sider og udførelse af analyser for at forbedre kvaliteten af vores forretning, sider, produkter og tjenester. Vi kræver, at disse tjenesteleverandører beskytter fortroligheden af dine personlige oplysninger.
* **Distributører og andre betroede forretningspartnere**. Vi kan dele dine personlige oplysninger med tredjeparter, der distribuerer vores produkter og andre betroede forretningspartnere til formål, der omfatter at tillade disse tredjeparter at sende markedsføringskommunikation til dig. En sådan deling af personlige oplysninger til markedsføringsformål vil blive udført i overensstemmelse med gældende love og bestemmelser.
* **Oplysninger i forbindelse med transaktioner**. I forbindelse med visse transaktioner kan vi videregive nogle eller alle dine personlige oplysninger til finansielle institutioner, offentlige enheder og fragtvirksomheder eller posttjenester, der er involveret i gennemførelsen af transaktionen.
* **Oplysninger i forbindelse med erhvervelser eller afhændelser**. Der kan opstå omstændigheder, hvor Honeywell af strategiske eller andre forretningsmæssige årsager beslutter at sælge, købe, afhænde, fusionere eller på anden måde omorganisere virksomheder i nogle lande. Vi kan videregive oplysninger, vi opbevarer om dig, i det omfang det med rimelighed er nødvendigt for at fortsætte med forhandlingen eller gennemførelsen af en fusion, erhvervelse, afhændelse eller salg af alle eller en del af Honeywells aktiver.
* **Videregivelse af andre grunde**. Vi kan videregive personoplysninger, hvis det er påkrævet eller autoriseret i henhold til loven eller i god tro om, at en sådan handling er nødvendig for at overholde de juridiske krav eller den juridiske proces, der gælder for os, for at beskytte og forsvare vores rettigheder eller ejendom eller, i hastetilfælde, for at beskytte den enkeltes personlige sikkerhed.

**Internationale overførsler**

Honeywell er en global organisation, og dine personlige oplysninger kan overføres til, opbevares, lagres eller bruges på tværs af forskellige steder over hele verden, såsom USA, Mexico og Indien, i overensstemmelse med gældende lovgivning. Det betyder, at når vi indsamler dine personlige oplysninger, kan de blive behandlet i lande, der kan have databeskyttelseslove, der er forskellige fra lovene i dit land. Honeywell vil dog altid træffe rimelige foranstaltninger for at beskytte dine data og for at sikre et beskyttelsesniveau for personlige oplysninger, der kan sammenlignes med niveauet i dit bopælsland, herunder implementering af Europa-Kommissionens standardkontraktklausuler. Du kan få flere oplysninger om de passende sikkerhedsforanstaltninger omkring beskyttelse af personlige oplysninger ved at kontakte os på [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com).

**Sikkerhed**

Vi er dedikerede til at beskytte dine personlige oplysninger. Vi bruger tekniske og organisatoriske foranstaltninger til at levere et sikkerhedsniveau, der er passende i forhold til risikoen for at behandle dine personlige oplysninger. Du kan få flere oplysninger om, hvordan Honeywell beskytter dine personlige oplysninger, ved at kontakte os på [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com)

**Dine rettigheder**

Afhængigt af gældende lovgivning, kan du have visse rettigheder med hensyn til dine personlige oplysninger.

* Du har muligvis ret til at **tilgå, rette, opdatere** eller **anmode om sletning** af dine personlige oplysninger.
* Du kan **modsige** behandlingen af dine personlige oplysninger, bede os om at **begrænse**behandling af dine personlige oplysninger eller anmode om **flytning** af dine personlige oplysninger.
* Du kan have ret **til ikke at få truffet en beslutning om dig, der udelukkende er baseret på automatiseret behandling, herunder profilering,** hvis denne beslutning har juridisk effekt omkring dig eller påvirker dig i væsentlig grad.
* Similarly, if we have indsamlet and proces dit personal information with dit consent, then **du kan når som helst trække dit samtykke tilbage**. Tilbagetrækning af dit samtykke vil ikke påvirke lovligheden af enhver behandling, vi foretog før din tilbagetrækning, og det vil heller ikke påvirke behandlingen af dine personlige oplysninger, der udføres under andre lovlige behandlingsgrunde end samtykket.
* Du kan have retten til **at fravælge salg af dine personlige oplysninger**. Honeywell sælger ikke dine personlige oplysninger til tredjeparter med fortjeneste for øje. Vi deler eller videregiver dog på anden måde dine personlige oplysninger til tredjeparter i overensstemmelse med denne databeskyttelseserklæring og vores [cookieerklæring](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#danish). Vi samarbejder eksempelvis med tredjeparter om at distribuere vores produkter, give dig teknisk hjælp, drive hjemmesideanalytiske værktøjer og funktioner, og udføre markedsføring og salg af vores produkter og tjenester. Sådanne aktiviteter kan indebære videregivelse af dine personlige oplysninger til tredjeparter og kan betragtes som et »salg« af data i henhold til visse (men ikke alle) databeskyttelseslove.
* Du kan have ret til at **klage** til en databeskyttelsesmyndighed, der er ansvarlig for at overvåge overholdelse af databeskyttelseslovgivningen i din jurisdiktion om vores indsamling og brug af dine personlige oplysninger, hvis du mener, at vores behandling af dine personlige oplysninger ikke er i overensstemmelse med databeskyttelseslovgivningen. Personer i EØS har f.eks. ret til at indgive en klage til den kompetente databeskyttelsesmyndighed, som du kan få en liste over på: [https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/board/members\_en](https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/board/members_en). Vi vil dog sætte pris på muligheden for at løse dine problemer, så du er velkommen til at kontakte os vedrørende eventuelle klager, du måtte have. Vi vil ikke diskriminere mod enkeltpersoner, der udøver deres databeskyttelsesrettigheder.

Vi vil muliggøre din udøvelse af de rettigheder, der gælder for dig i overensstemmelse med gældende lovgivning. Men selvom dine personoplysninger ikke er beskyttet i henhold til, eller på anden måde er underlagt, en databeskyttelseslov, kan vi forsøge at imødekomme enhver anmodning eller forespørgsel, du måtte have i forbindelse med vores databehandlingsaktiviteter. Hvis du har spørgsmål om dine rettigheder eller ønsker at udøve dem, kan du kontakte os på [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com) eller indsende spørgsmål om databeskyttelse via vores interaktive webformular på følgende link:

**Børns oplysninger**

Vores sider er ikke rettet mod og bør ikke bruges af børn under seksten år (16), og vi indsamler, bruger eller sælger ikke bevidst oplysninger fra sådanne personer. Hvis du er mindreårig, som forstået i henhold til lovgivningen i dit land, må du ikke indsende personoplysninger via vores sider.

**Links til andre hjemmesider**

Vores sider kan indeholde links til tredjeparters hjemmesider, produkter og tjenester. Vi påtager os intet ansvar for disse hjemmesider, produkter og tjenester, deres politikker eller deres indsamling eller anden behandling af dine personlige oplysninger. Disse tredjeparters praksis er underlagt deres egne databeskyttelsespolitikker. Vi opfordrer dig til at læse disse tredjeparters databeskyttelsespolitikker.

**Kontakt os**

Hvis du har spørgsmål vedrørende denne databeskyttelseserklæring eller vores håndtering af dine personlige oplysninger, ønsker at indgive en klage, eller ønsker at kontakte vores databeskyttelsesansvarlige, bedes du kontakte os ved hjælp af nedenstående kontaktoplysninger. Vi vil straks håndtere din bekymring og bestræbe os på at nå frem til en tilfredsstillende løsning.

Interaktiv webformular:  

E-mail:  

Postadresse:  
Honeywell Privacy  
4D5  
115 Tabor Road  
Morris Plains, NJ 07950

Gebyrfrit nummer:  

**Ændringer af denne databeskyttelseserklæring**

Vi kan lejlighedsvis opdatere denne databeskyttelseserklæring. Når vi gør dette, vil vi revidere den »senest opdaterede« dato øverst i databeskyttelseserklæringen og tage de yderligere skridt, der måtte være påkrævet i henhold til loven.

**Sidst opdateret den 11. juni 2021**

**Laatst bijgewerkt 11 juni 2021**

**Inleiding**

Honeywell International Inc. ("**Honeywell**", "**onze**", "**ons**", of "**wij/we**"), is de "gegevensbeheerder" van de persoonsgegevens die wij verzamelen over u wanneer u een van onze websites bezoekt of gebruikt, of producten, diensten en toepassingen gebruikt die zijn gekoppeld aan deze privacyverklaring (gezamenlijk onze "**sites**"). In deze privacyverklaring wordt uitgelegd hoe we uw op deze manier verzamelde persoonsgegevens verzamelen, delen en gebruiken en hoe u uw privacyrechten kunt uitoefenen.

Wanneer we met u communiceren, kunnen we u ook voorzien van aanvullende privacyverklaringen over specifieke verwerkingsactiviteiten of u aanvullende keuzes bieden over hoe Honeywell uw persoonsgegevens verwerkt op dat specifieke moment.

Klik op een van de onderstaande koppelingen om naar de paragraaf te gaan die u interesseert:

**Het verzamelen van gegevens door ons**

* **Direct van u verzamelde informatie**. We kunnen u vragen om persoonsgegevens voor het verlenen van diensten of transacties uit te voeren, waarom u hebt verzocht. U kunt ons ook persoonsgegevens verstrekken wanneer u contact opneemt met ons of ons benadert (bijvoorbeeld met een opmerking, vraag of verzoek om klantondersteuning) of wanneer u zich registreert voor een account voor gebruik van onze sites. Deze persoonsgegevens kunnen het volgende omvatten:
    * **Identiteitsgegevens,** zoals uw naam, functie, bedrijfs-/organisatienaam, e-mailadres, telefoon- en faxnummers en fysiek adres (inclusief straat, plaats, staat/provincie, postcode en/of land);
    * **Registratiegegevens,** die door u wordt verschaft wanneer u zich registreert voor een account voor het gebruik van onze sites, inclusief gebruikersnamen en wachtwoorden;
    * **Wervingsgegevens,** inclusief informatie die is verstrekt in verband met een sollicitatie of onderzoek (zoals hieronder beschreven);
    * **Zakelijke contactgegevens,** zoals informatie met betrekking tot andere werknemers, eigenaren, directeuren, functionarissen of contractanten van externe organisaties (bijvoorbeeld zaak, bedrijf, partnerschap, eenmanszaak, organisatie zonder winstoogmerk of overheidsinstantie).
    * **Marketing- en communicatiegegevens,** inclusief uw marketingvoorkeuren en uw abonnementen op onze publicaties;
    * **Financiële informatie,** inclusief creditcard- of andere financiële-rekeninginformatie, waarmee we uw aankoop mogelijk kunnen maken van producten en diensten van het Bedrijf die beschikbaar zijn op onze Sites;
    * **Informatie over exportcontrole,** zoals uw nationaliteit, burgerschap en land van verblijf, op basis waarvan wij kunnen beoordelen of u volgens de voorschriften voor exportcontrole in aanmerking komt voor het ontvangen van informatie over bepaalde technologieën;
    * **Transactiegegevens,** inclusief vragen over en bestellingen van onze producten en diensten en details van betalingen aan en van u, inclusief bestelgeschiedenis en informatie die nodig is om betalingstransacties te vergemakkelijken;
    * **Registratie-informatie voor evenementen,** inclusief informatie die u verstrekt bij het invullen van e-registratieformulieren; en
    * **Uw feedback,** inclusief enquêtes, aanbevelingen of andere feedback van u over onze sites, evenals onze producten en diensten in het algemeen.

Wanneer u de gevraagde informatie niet verstrekt, kunnen we u mogelijk niet de gevraagde dienst bieden of uw transactie voltooien.

* **Informatie over u die we automatisch verzamelen**. We verzamelen bepaalde informatie over uw bezoek aan onze sites met behulp van cookies en soortgelijke traceertechnologieën. We zullen altijd alle wettelijke rechten respecteren die u mogelijk hebt om ons hiervan te weerhouden. Op deze manier verzamelde gegevens omvatten:
    * **Gebruiksgegevens,** inclusief informatie over hoe u onze sites gebruikt, welke pagina's u bekijkt, het aantal overgedragen bytes, de koppelingen waarop u klikt, de materialen die u inziet, de datum en tijd waarop u de site bezoekt, de website waarvan u naar een van onze sites bent gekoppeld en andere acties die binnen de sites worden ondernomen; en
    * **Technische gegevens,** zoals uw IP-adres (Internet Protocol), uw browsertype en -capaciteiten en taal en uw besturingssysteem.

Voor informatie over de cookies en andere vergelijkbare volgtechnologieën die we op onze Sites gebruiken, verwijzen wij u naar onze [Kennisgeving over cookies](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice).

* **Geografische locatie-informatie**. Voor bepaalde sites kunnen we met uw toestemming de exacte, real time locatie (d.w.z. geografische locatie) van uw mobiele apparaat verzamelen. Deze informatie wordt alleen gebruikt om uw gebruik van de sites te vergemakkelijken, inclusief door onze serviceproviders die deze informatie kunnen verwerken in verband met het verlenen van diensten namens ons. Indien gegeven, kunt u deze toestemming aanpassen door uw voorkeuren voor locatieservices te beheren via de instellingen van uw mobiele apparaat.
* **Informatie verzameld van derden**. In overeenstemming met de toepasselijke wetgeving kunnen we persoonsgegevens over u verzamelen van derden, zoals sociale-mediawebsites en -toepassingen, en deze combineren met informatie die we al hebben, om ons te helpen onze sites te verbeteren en aan te passen aan uw voorkeuren en voor andere uiteengezette doeleinden in deze privacyverklaring. We kunnen ook uw zakelijke contactgegevens van uw werkgever of andere derde partijen verzamelen om traditionele zakelijke activiteiten en soortgelijke administratieve zaken te vergemakkelijken of anderszins uit te voeren.

**Ons gebruik van gegevens**

We kunnen de via onze sites of wanneer u contact met ons opneemt verzamelde persoonsgegevens gebruiken voor de volgende doeleinden:

* **Zakelijke contactgegevens**. Honeywell verzamelt en gebruikt zakelijke contactgegevens om communicatie of transacties aan te gaan, inclusief voor het uitvoeren van due diligence met betrekking tot, of het leveren of ontvangen van producten of diensten. Honeywell kan deze zakelijke contactgegevens bijvoorbeeld verzamelen en gebruiken om bestellingen, contracten, garanties, onderhoud en soortgelijke zakelijke functies te vergemakkelijken en te beheren, voor kredietanalyse en incassodoeleinden, om te helpen bij onze eigen interne nalevings- en wettelijke vereisten, en (indien nodig) om onze belangen en vorderingen te verdedigen.
* **Diensten en transacties**. We kunnen uw persoonsgegevens gebruiken voor het leveren van diensten aan u of voor het uitvoeren van door u aangevraagde transacties, inclusief, maar niet beperkt tot, het verstrekken van informatie over door u aangeschafte of anderszins gebruikte producten of diensten van het bedrijf, registratie van aangeschafte producten, verwerking van productbestellingen, afhandeling van garantieclaims, vervanging van producthandleidingen, het beantwoorden van klantenserviceverzoeken en ondersteuning van het gebruik van onze Sites.
* **Het beheren en beschermen van ons bedrijf en onze sites**. We kunnen uw persoonsgegevens gebruiken voor het beheer en de bescherming van ons bedrijf en onze sites, inclusief probleemoplossing, systeemonderhoud, ondersteuning, rapportage en hosting van gegevens.
* **Het verbeteren van onze zaken, sites, producten en services**. We kunnen uw persoonsgegevens mogelijk gebruiken voor het uitvoeren van zakelijke analyses of voor andere doeleinden die ons helpen bij het ontwikkelen en verbeteren van de kwaliteit van onze zaken, sites, producten en diensten (met inbegrip van nieuwe producten en diensten), bijvoorbeeld door het aanpassen van onze sites aan uw specifieke voorkeuren of interesses.
* **Marketing**. Overeenkomstig de toepasselijke wet- en regelgeving, kunnen wij uw persoonsgegevens gebruiken om u te informeren over producten of diensten die interessant kunnen zijn voor u en om anderszins met u te communiceren over aanbiedingen, evenementen en nieuws, enquêtes, speciale aanbiedingen en gerelateerde onderwerpen. U kunt zich op elk gewenst moment kosteloos uitschrijven voor het ontvangen van marketingberichten die per e-mail zijn verzonden via de koppeling "unsubscribe" (uitschrijven) in alle marketingmaterialen die u van ons per e-mail ontvangt of door contact met ons op te nemen via de contactgegevens die in deze privacyverklaring worden vermeld. Afhankelijk van uw land van verblijf, kunt u zich mogelijk ook uitschrijven voor andere soorten marketingcommunicatie; neem dan contact met ons op via de contactgegevens vermeld in de privacyverklaring voor meer informatie. Sommige rechtsgebieden bieden personen (bijvoorbeeld inwoners van Californië) het recht om bepaalde informatie op te vragen met betrekking tot onze openbaarmaking van persoonsgegevens aan derden voor doeleinden van directe marketing van deze derden. Neem contact met ons op in overeenstemming met de onderstaande instructies voor meer informatie over onze praktijken voor het vrijgeven van gegevens voor marketingdoeleinden.
* **Op interesses gebaseerde reclame**. We verzamelen gegevens over uw online activiteiten en identificeren uw interesses, zodat we advertenties kunnen aanbieden die het meest relevant zijn voor u. U kunt zich uitschrijven voor het ontvangen van op interesses gebaseerde reclame van Honeywell, zoals beschreven in onze [Kennisgeving over cookies](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice).
* **Financiële stimulerings- en loyaliteitsprogramma's**. We verzamelen en gebruiken persoonsgegevens voor het onderhouden en beheren van onze financiële stimulerings- en loyaliteitsprogramma's. We gebruiken de persoonsgegevens die u in deze programma's verstrekt om unieke beloningen aan te bieden, uw programmastatus bij te houden en om de uitwisseling van programmapunten voor producten, promotiemateriaal, trainingsworkshops en andere artikelen te vergemakkelijken. Voor zover wettelijk toegestaan, kunnen we ook gebruikmaken van alle persoonsgegevens die u verstrekt in het kader van een financieel stimuleringsprogramma voor elk ander doel dat wordt uiteengezet in deze privacyverklaring. Bestudeer de algemene voorwaarden van elk financieel stimuleringsprogramma waarvoor u zich wilt registreren of waaraan u wilt deelnemen, aangezien deze voorwaarden nauw kunnen zijn afgestemd op het toepasselijke programma. Als u ermee instemt om deel te nemen aan deze programma's, dan kunt u die toestemming op elk moment intrekken door contact met ons op te nemen via de contactgegevens aan het einde van deze privacyverklaring of in overeenstemming met de instructies in de toepasselijke algemene voorwaarden van het programma.
* **Sollicitaties voor werk**. U kunt ons, in verband met een sollicitatie of vraag voorzien van gegevens over uzelf, zoals een cv/curriculum vitae, professionele referenties, informatie over opleiding en werkachtergrond en informatie over beroepsopleidingen en certificeringen. Wij en leden van onze groep kunnen deze informatie gebruiken met het oog op tewerkstellingsoverwegingen, achtergrondonderzoeken en geschiktheid voor werk en zoals anders uiteengezet in een afzonderlijke privacyverklaring of andere kennisgeving die ter beschikking is gesteld in verband met uw sollicitatie. We kunnen gebruikmaken van een derde partij (bijv. recruiter) of een social-mediaplatform om sollicitaties te vragen, te verzamelen en te behouden. Lees voor meer informatie onze [Privacyverklaring voor sollicitanten](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/applicant-privacy-notice#dutch).
* **Onderzoek en analyse**. We kunnen uw persoonsgegevens gebruiken om onderzoek en analyse uit te voeren die ons kan helpen bij het analyseren van uw koopvoorkeuren, het identificeren van de producten en diensten die het beste in uw behoeften voorzien en het meten van de effectiviteit van de reclame die wij u aanbieden.
* **Handhaving**: We kunnen de persoonsgegevens die we verzamelen gebruiken voor het detecteren, voorkomen en aanpakken van fraude, inbreuken op intellectuele eigendomsrechten, schendingen van onze algemene voorwaarden, overtredingen van wetten of ander misbruik van onze sites.

Voor zover dit wettelijk is toegestaan, kunnen wij de via onze sites verzamelde informatie combineren met andere informatie die we over u aanhouden (zoals informatie over uw gebruik van onze producten en diensten) om u een betere en consistente klantervaring te bieden bij interacties met ons of voor andere doeleinden die worden uiteengezet in deze Privacyverklaring.

**De rechtsgrondslag voor het verwerken van gegevens**

Indien wettelijk vereist, verzekeren wij dat er een rechtsgrondslag is voor de verwerking van uw persoonsgegevens. In de meeste gevallen zal onze rechtsgrondslag afhangen van de betreffende persoonsgegevens en de specifieke context waarin we deze verzamelen.

* **Contract**: de verwerking is noodzakelijk voor de uitvoering van de diensten die wij aan u verlenen, of om (op uw verzoek) stappen te ondernemen voorafgaand aan en anticiperend op de uitvoering van dergelijke diensten;
* **Wettelijke verplichting**: de verwerking is noodzakelijk om te voldoen aan onze wettelijke verplichtingen, waaronder de naleving van toepasselijke wetgeving, voorschriften, verzoeken van overheids- en semi-overheidsinstanties, gerechtelijke bevelen of dagvaardingen;
* **Toestemming**: de verwerking is gebaseerd op uw toestemming voor de verwerking van uw persoonsgegevens voor een of meer gespecificeerde doeleinden (bijvoorbeeld marketing);
* **Legitieme belangen**: de verwerking is noodzakelijk om onze legitieme belangen te dienen, bijvoorbeeld voor het ontwikkelen en verbeteren van onze sites, producten en/of diensten ten behoeve van onze klanten; of
* **Vitale belangen**: De verwerking is noodzakelijk om uw vitale belangen te beschermen (bijvoorbeeld gezondheids- en veiligheidsredenen als u een vergadering bijwoont op een Honeywell-locatie).

Als u vragen hebt of meer informatie nodig hebt over de rechtsgrond waarop wij uw persoonsgegevens verzamelen en gebruiken, stuur dan een e-mail naar [HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com)

**Anonimisering van gegevens**

We kunnen uw persoonsgegevens anonimiseren, overeenkomstig toepasselijke wetgeving, zodat deze niet meer kunnen worden gebruikt om u te identificeren. Geanonimiseerde gegevens worden niet beschouwd als persoonsgegevens en zijn derhalve niet onderworpen aan deze privacyverklaring. We kunnen geanonimiseerde gegevens verzamelen, samenvoegen en delen voor elk gewenst doel.

**Bewaartermijnen voor gegevens**

De periode gedurende welke we uw persoonsgegevens opslaan, hangt af van het doel van de verwerking. We slaan bijvoorbeeld persoonsgegevens op die nodig zijn om u producten en diensten te leveren of om transacties te vergemakkelijken die u hebt aangevraagd, zolang u een klant van Honeywell bent; als u een sollicitatie indient via onze sites, bewaren wij details van uw sollicitatie zoals uiteengezet in de privacyverklaring die aan u ter beschikking is gesteld in verband met uw sollicitatie of zoals anderszins vereist door de wet. In alle andere gevallen bewaren we uw persoonsgegevens zolang als nodig is om de doeleinden te vervullen die worden uiteengezet in deze Privacyverklaring, waarna deze worden geanonimiseerd (waar toegestaan door toepasselijke wetgeving), verwijderd of vernietigd.

**Openbaarmaking van gegevens**

We kunnen uw persoonsgegevens delen met geselecteerde derden in overeenstemming met de toepasselijke wetgeving, inclusief zoals hieronder uiteengezet:

* **Bedrijven van onze groep**. We kunnen uw persoonsgegevens delen met onze verbonden ondernemingen en bedrijven van onze groep, voor zover redelijkerwijs noodzakelijk voor de doeleinden die worden uiteengezet in deze Privacyverklaring.
* **Dienstverleners**. We kunnen uw persoonsgegevens delen met bedrijven waarmee wij een contract zijn aangegaan om namens ons diensten te leveren, zoals het hosten van websites, het uitvoeren van enquêtes, het verwerken van transacties, het analyseren van onze sites en het uitvoeren van analyses om ter verbetering van de kwaliteit van onze onderneming, sites, producten en diensten. We vereisen de bescherming van de vertrouwelijkheid van uw persoonsgegevens van deze dienstverleners.
* **Distributeurs en andere vertrouwde zakenpartners**. We kunnen uw persoonsgegevens delen met derden die onze producten distribueren en andere vertrouwde zakenpartners voor doeleinden omvatten dat die derden toestemming hebben om marketingcommunicatie naar u te verzenden. Dergelijk delen van persoonsgegevens voor marketingdoeleinden wordt uitgevoerd in overeenstemming met de toepasselijke wet- en regelgeving.
* **Openbaarmaking in verband met transacties**. We kunnen in verband met bepaalde transacties sommige of alle persoonsgegevens van u openbaar maken aan financiële instellingen, overheidsinstellingen en transportbedrijven of postbedrijven die zijn betrokken bij de vervulling van de transactie.
* **Openbaarmakingen in verband met acquisities of desinvesteringen**. Er kunnen zich omstandigheden voordoen waarin Honeywell om strategische of andere zakelijke redenen besluit om bedrijven in sommige landen te verkopen, te kopen, af te stoten, te fuseren of anderszins te reorganiseren. We kunnen gegevens openbaar maken die we over u aanhouden, voor zover dat redelijkerwijs noodzakelijk is om door te gaan met onderhandelingen of voltooiing van een fusie, overname, afstoting of verkoop van een deel of het geheel van de activa van Honeywell.
* **Openbaarmaking om andere redenen**. We kunnen persoonsgegevens openbaar maken indien dit wordt vereist of toegestaan door wetgeving of indien we menen dat een dergelijke actie noodzakelijk is om aan wettelijke vereisten te voldoen of aan juridische actie mee te werken, om onze rechten of eigendommen te beschermen en te beveiligen of, in dringende omstandigheden, om de persoonlijke veiligheid van een persoon te beschermen.

**Internationale overdrachten**

Honeywell is een wereldwijde organisatie en uw persoonsgegevens kunnen worden overgedragen naar en bewaard, opgeslagen of gebruikt door verschillende locaties wereldwijd, zoals de VS, Mexico en India, in overeenstemming met toepasselijke wetgeving. Dit betekent dat, wanneer we uw persoonsgegevens verzamelen, deze kunnen worden verwerkt in landen met mogelijk wetten inzake gegevensbescherming die verschillen van de wetten van uw land. Honeywell zal echter altijd redelijke stappen ondernemen om uw privacy te beschermen en om een niveau van bescherming van persoonsgegevens te bieden dat vergelijkbaar is met dat van het land waar u woont, waaronder het implementeren van de standaardcontractbepalingen van de Europese Commissie. Neem contact met ons op via [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com) voor meer informatie over de passende veiligheidsmaatregelen voor de bescherming van uw persoonsgegevens.

**Beveiliging**

We doen onze uiterste best om de bescherming van uw persoonsgegevens te waarborgen. We gebruiken technische en organisatorische maatregelen om een beveiligingsniveau te bieden dat past bij het risico van het verwerken van uw persoonsgegevens. Neem contact met ons op via [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com), voor meer informatie over hoe Honeywell uw persoonsgegevens beschermt

**Uw rechten**

Afhankelijk van de toepasselijke wetgeving hebt u mogelijk bepaalde rechten met betrekking tot uw persoonsgegevens.

* U kunt het recht hebben op **toegang tot, correctie of bijwerking** van uw persoonsgegevens of **verzoeken om verwijdering** hiervan.
* U kunt **bezwaar maken** tegen de verwerking van uw persoonsgegevens, ons vragen om het verwerken van uw persoonsgegevens te **beperken** of verzoeken om **overdraagbaarheid** van uw persoonsgegevens.
* U kunt het recht hebben om **geen beslissing over u te laten nemen die uitsluitend is gebaseerd op geautomatiseerde verwerking, inclusief profilering**, als die beslissing juridische gevolgen voor u heeft of u aanzienlijk beïnvloedt.
* Evenzo, als we uw persoonsgegevens hebben verzameld en verwerkt met uw toestemming, dan **kunt u uw toestemming op elk moment intrekken**. Het intrekken van uw toestemming heeft geen invloed op de rechtmatigheid van enige verwerking die we voorafgaand aan uw intrekking hebben uitgevoerd, noch is dit van invloed op de verwerking van uw persoonsgegevens die wordt uitgevoerd op basis van andere rechtmatige verwerkingsgronden dan toestemming.
* U kunt het recht hebben om **uit te schrijven voor de verkoop van uw persoonsgegeven**s. Honeywell verkoopt uw persoonlijke gegevens niet aan derden met winstoogmerk. We delen uw persoonlijke gegevens echter wel of maken deze op een andere manieren bekend aan derden in overeenstemming met deze privacyverklaring en onze [Kennisgeving voor cookies](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice). We werken bijvoorbeeld samen met derden voor de distributie van onze producten, u te voorzien van technische ondersteuning, het gebruik van analytische hulpmiddelen en functies voor websites en het uitvoeren van marketing en verkoop van onze producten en diensten. Dergelijke activiteiten kunnen de openbaarmaking van uw persoonsgegevens aan derden inhouden en kunnen worden beschouwd als een "verkoop" van gegevens onder bepaalde (maar niet alle) wetten inzake gegevensbescherming.
* U hebt het recht om **in klacht in te dienen** bij een gegevensbeschermingsautoriteit die verantwoordelijk is voor het toezicht op de naleving van de wetgeving inzake gegevensbescherming in uw rechtsgebied over het verzamelen en gebruik van uw persoonsgegevens door ons, als u van mening bent dat onze verwerking van uw persoonsgegevens niet in overeenstemming is met de wetgeving inzake gegevensbescherming. Personen in de EER hebben bijvoorbeeld het recht om een klacht in te dienen bij de bevoegde gegevensbeschermingsautoriteit, waarvan een lijst beschikbaar is op: [https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/board/members\_en](https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/board/members_en). Wij zouden echter graag de kans krijgen uw punten van zorg aan te pakken, dus neem gerust contact met ons op betreffende eventuele klachten die u hebt. We discrimineren geen personen voor het uitoefenen van hun privacyrechten betreffende gegevens.

Wij zullen de uitoefening van de rechten die op u van toepassing zijn faciliteren in overeenstemming met de toepasselijke wetgeving. Maar zelfs als uw persoonlijke informatie geen bescherming biedt op grond van of anderszins onderworpen is aan een wet inzake gegevensbescherming, kunnen we proberen te voldoen aan elk verzoek dat u hebt met betrekking tot onze gegevensverwerkingsactiviteiten. Als u vragen hebt over uw rechten of uw rechten wilt uitoefenen, dan kunt u contact met ons opnemen via [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com) of stel privacyvragen via ons interactieve webformulier op de volgende koppeling:

**Gegevens van kinderen**

Onze sites zijn niet gericht op, en mogen niet worden gebruikt door, kinderen jonger dan zestien (16) en we verzamelen, gebruiken of verkopen niet bewust informatie van dergelijke personen. Als u minderjarig bent, zoals verstaan door de wetten van uw land, dient u geen persoonlijke informatie in te dienen via onze sites.

**Koppelingen naar andere websites**

Onze sites kunnen koppelingen bevatten naar websites, producten en diensten van derden. Wij zijn niet aansprakelijk of verantwoordelijk voor die websites, producten en diensten, hun beleid of hun verzameling of andere verwerking van uw persoonsgegevens. De praktijken van die derden worden beheerst door hun eigen privacybeleid. Wij moedigen u aan het privacybeleid van dergelijke derden te raadplegen.

**Neem contact met ons op**

Als u vragen hebt over deze Privacyverklaring of onze omgang met uw persoonsgegevens, een klacht wilt indienen of contact wilt opnemen met onze functionaris voor gegevensbescherming, kunt u contact met ons opnemen via onderstaande contactgegevens. We zullen spoedig op uw probleem antwoorden en streven ernaar een bevredigende oplossing te vinden.

Interactief webformulier:  

E-mail:  

Postadres:  
Honeywell Privacy  
4D5  
115 Tabor Road  
Morris Plains, NJ 07950

Gratis nummer:  

**Wijzigingen in deze Privacyverklaring**

We kunnen deze Privacyverklaring af en toe bij bijwerken. Wanneer we dit doen, herzien we de datum voor 'laatst bijgewerkt' boven en onder aan de Privacyverklaring en ondernemen we aanvullende stappen indien deze wettelijk zijn vereist.

**Laatst bijgewerkt 11 juni 2021**

**Viimeksi päivitetty 11. kesäkuuta 2021**

**Johdanto**

Honeywell International Inc. (jäljempänä ”**Honeywell**” tai ”**me**”), on sinulta sivustoillamme käymisen tai niiden tai tähän Tietosuojalausuntoon liittyvien tuotteidemme, palveluidemme ja sovellustemme käytön yhteydessä keräämiemme henkilötietojen rekisterinpitäjä (yhdessä ”**Sivustomme**”). Tässä Tietosuojalausunnossa kerromme, miten keräämme, jaamme ja käytämme näin kerättyjä henkilötietojasi ja miten käytät oikeuttasi yksityisyyteen.

Eri alustoillamme saatat kohdata muitakin tietosuojailmoituksia yksittäisten toimintojen yhteydessä. Saatamme myös tarjota sinulle mahdollisuutta valita, miten Honeywell kulloinkin käsittelee henkilötietojasi.

Alla olevista linkeistä voit siirtyä suoraan itseäsi kiinnostavaan osioon:

**Tietojen kerääminen**

* **Suoraan sinulta kerätyt tiedot**. Saatamme pyytää sinulta henkilötietoja, jotta pyytämäsi palvelu tai tapahtuma voidaan suorittaa. Saatat lisäksi antaa meille henkilötietoja ollessasi meihin yhteydessä (esimerkiksi kommentin, tiedustelun, asiakastukipyynnön tai sivustokäynnin yhteydessä) tai rekisteröidessäsi tilin Sivustojamme käyttääksesi. Nämä henkilötiedot voivat sisältää
    * **tunnistetietoja,** kuten nimi, arvonimi, yrityksen tai organisaation nimi, sähköpostiosoite, puhelinnumerot ja postiosoite (katuosoite, postitoimipaikka, postinumero ja/tai maa)
    * **rekisteröitymistietoja,** jotka annat rekisteröityessäsi Sivustojemme käyttäjäksi (käyttäjätunnukset ja salasanat)
    * **rekrytointitietoja,** kuten (jäljempänä kuvatun) työhakemuksen tai työpaikkatiedustelun yhteydessä antamasi tiedot
    * **yritysyhteystietoja,** kuten tietoja kolmannen osapuolen (esim. yrityksen, osakeyhtiön, henkilöyhtiön, toiminimen, voittoa tavoittelemattoman organisaation tai valtion viraston) muista työntekijöistä, omistajista, hallituksen jäsenistä, toimihenkilöistä tai urakoitsijoista
    * **markkinointi- ja viestintätietoja,** kuten markkinointiasetuksesi ja tiedot julkaisujemme tilauksista
    * **taloustietoja,** kuten luottokortti- tai tilitiedot, joiden avulla voimme mahdollistaa sinulle Sivustoilla tarjoamiemme Yhtiön tuotteiden ja palveluiden oston
    * **vientivalvontatietoja,** kuten kansallisuus, kansalaisuus ja asuinmaa, joiden avulla voimme päätellä oikeutesi saada tietoa tietyistä teknologioista
    * **transaktiotietoja,** kuten tuotteita ja palveluita koskevat tiedustelut ja tilaukset sekä maksutiedot saamistasi ja suorittamistasi maksuista, näiden joukossa ostotilaushistoria ja maksutapahtumiin tarvittavat tiedot
    * **rekisteröitymistietoja tapahtumiin**, kuten sähköisillä rekisteröitymislomakkeilla antamasi tiedot
    * **antamaasi palautetta,** kuten kyselyissä, suosituksissa tai muutoin Sivustoistamme sekä tuotteistamme ja palveluistamme yleisesti antamasi palaute.

Jos et anna pyydettyjä tietoja, emme ehkä voi tarjota pyytämääsi palvelua tai suorittaa tiettyä transaktiota.

* **Automaattisesti sinusta kerätyt tiedot**. Keräämme tiettyjä tietoja käynneistäsi Sivustoillamme evästeiden ja vastaavien seurantatekniikoiden avulla. Kunnioitamme aina laillista oikeuttasi estää tietojen kerääminen. Näin kerätyt tiedot sisältävät
    * **käyttötietoja,** kuten miten käytät Sivustojamme, millä sivuilla käyt, siirretty tavumäärä, napsauttamasi linkit, avaamasi materiaalit, Sivustolla käyntisi ajankohta, sivusto, jolta tulet Sivustollemme sekä muut Sivustoilla suorittamasi toimet
    * **teknisiä tietoja,** kuten IP-osoitteesi, selaimen tyyppi ja valmiudet, laitteen kieli ja käyttöjärjestelmä.

Lisätietoja Sivustoillamme käytetyistä evästeistä ja muista seurantatekniikoista saat lukemalla [Evästeilmoituksemme](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#language6).

* **Maantieteelliset tiedot**. Tietyillä Sivustoilla voimme suostumuksellasi poimia tarkan, reaaliaikaisen sijaintisi mobiililaitteeltasi. Tätä tietoa käytetään vain Sivustojen käyttösi helpottamiseen meidän tai palveluntarjoajien toimesta. He saattavat käsitellä näitä tietoja palvelujen tarjoamiseksi sinulle puolestamme. Annettuasi suostumuksesi voit perua sen muuttamalla sijaintipalveluiden asetuksia mobiililaitteesi asetuksista.
* **Kolmansilta osapuolilta kerätyt tiedot**. Lain salliessa voimme kerätä henkilötietojasi kolmansilta osapuolilta, kuten sosiaalisen median sivustoilta ja sovelluksista, ja yhdistää ne jo hallussamme oleviin tietoihin parantaaksemme ja mukauttaaksemme Sivustoja mieltymystesi mukaisiksi sekä muita tässä Tietosuojalausunnossa ilmoitettuja tarkoituksia varten. Voimme myös kerätä yritysyhteystietoja työnantajaltasi tai muilta kolmansilta osapuolilta hyödyntääksemme niitä perinteiseen yritystoimintaan tai yrityksen hallinnollisiin tarkoituksiin.

**Tietojen käyttö**

Voimme käyttää Sivustojemme kautta tai yhteydenottosi yhteydessä keräämiämme henkilötietoja muun muassa seuraavia tarkoituksia varten:

* **Yritysyhteystiedot**. Honeywell kerää ja käyttää yritysyhteystietoja viestinnän tai transaktioiden tukena, kuten tuotteen tai palvelun tarjoamista tai hankintaa koskevaa asianmukaisuusvalvontaa varten. Honeywell voi kerätä ja käyttää näitä yritysyhteystietoja esimerkiksi sujuvoittaakseen ja hallinnoidakseen tilauksia, sopimuksia, takuita, huoltoa ja vastaavia liiketoimintoja, luottokelpoisuuden arviointiin ja perintään, sisäisiin compliance-tarkoituksiin ja juridisiin tarkoituksiin sekä (tarpeen vaatiessa) etujensa ja saataviensa ajamiseen.
* **Palvelut ja transaktiot**. Voimme käyttää henkilötietojasi palvelujen toimittamiseen sinulle tai pyytämiesi transaktioiden suorittamiseen, kuten tietojen toimitukseen hankkimistasi tai käytössäsi olevista Yhtiön tuotteista tai palveluista, hankittujen tuotteiden rekisteröintiin, tuotetilausten käsittelyyn, takuukorvausvaatimusten käsittelyyn, tuoteoppaiden päivitykseen, asiakaspalvelupyyntöihin vastaamiseen ja Sivustojemme käytön mahdollistamiseen.
* **Liiketoimintamme ja sivustojemme hallinnointi ja suojaaminen**. Voimme käyttää henkilötietojasi liiketoimintamme ja Sivustojemme hallinnointiin ja suojaamiseen, kuten vianmääritykseen, järjestelmän kunnossapitoon, tukeen, raportointiin ja tietojen säilyttämiseen palvelimilla.
* **Liiketoimintamme, Sivustojemme, tuotteidemme ja palveluidemme parantaminen**. Voimme käyttää henkilötietojasi liiketoiminta-analyysiin tai muihin tarkoituksiin, joilla kehitetään ja parannetaan liiketoimintamme, Sivustojemme ja tuotteidemme ja palveluittemme (myös uusien tuotteiden ja palveluiden) laatua esimerkiksi mukauttamalla Sivustoja mieltymystesi ja intressiesi mukaan.
* **Markkinointi**. Voimme käyttää henkilötietojasi lakien ja määräysten puitteissa informoidaksemme sinua tuotteista tai palveluista, jotka saattaisivat kiinnostaa sinua, sekä tuotteista, tapahtumista ja uutisista, kyselyistä, erikoistarjouksista ja näihin liittyvistä asioista. Voit kieltäytyä vastaanottamasta markkinointisähköpostiviestejä milloin tahansa kustakin viestistä löytyvää tilauksen peruutuslinkkiä käyttäen tai ottamalla meihin yhteyttä tässä Tietosuojalausunnossa annettujen yhteystietojen kautta. Asuinmaasta riippuen sinulla saattaa olla myös oikeus kieltäytyä muusta markkinointiviestinnästä. Lisätietoja saat ottamalla yhteyttä meihin Tietosuojalausunnossa mainittuja yhteystietoja käyttäen. Joillakin alueilla (esim. Kaliforniassa) yksityishenkilöillä on oikeus pyytää tietoja henkilötietojen luovuttamisesta kolmansille osapuolille suoramarkkinointitarkoituksiin. Jos haluat lisätietoa tietojen luovutusta markkinointitarkoituksiin koskevista käytännöistämme, ota meihin yhteyttä alla olevien ohjeiden mukaisesti.
* **Räätälöity mainonta**. Keräämme tietoja verkon käytöstäsi ja tunnistamme kiinnostuksesi kohteet, jotta voimme tarjota sinulle relevanttia mainontaa. Voit kieltäytyä vastaanottamasta räätälöityä mainontaa Honeywelliltä [Evästeilmoituksen](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#language6) mukaisesti.
* **Kannustin- ja kanta-asiakasohjelmat**. Keräämme ja käytämme henkilötietoja kannustin- ja kanta-asiakasohjelmiemme ylläpitoa ja hallinnointia varten. Käytämme näissä ohjelmissa antamiasi henkilötietoja yksilöllisten palkintojen tarjoamiseen, ohjelmastatuksesi seurantaan sekä ohjelmapisteiden tuotteisiin, mainosmateriaaleihin, työpajoihin ja muuhun sisältöön vaihdon mahdollistamiseen. Lain salliessa saatamme käyttää kannustinohjelman puitteissa antamiasi henkilötietoja myös muuta tähän Tietosuojalausuntoon kirjattua tarkoitusta varten. Perehdy kunkin kannustinohjelman nimenomaisiin ehtoihin ennen rekisteröitymistä tai osallistumista, koska ehdot on räätälöity ohjelmakohtaisesti. Jos annat suostumuksesi ohjelmaan osallistumiseen, voit perua sen milloin tahansa ottamalla meihin yhteyttä tämän Tietosuojalausunnon lopussa olevia yhteystietoja käyttäen tai ohjelman käyttöehtojen ohjeita noudattaen.
* **Työhakemukset**. Saatat antaa meille tietoja itsestäsi työhakemuksen tai -tiedustelun yhteydessä: ansioluettelon tai CV:n, referenssejä, tietoja koulutuksesta ja aiemmista työpaikoista sekä ammatillisista tutkinnoista. Me ja konsernin muut yhtiöt voimme käyttää näitä tietoja harkitessamme työn tarjoamista, tarkistaessamme taustoja ja muutoin haun yhteydessä annetun erillisen tietosuojaselosteen tai muun ilmoituksen mukaisesti. Voimme pyytää, kerätä ja tallentaa työhakemuksia kolmatta osapuolta (rekrytointiammattilaista) tai sosiaalisen median alustaa käyttäen. Lisätietoja saat [Työnhakijan tietosuojalausunnosta](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/applicant-privacy-notice#finnish).
* **Tutkimus ja analysointi**. Voimme käyttää henkilötietojasi tutkimuksessa ja analyyseissä, joilla analysoimme ostomieltymyksiäsi, määritämme tarpeisiisi parhaiten sopivat tuotteet ja palvelut ja mittaamme sinulle esittämämme mainonnan tehoa.
* **Lainmukaisuusvalvonta**. Voimme käyttää keräämiämme henkilötietoja petosten, immateriaalioikeusloukkausten, ehtojemme rikkomusten, lainvastaisen toiminnan tai muun Sivustojemme väärinkäytön havaitsemiseen ja ehkäisyyn sekä tällaiseen toimintaan reagointiin.

Saatamme lain salliessa yhdistää Sivustojemme kautta keräämiämme tietoja muihin sinusta säilyttämiimme tietoihin (esimerkiksi tuotteidemme ja palveluidemme käyttöäsi koskeviin tietoihin) tarjotaksemme sinulle paremman ja yhtenäisen asiakaskokemuksen tai muuta tähän Tietosuojalausuntoon kirjattua tarkoitusta varten.

**Tietojen käsittelyn oikeusperuste**

Varmistamme lain niin vaatiessa, että henkilötietojesi käsittelylle on oikeusperuste. Useimmissa tapauksissa oikeusperuste riippuu kerätyistä henkilötiedoista ja keruun kontekstista.

* **Sopimusperuste**: käsittely on välttämätöntä, jotta voimme suorittaa sinulle tarjoamamme palvelut tai toimet, joita vaaditaan (pyynnöstäsi) ennen palvelujen suorittamista niihin valmistautumiseksi
* **Laillinen velvoite**: käsittely on välttämätöntä, jotta voimme täyttää lakisääteiset velvoitteemme, kuten sovellettavien lakien, asetusten, viranomaisen tai viranomaistehtävää hoitavan yksityisen yrityksen vaatimusten tai oikeuden määräysten tai haasteiden noudattamiseksi
* **Suostumusperuste**: käsittely perustuu henkilötietojesi käsittelyyn antamaasi suostumukseen yhtä tai useampaa nimettyä tarkoitusta (esim. markkinointia) varten
* **Oikeutetut edut**: käsittely on välttämätöntä oikeutetun etumme toteuttamiseksi, kuten Sivustojemme, tuotteidemme ja/tai palveluidemme kehittämiseksi ja parantamiseksi asiakkaidemme hyväksi
* **Elintärkeät edut**: käsittely on välttämätöntä elintärkeän etusi suojaamiseksi (esimerkiksi terveys- ja turvallisuussyistä, jos osallistut tapaamiseen Honeywellin toimipisteessä).

Jos sinulla on kysyttävää tai haluat lisätietoja oikeusperusteesta, jonka nojalla keräämme ja käytämme henkilötietojasi, lähetä sähköpostia osoitteeseen [HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com)

**Tietojen anonymisointi**

Saatamme anonymisoida henkilötietojasi sovellettavan lain sallimissa rajoissa siten, ettei sinua voida enää tunnistaa kyseisten tietojen perusteella. Anonymisoitujen tietojen ei katsota olevan henkilötietoja, eikä niihin sen vuoksi sovelleta tätä Tietosuojalausuntoa. Voimme kerätä, käyttää, koostaa ja jakaa anonymisoituja tietoja missä tahansa tarkoituksessa.

**Kauanko tietoja säilytetään**

Henkilötietojesi säilytysaika vaihtelee sen mukaan, missä tarkoituksessa niitä käsitellään. Säilytämme esimerkiksi tuotteiden ja palvelujen tarjoamiseen tai pyytämiesi transaktioiden mahdollistamiseen tarvittavia henkilötietoja niin kauan kuin olet Honeywellin asiakas. Jos lähetät työhakemuksen Sivustojemme kautta, säilytämme hakemuksesi tietoja sinulle haun yhteydessä annetun tietosuojailmoituksen tai lain vaatimusten mukaisesti. Kaikissa muissa tapauksissa henkilötietojasi säilytetään niin kauan kuin se on tarpeen tässä Tietosuojalausunnossa määriteltyjen tarkoitusten toteuttamiseksi, minkä jälkeen ne joko anonymisoidaan (sovellettavan lain sen salliessa), poistetaan tai tuhotaan.

**Tietojen luovuttaminen**

Saatamme luovuttaa henkilötietojasi valituille kolmansille osapuolille sovellettavan lain sallimissa rajoissa muun muassa seuraavasti.

* **Konserniyhtiömme**. Voimme luovuttaa henkilötietojasi tytäryhtiöillemme ja konserniyhtiöillemme, kun se katsotaan kohtuudella välttämättömäksi tähän Tietosuojalausuntoon kirjattua tarkoitusta varten.
* **Palveluntuottajat**. Voimme luovuttaa henkilötietojasi yrityksille, jotka toimeksiannostamme tuottavat palveluita, kuten ylläpitävät verkkosivustojamme, suorittavat kyselyitä, käsittelevät transaktioita, analysoivat Sivustojamme ja suorittavat analyyseja liiketoimintamme, Sivustojemme ja tuotteidemme ja palveluidemme laadun parantamiseksi. Edellytämme, että nämä palveluntuottajat pitävät henkilötietosi salassa.
* **Jakelijat ja muut luotetut liiketoimintakumppanit**. Voimme luovuttaa henkilötietojasi kolmansille osapuolille, jotka jakelevat tuotteitamme, ja muille luotetuille liiketoimintakumppaneillemme muun muassa siinä tarkoituksessa, että kyseiset kolmannet osapuolet voivat lähettää sinulle markkinointiviestejä. Markkinointitarkoituksiin henkilötietoja luovutetaan sovellettavien lakien ja määräysten puitteissa.
* **Transaktioihin liittyvä tietojen luovuttaminen**. Joidenkin tapahtumien yhteydessä saatamme luovuttaa kaikki tai osan meillä olevista henkilötiedoistasi rahoituslaitoksille, viranomaisille ja kuljetusyrityksille tai postipalveluille, jotka osallistuvat transaktion toteutukseen.
* **Yritysostoon tai myyntiin liittyvä tietojen luovuttaminen**. Strategisista tai muista liiketoiminnallisista syistä Honeywell saattaa päätyä myymään, ostamaan, divestoimaan, yhdistämään tai uudelleenorganisoimaan yritystoimintaa joissakin maissa. Honeywell voi luovuttaa asiakastietoja kohtuudella tarpeellisessa määrin fuusioitumista, yritysostoa tai myyntiä tai yritystoimintojen osittaista tai täysimääräistä myyntiä koskevien neuvottelujen jatkamiseksi tai loppuunsaattamiseksi.
* **Tietojen luovuttaminen muista syistä**. Voimme luovuttaa henkilötietoja oikeuksiemme tai omaisuutemme suojaamiseksi ja puolustamiseksi tai hätätilanteessa henkilön turvallisuuden suojaamiseksi, mikäli laki sitä edellyttää tai sen sallii, kun luovuttamisen perustana on käsityksemme mukaan lakisääteinen velvoite tai laillinen kanne.

**Kansainväliset tiedonsiirrot**

Honeywell on globaali organisaatio, ja henkilötietojasi voidaan siirtää eri maihin, kuten Yhdysvaltoihin, Meksikoon tai Intiaan sovellettavan lain mukaisesti sekä säilyttää, tallettaa tai käyttää näissä maissa. Tämä tarkoittaa, että kun keräämme henkilötietojasi, niitä voidaan käsitellä maissa, joiden tietosuojalait poikkeavat oman maasi laeista. Honeywell pyrkii kuitenkin aina kohtuullisiin toimin turvaamaan yksityisyytesi ja tarjoamaan oman asuinmaasi tietosuojan tasoisen henkilötietojen suojan. Näihin toimiin kuuluu Euroopan komission vakiosopimuslausekkeiden käyttö. Jos haluat lisätietoja henkilötietojesi suojaamiseksi toteutetuista toimista, ota yhteyttä sähköpostitse osoitteeseen [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com).

**Turva**

Olemme sitoutuneet pitämään henkilötietosi turvassa. Turvaamme henkilötietojasi teknisin ja organisatorisin toimin taataksemme niille käsittelyn riskeihin nähden asianmukaisen suojan. Jos haluat lisätietoja siitä, miten Honeywell suojaa henkilötietojasi, ota yhteyttä sähköpostitse osoitteeseen [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com)

**Oikeutesi**

Kulloinkin sovellettavasta laista riippuen sinulla voi olla tiettyjä henkilötietoihisi liittyviä oikeuksia.

* Sinulla voi olla oikeus **tarkastaa, korjata ja päivittää** henkilötietosi tai **pyytää niiden poistoa**.
* Voit **vastustaa** henkilötietojesi käsittelyä, pyytää meitä **rajoittamaan** henkilötietojesi käsittelyä tai esittää henkilötietojesi **siirrettävyyttä** koskevan pyynnön.
* Sinulla voi olla oikeus **estää yksinomaan automatisoituun käsittelyyn perustuva itseäsi koskeva päätöksenteko, kuten profilointi,** jos päätöksellä on sinua koskevia oikeusvaikutuksia tai se vaikuttaa sinuun merkittävästi.
* Jos henkilötietojesi keruu ja käsittely on tapahtunut suostumuksellasi, **voit perua suostumuksesi milloin tahansa**. Suostumuksesi peruminen ei vaikuta ennen perumista suoritetun käsittelyn laillisuuteen. Se ei myöskään vaikuta henkilötietojesi käsittelyyn siltä osin kuin käsittelyn oikeusperuste on muu kuin suostumus.
* Sinulla voi olla oikeus kieltää **henkilötietojesi myynti edelleen**. Honeywell ei myy henkilötietojasi kolmansille osapuolille saadakseen taloudellista hyötyä. Me kuitenkin jaamme tai luovutamme henkilötietojasi kolmansille osapuolille tämän Tietosuojalausunnon ja [Evästeilmoituksemme](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#language6) rajauksin. Ulkoistamme kolmansille osapuolille esimerkiksi jälleenmyyntiä, teknisen tuen tarjoamista, verkkosivustojen analytiikkaa sekä tuotteiden ja palveluiden markkinointia ja myyntiä. Tällaiseen toimintaan voi liittyä henkilökohtaisten tietojesi luovuttaminen kolmansille osapuolille, joka voidaan katsoa tietojen myynniksi joidenkin (mutta ei kaikkien) tietosuojalakien nojalla.
* Sinulla on oikeus **tehdä valitus** sille tietosuojaviranomaiselle, joka vastaa henkilötietojen keruuta ja käyttöä koskevasta laillisuusvalvonnasta omassa maassasi, jos uskot meidän käsittelevän henkilötietojasi tietosuojalain vastaisesti. Esimerkiksi Euroopan talousalueella henkilö voi tehdä valituksen toimivaltaiselle tietosuojaviranomaiselle, jotka on listattu osoitteessa [https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/board/members\_fi](https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/board/members_fi). Toivomme kuitenkin, että keskustelet asiasta meidän kanssamme. Ota meihin yhteyttä, kun haluaisit valittaa. Emme syrji ketään siksi, että hän on ajanut tietosuojalakeihin perustuvia oikeuksiaan.

Olemme apuna lakisääteisten oikeuksiesi takaamisessa. Siinäkin tapauksessa, ettei tietosuojalaki suojaisi henkilötietojasi tietyssä tilanteessa, voimme kuitenkin pyrkiä vastaamaan tietojenkäsittelyämme koskeviin pyyntöihisi ja tiedusteluihisi. Jos sinulla on kysyttävää oikeuksistasi tai haluat käyttää niitä, ota meihin yhteyttä sähköpostitse osoitteeseen [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com) tai lähetä tietosuojakysymyksesi interaktiivisen verkkolomakkeemme kautta osoitteessa

**Lasten tiedot**

Sivustojamme ei ole suunnattu alle 16-vuotiaille lapsille. Heidän ei tulisi käyttää sivustoa, emmekä tietoisesti kerää, käytä tai myy alle 16-vuotiaiden tietoja. Jos olet oman maasi lainsäädännön nojalla alaikäinen, älä lähetä meille henkilötietoja Sivustojemme kautta.

**Linkit muihin sivustoihin**

Sivustomme saattavat sisältää linkkejä kolmansien osapuolten sivustoihin, tuotteisiin ja palveluihin. Emme ole vastuussa näistä sivustoista, tuotteista tai palveluista, niiden käytännöistä tai niiden henkilötietojesi keruusta tai muusta käsittelystä. Kolmansilla osapuolilla on omat tietosuojakäytäntönsä. Kehotamme sinua perehtymään näiden kolmansien osapuolten tietosuojakäytäntöihin.

**Ota yhteyttä**

Jos sinulla on kysyttävää tästä tietosuojalausunnosta tai henkilötietojesi käsittelystä, jos haluat tehdä valituksen tai saada yhteyden tietosuojavastaavaamme, ota meihin yhteys käyttäen seuraavia yhteystietoja. Perehdymme asiaasi viivytyksettä ja pyrimme pääsemään tyydyttävään ratkaisuun.

Interaktiivinen verkkolomake:  

Sähköposti:  

Postiosoite:  
Honeywell Privacy  
4D5  
115 Tabor Road  
Morris Plains, NJ 07950

Maksuton puhelin:  

**Tämän tietosuojalausunnon muutokset**

Tätä tietosuojalausuntoa voidaan päivittää ajoittain. Kun niin käy, muutamme Tietosuojalausunnon yläosassa olevaa ”Viimeksi päivitetty” -päiväystä ja ryhdymme muihin lainsäädännön mahdollisesti edellyttämiin lisätoimiin.

**Viimeksi päivitetty 11. kesäkuuta 2021**

**Dernière mise à jour le 11 juin 2021**

**Introduction**

Honeywell International Inc. (« **Honeywell** », « **notre** », « **nos** » ou « **nous** »), est le « responsable du traitement des données » des informations personnelles que nous collectons à votre sujet lorsque vous visitez ou utilisez l’un de nos sites Web, ou lorsque vous utilisez des produits, des services et des applications qui sont associés à la présente Déclaration de confidentialité (collectivement, nos « **Sites** »). La présente Déclaration de confidentialité explique comment nous collectons, partageons et utilisons vos informations personnelles collectées de cette façon et comment vous pouvez exercer vos droits à la confidentialité.

Lorsque nous interagissons avec vous, nous pouvons également vous fournir des notifications de confidentialité supplémentaires concernant des activités de traitement spécifiques ou vous proposer des options supplémentaires pour vous informer de la façon dont Honeywell traite vos informations personnelles à ce moment précis.

Cliquez sur l’un des liens ci-dessous pour accéder à la section qui vous intéresse :

[**La base juridique sur laquelle repose notre traitement des informations**](#fr-heading3)

**Notre collecte des informations**

* **Informations collectées directement auprès de vous**. Nous pouvons être amenés à vous demander des informations personnelles afin de pouvoir assurer le service ou la transaction que vous avez demandé. Vous pouvez également nous communiquer des informations personnelles lorsque vous nous contactez ou que vous collaborez avec nous (via un commentaire, une question ou une demande d’aide, en tant que visiteur de site), ou encore si vous créez un compte pour utiliser nos Sites. Ces informations personnelles peuvent comprendre :
    * **Les données relatives à votre identité** : votre nom, titre, le nom de votre société/organisation, votre adresse e-mail, vos numéros de téléphone et de télécopieur, votre adresse postale (y compris la rue, la ville, la région, le code postal et/ou le pays) ;
    * **Les données relatives à votre inscription** : les données que vous fournissez lorsque vous vous inscrivez à un compte pour utiliser nos Sites, y compris les noms d’utilisateur et les mots de passe ;
    * **Les données relatives à votre recrutement** : notamment les informations soumises dans le cadre d’une demande d’emploi ou d’une candidature à un emploi (voir ci-dessous) ;
    * **Les données relatives à vos informations professionnelles** : des informations relatives à d’autres employés, propriétaires, administrateurs, responsables ou sous-traitants d’une organisation tierce (par exemple, une entreprise, une société, un partenariat, un propriétaire unique, un organisme à but non lucratif ou gouvernemental).
    * **Les données relatives au marketing et aux communications** : vos préférences en matière de marketing et vos abonnements à nos publications ;
    * **Les données financières** : les informations relatives aux cartes de crédit ou autres comptes bancaires aux fins de faciliter vos achats de produits et de services de la Société disponibles sur nos Sites ;
    * **Les informations sur le contrôle des exportations** : les informations portant sur votre nationalité, votre citoyenneté et votre pays de résidence, qui nous permettent de déterminer si vous avez le droit de recevoir des informations au sujet de certaines technologies en vertu des lois en matière d’exportations ;
    * **Les données relatives aux transactions** : les demandes de renseignements et les commandes de nos produits et services, ainsi que les détails des paiements qui vous sont destinés et ceux que vous nous faites, y compris l’historique des commandes d’achat et les informations nécessaires pour faciliter les transactions de paiement ;
    * **Les données relatives à l’inscription à des évènements** : les renseignements que vous fournissez lorsque vous remplissez les formulaires d’inscription électronique ; ainsi que
    * **Vos commentaires** : vos commentaires concernant nos Sites ainsi que nos produits et services en général.

Lorsque vous ne fournissez pas les renseignements demandés, il ne nous est pas toujours possible de satisfaire vos demandes en matière de service ou de finaliser votre transaction.

* **Informations que nous collectons automatiquement à votre sujet**. Nous collectons certaines informations sur votre visite de nos Sites à l’aide de cookies et de technologies de suivi similaires. Nous respecterons toujours tous les droits légaux dont vous pourriez disposer pour nous en empêcher. Les données collectées de cette façon incluent :
    * **Données d’utilisation,** y compris les informations sur la manière dont vous utilisez nos Sites, les pages consultées, le nombre d’octets transférés, les liens sur lesquels vous cliquez, les documents auxquels vous accédez, la date et l’heure d’accès au site, le site à partir duquel vous avez accédé à l’un de nos Sites et d’autres actions effectuées sur les Sites ; et
    * **Données techniques,** telles que votre adresse IP (Internet Protocol), le type et les fonctionnalités de votre navigateur, votre langue et votre système d’exploitation.

Pour plus d’informations sur les cookies et d’autres technologies de suivi similaires que nous utilisons sur nos sites, veuillez consulter notre [Avis relatif aux cookies](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#french).

* **Informations sur la géolocalisation**. Pour certains Sites, avec votre consentement, nous pouvons collecter en temps réel l’emplacement précis (c’est-à-dire la géolocalisation) de votre appareil mobile. Ces informations ne seront utilisées que dans le but de faciliter votre utilisation des Sites, et pourront notamment être utilisées par nos fournisseurs de services, qui pourront traiter ces informations en relation avec la prestation de services en notre nom. Si vous accordez votre consentement, vous pouvez modifier celui-ci en gérant vos préférences de Services de localisation dans les paramètres de votre appareil mobile.
* **Informations provenant de tiers**. Conformément à la législation en vigueur, nous pouvons collecter des informations personnelles à votre sujet auprès de tiers, comme des sites de réseaux sociaux ou des applications, et les combiner avec des informations que nous détenons déjà, afin de nous aider à améliorer et à personnaliser nos Sites en fonction de vos préférences et à d’autres fins définies dans la présente Déclaration de confidentialité. Nous pouvons également collecter vos coordonnées professionnelles auprès de votre organisation ou d’autres tiers afin de faciliter ou d’exercer des activités commerciales classiques et des tâches administratives similaires.

**Notre utilisation des informations**

Nous pouvons utiliser les informations personnelles collectées via nos Sites ou lorsque vous nous contactez à des fins qui incluent les suivantes :

* **Coordonnées professionnelles**. Honeywell collecte et utilise les coordonnées professionnelles afin d’effectuer des communications ou des transactions, y compris pour réaliser une vérification au préalable sur, ou fournir ou recevoir, un produit ou un service. Par exemple, Honeywell peut collecter et utiliser ces coordonnées professionnelles afin de faciliter et de gérer les commandes, les contrats, les garanties, la maintenance et des fonctions professionnelles similaires, à des fins d’analyse du crédit et de collecte, pour nous assister dans le cadre de nos obligations juridiques et de conformité internes, et (si nécessaire) de défendre nos intérêts et nos demandes.
* **Services and transactions**. Nous pouvons utiliser vos informations personnelles pour vous fournir les services ou réaliser les opérations que vous avez demandées, y compris, mais sans s’y limiter, l’envoi d’informations sur les produits ou services de la Société que vous avez achetés ou que vous utilisez par ailleurs, l’enregistrement des produits achetés, le traitement des commandes, la gestion des réclamations liées à la garantie, le remplacement des manuels de référence des produits, le traitement des demandes de service client, l’aide à l’utilisation de nos Sites.
* **Administration et protection de nos activités et de nos Sites**. Nous pouvons utiliser vos informations personnelles pour administrer et protéger notre entreprise et nos Sites, y compris le dépannage, la maintenance du système, l’assistance, le reporting et l’hébergement des données.
* **Amélioration de nos activités, de nos Sites, de nos produits et de nos services**. Nous pouvons utiliser vos informations personnelles pour effectuer des analyses commerciales ou à d’autres fins pouvant nous aider à développer et améliorer la qualité de nos activités, Sites, produits et services (y compris les nouveaux produits et services), par exemple en personnalisant nos Sites selon vos préférences ou centres d’intérêts.
* **Marketing**. Conformément aux lois et réglementations applicables, nous pouvons utiliser vos informations personnelles pour vous informer des produits ou services susceptibles de vous intéresser, mais aussi pour communiquer avec vous concernant des offres, événements et actualités, sondages, offres spéciales et sujets connexes. Vous pouvez à tout moment vous désabonner des communications marketing envoyées par e-mail en utilisant le lien « Désabonnement » contenu dans nos e-mails de marketing, ou en nous contactant avec les coordonnées présentes dans cette Déclaration de confidentialité. En fonction de votre pays de résidence, vous pouvez également désactiver d’autres types de communications marketing. Pour plus d’informations, veuillez nous contacter en utilisant les coordonnées répertoriées dans la présente Déclaration de confidentialité. Certaines juridictions donnent le droit à des individus (par exemple, les résidents de la Californie) de demander certaines informations concernant la divulgation de leurs informations personnelles à des tiers dans le cadre des objectifs de marketing direct du tiers. Pour de plus amples informations sur nos pratiques en matière de divulgation de données à des fins de marketing, veuillez nous contacter en suivant les instructions énumérées ci-dessous.
* **Publicités ciblées par centre d’intérêt**. Nous collectons des données sur vos activités en ligne et identifions vos centres d’intérêt afin de pouvoir vous proposer les publicités les plus pertinentes pour votre profil. Vous pouvez refuser de recevoir de la part de Honeywell des publicités ciblées par centre d’intérêt, comme décrit dans notre [Avis relatif aux cookies](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#french).
* **Programmes d’incitation financière et de fidélité**. Nous collectons et utilisons des informations personnelles pour gérer et administrer nos programmes d’incitation financière et de fidélité. Nous utilisons les informations personnelles que vous fournissez dans le cadre de ces programmes pour offrir des récompenses uniques, suivre l’état de votre programme et faciliter l’échange de points de programme pour des produits, du matériel promotionnel, des ateliers de formation et d’autres articles. Dans la mesure permise par la loi, nous pouvons également utiliser les informations personnelles que vous fournissez dans le cadre d’un programme d’incitation financière pour toute autre fin énoncée dans la présente Déclaration de confidentialité. Veuillez consulter les conditions générales de chaque programme d’incitation financière dans lequel vous souhaitez vous inscrire ou auquel vous souhaitez participer, car ces conditions générales peuvent être adaptées avec précision au programme applicable. Si vous acceptez de participer à ces programmes, vous pouvez à tout moment nous contacter en utilisant les coordonnées à la fin de la présente Déclaration de confidentialité ou en suivant les instructions détaillées des conditions générales du programme en vigueur.
* **Demandes d’emploi**. Dans le cadre d’une demande d’emploi ou d’une requête, vous pouvez nous fournir des informations sur vous-même, par exemple un CV, des références professionnelles, des informations sur votre niveau d’éducation et vos antécédents professionnels, ainsi que des informations sur vos formations et certifications professionnelles. Les membres de notre groupe et nous-même pouvons utiliser ces informations à des fins de recrutement, de contrôle des antécédents et d’éligibilité à l’emploi, et tel qu’établi dans toute Déclaration de confidentialité ou tout autre avis distinct disponible en relation avec votre demande. Nous pouvons faire appel à un tiers (par exemple, un recruteur) ou utiliser une plateforme de réseaux sociaux pour solliciter, collecter et conserver des demandes d’emploi. Pour plus d’informations, veuillez lire notre [Avis de confidentialité des candidats à un emploi](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/applicant-privacy-notice#french).
* **Recherche et analyse**. Nous pouvons utiliser vos informations personnelles pour effectuer des recherches et des analyses afin de nous aider à analyser vos préférences d’achat, d’identifier les produits et services qui répondent le mieux à vos besoins, mais aussi pour mesurer l’efficacité des publicités que nous vous proposons.
* **Application** : nous nous réservons le droit d’utiliser les informations personnelles recueillies afin de détecter et prévenir des fraudes ou de réagir si elles sont avérées, des violations de la propriété intellectuelle, tout non-respect de nos Conditions d’utilisation ou de la loi ainsi que toute autre utilisation non appropriée de nos Sites.

Lorsque la loi l’autorise, nous pouvons combiner les données que nous collectons via nos Sites avec d’autres informations que nous détenons à votre sujet (telles que des informations sur votre utilisation de nos produits et services) afin de vous offrir une expérience client améliorée et cohérente lorsque vous interagissez avec nous ou à d’autres fins énoncées dans la présente Déclaration de confidentialité.

**La base juridique sur laquelle repose notre traitement des informations**

Lorsque cela est requis par la loi, nous nous assurons qu’il existe une base juridique pour le traitement de vos informations personnelles. Dans la plupart des cas, notre base juridique dépend de la protection des informations personnelles et du contexte spécifique dans lequel nous les collectons.

* **Contrat** : le traitement est nécessaire pour l’exécution des services que nous vous fournissons, ou afin de prendre les mesures (à votre demande) avant et en prévision de l’exécution de ces services ;
* **Obligation juridique** : le traitement est nécessaire pour nous conformer à nos obligations légales, y compris le respect des lois, règlements, demandes gouvernementales et paragouvernementales, ordonnances des tribunaux ou assignations à comparaître ;
* **Consentement** : le traitement se base sur votre consentement au traitement de vos informations personnelles à une ou plusieurs fins spécifiées (par exemple, le marketing) ;
* **Intérêts légitimes** : le traitement est nécessaire pour répondre à nos intérêts légitimes, par exemple pour développer et améliorer nos Sites, produits et/ou services au bénéfice de nos clients ; ou
* **Intérêts vitaux** : le traitement est nécessaire pour protéger vos intérêts vitaux (par exemple, pour des raisons de santé et de sécurité si vous assistez à une réunion sur un site Honeywell).

Si vous avez des questions ou si vous avez besoin d’informations complémentaires relatives à la base juridique sur laquelle nous recueillons et utilisons vos informations personnelles, veuillez envoyer un e-mail à l’adresse [HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com).

**Anonymisation des informations**

Conformément à la législation applicable, nous pouvons anonymiser vos informations personnelles afin qu’elles ne puissent plus être utilisées pour vous identifier. Les informations anonymisées ne sont pas considérées comme des informations personnelles et ne sont donc pas soumises à cette Déclaration de confidentialité. Nous pouvons collecter, utiliser, regrouper et partager des informations anonymisées à n’importe quelle fin.

**Combien de temps conservons-nous les informations ?**

La période durant laquelle nous stockons vos informations personnelles varie en fonction de l’objectif du traitement. Par exemple, nous stockons les informations personnelles nécessaires pour vous fournir des produits et des services, ou pour faciliter les transactions que vous avez demandées, tant que vous êtes client de Honeywell ou si vous envoyez une candidature à un poste via nos Sites, nous conserverons les détails de votre demande tel que défini dans l’avis de confidentialité qui vous est fourni en lien avec votre candidature ou tel qu’exigé par la loi. Dans tous les autres cas, nous conservons vos informations personnelles aussi longtemps que nécessaire pour atteindre les objectifs énoncés dans la présente Déclaration de confidentialité, après quoi elles seront anonymisées (lorsque la loi l’autorise), supprimées ou détruites.

**Divulgation des informations**

Conformément à la législation applicable, nous pouvons partager vos informations personnelles avec des tiers sélectionnés, y compris de la manière indiquée ci-dessous :

* **Les sociétés du groupe**. Nous pouvons partager vos informations personnelles avec les filiales et sociétés du groupe dans la mesure où cela est raisonnablement nécessaire aux fins énoncées dans la présente Déclaration de confidentialité.
* **Prestataires de services**. Nous pouvons partager vos informations personnelles avec des entreprises avec lesquelles nous sommes sous contrat afin de leur permettre de fournir des services en notre nom, tels que l’hébergement de sites Web, la réalisation de sondages, le traitement des transactions, l’analyse de nos Sites ainsi que l’exécution d’analyses pour améliorer la qualité de nos activités, Sites, produits et services. Nous demandons à ces prestataires de services de protéger la confidentialité de vos informations personnelles.
* **Distributeurs et autres partenaires commerciaux de confiance**. Nous pouvons partager vos informations personnelles avec des tiers qui distribuent nos produits, mais aussi avec d’autres partenaires commerciaux de confiance dans le but de permettre à ces tiers de vous envoyer des e-mails de marketing. Un tel partage d’informations personnelles à des fins de marketing sera effectué conformément aux législations et règlements applicables.
* **Divulgation en rapport avec des transactions**. Dans le cadre de certaines transactions, nous nous réservons le droit de divulguer tout ou partie de vos informations personnelles à des institutions financières, à des organismes publics et à des sociétés assurant des services de livraison ou postaux, qui en auraient besoin pour mener à bien la transaction en question.
* **Divulgations en lien avec des acquisitions ou des cessions**. Dans certains cas, Honeywell peut décider pour des raisons stratégiques ou d’autres motifs d’affaires de vendre, d’acheter, de fusionner ou de réorganiser des activités dans certains pays. Nous nous réservons le droit de dévoiler certaines informations vous concernant et dont nous disposons, uniquement si c’est nécessaire, au cours de négociations dans le cadre d’une fusion, d’une acquisition, d’une cession ou d’une vente de tout ou partie des actifs de Honeywell.
* **Divulgation pour d’autres motifs**. Nous pouvons divulguer des informations personnelles dans le cas où la loi l’exige/l’autorise ou si nous jugeons, en toute bonne foi, que cela est indispensable pour nous conformer aux obligations légales ou aux réglementations qui nous sont imposées, pour défendre et faire valoir nos droits de propriété ou autres, ou dans des cas d’urgence en vue de garantir la sécurité des individus.

**Transferts internationaux**

Honeywell est une société mondiale et vos informations personnelles peuvent être transmises, conservées, stockées ou utilisées dans diverses implantations du monde entier, tel qu’aux États-Unis, au Mexique et en Inde conformément à la législation en vigueur. Cela signifie que lorsque nous recueillons vos informations personnelles, elles peuvent être traitées dans des pays qui peuvent disposer de lois sur la protection des données qui sont différentes des lois de votre pays. Cependant, Honeywell prendra toujours des mesures raisonnables pour protéger votre vie privée et fournir un niveau de protection des informations personnelles comparable à celui de votre pays de résidence, ce qui inclut la mise en œuvre des Clauses contractuelles types de la Commission européenne. Pour de plus amples informations sur les mesures de protection appropriées qui ont été mises en place pour protéger vos informations personnelles, veuillez nous contacter à l’adresse [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com).

**Sécurité**

Nous nous engageons à assurer la protection de vos informations personnelles. Nous avons recours à des mesures techniques et organisationnelles pour fournir un niveau de sécurité adapté au risque de traitement de vos informations personnelles. Pour plus d’informations sur la façon dont Honeywell protège vos informations personnelles, veuillez nous contacter à l’adresse [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com).

**Vos droits**

Selon la loi en vigueur, vous pouvez disposer de certains droits quant à vos informations personnelles.

* Vous pouvez disposer du droit de **consulter, corriger, mettre à jour** ou **demander la suppression** de vos informations personnelles.
* Vous pouvez **vous opposer** au traitement de vos informations personnelles, nous demander de **restreindre** le traitement de vos informations personnelles ou demander la **portabilité** de vos informations personnelles.
* Vous disposez du droit **de refuser qu’une décision soit prise uniquement sur la base d’un traitement automatisé, y compris le profilage,** si cette décision génère des effets juridiques à votre encontre ou vous affecte de manière significative.
* De même, si nous avons recueilli et traité vos informations personnelles avec votre consentement, **vous pouvez retirer votre consentement à tout moment**. Le retrait de votre consentement n’affectera en rien la légalité des traitements que nous avons effectués avant votre retrait, et cela n’affectera pas le traitement de vos informations personnelles effectué en se fondant sur des motifs de traitement licites autres que le consentement.
* Vous pouvez avoir le droit de **refuser la vente de vos informations personnelles**. Honeywell ne vend pas vos informations personnelles à des tiers afin d’en tirer profit. Toutefois, nous partageons ou divulguons vos informations personnelles à des tiers conformément à la présente Déclaration de confidentialité et à notre [Avis relatif aux cookies](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#french). Par exemple, nous collaborons avec des tiers pour distribuer nos produits, vous fournir une assistance technique, exploiter des outils et des fonctionnalités analytiques du site Web, et procéder à la commercialisation et à la vente de nos produits et services. Ces activités peuvent impliquer la divulgation de vos informations personnelles à des tiers et peuvent être considérées comme une « vente » de données en vertu de certaines lois (mais pas toutes) sur la protection des données.
* Vous avez le droit de **porter plainte auprès** d’une autorité de protection des données responsable de l’application de la loi sur la protection des données dans votre juridiction concernant la collecte et l’utilisation de vos données personnelles si vous pensez que le traitement de vos données personnelles ne respecte pas la loi sur la protection des données. Par exemple, les personnes de l’EEE ont le droit de déposer une plainte auprès de l’autorité compétente en matière de protection des données, dont la liste est accessible à l’adresse suivante : [https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/board/members\_en](https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/board/members_en). Nous serions toutefois heureux de pouvoir répondre à vos préoccupations, alors n’hésitez pas à nous contacter pour toute plainte que vous pourriez avoir. Nous n’exercerons aucune discrimination à l’encontre de personnes ayant exercé leurs droits à la confidentialité des données.

Nous faciliterons l’exercice des droits qui vous sont applicables conformément à la législation en vigueur. Cependant, même si vos informations personnelles ne sont pas protégées par une loi sur la protection des données, ou autrement assujetties à cette législation, nous pouvons nous efforcer de répondre à toute demande ou requête que vous pourriez avoir en ce qui concerne nos activités de traitement de données. Si vous avez des questions sur vos droits ou souhaitez exercer vos droits, vous pouvez nous contacter à l’adresse [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com) ou soumettre des questions relatives à la confidentialité en utilisant notre formulaire Web interactif disponible via le lien suivant :

**Informations relatives aux enfants**

Nos Sites ne sont pas destinés aux enfants de moins de seize (16) ans et ne doivent pas être utilisés par ceux-ci, et nous ne recueillons pas, n’utilisons pas ou ne vendons pas volontairement des informations relatives à ces personnes. Si vous êtes mineur au sens des lois de votre pays, veuillez ne pas soumettre d’informations personnelles via nos Sites.

**Liens vers d’autres sites Web**

Nos Sites peuvent contenir des liens vers des sites Web, produits et services de tiers. Nous n’avons aucune responsabilité ou obligation envers ces sites, produits et services, leurs politiques, leur collecte ou tout autre traitement de vos informations personnelles. Les pratiques de ces tiers sont régies par leurs propres politiques de confidentialité. Nous vous encourageons à vous familiariser avec les politiques de confidentialité de ces tiers.

**Nous contacter**

Si vous avez des questions concernant cette Déclaration de confidentialité ou notre traitement de vos informations personnelles, si vous souhaitez déposer une plainte ou contacter notre agent de protection des données, veuillez nous contacter en utilisant les coordonnées ci-dessous. Nous ferons tout ce qui est en notre pouvoir pour répondre rapidement à votre requête et trouver une juste issue au problème.

Formulaire Web interactif:  

E-mail:  

Adresse postale:  
Honeywell Privacy  
4D5  
115 Tabor Road  
Morris Plains, NJ 07950

Numéro gratuit:  

**Modification de la Déclaration de confidentialité**

Nous pouvons de temps à autre mettre à jour la présente déclaration de confidentialité. Dans un tel cas, nous actualiserons la date de la « dernière mise à jour » en haut de la Déclaration de confidentialité et prendrons les mesures supplémentaires requises par la loi.

**Dernière mise à jour le 11 juin 2021**

**Dernière mise à jour le 11 juin 2021**

**Introduction**

Honeywell International Inc. (« **Honeywell** », « **notre** », « **nos** » ou « **nous** »), est le « contrôleur des données » pour les renseignements personnels que nous recueillons à votre sujet lorsque vous visitez ou utilisez l’un de nos Sites Web, ou lorsque vous utilisez des produits, des services et des applications qui sont associés à la présente Déclaration de confidentialité (collectivement, nos « **Sites** »). La présente Déclaration de confidentialité explique comment nous recueillons, partageons et utilisons vos renseignements personnels recueillis de cette façon et comment vous pouvez exercer vos droits à la confidentialité.

Lorsque nous interagissons avec vous, nous pouvons également vous fournir des notifications de confidentialité supplémentaires concernant des activités de traitement spécifiques ou vous proposer des options supplémentaires pour vous informer de la façon dont Honeywell traite vos renseignements personnels à ce moment précis.

Cliquez sur l’un des liens ci-dessous pour accéder à la section qui vous intéresse :

[**Le fondement juridique sur lequel s’appuie notre traitement des renseignements**](#fr-ca-heading3)

**Notre procédure de collecte de renseignements**

* **Informations recueillies directement auprès de vous**. Nous pourrions vous demander des renseignements personnels afin de vous fournir un service ou d’effectuer une transaction que vous avez demandée. Il se peut également que vous fournissiez des renseignements personnels lorsque vous communiquez avec nous (par exemple, pour envoyer un commentaire, une demande de renseignements ou une demande de soutien à la clientèle, visiter un site) ou que vous créiez un compte pour utiliser nos Sites. Ces renseignements personnels peuvent comprendre :
    * **Des données d’identification,** comme votre nom, titre, nom d’entreprise ou d’organisation, adresse courriel, numéros de téléphone, adresse postale ou code postal (y compris la rue, la ville, la province, le code postal ou le pays);
    * **Des données d’enregistrement,** comme les renseignements que vous nous fournissez lorsque vous créez un compte pour utiliser nos Sites, y compris les noms d’utilisateur et les mots de passe;
    * **Des données de recrutement,** y compris les renseignements soumis associés à une demande d’emploi ou de renseignements (comme décrit ci-dessous);
    * **Des coordonnées professionnelles,** comme des informations relatives à d’autres employés, propriétaires, administrateurs, responsables ou sous-traitants d’une organisation tierce (par exemple, une entreprise, une société, un partenariat, un propriétaire unique, un organisme à but non lucratif ou gouvernemental).
    * **De données de marketing et de communication,** y compris vos préférences marketing et vos abonnements à nos publications;
    * **Des données financières,** y compris des renseignements de carte de crédit ou d’autres renseignements financiers afin de nous permettre de faciliter votre achat de produits et services de la Société pouvant être offerts sur nos Sites;
    * **Des renseignements pour les contrôles des exportations,** comme votre nationalité et votre pays de résidence pour nous permettre de déterminer, conformément aux contrôles des exportations, votre admissibilité à recevoir des renseignements au sujet de certaines technologies;
    * **Des données de transaction,** y compris les demandes de renseignements et les commandes pour nos produits et services ainsi que les détails des paiements que vous recevez et que vous effectuez, dont l’historique des commandes et les informations nécessaires pour faciliter les transactions de paiement;
    * **Des renseignements d’inscription aux événements,** y compris les renseignements que vous fournissez lorsque vous remplissez des formulaires d’inscription en ligne;
    * **Vos commentaires, y compris des sondages,** des recommandations ou d’autres commentaires généraux que vous transmettez concernant nos Sites et nos produits et services.

Si ne vous ne communiquez pas les renseignements demandés, nous pourrions ne pas être en mesure de vous fournir le service demandé ou d’effectuer votre transaction.

* **Les renseignements que nous recueillons automatiquement sur vous**. Nous recueillons automatiquement certaines informations vous concernant lors de votre visite sur nos Sites à l’aide de témoins et d’autres technologies de suivi similaires. Nous respecterons toujours tous les droits légaux dont vous pourriez disposer et qui nous empêcheraient de le faire. Les données collectées de cette façon comprennent :
    * **Des données sur l’utilisation,** y compris des renseignements sur l’utilisation que vous faites de nos Sites, les pages affichées, la quantité d’octets transférés, les liens visités, le contenu consulté, la date et l’heure auxquelles vous avez accédé au site, le site Web à partir duquel vous avez été redirigé vers l’un de nos Sites ainsi que toute autre activité effectuée sur les sites;
    * **Des données techniques,** comme votre adresse IP (Internet Protocol), le type et les capacités de votre navigateur, votre langue et votre système d’exploitation.

Pour plus d’informations sur les témoins et d’autres technologies de suivi similaires que nous utilisons sur nos Sites, veuillez consulter notre [Avis relatif aux témoins](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#french-canadian).

* **Des données de géolocalisation**.Sur certains sites, avec votre consentement, nous pourrions collecter avec précision l’emplacement exact en temps réel de votre appareil mobile (c.-à-d. la géolocalisation). Ces informations ne seront utilisées que dans le but de faciliter votre utilisation des Sites, et pourront notamment être utilisées par nos fournisseurs de services, qui pourront traiter ces informations en relation avec la prestation de services en notre nom. Si vous accordez votre consentement, vous pouvez modifier celui-ci en gérant vos préférences de Services de localisation dans les paramètres de votre appareil mobile.
* **Renseignements recueillis auprès de tiers**. Conformément à la loi applicable, nous pouvons recueillir des renseignements personnels vous concernant auprès de tiers, comme des sites Web ou des applications de médias sociaux, et les combiner aux renseignements que nous détenons déjà afin de nous aider à améliorer et à personnaliser nos Sites selon vos préférences ainsi qu’à d’autres fins indiquées dans cet énoncé de confidentialité. Nous pouvons également recueillir vos coordonnées professionnelles auprès de votre employeur ou d’autres tiers afin de faciliter ou d’entreprendre des activités commerciales traditionnelles et des questions administratives similaires.

**La façon dont nous utilisons l’information**

Nous pouvons utiliser les renseignements personnels recueillis sur nos Sites ou lorsque vous communiquez avec nous aux fins suivantes :

* **Coordonnées professionnelles**. Honeywell collecte et utilise les coordonnées professionnelles afin d’effectuer des communications ou des transactions, y compris pour réaliser une vérification au préalable sur un produit ou un service ou la prestation ou réception d’un produit ou d’un service. Par exemple, Honeywell peut collecter et utiliser ces coordonnées professionnelles afin de faciliter et de gérer les commandes, les contrats, les garanties, la maintenance et des fonctions professionnelles similaires à des fins d’analyse du crédit et de collecte, pour nous assister dans le cadre de nos obligations juridiques et de conformité internes, et, si nécessaire, de défendre nos intérêts et nos demandes.
* **Services et transactions**. Nous pouvons utiliser vos renseignements personnels pour vous fournir des services ou effectuer des transactions que vous avez demandées, y compris, mais sans s’y limiter, pour vous fournir des informations sur des produits ou des services de la Société que vous avez achetés ou que vous utilisez, enregistrer des produits achetés, traiter des commandes de produits, traiter des réclamations sous garantie, remplacer des manuels des produits, répondre aux questions adressées au service à la clientèle et faciliter l’utilisation de nos Sites.
* **Gestion et protection de notre entreprise et de nos Sites**. Nous pouvons utiliser vos renseignements personnels pour gérer et protéger nos activités et nos Sites, y compris le dépannage, la maintenance du système, le soutien, la production de rapport et l’hébergement des données.
* **Amélioration de notre entreprise, de nos Sites, de nos produits et de nos services**. Nous pouvons utiliser vos renseignements personnels aux fins d’analyses commerciales ou à d’autres fins qui nous aident à développer et à améliorer la qualité de divers aspects de notre entreprise, de nos Sites et de nos produits et services (y compris les nouveaux produits et services), par exemple en adaptant nos Sites à vos préférences et à vos champs d’intérêt.
* **Marketing**. Conformément aux lois et réglementations applicables, nous pouvons utiliser vos renseignements personnels pour vous informer des produits ou des services susceptibles de vous intéresser et pour communiquer avec vous concernant des offres, des événements, des nouvelles, des sondages, des offres spéciales et des sujets connexes. Vous pouvez vous désabonner des communications marketing envoyées par courriel en tout temps en cliquant sur le lien de désabonnement figurant dans tout matériel de marketing par courriel que nous vous envoyons ou en communiquant avec nous à l’aide des coordonnées indiquées dans cet énoncé de confidentialité. Selon votre pays de résidence, vous pouvez également vous désabonner d’autres types de communications marketing; veuillez communiquer avec nous à l’aide des coordonnées indiquées dans l’énoncé de confidentialité pour plus d’informations. Certaines administrations (p. ex. les résidents de Californie) donnent aux personnes le droit de demander certaines informations concernant notre divulgation de renseignements personnels à des tiers à des fins de marketing direct. Pour de plus amples informations sur nos pratiques en matière de divulgation de données à des fins de marketing, veuillez nous contacter en suivant les directives ci-dessous.
* **Publicités ciblées par centre d’intérêt**. Nous collectons des données sur vos activités en ligne et déterminons vos centres d’intérêt afin de pouvoir vous proposer les publicités les plus pertinentes pour votre profil. Vous pouvez refuser de recevoir de la part de Honeywell des publicités ciblées par centre d’intérêt, comme décrit dans notre [Avis relatif aux témoins](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#french-canadian).
* **Programmes d’incitation financière et de fidélité**. Nous collectons et utilisons des renseignements personnels pour gérer et administrer nos programmes d’incitation financière et de fidélité. Nous utilisons les renseignements personnels que vous fournissez dans le cadre de ces programmes pour offrir des récompenses uniques, suivre l’état de votre programme et faciliter l’échange de points de programme pour des produits, du matériel promotionnel, des ateliers de formation et d’autres articles. Dans la mesure permise par la loi, nous pouvons également utiliser les renseignements personnels que vous fournissez dans le cadre d’un programme d’incitation financière pour toute autre fin énoncée dans la présente Déclaration de confidentialité. Veuillez consulter les conditions générales de chaque programme d’incitation financière dans lequel vous souhaitez vous inscrire ou auquel vous souhaitez participer, car ces conditions générales peuvent être adaptées avec précision au programme applicable. Si vous acceptez de participer à ces programmes, vous pouvez à tout moment communiquer avec nous en utilisant les coordonnées à la fin de la présente Déclaration de confidentialité ou en suivant les instructions détaillées des conditions générales du programme en vigueur.
* **Demandes d’emploi**. Dans le cadre d’un renseignement ou d’une demande d’emploi, vous pourriez nous fournir des renseignements personnels, comme votre CV, des références professionnelles, des renseignements sur votre scolarité et vos antécédents d’emploi, ainsi que des renseignements sur vos formations ou certifications professionnelles. Les membres de notre groupe et nous-mêmes pouvons utiliser ces renseignements à des fins de recrutement, de vérification des antécédents et d’admissibilité à l’emploi, et tel qu’établi dans toute Déclaration de confidentialité ou tout autre avis distinct disponible en relation avec votre demande. Nous pouvons utiliser un tiers (p. ex. un recruteur) ou une plateforme de médias sociaux pour solliciter, collecter et conserver les demandes d’emploi. Pour plus d’informations, veuillez lire notre [Avis de confidentialité du candidat](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/applicant-privacy-notice#french-canadian).
* **Recherche et analyse**. Nous pouvons utiliser vos renseignements personnels pour effectuer des recherches et des analyses afin de nous aider à examiner vos préférences d’achat, à déterminer les produits et services qui répondent le mieux à vos besoins et à mesurer l’efficacité de la publicité que nous vous présentons.
* **Application**: Nous pouvons utiliser les renseignements personnels que nous recueillons afin de détecter, de prévenir et de combattre la fraude, l’utilisation abusive de nos Sites et la violation de la propriété intellectuelle, de nos conditions générales et des lois.

Si la loi le permet, nous pouvons combiner les renseignements que nous recueillons sur nos Sites à d’autres renseignements vous concernant que nous détenons (comme des renseignements sur votre utilisation de nos produits et services) afin de vous offrir une expérience client améliorée et cohérente lorsque vous interagissez avec nous ou à d’autres fins indiquées dans cet énoncé de confidentialité.

**Le fondement juridique sur lequel s’appuie notre traitement des renseignements**

Lorsque la loi l’exige, nous nous assurons qu’il existe un fondement juridique pour le traitement de vos renseignements personnels. Dans la plupart des cas, notre fondement juridique pour la collecte et l’utilisation des renseignements personnels décrits dans le présent Avis de confidentialité dépendra des renseignements personnels applicables et du contexte spécifique dans lequel nous les recueillons.

* **Contrat** : le traitement est nécessaire pour l’exécution des services que nous vous fournissons ou afin de prendre les mesures (à votre demande) avant et en prévision de l’exécution de ces services;
* **Obligation juridique** : le traitement est nécessaire pour nous conformer à nos obligations légales, y compris le respect des lois, des règlements, des demandes gouvernementales et quasi gouvernementales, des ordonnances ou des citations à comparaître applicables;
* **Consentement** : le traitement est fondé sur votre consentement au traitement de vos renseignements personnels à une ou plusieurs fins précisées (par exemple, à des fins de marketing);
* **Intérêts légitimes** : le traitement est nécessaire pour répondre à nos intérêts légitimes, par exemple pour développer et améliorer nos Sites, nos produits ou nos services au profit de nos clients.
* **Intérêts vitaux** : le traitement est nécessaire pour protéger vos intérêts vitaux (par exemple, pour des raisons de santé et de sécurité si vous assistez à une réunion dans un établissement Honeywell).

Si vous avez des questions ou avez besoin d’autres renseignements en ce qui concerne le fondement juridique de notre collecte et de notre utilisation de vos renseignements personnels, veuillez envoyer un courriel à [HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com).

**L’anonymisation des informations**

Conformément à la loi applicable, nous pouvons anonymiser vos renseignements personnels afin qu’ils ne puissent plus être utilisés pour vous identifier. Les renseignements anonymisés ne sont pas considérés comme des renseignements personnels; ils ne sont donc pas assujettis à cet énoncé de confidentialité. Nous pouvons recueillir, utiliser, regrouper et partager des renseignements anonymisés à n’importe quelle fin.

**Durée de conservation des renseignements**

La période durant laquelle nous conservons vos renseignements personnels varie en fonction de l’objectif de traitement. Par exemple, nous conservons les renseignements personnels nécessaires pour vous fournir des produits et des services ou pour faciliter les transactions que vous avez demandées aussi longtemps que vous êtes un client de Honeywell ou si vous soumettez une demande d’emploi sur nos Sites, nous conserverons les détails de votre demande comme l’indique l’énoncé de confidentialité ou tout autre avis mis à votre disposition dans le cadre de votre demande ou comme la loi l’exige. Dans tous les autres cas, nous conservons vos renseignements personnels aussi longtemps que nécessaire aux fins décrites dans cet énoncé de confidentialité, après quoi ils sont anonymisés (lorsque la loi applicable le permet), supprimés ou détruits.

**Divulgation des informations**

Nous pouvons partager vos renseignements personnels avec des tiers sélectionnés conformément à la loi applicable, y compris comme indiqué ci-dessous :

* **Les sociétés de notre groupe**. Nous pouvons partager vos renseignements personnels avec nos sociétés affiliées et les sociétés de notre groupe pour des utilisations raisonnablement nécessaires aux fins décrites dans le présent énoncé de confidentialité.
* **Les fournisseurs de services**. Nous pouvons partager vos renseignements personnels avec des entreprises que nous avons engagées pour la prestation de services pour notre compte, comme l’hébergement de sites Web, la réalisation de sondages, le traitement de transactions, l’analyse de nos Sites et la production d’analyses pour améliorer la qualité de divers aspects de notre entreprise, de nos Sites et de nos produits et services. Nous exigeons que ces fournisseurs de services protègent la confidentialité de vos renseignements personnels.
* **Les distributeurs et autres partenaires commerciaux de confiance**. Nous pourrions partager vos renseignements personnels avec des tiers qui distribuent nos produits et avec d’autres partenaires commerciaux de confiance à des fins comprenant la possibilité que ces tiers communiquent avec vous à des fins de marketing. Le partage de renseignements personnels à des fins de marketing sera effectué conformément aux lois et règlements applicables.
* **Divulgation de renseignements dans le contexte d’une transaction**. Dans le cadre de certaines transactions, nous pourrions divulguer une partie ou l’intégralité de vos renseignements personnels aux institutions financières, entités gouvernementales et sociétés d’expédition ou services postaux qui participent à l’exécution de la transaction.
* **Divulgation en lien avec des acquisitions ou des cessions**. Dans certaines circonstances, il est possible que la Société décide, pour des questions stratégiques ou d’autres raisons professionnelles, de vendre, d’acheter, de désinvestir, de fusionner ou de réorganiser autrement les activités dans certains pays ou de se départir de ces activités. Il se peut que nous divulguions des renseignements à votre sujet dans la mesure nécessaire à juste titre afin de mener les négociations, voire de procéder à la fusion, à l’acquisition, au désinvestissement ou à la vente des actifs de Honeywell en tout ou en partie.
* **Divulgation pour d’autres motifs**. Nous pouvons divulguer des renseignements personnels si la loi l’exige ou l’autorise ou si nous jugeons en toute bonne foi qu’une telle action est nécessaire pour nous conformer à des obligations légales ou à des recours en droit exercés à notre égard, pour protéger et défendre nos droits et nos biens, ou dans des circonstances urgentes de protection de la sécurité personnelle de tout individu.

**Transferts internationaux**

Compte tenu du fait que Honeywell est une organisation internationale, vos renseignements personnels peuvent être transférés, détenus, conservés ou utilisés sur différentes plateformes à travers le monde, par exemple aux États-Unis, au Mexique et en Inde conformément aux lois applicables. Cela signifie que lorsque nous recueillons vos renseignements, ceux-ci peuvent être traités dans des pays appliquant des lois sur la protection des données différentes des lois de votre pays. Toutefois, Honeywell prendra toujours des mesures raisonnables pour protéger votre vie privée et pour assurer un niveau de protection des renseignements personnels comparable à celui de votre pays de résidence, y compris par la mise en œuvre des clauses contractuelles standard de la Commission européenne. Pour de plus amples informations sur les mesures de protection appropriées qui ont été mises en place pour protéger vos renseignements personnels, veuillez nous contacter à l’adresse [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com).

**Sécurité**

Nous nous engageons à protéger la sécurité de vos renseignements personnels. Nous avons recours à des mesures techniques et organisationnelles pour fournir un niveau de sécurité adapté au risque de traitement de vos renseignements personnels. Pour plus d’informations sur la façon dont Honeywell protège vos renseignements personnels, veuillez nous contacter à l’adresse [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com).

**Vos droits**

Selon la loi en vigueur, vous pouvez disposer de certains droits quant à vos renseignements personnels.

* Vous pouvez avoir le droit **d’accéder, de corriger, de mettre à jour** ou **de demander la suppression** de vos renseignements personnels.
* Vous pouvez vous **opposer** au traitement de vos renseignements personnels, nous demander de **restreindre** le traitement de vos renseignements personnels ou demander la **transférabilité** de vos renseignements personnels.
* Vous disposez du droit **de refuser qu’une décision soit prise uniquement sur la base d’un traitement automatisé, y compris le profilage,** si cette décision génère des effets juridiques à votre encontre ou vous affecte de manière significative.
* De la même façon, si nous avons recueilli et traité vos renseignements personnels avec votre consentement, **vous pouvez retirer votre consentement en tout temps**. Le retrait de votre consentement n’aura aucune incidence sur la légalité de tout traitement que nous avons effectué avant votre retrait, et cela n’affectera pas le traitement de vos renseignements personnels reposant sur des motifs de traitement licites autres que le consentement.
* Vous pouvez avoir le droit de **refuser la vente de vos renseignements personnels**. Honeywell ne vend pas vos renseignements personnels à des tiers afin d’en tirer profit. Toutefois, nous partageons ou divulguons vos renseignements personnels à des tiers conformément à la présente Déclaration de confidentialité et à notre [Avis relatif aux témoins](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#french-canadian). Par exemple, nous collaborons avec des tiers pour distribuer nos produits, vous fournir une assistance technique, exploiter des outils et des fonctionnalités analytiques du site Web, et procéder à la commercialisation et à la vente de nos produits et services. Ces activités peuvent impliquer la divulgation de vos renseignements personnels à des tiers et peuvent être considérées comme une « vente » de données en vertu de certaines lois (mais pas toutes) sur la protection des données.
* Vous avez le droit de **porter plainte auprès** d’une autorité de protection des données responsable de l’application de la loi sur la protection des données dans votre juridiction concernant la collecte et l’utilisation de vos renseignements personnels si vous pensez que le traitement de vos renseignements personnels ne respecte pas la loi sur la protection des données. Par exemple, les personnes de l’EEE ont le droit de déposer une plainte auprès de l’autorité compétente en matière de protection des données, dont la liste est accessible à l’adresse suivante : [https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/board/members\_en](https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/board/members_en). Nous serions toutefois reconnaissants d’avoir l’occasion de répondre à vos préoccupations, alors n’hésitez pas à communiquer avec nous pour toute plainte que vous pourriez avoir. Nous n’exercerons aucune discrimination à l’encontre de personnes ayant exercé leurs droits à la confidentialité des données.

Nous faciliterons l’exercice des droits qui s’appliquent à vous conformément aux lois applicables. Cependant, même si vos renseignements personnels ne sont pas protégés par une loi sur la protection des données, ou autrement assujettis à cette législation, nous pouvons nous efforcer de répondre à toute demande ou requête que vous pourriez avoir en ce qui concerne nos activités de traitement de données. Si vous avez des questions concernant vos droits ou souhaitez exercer vos droits, vous pouvez communiquer avec nous à l’adresse [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com) ou envoyer des questions relatives à la confidentialité en utilisant notre formulaire Web interactif en cliquant sur lien suivant :

**Renseignements sur les enfants**

Nos Sites ne sont pas destinés aux enfants de moins de seize (16) ans et ne doivent pas être utilisés par ceux-ci, et nous ne recueillons pas, n’utilisons pas ou ne vendons pas volontairement des informations relatives à ces personnes. Si vous êtes mineur au sens des lois de votre pays, veuillez ne pas transmettre de renseignements personnels sur nos Sites.

**Liens vers d’autres sites Web**

Nos sites peuvent contenir des liens vers des sites Web, des produits et des services de tiers. Nous n’assumons aucune responsabilité relativement à ces sites Web, produits ou services ni à leurs politiques et à leur collecte ou à leur traitement de vos renseignements personnels. Les pratiques de ces tiers sont régies par leurs propres politiques de confidentialité. Nous vous invitons à vous informer sur les politiques de confidentialité de ces tiers.

**Communiquer avec nous**

Si vous avez des questions concernant cette Déclaration de confidentialité ou notre traitement de vos renseignements personnels, si vous souhaitez déposer une plainte ou contacter notre agent de protection des données, veuillez nous contacter en utilisant les coordonnées ci-dessous. Nous traiterons dans les plus brefs délais votre problème et chercherons à parvenir à une résolution satisfaisante.

Formulaire Web interactif:  

Courriel:  

Adresse postale:  
Honeywell Privacy  
4D5  
115 Tabor Road  
Morris Plains, NJ 07950

Numéro sans frais:  

**Modification de la Déclaration de confidentialité**

Nous pourrions de temps à autre mettre cette déclaration de confidentialité à jour. Lorsque nous le ferons, nous modifierons la date de la dernière mise à jour au haut de l’énoncé de confidentialité et prendrons toute autre mesure exigée par la loi.

**Dernière mise à jour le 11 juin 2021**

**Zuletzt aktualisiert am 11. Juni 2021**

**Einführung**

Honeywell International Inc. („**Honeywell**“, „**unser**“, „**uns**“ oder „**wir**“) ist der „Verantwortliche“ für die personenbezogenen Daten, die wir über Sie erheben, wenn Sie eine unserer Websites besuchen oder nutzen oder Produkte, Dienstleistungen und Anwendungen verwenden, die mit dieser Datenschutzerklärung verknüpft sind (gemeinsam unsere „**Sites**“). In dieser Datenschutzerklärung wird erläutert, wie wir Ihre personenbezogenen Daten erheben und die auf diese Weise erhobenen Daten weitergeben und nutzen und wie Sie Ihre Datenschutzrechte ausüben können.

Bei der Interaktion mit Ihnen können wir Ihnen auch zusätzliche Datenschutzhinweise zu bestimmten Verarbeitungsaktivitäten erteilen oder Ihnen zusätzliche Wahlmöglichkeiten bezüglich der Verarbeitung Ihrer personenbezogenen Daten durch Honeywell zu dem betreffenden Zeitpunkt bieten.

Klicken Sie auf einen der folgenden Links, um direkt zu dem für Sie interessanten Abschnitt zu gelangen:

[**Rechtliche Grundlage für die Verarbeitung von Informationen**](#ps-german-heading3)

**Unsere Datenerhebung**

* **Direkt von Ihnen erhobene Informationen**. Es kann sein, dass wir Sie nach personenbezogenen Daten fragen, um eine Dienstleistung zu erbringen oder eine von Ihnen angeforderte Transaktion auszuführen. Möglicherweise stellen Sie uns auch personenbezogene Daten bereit, wenn Sie Kontakt mit uns aufnehmen oder mit uns interagieren (beispielsweise in Form eines Kommentars, einer Anfrage oder einer Kundensupportanforderung, als Besucher unserer Website) oder wenn Sie ein Konto registrieren, um unsere Sites zu nutzen. Zu diesen personenbezogenen Daten können folgende Daten gehören:
    * **Identitätsdaten,** beispielsweise Ihr Name, Ihr Titel, der Name Ihres Unternehmens/Ihrer Organisation, Ihre E-Mail-Adresse, Ihre Telefonnummern und Ihre Postanschrift (einschließlich Straße, Ort, Postleitzahl und/oder Land);
    * **Registrierungsdaten**, die Sie bei der Registrierung eines Kontos bereitgestellt haben, um unsere Sites zu nutzen, einschließlich Benutzernamen und Kennwörtern;
    * **Einstellungsdaten,** einschließlich Informationen, die Sie in Verbindung mit einer Bewerbung oder Stellenanfrage übermittelt haben (wie unten beschrieben);
    * **Geschäftskontaktdaten,** beispielsweise Informationen zu anderen Mitarbeitern, Eigentümern, Direktoren, leitenden Angestellten oder Auftragnehmern einer Drittorganisation (z. B. Geschäft, Firma, Partnerschaft, Einzelunternehmen, gemeinnützige Organisation oder Behörde);
    * **Marketing- und Kommunikationsdaten,** einschließlich Ihrer Marketingpräferenzen und Ihrer Abonnements unserer Veröffentlichungen;
    * **Finanzdaten,** einschließlich Kreditkarteninformationen oder sonstiger Kontoinformationen, die Sie uns zur Abwicklung Ihres Kaufs von Produkten und Dienstleistungen bereitstellen, die möglicherweise auf unseren Sites verfügbar sind;
    * **Informationen im Zusammenhang mit Ausfuhrbestimmungen,** beispielsweise Angaben zu Ihrer Nationalität, zu Ihrer Staatsangehörigkeit und zu Ihrem Wohnsitzland, die es uns ermöglichen, Ihre Berechtigung zum Erhalt von Informationen zu bestimmten Technologien gemäß den Ausfuhrbestimmungen zu ermitteln;
    * **Transaktionsdaten,** beispielsweise Anfragen und Bestellungen für unsere Produkte und Dienstleistungen sowie Details zu den an Sie und von Ihnen geleisteten Zahlungen, einschließlich der Bestellhistorie und der für die Durchführung von Zahlungen erforderlichen Informationen;
    * **Informationen zu Registrierungen für Veranstaltungen,** einschließlich Informationen, die Sie beim Ausfüllen elektronischer Registrierungsformulare bereitstellen; und
    * **Ihr Feedback**, einschließlich Umfragen, Empfehlungen oder sonstigen Feedbacks, das Sie uns allgemein zu unseren Sites sowie zu unseren Produkten und Dienstleistungen bereitstellen.

Wenn Sie die angeforderten Informationen nicht zur Verfügung stellen, sind wir möglicherweise nicht in der Lage, Ihnen die angeforderte Leistung zu erbringen oder Ihre Transaktion abzuschließen.

* **Informationen, die wir automatisch über Sie erfassen**. Mithilfe von Cookies und ähnlichen Nachverfolgungstechnologien erfassen wir bestimmte Informationen zu Ihrem Besuch unserer Sites. Wir respektieren stets alle Ihnen möglicherweise gesetzlich zustehenden Rechte, uns daran zu hindern. Zu den auf diese Weise erhobenen Daten gehören:
    * **Nutzungsdaten,** einschließlich Informationen zu Ihrer Verwendung unserer Sites, zu den aufgerufenen Seiten, zur Anzahl der übertragenen Bytes, zu den angeklickten Links, zu den Materialien, auf die Sie zugreifen, zum Datum und zur Uhrzeit Ihres Zugriffs auf die Website, von der Sie zu einer unserer Sites gelangt sind, sowie zu anderen Aktionen innerhalb der Sites; und
    * **Technische Daten,** wie beispielsweise Ihre Internetprotokolladresse (IP-Adresse), Typ, Funktionalität und Sprache Ihres Browsers und Ihr Betriebssystem.

Informationen zu Cookies und anderen ähnlichen Nachverfolgungstechnologien, die wir auf unseren Sites verwenden, finden Sie in unserem [Hinweis zu Cookies](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#german).

* **Geo-Standortdaten**. Für bestimmte Sites können wir mit Ihrer Zustimmung den genauen Echtzeit-Standort (d. h. die Geolokalisierung) Ihres mobilen Geräts erfassen. Diese Informationen werden ausschließlich zu dem Zweck verwendet, Ihre Nutzung der Sites zu erleichtern. Dies gilt auch für unsere Dienstleister, die diese Informationen möglicherweise im Zusammenhang mit der Erbringung von Dienstleistungen in unserem Namen verarbeiten. Nachdem Sie uns Ihre Zustimmung erteilt haben, können Sie diese Zustimmung jederzeit über die Einstellungen für Standortservices Ihres Mobilgeräts ändern.
* **Informationen, die wir von Dritten erheben**. In Übereinstimmung mit geltendem Recht können wir personenbezogene Daten über Sie von Dritten, beispielsweise Social-Media-Websites und Anwendungen, erheben und mit unseren bereits vorhandenen Informationen kombinieren, um unsere Sites zu verbessern und an Ihre Präferenzen anzupassen, sowie zu anderen in dieser Datenschutzerklärung dargelegten Zwecken. Wir können Ihre Geschäftskontaktinformationen auch von Ihrem Arbeitgeber oder anderen Dritten erheben, um traditionelle Geschäftsaktivitäten und ähnliche Verwaltungsangelegenheiten zu ermöglichen oder anderweitig durchzuführen.

**Unsere Nutzung von Informationen**

Wir können die personenbezogenen Daten, die wir über unsere Sites oder bei Ihrer Kontaktaufnahme erheben, u. a. zu folgenden Zwecken verwenden:

* **Geschäftskontaktdaten**. Honeywell erhebt und verwendet Geschäftskontaktdaten für Kommunikationen oder Transaktionen. Hierzu gehören u. a. Due-Diligence-Prüfungen in Bezug auf ein Produkt oder eine Dienstleistung bzw. die Bereitstellung oder der Erhalt eines Produkts oder einer Dienstleistung. Honeywell kann diese Geschäftskontaktdaten beispielsweise zur Unterstützung und Verwaltung von Bestellungen, Verträgen, Garantien, Wartungsarbeiten und ähnlichen Geschäftsfunktionen, für Kreditanalysen und Inkassozwecke, zur Unterstützung unserer internen Compliance-Anforderungen und gesetzlicher Bestimmungen sowie (falls erforderlich) zur Verteidigung unserer Interessen und Ansprüche erheben und verwenden.
* **Dienstleistungen und Transaktionen** Wir können Ihre personenbezogenen Daten verwenden, um Dienstleistungen für Sie bereitzustellen oder von Ihnen angeforderte Transaktionen auszuführen. Hierzu zählen, ohne hierauf beschränkt zu sein, die Bereitstellung von Informationen zu Produkten oder Dienstleistungen des Unternehmens, die Sie erworben haben oder anderweitig verwenden, die Registrierung erworbener Produkte, die Verarbeitung von Produktbestellungen, die Bearbeitung von Garantieansprüchen, die Ersetzung von Produkthandbüchern, die Beantwortung von Kundendienstanfragen und die Unterstützung der Verwendung unserer Sites.
* **Verwaltung und Schutz unseres Geschäfts und unserer Sites**. Wir können Ihre personenbezogenen Daten verwenden, um unser Geschäft und unsere Sites zu verwalten und zu schützen, einschließlich Fehlerbehebung, Systemwartung, Support, Berichterstellung und Hosting von Daten.
* **Verbesserung unseres Geschäfts sowie unserer Sites, Produkte und Dienstleistungen**. Wir können Ihre personenbezogenen Daten zur Ausführung geschäftlicher Analysen oder zu anderen Zwecken verwenden, die uns helfen, die Qualität unseres Geschäfts, unserer Sites, unserer Produkte und Dienstleistungen (einschließlich neuer Produkte und Dienstleistungen) weiterzuentwickeln und zu verbessern, indem wir beispielsweise unsere Sites an Ihre spezifischen Präferenzen oder Interessen anpassen.
* **Marketing**. Soweit nach geltenden Gesetzen und Vorschriften zulässig, können wir Ihre personenbezogenen Daten verwenden, um Sie über Produkte oder Dienstleistungen zu informieren, die für Sie möglicherweise von Interesse sind, und um auf andere Weise mit Ihnen über Angebote, Veranstaltungen und Neuigkeiten, Umfragen, Sonderangebote und verwandte Themen zu kommunizieren. Sie können Marketingmitteilungen, die Sie per E-Mail erhalten, jederzeit kostenlos abbestellen, indem Sie auf den Link „Abbestellen“ klicken. Dieser Link ist in allen Marketing-E-Mails enthalten, die Sie von uns erhalten. Sie können sich auch über die in dieser Datenschutzerklärung enthaltenen Kontaktinformationen an uns wenden. Je nach Wohnsitzland können Sie sich auch von anderen Arten von Marketingmitteilungen abmelden. Bitte kontaktieren Sie uns unter Verwendung der in der Datenschutzerklärung aufgeführten Kontaktinformationen, um weitere Informationen zu erhalten. Einige Rechtsräume geben Einzelpersonen das Recht, bestimmte Informationen über unsere Offenlegung personenbezogener Daten gegenüber Dritten für Direktmarketingzwecke dieser Dritten anzufordern (dies gilt beispielsweise für die Einwohner von Kalifornien). Wenn Sie weitere Informationen über unsere Vorgehensweisen zur Offenlegung von Daten zu Marketingzwecken wünschen, kontaktieren Sie uns bitte unter Berücksichtigung der unten aufgeführten Anweisungen.
* **Interessenbezogene Werbung**. Wir erheben Daten über Ihre Online-Aktivitäten und ermitteln Ihre Interessen, damit wir Ihnen für Sie besonders relevante Werbung bereitstellen können. Sie können den Erhalt von interessenbezogener Werbung von Honeywell deaktivieren, wie in unserem [Hinweis zu Cookies](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#german) beschrieben.
* **Finanzielle Anreiz- und Treueprogramme**. Wir erheben und verwenden personenbezogene Daten, um unsere finanziellen Anreiz- und Treueprogramme zu verwalten und zu organisieren. Unter Verwendung der im Rahmen dieser Programme bereitgestellten personenbezogenen Daten bieten wir besondere Belohnungen, verfolgen den Status Ihres Programms und ermöglichen den Austausch von Programmpunkten gegen Produkte, Werbematerialien, Schulungsworkshops und mehr. Soweit gesetzlich zulässig, können wir personenbezogene Daten, die Sie im Rahmen eines finanziellen Anreizprogramms angeben, auch für andere in dieser Datenschutzerklärung dargelegte Zwecke verwenden. Bitte überprüfen Sie die Bedingungen für jedes finanzielle Anreizprogramm, für das Sie sich registrieren oder an dem Sie teilnehmen möchten, da diese Bedingungen stark auf das jeweilige Programm zugeschnitten sein können. Wenn Sie in die Teilnahme an diesen Programmen eingewilligt haben, können Sie diese Einwilligung jederzeit widerrufen, indem Sie uns über die Kontaktdaten am Ende dieser Datenschutzerklärung oder gemäß den Anweisungen in den Bedingungen des jeweiligen Programms kontaktieren.
* **Bewerbungen**. Im Zusammenhang mit einer Bewerbung oder Stellenanfrage können Sie uns Informationen über sich selbst zur Verfügung stellen, beispielsweise einen Lebenslauf, berufliche Referenzen, Informationen über Ihre Schulbildung und Ihren beruflichen Hintergrund sowie Informationen zu Ihrer Berufsausbildung und zu Zertifizierungen. Wir und die Mitglieder unserer Gruppe können diese Informationen zum Zwecke der Prüfung einer möglichen Beschäftigung, der Überprüfung Ihres Hintergrunds und Ihrer Eignung für eine Anstellung sowie zu anderen Zwecken verwenden, die in einer separaten Datenschutzerklärung oder einem anderen Hinweis in Verbindung mit Ihrer Bewerbung dargelegt sind. Wir können auf Dritte (beispielsweise Personalvermittler) oder Social-Media-Plattformen zurückgreifen, um Bewerbungen einzuholen, zu sammeln und einzubehalten. Weitere Informationen finden Sie in unserer [Datenschutzerklärung für Bewerber](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/applicant-privacy-notice#german).
* **Forschung und Analyse**. Wir können Ihre personenbezogenen Daten verwenden, um Studien und Analysen auszuführen, die uns helfen, Ihre Kaufpräferenzen zu analysieren, die Produkte und Dienstleistungen zu identifizieren, die Ihre Anforderungen am besten erfüllen, und die Effektivität der Werbung zu ermitteln, die wir Ihnen bereitstellen.
* **Durchsetzung**: Wir können die von uns erhobenen personenbezogenen Daten verwenden, um Betrugsfälle, Verletzungen von Rechten an geistigem Eigentum, Verstöße gegen unsere Geschäftsbedingungen, Verstöße gegen Gesetze oder andere missbräuchliche Verwendungen unserer Sites zu entdecken, zu verhindern und entsprechend zu reagieren.

Soweit gesetzlich zulässig, können wir die über unsere Sites erhobenen Informationen mit anderen Informationen kombinieren, die wir über Sie besitzen (beispielsweise Informationen zu Ihrer Verwendung unserer Produkte und Dienstleistungen), um Ihnen eine verbesserte und konsistente Kundenerfahrung zu bieten, wenn Sie mit uns interagieren, oder zu anderen, in dieser Datenschutzerklärung beschriebenen Zwecken.

**Rechtliche Grundlage für die Verarbeitung von Informationen**

Wenn gesetzlich vorgeschrieben, stellen wir sicher, dass es eine rechtliche Grundlage für die Verarbeitung Ihrer personenbezogenen Daten gibt. In den meisten Fällen ist unsere Rechtsgrundlage von den betreffenden personenbezogenen Daten und dem spezifischen Kontext abhängig, in dem wir die Daten erheben.

* **Vertrag**: Die Verarbeitung ist für die Dienstleistungen, die wir für Sie erbringen, oder für (auf Ihre Anfrage) zu ergreifende Maßnahmen vor und in Erwartung der Erbringung dieser Dienstleistungen erforderlich;
* **Gesetzliche Verpflichtungen**: Die Verarbeitung ist notwendig, um unsere gesetzlichen Verpflichtungen einzuhalten, einschließlich der Einhaltung geltender Gesetze und Vorschriften, der Erfüllung behördlicher und offizieller Auflagen, gerichtlicher Anordnungen oder Verfügungen;
* **Zustimmung**: Die Verarbeitung basiert auf Ihrer Zustimmung zur Verarbeitung Ihrer personenbezogenen Daten zu mindestens einem angegebenen Zweck (z. B. Marketing);
* **Legitime Interessen**: Die Verarbeitung ist notwendig, um unsere legitimen Interessen zu verfolgen, beispielsweise die Entwicklung und Verbesserung unserer Sites, Produkte und/oder Dienstleistungen zum Vorteil unserer Kunden; oder
* **Essenzielle Interessen**: Die Verarbeitung ist notwendig, um Ihre essenziellen Interessen zu schützen (z. B. aus Gesundheits- und Sicherheitsgründen, wenn Sie an einem Meeting an einem Honeywell-Standort teilnehmen).

Wenn Sie Fragen haben oder weitere Informationen zur Rechtsgrundlage benötigen, anhand derer wir Ihre personenbezogenen Daten erfassen und verwenden, senden Sie bitte eine E-Mail an [HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com)

**Anonymisierung von Informationen**

Gemäß geltendem Recht kann es sein, dass wir Ihre personenbezogenen Daten anonymisieren, sodass sie nicht mehr verwendet werden können, um Sie zu identifizieren. Anonymisierte Informationen gelten nicht als personenbezogene Daten und unterliegen daher nicht dieser Datenschutzerklärung. Wir können anonymisierte Informationen zu jedem Zweck erheben, verwenden, aggregieren und weitergeben.

**Dauer der Aufbewahrung von Informationen**

Der Zeitraum, über den wir Ihre personenbezogenen Daten speichern, ist vom Zweck der Verarbeitung abhängig. Personenbezogene Daten, die wir benötigen, um Ihnen Produkte und Dienstleistungen zur Verfügung zu stellen oder um Transaktionen zu ermöglichen, die Sie angefordert haben, speichern wir beispielsweise, solange Sie Kunde von Honeywell sind. Wenn Sie eine Bewerbung über unsere Sites einreichen, bewahren wir Informationen über Ihre Bewerbung wie in der Datenschutzerklärung, die Ihnen im Zusammenhang mit Ihrer Bewerbung zur Verfügung gestellt wurde, dargelegt oder wie anderweitig gesetzlich vorgeschrieben auf. In allen anderen Fällen speichern wir Ihre personenbezogenen Daten solange wie notwendig, um die in dieser Datenschutzerklärung beschriebenen Zwecke zu erfüllen. Anschließend werden sie entweder anonymisiert (soweit gesetzlich zulässig), gelöscht oder vernichtet.

**Offenlegung von Informationen**

Gemäß geltendem Gesetz geben wir Ihre personenbezogenen Daten möglicherweise an ausgewählte Dritte weiter, einschließlich der im Folgenden beschriebenen Dritten:

* **Unternehmen unserer Gruppe**. Möglicherweise geben wir Ihre personenbezogenen Daten an unsere Tochterunternehmen und Unternehmen der Gruppe weiter, wie angemessenerweise für die in dieser Datenschutzerklärung beschriebenen Zwecke notwendig.
* **Dienstanbieter**. Möglicherweise geben wir Ihre personenbezogenen Daten an Unternehmen weiter, die wir mit der Bereitstellung von Dienstleistungen in unserem Namen beauftragt haben, beispielsweise dem Hosten von Websites, der Durchführung von Umfragen, der Verarbeitung von Transaktionen, der Analyse unserer Sites und der Durchführung von Analysen zur Verbesserung der Qualität unseres Geschäfts, unserer Sites, Produkte und Dienstleistungen. Diese Dienstanbieter müssen die Vertraulichkeit Ihrer personenbezogenen Daten sicherstellen.
* **Vertriebspartner und andere vertrauenswürdige Geschäftspartner**. Möglicherweise geben wir Ihre personenbezogenen Daten an Dritte, die unsere Produkte vertreiben, und andere vertrauenswürdige Geschäftspartner weiter. Dies dient möglicherweise auch dem Zweck, dass diese Dritten Ihnen Marketingmitteilungen senden. Die Weitergabe personenbezogener Daten zu Marketingzwecken erfolgt gemäß geltenden Gesetzen und Vorschriften.
* **Offenlegung in Verbindung mit Transaktionen**. In Verbindung mit bestimmten Transaktionen kann es vorkommen, dass wir Ihre persönlichen Daten oder einen Teil davon Geldinstituten, Regierungsbehörden, Frachtunternehmen oder Postbehörden offenlegen, die an der Transaktionsabwicklung beteiligt sind.
* **Offenlegung von Informationen in Verbindung mit Akquisitionen oder Veräußerungen**. Es kann Situationen geben, in denen Honeywell aus strategischen oder anderen geschäftlichen Gründen beschließt, Unternehmen in einigen Ländern zu verkaufen, zu kaufen, zu veräußern, zu fusionieren oder anderweitig neu zu organisieren. Wir können Informationen, die wir über Sie aufbewahren, in dem Umfang offenlegen, der vernünftigerweise notwendig ist, um einen Zusammenschluss, eine Akquisition, eine Veräußerung oder einen Verkauf von Honeywell-Vermögen oder -Teilvermögen aushandeln und durchführen zu können.
* **Offenlegung von Informationen aus anderen Gründen**. Wir können personenbezogene Daten offenlegen, sofern dies im Rahmen von Gesetzesvorschriften bzw. im Vertrauen darauf erfolgt, dass diese Maßnahme aus einem der folgenden Gründe erforderlich ist: Einhaltung gesetzlicher Verpflichtungen oder Anordnungen, Schutz unserer Rechte und unseres Eigentums oder in dringenden Fällen Schutz der persönlichen Sicherheit einer Person.

**Internationale Datenübermittlungen**

Honeywell ist ein weltweit tätiges Unternehmen. Daher werden Ihre personenbezogenen Daten möglicherweise gemäß geltendem Recht an verschiedene Standorte weltweit – beispielsweise die USA, Mexiko und Indien – übermittelt und dort aufbewahrt, gespeichert oder verwendet. Das bedeutet, dass die von uns erhobenen personenbezogenen Daten möglicherweise in Ländern verarbeitet werden, deren Datenschutzgesetze sich von den Datenschutzgesetzen Ihres Landes unterscheiden. Honeywell wird jedoch stets angemessene Schritte unternehmen, um Ihre Privatsphäre zu schützen und einen Grad an Schutz für Ihre personenbezogene Daten zu bieten, der mit dem Grad an Schutz in Ihrem Wohnsitzland vergleichbar ist. Dies umfasst auch die Implementierung der Standardvertragsklauseln der Europäischen Kommission. Wenn Sie weitere Informationen über die geeigneten Sicherheitsvorkehrungen zum Schutz Ihrer personenbezogenen Daten wünschen, kontaktieren Sie uns bitte unter [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com).

**Sicherheit**

Wir sind bestrebt, die Sicherheit Ihrer personenbezogenen Daten zu schützen. Wir setzen technische und organisatorische Maßnahmen ein, um ein Sicherheitsniveau zu bieten, das dem mit der Verarbeitung Ihrer personenbezogenen Daten verbundenen Risiko angemessen ist. Wenn Sie weitere Informationen darüber wünschen, wie Honeywell Ihre personenbezogenen Daten schützt, kontaktieren Sie uns bitte unter [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com)

**Ihre Rechte**

Abhängig von den geltenden Gesetzen haben Sie möglicherweise bestimmte Rechte in Bezug auf Ihre personenbezogenen Daten.

* Sie haben möglicherweise das Recht, auf Ihre personenbezogenen Daten **zuzugreifen, diese zu korrigieren, zu aktualisieren** oder **ihre Löschung zu beantragen**.
* Sie können der Verarbeitung Ihrer personenbezogenen Daten **widersprechen**, uns auffordern, die Verarbeitung Ihrer personenbezogenen Daten **einzuschränken** oder die **Übertragbarkeit** Ihrer personenbezogenen Daten anfordern.
* Möglicherweise haben Sie ein Recht darauf, **dass keine Entscheidung über Sie getroffen wird, die ausschließlich auf einer automatisierten Verarbeitung basiert, einschließlich Profilierung,** wenn eine solche Entscheidung rechtliche Folgen für Sie hat oder Sie erheblich beeinträchtigt.
* Wenn wir Ihre personenbezogenen Daten mit Ihrer Zustimmung erfasst und verarbeitet haben, **können Sie Ihre Zustimmung jederzeit zurückziehen**. Die Zurückziehung Ihrer Zustimmung hat keinen Einfluss auf die Gesetzlichkeit einer Verarbeitung, die wir vor dieser Zurückziehung ausgeführt haben. Sie hat auch keinen Einfluss auf eine Verarbeitung Ihrer personenbezogenen Daten, die auf anderen gesetzlichen Grundlagen als Ihrer Zustimmung basiert.
* Sie haben möglicherweise das Recht, dem **Verkauf Ihrer personenbezogenen Daten zu widersprechen**. Honeywell verkauft Ihre personenbezogenen Daten nicht gewinnbringend an Dritte. Allerdings geben wir Ihre personenbezogenen Daten in Übereinstimmung mit dieser Datenschutzerklärung und unserem [Hinweis zu Cookies](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#german) an Dritte weiter oder legen sie anderweitig Dritten gegenüber offen. So beauftragen wir beispielsweise Drittanbieter, unsere Produkte zu vertreiben, Ihnen technische Unterstützung zu bieten, analytische Tools und Funktionen für die Website zu betreiben und unsere Produkte und Dienstleistungen zu vermarkten und zu verkaufen. Solche Aktivitäten können die Offenlegung Ihrer personenbezogenen Daten gegenüber Dritten beinhalten und gemäß bestimmten (jedoch nicht allen) Datenschutzgesetzen als „Verkauf“ von Daten angesehen werden.
* Sie haben das Recht, sich bei einer Datenschutzbehörde, die für die Überwachung der Einhaltung der Datenschutzgesetze in Ihrem Rechtsraum zuständig ist, über unsere Erhebung und Verwendung Ihrer personenbezogenen Daten zu **beschweren**, wenn Sie der Meinung sind, dass unsere Verarbeitung Ihrer personenbezogenen Daten nicht den Datenschutzgesetzen entspricht. Personen im EWR haben beispielsweise das Recht, bei der zuständigen Datenschutzbehörde eine Beschwerde einzureichen. Eine Liste dieser Datenschutzbehörden finden Sie unter folgendem Link: [https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/board/members\_en](https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/board/members_en). Wir würden es jedoch schätzen, wenn wir Gelegenheit erhielten, auf Ihre Bedenken zu reagieren. Bitte nehmen Sie daher im Fall einer Beschwerde Kontakt mit uns auf. Wir werden Einzelpersonen nicht diskriminieren, wenn sie ihre Datenschutzrechte ausüben.

Wir unterstützen Sie bei der Ausübung Ihrer Rechte entsprechend den geltenden Gesetzen. Doch auch wenn Ihre personenbezogenen Daten nicht durch ein Datenschutzgesetz geschützt sind und auch nicht anderweitig unter ein Datenschutzgesetz fallen, werden wir versuchen, Ihren Wünschen oder Anfragen in Bezug auf unsere Datenverarbeitung nachzukommen. Wenn Sie Fragen zu Ihren Rechten haben oder Ihre Rechte ausüben möchten, können Sie uns unter [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com) kontaktieren oder Datenschutzfragen über unser interaktives Webformular unter folgendem Link einreichen:

**Informationen von Kindern**

Unsere Sites richten sich nicht an Kinder unter sechzehn (16) Jahren und sollten von diesen nicht genutzt werden. Wir werden nicht wissentlich Informationen von solchen Personen erheben, verwenden oder verkaufen. Wenn Sie nach den Gesetzen Ihres Landes minderjährig sind, übermitteln Sie bitte keine personenbezogenen Daten über unsere Sites.

**Links zu anderen Websites**

Unsere Sites enthalten möglicherweise Links zu Websites, Produkten und Services Dritter. Wir sind für diese Websites, Produkte und Services, ihre Richtlinien und ihre Erfassungs- oder anderen Verarbeitungsaktivitäten in Bezug auf Ihre personenbezogenen Daten nicht haftbar oder verantwortlich. Die Verfahren dieser Dritten unterliegen ihren eigenen Datenschutzrichtlinien. Wir empfehlen Ihnen, sich über die Datenschutzrichtlinien dieser Dritten zu informieren.

**Kontakt**

Wenn Sie Fragen zu dieser Datenschutzerklärung oder zu unserer Verarbeitung Ihrer personenbezogenen Daten haben, eine Beschwerde einreichen möchten oder sich an unseren Datenschutzbeauftragten wenden möchten, nehmen Sie bitte unter Verwendung der folgenden Kontaktdaten Kontakt mit uns auf. Wir werden uns umgehend mit der von Ihnen vorgebrachten Angelegenheit auseinandersetzen und uns bemühen, eine zufriedenstellende Lösung zu finden.

Interaktives Webformular:  

E-Mail:  

Postanschrift:  
Honeywell Privacy  
4D5  
115 Tabor Road  
Morris Plains, NJ 07950

Gebührenfreie Rufnummer:  

**Änderungen dieser Datenschutzerklärung**

Wir können diese Datenschutzerklärung von Zeit zu Zeit aktualisieren. Wen wir dies tun, ändern wir das Datum für die letzte Aktualisierung oben in der Datenschutzerklärung und unternehmen alle weiteren möglicherweise gesetzlich vorgeschriebenen Schritte.

**Zuletzt aktualisiert am 11. Juni 2021**

**Utolsó módosítás: 2021. június 11.**

**Bevezetés**

A Honeywell International Inc. (a továbbiakban „**Honeywell**” vagy „**mi**”) adatkezelőként jár el azoknak az adatoknak az esetében, amelyeket akkor gyűjtünk, amikor Ön felkeresi vagy használja bármelyik webhelyünket, vagy amikor a jelen Adatvédelmi nyilatkozat hatálya alá eső termékeket, szolgáltatásokat és alkalmazásokat használ (együttesen: „**Webhelyeink**”). A jelen Adatvédelmi nyilatkozat ismerteti, hogyan gyűjtjük, osztjuk meg és használjuk fel a fent ismertetett módon gyűjtött személyes adatokat, és leírja, hogyan gyakorolhatja Ön az adatvédelemhez fűződő jogait.

Amikor kapcsolatba lépünk Önnel, további adatvédelmi tájékoztatókat is küldhetünk az egyes konkrét adatkezelési tevékenységekre vonatkozóan, vagy további választási lehetőségeket kínálhatunk a Honeywell által az Ön adatain az adott esetben végzett adatkezelési tevékenységek kapcsán.

Kattintson az alábbi hivatkozások egyikére a megtekinteni kívánt fejezet megnyitásához:

**Az általunk végzett adatgyűjtés**

* **Közvetlenül Öntől gyűjtött adatok**. A szolgáltatások biztosításához, valamint a kért tranzakciók végrehajtásához szükség esetén személyes adatokat kérünk Öntől. Emellett akkor is megadhat nekünk személyes adatokat, amikor Ön veszi fel velünk a kapcsolatot vagy valamilyen interakcióba lép velünk (például kommentet ír, érdeklődést vagy ügyfélszolgálati megkeresést küld be, esetleg felkeresi az oldalainkat), vagy felhasználói fiókot hoz létre Webhelyeink használatához. Ezeknek a személyes adatoknak a körébe az alábbiak tartoznak:
    * **Személyazonosító adatok,** például név, cím, vállalat/szervezet neve, e-mail-cím, telefon- és faxszám és postacím (utca, település, állam, irányítószám és/vagy ország);
    * **Regisztrációs adatok**, azaz a webhelyeink használatához szükséges fiók regisztrálása során megadott adatok, például felhasználónév és jelszó;
    * **Munkaerő-felvétellel kapcsolatos adatok,** ideértve a meghirdetett állásokkal vagy a beküldött érdeklődésekkel kapcsolatban megadott információkat (ezeket alább ismertetjük);
    * **Üzleti kapcsolattartási adatok,** például egy harmadik szervezet (például vállalkozás, cég, társaság, egyéni vállalkozás, nonprofit szervezet vagy kormányzati szerv) alkalmazottjaira, tulajdonosaira, igazgatóira, tisztségviselőire vagy alvállalkozóira vonatkozó információk,
    * **Marketing- és kommunikációs adatok,** ideértve a marketingpreferenciákat és a kiadványainkra vonatkozó előfizetéseket;
    * **Pénzügyi adatok,** például bankkártya- és egyéb számlaadatok a webhelyeinken elérhető termékek és szolgáltatások megvásárlásának elősegítése érdekében;
    * **Exportellenőrzési adatok,** például nemzetiség, állampolgárság és lakhely szerinti ország, amelyek segítségével meghatározhatjuk, hogy az exportellenőrzési rendeletek értelmében küldhetünk-e Önnek információkat bizonyos technológiákról;
    * **Tranzakciós adatok,** ideértve a termékeinkkel és a szolgáltatásainkkal kapcsolatos érdeklődések, megrendelések és az Önnek küldött, valamint az Öntől fogadott kifizetések részleteit, valamint a megrendelési előzményeket és a fizetési tranzakciók lebonyolításához szükséges információkat;
    * **Eseményregisztrációval kapcsolatos adatok,** többek között az e-regisztrációs űrlapok kitöltése során megadott adatok; és
    * **Az Ön visszajelzései,** beleértve a felméréseket, az ajánlásokat és más, a Webhelyeinkkel, valamint a termékeinkkel és szolgáltatásainkkal kapcsolatos általános visszajelzéseket.

Ha nem adja meg a kért adatokat, előfordulhat, hogy nem tudjuk Önnek biztosítani a kért szolgáltatást, vagy nem tudjuk teljesíteni tranzakcióit.

* **Az Önről automatikusan gyűjtött adatok**. Bizonyos információkat cookie-k és hasonló nyomkövető technológiák segítségével rögzítünk a Webhelyeinken tett látogatásáról. Ha Önnek joga van letiltani az ilyen adatgyűjtést, ezt a kérését minden esetben tiszteletben tartjuk. Az ilyen módon gyűjtött adatok közé a következők tartoznak:
    * **Használati adatok,** például azzal kapcsolatos adatok, hogy Ön hogyan használja a Webhelyeket, a megtekintett oldalak, az átvitt bájtok száma, a megnyitott hivatkozások, a megtekintett anyagok, a Webhely megnyitásának dátuma és időpontja, a webhely, amelyről a mi Webhelyünkre érkezett, valamint a Webhelyen végzett egyéb műveletek; és
    * **Technikai adatok,** például IP-cím, a böngésző típusa, valamint az operációs rendszer jellemzői és nyelve.

A Webhelyeinken használt cookie-król és más hasonló nyomkövető technológiákról a [Cookie-kkal kapcsolatos közleményben](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#hungarian) olvashat.

* **Földrajzi helyekkel kapcsolatos adatok**. Egyes Webhelyek esetén az Ön hozzájárulásával rögzíthetjük a mobileszköz pontos, valós idejű helyét (azaz az eszköz helyadatait). Ezeket az adatokat kizárólag arra használjuk fel, hogy lehetővé tegyük Önnek a Webhelyek használatát. Az általunk különböző szolgáltatások biztosításával megbízott partnerek is kizárólag ebből a célból dolgozzák fel ezeket az adatokat. A hozzájárulást a későbbiekben a mobileszköz helyadatokkal kapcsolatos beállításaiban módosíthatja.
* **Harmadik felektől gyűjtött adatok**. A hatályos törvények betartásával harmadik felektől, például közösségimédia-webhelyekről és -alkalmazásokból is gyűjthetünk adatokat Önről, amlyeket az Önről más forrásokból gyűjtött információkkal kombinálhatunk. Ezekat az adatokat Webhelyeink fejlesztésére és az Ön igényei szerinti személyre szabására, valamint a jelen Adatvédelmi nyilatkozatban meghatározott egyéb célokra használhatjuk fel. Emellett az Ön munkáltatójától vagy más harmadik felektől is gyűjthetünk üzleti kapcsolattartási adatokat Önről, amelyeket a szokásos üzleti tevékenységek és adminisztratív feladatok elvégzésére használunk fel.

**Az adatok felhasználása**

A Webhelyeinken keresztül, valamint a velünk való kapcsolatfelvétel során gyűjtött személyes adatokat többek között az alábbi célokra használhatjuk fel:

* **Üzleti kapcsolattartási adatok**. A Honeywell a kapcsolat felvétele vagy tranzakciók lebonyolítása céljából gyűjti össze és használja fel az üzleti kapcsolattartási adatokat. Ilyen tevékenység lehet például a termék vagy szolgáltatások biztosításával vagy fogadásával kapcsolatos átvilágítás. A Honeywell például összegyűjtheti és felhasználhatja az üzleti kapcsolattartási adatokat a megrendelések, a szerződések, a jótállások, a karbantartási tevékenységek és más, hasonló üzleti feladatkörök elvégzése és kezelése érdekében, hitelelemzési és behajtási célokra, saját belső megfelelőségi és jogi követelményeink teljesítése érdekében, valamint (szükség esetén) érdekeink és követeléseink védelmére.
* **Szolgáltatások és tranzakciók**. Személyes adatait felhasználhatjuk az Ön által kért szolgáltatások biztosítására és tranzakciók lebonyolítására, ideértve többek között a következőket: a megvásárolt vagy használt vállalati termékekkel és szolgáltatásokkal kapcsolatos tájékoztatás, megvásárolt termékek regisztrálása, megrendelések feldolgozása, jótállási igények kezelése, kézikönyvek cseréje, ügyfélszolgálati kérések megválaszolása és a Webhelyeink használatának elősegítése.
* **Üzleti tevékenységünk és Webhelyeink kezelése és védelme** Személyes adatait felhasználhatjuk üzleti tevékenységünk és Webhelyeink kezelésére és védelmére, ideértve többek között a hibaelhárítást, a rendszerkarbantartást, a támogatást, a jelentések készítését és az adatok hosztolását.
* **Üzleti tevékenységünk, Webhelyeink, termékeink és szolgáltatásaink fejlesztése**. Személyes adatait felhasználhatjuk üzleti elemzések készítéséhez, valamint üzleti tevékenységünk, Webhelyeink, termékeink és szolgáltatásaink minőségének fejlesztését szolgáló további célokra (az új termékeket és szolgáltatásokat is beleértve), például arra, hogy Webhelyeinket az Ön preferenciáinak és érdeklődési körének megfelelően személyre szabjuk.
* **Marketing**. A hatályos törvényeknek és rendeleteknek megfelelően személyes adatait felhasználhatjuk arra, hogy tájékoztassuk azokról a termékekről és szolgáltatásokról, amelyek érdekelhetik Önt, és más módokon is megkeressük Önt különböző ajánlatok, események, hírek, felmérések, különleges ajánlatok és más, hasonló témák kapcsán. Az e-mailben kapott marketingkommunikációs anyagokról bármikor díjmentesen leiratkozhat. Ehhez kattintson a tőlünk kapott e-marketing anyagokban található „Leiratkozás” hivatkozásra, vagy vegye fel velünk a kapcsolatot a jelen Adatvédelmi nyilatkozatban felsorolt elérhetőségek egyikén. A lakóhelye szerinti országtól függően előfordulhat, hogy más típusú marketingkommunikációs anyagokról is leiratkozhat; további információért vegye fel velünk a kapcsolatot a jelen Adatvédelmi nyilatkozatban felsorolt elérhetőségek egyikén. Egyes joghatóságok (például Kalifornia) lehetővé teszik, hogy polgáraik tájékoztatást kérjenek tőlünk arról, hogy milyen személyes adataikat adjuk át harmadik feleknek közvetlen üzletszerzési célokra. Ha szeretne többet tudni az adatok marketingcélú továbbítására vonatkozó gyakorlatunkról, vegye fel velünk a kapcsolatot az alábbiakban olvasható utasításokat követve.
* **Érdeklődésen alapuló hirdetések**. Adatokat gyűjtünk az interneten Ön által végzett tevékenységekről, és ezek alapján azonosítjuk az érdeklődési köreit, hogy így relevánsabb hirdetéseket tudjunk megjeleníteni Önnek. A Honeywell érdeklődésen alapuló hirdetéseiről a [Cookie-kkal kapcsolatos közleményben](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#hungarian) leírtak szerint iratkozhat le.
* **Pénzügyi ösztönzők és hűségprogramok**. Pénzügyi ösztönzőink és hűségprogramjaink működtetéséhez és kezeléséhez is személyes adatokat gyűjtünk és használunk fel. Az Ön által e programok kapcsán megadott személyes adatokat arra használjuk fel, hogy egyedi jutalmakat ajánljunk fel, nyomon kövessük a program státuszát, és lehetővé tegyük a programban szerzett pontok termékekre, promóciós anyagokra, képzésekre és másokra való beváltását. A jogszabályok által megengedett mértékben a pénzügyi ösztönzőprogramok keretében megadott személyes adatokat a jelen Adatvédelmi nyilatkozatban meghatározott egyéb célokra is felhasználhatjuk. Ha szeretne regisztrálni egy ilyen pénzügyi ösztönzőprogramra, vagy részt venni valamelyik programban, olvassa el a program feltételeit, mivel bizonyos esetekben ezek a feltételek kizárólag az adott programra vonatkozó információkat tartalmaznak. Ha vállalja, hogy részt vesz egy ilyen programban, bármikor visszavonhatja ezt a hozzájárulását. Ehhez lépjen kapcsolatba velünk a jelen Adatvédelmi nyilatkozat végén megadott elérhetőségeken keresztül, vagy kövesse az adott program feltételeiben meghatározott utasításokat.
* **Álláspályázatok**. Álláspályázata vagy hasonló megkeresése kapcsán is személyes adatokat adhat át nekünk, ilyen például az önéletrajza, a szakmai referenciái, a végzettségével és a szakmai hátterével, valamint a szakmai képzettségével és bizonyítványaival kapcsolatos információk. Mi és vállalatcsoportunk tagjai felhasználhatjuk ezeket az adatokat az állás betöltéséhez, a háttérellenőrzések elvégzéséhez és a munkavállalásra való alkalmasság ellenőrzéséhez, valamint a jelentkezése kapcsán rendelkezésre bocsátott külön adatvédelmi nyilatkozatban vagy más tájékoztatóban foglalt további célokra. Bizonyos esetben harmadik feleket (például állásközvetítő céget) vagy közösségimédia-platformokat is igénybe vehetünk az álláspályázatok bekéréséhez, összegyűjtéséhez és megőrzéséhez. További információkért olvassa el az [állásra jelentkezőkre vonatkozó adatvédelmi nyilatkozatunka](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/applicant-privacy-notice#hungarian)t.
* **Kutatás és elemzések**. Személyes adatait felhasználhatjuk különböző kutatások és elemzések elvégzésére, amelyek célja a vásárlási preferenciák vizsgálata, az Ön igényeinek leginkább megfelelő termékek és szolgáltatások megkeresése, valamint az Önnek megjelenített hirdetések hatékonyságának felmérése.
* **Végrehajtás**: Az Önről gyűjtött személyes adatokat felhasználhatjuk a csalások, a szerzői jogsértések, a törvénysértések, a felhasználási feltételeink megsértésének, valamint a Webhelyeink egyéb helytelen használatának észlelésére, megelőzésére és kezelésére.

Ha a jogszabályok megengedik, a Webhelyeinken gyűjtött információkat az Önről tárolt egyéb adatokkal (például a termékek és szolgáltatások használatával kapcsolatos adatokkal) kombinálva felhasználhatjuk a jelen Adatvédelmi nyilatkozatban meghatározott célokra és arra, hogy jobb és egységesebb ügyfélélményt biztosítsunk Önnek a velünk folytatott interakciók során.

**Az adatkezelés jogalapja**

Ha a jogszabályok előírják, gondoskodunk arról, hogy személyes adatai feldolgozásának megfelelő jogalapja legyen. A legtöbb esetben a hivatkozott jogalap az érintett személyes adatoktól és ezek begyűjtésének konkrét körülményeitől függ.

* **Szerződés**: az adatkezelés az általunk Önnek nyújtott szolgáltatások biztosításához szükséges, vagy ahhoz, hogy (az Ön kérésére) megtegyük az ilyen szolgáltatások teljesítését megelőzően szükséges lépéseket;
* **Jogi kötelezettség**: az adatok kezelésére jogi kötelezettségeinknek, többek között a hatályos törvényeknek, jogszabályoknak, kormányzati és ezzel egyenértékű kérelmeknek, bírósági rendeleteknek vagy idézéseknek való megfelelés érdekében van szükség;
* **Hozzájárulás**: az adatkezelés alapja, hogy Ön hozzájárult személyes adatai egy vagy több célra (például marketingcélokra) való kezeléséhez;
* **Jogos érdek**: az adatkezelésre jogos érdekből, például Webhelyeink, termékeink és/vagy szolgáltatásaink ügyfeleink érdekében történő fejlesztéséhez és javításához van szükség; vagy
* **Létfontosságú érdek**: az adatkezelés az Ön létfontosságú érdekeinek védelméhez szükséges (például egészségügyi és biztonsági okokból, ha Ön a Honeywell egyik telephelyén vesz részt egy megbeszélésen).

Ha bármilyen kérdése van, vagy további információra van szüksége a személyes adatok gyűjtésének és felhasználásának jogalapjáról, írjon nekünk a következő e-mail-címre: [HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com)

**Az adatok névtelenítése**

A hatályos jogszabályoknak megfelelően bizonyos esetekben anonimizáljuk személyes adatait, amelyek ezt követően nem lesznek alkalmasak az Ön azonosítására. A névtelenített adatok nem számítanak személyes adatoknak, azért ezekre a jelen Adatvédelmi nyilatkozat nem vonatkozik. Névtelen adatokat bármilyen célból gyűjthetünk, felhasználhatunk, összesíthetünk és megoszthatunk.

**Az adatok megőrzésének időtartama**

A személyes adatok megőrzésének időtartama a feldolgozás céljától függően eltérő lehet. Például az Ön által kért termékek és szolgáltatások biztosításához vagy a tranzakciók teljesítéséhez szükséges személyes adatokat mindaddig megőrizzük, amíg Ön a Honeywell ügyfele. Továbbá ha Ön a Webhelyeinken keresztül állásra jelentkezik nálunk, a jelentkezés kapcsán átadott adatvédelmi tájékoztatóban vagy a jogszabályokban előírtaknak megfelelően őrizzük meg a jelentkezéséhez kapcsolódó adatokat. A személyes adatokat minden más esetben a jelen Adatvédelmi nyilatkozatban meghatározott célok teljesítéséhez szükséges ideig őrizzük meg, amelyet követően az adatokat névtelenítjük (ha a hatályos jogszabályok ezt lehetővé teszik), töröljük vagy megsemmisítjük.

**Az adatok továbbítása**

A hatályos törvényeknek megfelelően személyes adatait bizonyos harmadik felekkel is megoszthatjuk. Ezeket a harmadik feleket az alábbiakban ismertetjük:

* **Vállalatcsoportunkhoz tartozó társaságok**. Személyes adatait a jelen Adatvédelmi nyilatkozatban meghatározott célokhoz szükséges mértékben megoszthatjuk társvállalatainkkal és a csoporthoz tartozó vállalatokkal.
* **Szolgáltatók**. Személyes adatait megoszthatjuk a megbízásunkból szerződéses alapon különböző szolgáltatásokat nyújtó vállalatokkal, amelyek például webhelyeinket üzemeltetik, felméréseket végeznek, tranzakciókat dolgoznak fel, elemzéseket végeznek Webhelyeinken, valamint üzleti tevékenységünk, Webhelyeink, termékeink és szolgáltatásaink minőségének javítását célzó elemzéseket végeznek. E szolgáltatók számára előírjuk, hogy minden esetben bizalmasan kezeljék az Ön személyes adatait.
* **Forgalmazók és más megbízható üzleti partnerek**. Személyes adatait megoszthatjuk a termékeinket forgalmazó harmadik felekkel és más megbízható üzleti partnerekkel, és többek között engedélyezhetjük az ilyen harmadik feleknek, hogy marketinganyagokat küldjenek Önnek. A személyes adatok marketingcélokból történő megosztása során mindig a hatályos törvényeknek és jogszabályoknak megfelelően járunk el.
* **Tranzakciókkal kapcsolatos adattovábbítás**. Bizonyos tranzakciók során pénzügyi intézményekkel, kormányzati szervekkel, valamint a tranzakciók végrehajtásában érintett szállítmányozási vállalatokkal és postai szolgáltatókkal is megoszthatjuk az Ön egyes személyes adatait vagy valamennyi személyes adatát.
* **Felvásárlással vagy vállalatrész eladásával kapcsolatos adattovábbítás**. Előfordulhat, hogy a Honeywell stratégiai vagy üzleti célokból úgy dönt, hogy bizonyos országokban elad, megvásárol, leválaszt, egybeolvaszt vagy más módon átszervez egyes alvállalatokat. Ebben az esetben a Honeywell-vállalat eszközeinek egy részének vagy egészének egybeeolvasztásával, felvásárlásával, leválasztásával vagy eladásával járó tevékenységekkel kapcsolatos tárgyalások lebonyolításához, valamint az ilyen tevékenységek elvégzéséhez szükséges mértékben megoszthatjuk az Önről tárolt adatokat.
* **Adattovábbítás más okból**. Személyes adatait abban az esetben is továbbíthatjuk, ha ezt a törvények előírják vagy lehetővé teszik, valamint ha jóhiszeműen úgy véljük, hogy az adatok továbbítására törvényi kötelezettségeknek vagy jogi eljárásban született döntésnek való megfelelés, jogaink vagy vagyonunk védelme, valamint sürgős esetekben egy személy biztonságának védelme érdekében van szükség.

**Nemzetközi adattovábbítás**

A Honeywell globális vállalat, ezért az Ön személyes adatait a hatályos jogszabályoknak megfelelően világszerte különböző helyszínekre, például az Amerikai Egyesült Államokba, Mexikóba és Indiába továbbíthatjuk, így az Ön adatait ezekben az országokban is tárolhatjuk és felhasználhatjuk. Tehát az Öntől gyűjtött személyes adatokat olyan országokban is kezelhetjük, amelyek adatvédelmi jogszabályai eltérhetnek az Ön országában hatályos törvényektől. A Honeywell minden észszerűen elvárható lépést megtesz az Ön magánéletének és személyes adatainak megóvása érdekében, valamint hogy az Ön lakóhelye szerinti országhoz hasonló szintű védelmet biztosítson adatainak. Ennek részeként az Európai Bizottság által jóváhagyott általános szerződési feltételeket is alkalmazunk. A személyes adatok védelmét szolgáló intézkedésekkel kapcsolatos további tájékoztatásért írjon nekünk a [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com) e-mail-címre.

**Biztonság**

Elkötelezettek vagyunk személyes adatai védelme mellett. Technikai és szervezési intézkedéseket vezettünk be annak érdekében, hogy az adatkezelésben rejlő kockázatokhoz mérten megfelelő szintű biztonságot érjünk el. Ha szeretne többet megtudni arról, hogyan védi a Honeywell az Ön személyes adatait, írjon nekünk a [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com) e-mail-címre.

**Az Ön jogai**

A hatályos jogszabályoktól függően Önt bizonyos jogok illethetik meg személyes adataival kapcsolatban.

* Például jogosult lehet arra, hogy **hozzáférjen személyes adataihoz, valamint helyesbítse és frissítse őket**, vagy kérelmezze a **törlésüket**.
* Emellett **tiltakozhat** személyes adatainak feldolgozása ellen, kérheti, hogy **korlátozzuk** személyes adatainak feldolgozását, valamint az adatok **hordozhatóságával** kapcsolatos kérelmet is küldhet nekünk.
* Emellett joga lehet ahhoz, **hogy ne hozzanak Önről kizárólag automatizált adatkezelésen, például profilalkotáson alapuló döntést,** ha ez a döntés joghatással bír Önre, vagy jelentős mértékben érinti Önt.
* Emellett ha személyes adatait az Ön hozzájárulása alapján gyűjtöttük össze és kezeljük, akkor **Ön bármikor visszavonhatja a hozzájárulását**. A hozzájárulás visszavonása nem érinti a korábban végzett adatkezelés jogszerűségét, valamint nem befolyásolja azokat az adatkezelési tevékenységeket, amelyeket nem az Ön hozzájárulása alapján, hanem más jogalappal végzünk.
* Jogában áll úgy dönteni, hogy **nem engedélyezi személyes adatainak értékesítését**. A Honeywell nem értékesíti az Ön személyes adatait harmadik feleknek nyereség céljából Az Ön személyes adatait azonban bizonyos, a jelen Adatvédelmi nyilatkozatban és a [Cookie-kkal kapcsolatos közleményben](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#hungarian) megadott esetekben megoszthatjuk harmadik felekkel, valamint harmadik feleknek továbbíthatjuk. Például harmadik felekkel együttműködve forgalmazzuk a termékeinket, műszaki segítséget nyújtunk Önnek, webhelyelemző eszközöket és funkciókat használunk, valamint különböző módszerekkel népszerűsítjük és értékesítjük termékeinket és szolgáltatásainkat. E tevékenységek során előfordulhat, hogy harmadik feleknek kell továbbítanunk az Ön személyes adatait, és egyes adatvédelmi törvények értelmében ez az adatok „értékesítésének” minősülhet.
* Önnek joga van **panaszt tenni** a joghatóságában hatályos adatvédelmi törvények betartásának felügyeletéért felelős adatvédelmi hatóságnál személyes adatainak gyűjtésével és felhasználásával kapcsolatban, ha úgy véli, hogy az adatkezelés során nem tartottuk be az adatvédelmi jogszabályokat. Az EGT területén élő magánszemélyek például panaszt tehetnek az illetékes adatvédelmi hatóságnál. E hatóságok listája a következő címen érhető el: [https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/board/members\_en](https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/board/members_en). Nagyra értékelnénk azonban, ha lehetőséget adna nekünk, hogy mi foglalkozzunk az aggályaival. Ha panasza merül fel, vegye fel velünk bátran a kapcsolatot! Nem alkalmazunk hátrányos megkülönböztetést az adatvédelmi jogaikat gyakorló magánszemélyekkel szemben.

Minden esetben lehetővé tesszük, hogy Ön élhessen a hatályos törvények értelmében fennálló jogaival. Bizonyos esetekben még akkor is megpróbálunk eleget tenni az Ön adatkezelési tevékenységeinkkel kapcsolatos kéréséinek, ha az Ön személyes adatait nem védik az adatvédelmi törvények, vagy nem tartoznak az adatvédelmi törvények hatálya alá. Ha kérdése merül fel a jogaival kapcsolatban, vagy szeretné gyakorolni a jogait, írjon nekünk a [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com) e-mail-címre, vagy küldje el adatvédelemmel kapcsolatos kérdéseit az alábbi hivatkozáson elérhető interaktív webes űrlapon keresztül:

**Gyermekek adatai**

Webhelyeink nem tizenhat (16) éven aluli gyermekek számára készültek, és tudatosan nem gyűjtünk és nem is használunk fel adatokat ilyen személyekről, és nem értékesítjük ilyen személyek adatait. Ha Ön az országa törvényei szerint kiskorúnak minősül, ne adjon meg személyes adatokat a Webhelyeinken keresztül.

**Más webhelyekre mutató hivatkozások**

Webhelyeink harmadik felek webhelyeire, termékeire és szolgáltatásaira mutató hivatkozásokat tartalmazhatnak. Az ilyen webhelyekért, termékekért és szolgáltatásokért, valamint az általuk végzett adatgyűjtésért és -kezelésért nem vállalunk felelősséget. Az ilyen harmadik felek gyakorlatait saját adatvédelmi szabályzataik határozzák meg. Javasoljuk, hogy tájékozódjon e harmadik felek adatvédelmi gyakorlatairól.

**Kapcsolatfelvétel**

Ha kérdése merül fel a jelen Adatvédelmi nyilatkozattal vagy személyes adatai kezelésével kapcsolatban, szeretne panaszt benyújtani, vagy kapcsolatba lépni adatvédelmi tisztségviselővel, keressen meg minket az alábbi elérhetőségek valamelyikén keresztül. A lehető leghamarabb válaszolunk kérdéseire, és arra törekszünk, hogy minden problémára kielégítő megoldást találjunk.

Interaktív webes űrlap:  

E-mail:  

Levelezési cím:  
Honeywell Privacy  
4D5  
115 Tabor Road  
Morris Plains, NJ 07950

Ingyenes hívható telefonszám:  

**A jelen Adatvédelmi nyilatkozat módosításai**

Időről időre módosíthatjuk a jelen Adatvédelmi nyilatkozatot. Az Adatvédelmi nyilatkozat módosítása esetén megváltoztatjuk az Adatvédelmi nyilatkozat tetején olvasható „utolsó módosítás” dátumát, és megtesszük a törvények által előírt további lépéseket.

**Utolsó módosítás: 2021. június 11.**

**Ultimo aggiornamento in data: 11 giugno 2021**

**Introduzione**

Honeywell International Inc. (“**Honeywell**”, “**nostro**”, “**noi**”, o “**ci**”), è il "titolare del trattamento" dei dati personali che acquisiamo sugli utenti quando visitano o utilizzano i nostri siti web o i prodotti, i servizi e le applicazioni collegati alla presente Informativa sulla privacy (collettivamente, i nostri “**siti**”). La presente Informativa sulla privacy illustra le modalità con cui acquisiamo, condividiamo e utilizziamo i dati personali ottenuti in questo modo e come è possibile esercitare i propri diritti di tutela della privacy.

Quando interagiamo con gli utenti, possiamo anche fornire loro ulteriori informazioni sulla privacy in merito a specifiche attività di trattamento o offrir loro ulteriori alternative sul modo in cui Honeywell tratta i loro dati personali in un determinato momento.

Fare clic su uno dei collegamenti di seguito per andare direttamente alla sezione di interesse:

**Acquisizione dei dati**

* **Informazioni ottenute direttamente dall'utente**. È possibile che siano richiesti dati personali per fornire il servizio o effettuare la transazione che l'utente ha specificato. L'utente può inoltre fornire alcuni dati personali quando contatta o si rivolge a noi (per esempio, quando invia un commento, un quesito o una richiesta di assistenza cliente, visitatori del sito) o creare un account per utilizzare i nostri siti. Tali dati personali possono includere:
    * **Dati identificativi,** come il nome, il titolo, la ragione sociale dell'azienda/organizzazione, l'indirizzo e-mail, i numeri di telefono e l'indirizzo postale (inclusi via, città, provincia, codice postale e/o paese);
    * **Dati di registrazione,** forniti dall'utente al momento della creazione di un account per poter accedere ai nostri siti, inclusi nomi utente e password;
    * **Dati di selezione,** incluse le informazioni fornite in relazione a una candidatura o richiesta di lavoro (come di seguito illustrato);
    * **Dati di contatti aziendali,** come informazioni relative ad altri dipendenti, proprietari, dirigenti, funzionari o fornitori di organizzazioni terze (per esempio, aziende, società, partnership, imprese individuali, no-profit o agenzie governative).
    * **Dati relativi al marketing e alle comunicazioni,** compresi le preferenze di marketing e gli abbonamenti alle nostre pubblicazioni;
    * **Informazioni finanziarie,** incluse le informazioni relative alle carte di credito o ad altri conti finanziari al fine di agevolare l'acquisto da parte dell'utente di prodotti e servizi Honeywell disponibili sui nostri siti;
    * **Informazioni sul controllo delle esportazioni,** come la nazionalità, la cittadinanza e il paese di residenza, che ci consentono di determinare se l'utente è idoneo a ricevere informazioni relative a determinate tecnologie in base alle normative sul controllo delle esportazioni;
    * **Dati sulle transazioni,** compresi richieste e ordini per i nostri prodotti e servizi e i dettagli dei pagamenti da e verso l'utente, compresa la cronologia degli ordini di acquisto e le informazioni necessarie per agevolare le transazioni di pagamento;
    * **Informazioni relative alla registrazione a eventi,** inclusi i dati forniti dall'utente durante la compilazione di moduli di registrazione online; e
    * **Feedback dell'utente,** inclusi sondaggi, raccomandazioni o altri feedback ricevuti dagli utenti in merito ai nostri siti e ai nostri prodotti e servizi in generale.

Nel caso in cui l'utente non fornisca le informazioni previste, potremmo non essere in grado di fornire il servizio richiesto o di completare la transazione.

* **Informazioni che acquisiamo automaticamente sui nostri utenti**. Raccogliamo alcune informazioni sulle visite ai nostri siti utilizzando cookie e tecnologie di tracciamento assimilabili. Rispetteremo in ogni caso qualsiasi diritto legale che l'utente possa vantare per impedirci di farlo. I dati in tal modo acquisiti includono:
    * **Dati di utilizzo,** incluse le informazioni relative all'utilizzo dei nostri siti da parte dall'utente, tra cui le pagine visualizzate, il numero di byte trasferiti, i collegamenti aperti, il materiale consultato, la data e l'ora di accesso al sito, il sito dal quale l'utente è stato rimandato a uno dei nostri siti e ulteriori azioni intraprese nei siti Honeywell; e
    * **Dati tecnici,** come l'indirizzo IP (Internet Protocol) dell'utente, il tipo di browser utilizzato, le funzionalità e la lingua, nonché il sistema operativo in uso.

Per informazioni sui cookie e altre tecnologie di tracciamento assimilabili che utilizziamo sui nostri siti, si rimanda alla nostra [Informativa sui cookie](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#italian).

* **Informazioni di geo-localizzazione**. Per alcuni siti, previo consenso dell'utente, potremmo acquisire la posizione precisa e in tempo reale (ovvero, la geolocalizzazione) del suo dispositivo mobile. Queste informazioni saranno utilizzate solo per agevolare l'uso dei siti da parte degli utenti, compresi i nostri fornitori di servizi che possono elaborare tali dati in relazione alla fornitura di servizi per nostro conto. Se si decide di autorizzare questa operazione, l'utente può adeguare il proprio consenso gestendo le preferenze dei Servizi di localizzazione attraverso le impostazioni del dispositivo mobile.
* **Informazioni acquisite da terze parti**. In conformità con la legge applicabile, possiamo acquisire dati personali sugli utenti tramite terze parti, come siti web e applicazioni di social media, e associarli con le informazioni già in nostro possesso, al fine di migliorare e personalizzare i nostri siti in base alle preferenze degli utenti e per altri scopi indicati nella presente Informativa sulla privacy. Possiamo inoltre acquisire informazioni di contatto aziendali dal datore di lavoro o da altre terze parti per favorire o altrimenti intraprendere attività commerciali tradizionali e questioni amministrative di tipo analogo.

**Utilizzo delle informazioni**

Le informazioni personali acquisite da Honeywell attraverso i nostri siti o quando l'utente ci contatta possono essere utilizzate per i seguenti scopi:

* **Dati di contatto aziendali**. Honeywell acquisisce e utilizza i dati di contatto aziendali per effettuare comunicazioni o transazioni, anche per condurre attività di due diligence, o fornire o ricevere, un prodotto o un servizio. Per esempio, Honeywell può acquisire e utilizzare questi dati di contatto aziendali per agevolare e gestire ordini, contratti, garanzie, interventi di manutenzione e funzioni aziendali analoghe, per finalità di analisi e riscossione dei crediti, per contribuire alla nostra conformità interna e soddisfare i requisiti legali e (se necessario) per difendere i nostri interessi e diritti.
* **Servizi e transazioni**. Ci riserviamo il diritto di utilizzare le informazioni personali per offrire servizi o effettuare transazioni richieste dall'utente, come per esempio la fornitura di informazioni su prodotti e servizi Honeywell acquistati o altrimenti utilizzati dall'utente, la registrazione dei prodotti acquistati, il monitoraggio degli ordini di prodotti, la gestione delle richieste di garanzia, la sostituzione di manuali dei prodotti, le risposte alle richieste effettuate al servizio clienti, l'assistenza nell'utilizzo dei nostri siti web e così via.
* **Amministrazione e tutela della nostra attività e dei nostri siti**. Ci riserviamo il diritto di utilizzare i dati personali dell'utente allo scopo di gestire e proteggere l'azienda e i nostri siti, incluse la risoluzione dei problemi, la manutenzione del sistema, l'assistenza, la segnalazione e la conservazione di dati.
* **Miglioramento di attività, siti, prodotti e servizi**. Ci riserviamo il diritto di utilizzare i dati personali dell'utente per eseguire business analysis o per altri scopi che ci consentano di sviluppare e migliorare la qualità dell'attività aziendale, dei nostri siti e dei prodotti e servizi offerti (inclusi i nuovi prodotti e servizi), ad esempio, personalizzando i siti in base alle preferenze e agli interessi specifici dell'utente.
* **Marketing**. In accordo con le leggi e le normative applicabili, ci riserviamo il diritto di utilizzare i dati personali dell'utente per informarlo di prodotti o servizi a cui l'utente potrebbe essere interessato e per comunicazioni di altro genere in relazione a promozioni, eventi e novità, sondaggi, offerte speciali e temi correlati. L'utente ha il diritto di revocare il consenso alla ricezione di comunicazioni di marketing via e-mail in qualsiasi momento, gratuitamente, mediante il link "annulla iscrizione" presente in tutte le e-mail contenenti materiale di marketing ricevute da Honeywell o contattandoci attraverso le informazioni di contatto contenute nella presente Informativa sulla privacy. In base al paese di residenza, l'utente può scegliere di annullare la ricezione anche di altri tipi di comunicazioni di marketing; per ulteriori informazioni, è possibile contattarci utilizzando le informazioni riportate nella presente Informativa sulla privacy. Alcune giurisdizioni forniscono ai singoli (per esempio, i residenti in California) il diritto di richiedere specifiche informazioni riguardanti la nostra divulgazione di dati personali a terzi per scopi di marketing diretto degli stessi. Per ricevere maggiori informazioni sulle nostre pratiche di divulgazione dei dati per scopi di marketing, è possibile contattarci secondo le istruzioni elencate di seguito.
* **Pubblicità basata sugli interessi dell'utente**. Acquisiamo dati sulle attività online degli utenti e identifichiamo i loro interessi in modo da poter offrire la pubblicità per loro più rilevante. È possibile disattivare le comunicazioni pubblicitarie basate sugli interessi degli utenti inviate da Honeywell, come descritto nella nostra [Informativa sui cookie](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#italian).
* **Programmi di incentivazione finanziaria e di fidelizzazione**. Acquisiamo e utilizziamo i dati personali per mantenere e amministrare i nostri programmi di incentivazione finanziaria e di fidelizzazione. Utilizziamo i dati personali comunicati dall'utente in questi programmi per offrire premi unici, monitorare lo stato del programma e agevolare lo scambio di punti del programma per prodotti, materiali promozionali, laboratori di formazione e altri articoli. Nei limiti consentiti dalla legge, possiamo anche utilizzare qualsiasi dato personale da voi fornito nel contesto di un programma di incentivi finanziari per qualsiasi altro scopo indicato nella presente Informativa sulla privacy. Si raccomanda di esaminare i termini e le condizioni di ciascun programma di incentivi finanziari a cui si desidera registrarsi o partecipare, in quanto tali termini e condizioni possono essere strettamente adattati al programma specifico. Qualora l'utente dia il proprio consenso a partecipare a tali programmi, può revocare tale consenso in qualsiasi momento contattandoci attraverso i dettagli di contatto riportati in calce alla presente Informativa sulla privacy o in conformità con le istruzioni stabilite nei termini e nelle condizioni del programma specifico.
* **Domande d'impiego.** In relazione a una domanda o richiesta di impiego, l'utente può fornirci informazioni su di sé, come per esempio il curriculum vitae, le referenze professionali, le informazioni relative ai titoli di studio e al background lavorativo, le informazioni relative alla formazione professionale e alle certificazioni. Noi e i membri del nostro gruppo possiamo utilizzare tali informazioni allo scopo di prendere in considerazione la possibilità di assunzione, verificarne la veridicità e l'idoneità per l'impiego specifico, e come altrimenti indicato in qualsiasi dichiarazione separata sulla privacy o altro avviso reso disponibile in relazione alla candidatura dell'utente. È possibile utilizzare una terza parte (ad esempio, Recruiter di processo) o la piattaforma dei social media per sollecitare, raccogliere e conservare le domande d'impiego. Per maggiori informazioni, raccomandiamo di prendere visioni della nostra [Informativa sulla privacy dei candidati](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/applicant-privacy-notice#italian).
* **Ricerca e analisi**. Ci riserviamo il diritto di utilizzare le informazioni personali dell'utente per condurre ricerche e analisi sulle sue preferenze di acquisto, individuare i prodotti e i servizi che meglio rispondono alle sue esigenze e misurare l'efficacia dell'offerta pubblicitaria.
* **Applicazione**: Ci riserviamo il diritto di utilizzare i dati personali che raccogliamo per rilevare, prevenire e rispondere a frodi, violazioni della proprietà intellettuale, violazioni dei nostri termini e condizioni, violazioni di leggi o altri usi impropri dei nostri siti.

Ove previsto dalla legge, ci riserviamo il diritto di integrare le informazioni raccolte attraverso i nostri siti con le informazioni relative all'utente già in nostro possesso (come informazioni relative all'utilizzo dei nostri prodotti e servizi) per poter offrire all'utente un'esperienza di livello più elevato durante l'interazione con Honeywell e per altre finalità disposte nella presente Informativa sulla privacy.

**Fondamento giuridico alla base del trattamento dei dati**

Ove previsto dalla legge, garantiremo all'utente una base giuridica per il trattamento dei dati personali. Nella maggior parte dei casi la nostra base giuridica dipenderà dai dati personali trattati e dal contesto specifico di acquisizione.

* **Contratto**: il trattamento è necessario per l'esecuzione dei servizi che forniamo all'utente, o per prendere provvedimenti (su richiesta dell'utente) prima e in previsione dell'esecuzione di tali servizi;
* **Obbligo legale**: il trattamento dei dati è necessario per ottemperare ai nostri obblighi di legge, inclusa la conformità alle leggi e alle normative applicabili, alle richieste di enti governativi e parastatali nonché a ordinanze e citazioni giudiziarie;
* **Consenso**: il trattamento dei dati si basa sul consenso prestato dall'utente al trattamento dei dati personali per uno o più scopi specifici (es. marketing);
* **Interessi legittimi**: il trattamento dei dati è necessario per soddisfare i nostri legittimi interessi, come sviluppare e migliorare i siti Honeywell nonché prodotti e/o servizi offerti a beneficio dei nostri clienti ; o
* **Interessi vitali**: il trattamento è necessario per proteggere gli interessi vitali dell'utente (per esempio, motivi di salute e sicurezza se si partecipa a una riunione in una sede Honeywell).

In caso di domande o necessità di ulteriori informazioni sulla base giuridica su cui raccogliamo e utilizziamo i dati personali, inviate un'e-mail all'indirizzo [HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com)

**Trasformazione in forma anonima dei dati**

Conformemente alla legislazione applicabile, siamo autorizzati a rendere anonimi i dati personali dell'utente affinché non possano più essere utilizzati per identificarlo. I dati resi anonimi non si classificano più come dati personali, pertanto non sono soggetti alla presente Informativa sulla privacy. Ci riserviamo il diritto di acquisire, utilizzare, aggregare e condividere dati in forma anonima per qualsiasi scopo.

**Durata della conservazione dei dati**

Il periodo durante il quale i dati personali dell'utente vengono conservati varia in base allo scopo per cui vengono trattati. Per esempio, conserviamo i dati personali necessari per fornire prodotti e servizi, o per agevolare le transazioni richieste, per tutto il tempo in cui l'utente è cliente di Honeywell o se presenta una domanda di assunzione tramite i nostri siti, conserviamo i dettagli della sua domanda come indicato nell'informativa sulla privacy messa a disposizione dell'utente in relazione alla sua candidatura o come altrimenti previsto a norma di legge. In tutti gli altri casi, Honeywell conserva i dati personali dell'utente per il tempo necessario ad adempiere alle finalità descritte nella presente Informativa sulla privacy. Al termine di tale periodo, i dati saranno resi anonimi (ove consentito dalla legislazione applicabile), eliminati o distrutti.

**Divulgazione dei dati**

Conformemente alla legislazione applicabile, siamo autorizzati a condividere i dati personali dell'utente con terzi selezionati, incluso quanto riportato di seguito:

* **Società del gruppo**. Siamo, inoltre, autorizzati a condividere i dati personali dell'utente con le nostre affiliate e con le società del gruppo Honeywell per le finalità descritte nella presente Informativa sulla privacy.
* **Fornitori di servizi**. Siamo autorizzati a condividere i dati personali dell'utente con le aziende che forniscono servizi per nostro conto, quali hosting di siti web, conduzione di sondaggi, elaborazione delle transazioni, analisi dei nostri siti e conduzione di analisi per migliorare la qualità dell'attività aziendale, dei nostri siti e dei prodotti e servizi offerti. Honeywell richiede a tali fornitori di servizi di tutelare la confidenzialità dei dati personali dell'utente.
* **Distributori e altri partner commerciali di fiducia**. Siamo autorizzati a condividere i dati personali dell'utente con i terzi incaricati della distribuzione dei nostri prodotti e con altri partner commerciali di fiducia per finalità che includono l'invio, da parte di tali terzi, di comunicazioni di marketing all'utente. Tale condivisione dei dati personali dell'utente per scopi di marketing verrà realizzata in conformità alle leggi e alle normative applicabili.
* **Divulgazione correlata alle transazioni**. In relazione a determinate transazioni, possiamo divulgare in parte o interamente i dati personali dell'utente a istituzioni finanziarie, enti governativi e società di spedizione o servizi postali coinvolti nell'adempimento della transazione.
* **Divulgazione in relazione ad acquisizioni o cessioni**. Possono verificarsi circostanze in cui, per ragioni strategiche o per altre ragioni commerciali, Honeywell decide di vendere, acquistare, cedere, fondere o riorganizzare diversamente le attività in alcuni paesi. Honeywell può divulgare i dati dell'utente che essa conserva nella misura necessaria e opportuna a continuare la trattativa o a completare una fusione, un'acquisizione, una cessione o una vendita di tutte le attività di Honeywell o di una loro parte.
* **Divulgazione per altre ragioni**. Ci riserviamo il diritto di divulgare dati personali se richiesto o consentito dalla legge o in caso di buona fede che tale procedura sia necessaria per rispondere a obblighi o procedure di legge, per proteggere e difendere i nostri diritti o proprietà o, in casi urgenti, per difendere la sicurezza personale di un individuo.

**Trasferimenti internazionali**

Honeywell è un'organizzazione globale e i dati personali degli utenti possono essere trasferiti, conservati, memorizzati o utilizzati in varie località del mondo, come gli Stati Uniti, il Messico e l'India, in conformità alle leggi vigenti. Ciò significa che, quando raccogliamo i vostri dati personali, questi possono essere trattati in paesi che possono avere leggi sulla protezione dei dati diverse da quelle del vostro paese. Tuttavia, Honeywell adotterà sempre le misure necessarie per tutelare la tua privacy e per fornire un livello di protezione dei dati personali paragonabile a quello del tuo paese di residenza, il che include l'attuazione delle clausole contrattuali tipo della Commissione europea. Per maggiori informazioni sulle misure di sicurezza appropriate in atto a protezione dei dati personali, contattateci all'indirizzo [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com).

**Sicurezza**

Abbiamo come priorità la tutela della sicurezza dei dati personali. Utilizziamo misure tecniche e organizzative per fornire un livello di sicurezza adeguato al rischio di trattamento dei dati personali. Per maggiori informazioni sulle modalità adottate da Honeywell a tutela dei dati personali, contattateci all'indirizzo [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com)

**Diritti dell'utente**

A seconda della legge applicabile, l'utente può esercitare alcuni diritti in relazione ai propri dati personali.

* Può avere il diritto di **accedere, correggere, aggiornare** o **richiedere la cancellazione** dei propri dati personali.
* Può **opporsi** al trattamento dei propri dati personali, chiederci di **limitare** il trattamento dei propri dati personali o richiederne la **portabilità**.
* Ha il diritto **di non accettare che sia presa una decisione su di lui basata esclusivamente sull'elaborazione automatizzata, compresa la profilazione,** se tale decisione produce effetti giuridici sulla sua persona o la colpisce in modo significativo.
* Allo stesso modo, se abbiamo raccolto ed elaborato i dati personali con il suo consenso, l'utente può **ritirare il proprio consenso in qualsiasi momento**. La revoca del consenso non influirà sulla liceità di qualsiasi trattamento eseguito prima della revoca, né influenzerà il trattamento dei dati personali condotto facendo affidamento su criteri di liceità del trattamento diversi dal consenso.
* L'utente ha il diritto di **opporsi alla vendita dei propri dati personal**i. Honeywell si impegna a non vendere a terzi i dati personali degli utenti a scopo di lucro. Tuttavia, condividiamo o divulghiamo in altro modo i dati personali degli utenti a terze parti in conformità con la presente Informativa sulla privacy e la nostra [Informativa sui cookie](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#italian). Per esempio, ci avvaliamo di società terze per distribuire i nostri prodotti, fornire assistenza tecnica, gestire strumenti e funzioni di analisi del sito web e svolgere attività di marketing e vendita dei nostri prodotti e servizi. Tali attività possono comportare la divulgazione dei dati personali a terzi e possono essere considerate una "vendita" di dati secondo alcune (ma non tutte) le leggi in materia di tutela dei dati.
* L'utente ha il diritto di **presentare reclamo** all'autorità preposta alla tutela dei dati personali, responsabile del controllo del rispetto della legge sulla sicurezza dei dati nella propria giurisdizione, in merito alla nostra acquisizione e all'utilizzo dei propri dati personali, qualora ritenga che il trattamento dei dati personali non sia conforme alla legge sulla loro tutela. Per esempio, gli individui residenti nel SEE hanno il diritto di presentare reclamo all'autorità competente per la protezione dei dati; l'elenco è consultabile all'indirizzo: [https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/board/members\_en](https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/board/members_en). Tuttavia saremmo lieti di avere la possibilità di risolvere direttamente eventuali dubbi, pertanto invitiamo gli utenti a contattarci in relazione a qualsiasi motivo di insoddisfazione. Non opereremo alcuna discriminazione nei confronti degli individui che esercitano i loro diritti in materia di privacy.

Contribuiremo ad agevolare l'esercizio dei diritti dell'utente in conformità con la legge vigente. Tuttavia, anche se i vostri dati personali non sono protetti da una legge sulla tutela dei dati, o altrimenti soggetti a tale legge, possiamo cercare di soddisfare qualsiasi richiesta o istanza che possiate avanzare in merito alle nostre attività di trattamento dei dati. Per domande sui propri diritti o per esercitare i propri diritti, è possibile contattarci all'indirizzo [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com) o inviare domande sulla privacy tramite il nostro modulo web interattivo disponibile al seguente link:

**Informazioni sui minori**

I nostri siti non sono destinati a, e non dovrebbero essere utilizzati da, soggetti di età inferiore ai sedici (16) anni, né noi acquisiamo, utilizziamo o vendiamo intenzionalmente informazioni su tali soggetti. Se sei un minore come inteso dalle leggi del tuo paese, ti preghiamo di non inviare nessun dato personale attraverso i nostri siti.

**Collegamenti ad altri siti web**

I nostri siti potrebbero contenere collegamenti a siti web, prodotti e servizi di terze parti. Honeywell declina ogni responsabilità relativa a tali siti web, prodotti e servizi e alla relative politiche o modalità di acquisizione e trattamento dei dati personali dell'utente. Le prassi di tali terze parti sono disciplinate dalle proprie politiche sulla privacy. Invitiamo l'utente a informarsi riguardo alle politiche in materia di privacy adottate da tali terzi.

**Contattateci**

Se avete domande sulla presente Informativa sulla privacy o sulla gestione dei vostri dati personali, se desiderate presentare un reclamo o se volete contattare il nostro Responsabile della protezione dei dati, contattateci utilizzando le informazioni di contatto elencate di seguito. Esamineremo sollecitamente il vostro problema e cercheremo di raggiungere una risoluzione soddisfacente.

Modulo web interattivo:  

E-mail:  

Indirizzo postale:  
Privacy Honeywell  
4D5  
115 Tabor Road  
Morris Plains, NJ 07950

Numero verde gratuito:  

**Modifiche alla presente Informativa sulla Privacy**

Ci riserviamo il diritto di aggiornare periodicamente la presente Informativa sulla privacy. In tal caso, modificheremo la data dell'"ultimo aggiornamento" all'inizio dell'Informativa sulla privacy e adotteremo eventuali ulteriori misure secondo quanto disposto dalla legge.

**Ultimo aggiornamento in data: 11 giugno 2021**

**最終更新日：2024年4月29日**

**はじめに**

Honeywell International Inc.（「**ハネウェル**」、「**我々**」、「**弊社**」、あるいは「**当社**」）は、お客様が本個人情報保護方針にリンクされている当社のWebサイト（以下、総称して当社「**サイト**」）にアクセスしたとき、または製品、サービスおよびアプリケーションを使用したときに当社がお客様について収集する個人情報の「データ管理者」です。本個人情報保護方針では、当社がこのようにして収集したお客様の個人情報を収集、共有、使用する方法、およびお客様がプライバシーの権利を行使する方法について説明しています。

当社がお客様とやり取りする場合、当社は、特定の処理活動に関する追加のプライバシー通知をお客様に提供するか、またはハネウェルが特定の時点でお客様の個人情報を処理する方法について追加の選択肢を提供する場合があります。  

 関心のあるセクションに移動するには、以下の該当するリンクをクリックしてください。

**当社による情報の収集**

* **お客様から直接収集された情報**。 当社はサービスを提供するため、またはお客様から要求された取引を実行するために、個人情報の提供をお願いする場合があります。また、お客様は、(コメント、お問い合わせ、カスタマー サポート要求、サイト訪問などを通じて) 当社に連絡するか当社とやり取りをする際に当社に個人情報を提供したり、当社サイトを利用するためにアカウントに登録したりすることもできます。この個人情報には以下が含まれます。
    * **身元データ。** お客様の名前、役職、会社/組織名、電子メール アドレス、電話番号、ファックス番号、住所（番地、市、州、郵便番号、国を含む）など。      
    * **登録データ、**お客様が当社サイトを利用するためにアカウントに登録する際に提供する情報（ユーザー名とパスワードを含む）など。  
        
    * **採用データ** 。 求職またはお問い合わせに関連して提出された情報（以下に記載）を含みます。 
    * **業務連絡先データ**。第三者組織（企業、会社、パートナーシップ、個人事業主、非営利団体、政府機関など）の他の従業員、所有者、取締役、役員または請負業者に関連する情報など。
    * **生体認証データ**。健康、安全、セキュリティスクリーニングおよびその他の管理機能のための顔認識スキャンなど。
    * **マーケティングおよびコミュニケーションデータ。** お客様のマーケティングの好みや当社の発行物へのサブスクリプションを含みます。  
        
    * **財務情報。** 当社サイトで利用可能な当社の製品およびサービスの購入処理を円滑に進めることができるようにするための、クレジットカードまたはその他の金融口座の情報を含みます。  
        
    * **輸出管理情報。** 国籍、市民権、居住国など。これにより、当社はお客様が輸出管理規制の下で特定の技術に関する情報を受け取る資格を有しているかどうかを判断できます。  
        
    * **取引データ。** 当社の製品およびサービスに関するお問い合わせと注文、ならびにお客様との間の支払いの詳細（発注履歴、支払い取引の円滑化に必要な情報など）を含みます。   
        
    * **イベント登録情報。** お客様が電子登録フォームに記入するときに提供する情報を含みます。  
        
    * **お客様からのフィードバック。** 当社サイトならびに当社の製品およびサービス全般に関する、お客様からのアンケート回答、推奨事項またはその他のフィードバックを含みます。

お客様が要求された情報を提供されない場合、当社は要求されたサービスを提供したり、取引を完了したりできないことがあります。

* **当社がお客様に関して自動的に収集する情報**。 当社は、クッキーおよび類似の追跡技術を使用して、当社サイトへのお客様の訪問に関する特定の情報を収集します。当社は、お客様が有し得る、当社のこの行為を阻止する法的権利を常に尊重します。この方法で収集されるデータには以下が含まれます。
    * **利用状況データ。** お客様が当社サイトをどのように利用しているか、表示したページ、転送バイト数、クリックしたリンク、アクセスした資料、当社サイトへのアクセス日時、いずれかの当社サイトへのリンク元のWebサイト、および当社サイト内で行われたその他のアクションに関する情報を含みます。  
        
    * **技術データ。** インターネット プロトコル (IP) アドレス、ブラウザーの種類と機能、言語、オペレーティング システムなど。

当社サイトで当社が使用するクッキーおよびその他の類似の追跡技術については、当社の[クッキーに関する通知](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice)を参照してください。

* **位置情報**。特定の当社サイトでは、お客様から同意を得たうえで、ハンディデバイスの正確なリアルタイムの位置 (つまり、地理的位置) を収集する場合があります。この情報は、お客様による本サイトの利用を促進する目的でのみ使用し、当社に代わってサービスを提供することに関連してこの情報を処理する可能性のある当社のサービスプロバイダーによる場合もあります。同意された場合は、ハンディデバイスの設定を通じて位置情報サービスの設定を管理することで、この同意を調整できます。
* **第三者から収集された情報**。当社は、適用法に従い、ソーシャルメディアの Webサイトとアプリケーションなどの第三者からお客様に関する個人情報を収集し、この情報を当社が既に保有している情報と組合せ、お客様の好みに合わせて当社サイトを改善およびカスタマイズし、または本個人情報保護方針に記載されているその他の目的を果たします。また、お客様の雇用主またはその他の第三者から業務連絡先情報を収集する場合があり、これにより従来のビジネス活動や同様の管理事項を円滑に進める、またはその他の方法で実施します。

**当社による情報の使用**

当社は、当社サイトを通じて収集された個人情報、またはお客様が以下のような目的で当社に連絡された際に収集された個人情報を使用する場合があります。

* **業務連絡先データ**。ハネウェルは、製品もしくはサービスに関するデューデリジェンスの実施、または製品やサービスの提供もしくは受領を含め、連絡または取引を行うために、業務連絡先データを収集および使用します。たとえば、ハネウェルは、注文、契約、保証、保守および同様の職務を円滑に進めたり管理したりするため、信用分析および収集を実施するため、当社内のコンプライアンスおよび法的要件を支援するため、ならびに（必要に応じて）当社の利益と主張を防御するために、この業務連絡先データを収集および使用することがあります。
* **サービスおよび取引。** 当社は、お客様にサービスを提供したり、お客様から要求された取引（お客様が購入または利用した当社の製品またはサービスに関する情報の提供、購入した製品の登録、製品の注文処理、保証請求への対応、製品マニュアルの交換、カスタマー サービス要求への回答、当社サイトの利用の円滑化を含むがこれらに限定されない）を実行したりするために、お客様の個人情報を使用することがあります。
* **当社のビジネスと当社サイトの管理および保護。** 当社は、当社のビジネスと当社サイトを管理および保護（トラブルシューティング、システム メンテナンス、サポート、レポート、データのホスティングを含む）するために、お客様の個人情報を使用することがあります。
* **当社サイト、当社のビジネス、製品およびサービスの改善。** 当社は、ビジネス分析を実行するため、または当社サイト、当社のビジネス、製品およびサービス（新しい製品およびサービスを含む）を開発し、その品質を改善するのに役立つその他の目的（当社サイトをお客様の特定の好みまたは関心に合わせてカスタマイズする、など）のために、お客様の個人情報を使用することがあります。
* **マーケティング。** 当社は、適用される法律および規制に従って、お客様が関心を持ちそうな製品またはサービスをお客様に通知するため、ならびにその他の方法でサービス、イベントやニュース、アンケート、特別オファーおよび関連トピックについてお客様にお知らせするため、お客様の個人情報を使用することがあります。お客様は、当社から受け取った電子メールの宣伝用資料の「登録解除」リンクを使用するか、本個人情報保護方針に記載されている連絡先情報を使用して当社に連絡することにより、いつでも無料で電子メールで送信されるマーケティング コミュニケーションをオプトアウトできます。居住国によっては、他の種類のマーケティング コミュニケーションをオプトアウトすることもできます。詳細については、個人情報保護方針に記載されている連絡先情報を使用して当社までお問い合わせください。一部の法域では、個人 (カリフォルニア州居住者など) に、第三者のダイレクト マーケティング目的で当社が個人情報を第三者に開示することに関して特定の情報を要求する権利が付与されています。マーケティング目的でのデータ開示に関する慣行の詳細については、下記の指示に従って当社までお問い合わせください。
* **興味関心連動型広告。**当社は、お客様に最も関連性の高い広告を提供できるよう、お客様のオンライン活動に関するデータを収集してお客様の関心を特定します。お客様は、当社の[クッキーに関する通知](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice)で定めるとおり、ハネウェルからの興味関心連動型広告の配信をオプトアウトすることができます。
* **報奨金およびロイヤルティ プログラム**。当社は、報奨金およびロイヤルティ プログラムを維持および管理するために、個人情報を収集して使用します。これらのプログラムにおいて、お客様から提供された個人情報を使用して、独自の報酬を提供したり、プログラムのステータスを追跡したり、製品、販売促進資料、トレーニングワークショップなどに対するプログラムポイントの交換を円滑に進めたりします。法律により認められる範囲で、当社は、本個人情報保護方針に記載されている他の目的のために、報奨金プログラムに関連してお客様から提供される個人情報を使用する場合もあります。登録または参加を希望する各報奨金プログラムの利用規約は、該当するプログラムに合わせて細かく調整されている場合があるため、確認するようお願いいたします。お客様は、これらのプログラムへの参加に同意された場合、本個人情報保護方針の最後にある連絡先の詳細を使用して、または該当するプログラムの利用規約に記載されている指示に従って、いつでもその同意を撤回することができます。
* **求職。** お客様は、求職やそのお問い合わせに関連して、履歴書、推薦状、学歴や職歴に関する情報、職業訓練や認定に関する情報など、自身に関する情報を当社に提供する場合があります。当社とそのグループ会社は、雇用の検討、経歴調査および雇用資格を目的として、別途の個人情報保護方針または求職に関連して提供されるその他の通知に記載されているように、この情報を使用することがあります。当社は、求職を勧誘、募集、および雇用申込書を保持するために、第三者 (職業紹介事業者など) またはソーシャルメディアプラットフォームを使用する場合があります。詳細については、[応募者のプライバシーに関する通知](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/applicant-privacy-notice)をお読みください。
* **研究および分析。** 当社は、お客様の購入傾向の分析、お客様のニーズに最適な製品やサービスの特定、およびお客様に提供する広告の効果測定に役立てるため、お客様の個人情報を使用して調査および分析を行うことがあります。
* **執行：** 当社は、詐欺、知的財産権の侵害、当社の利用規約の違反、法律の違反、または当社サイトのその他の誤用を検出、防止し、それらに対応するために、収集した個人情報を使用することがあります。

法律で認められている場合、当社は、お客様とのやり取りの際に、または本個人情報保護方針に記載されているその他の目的で、顧客体験を改善して一貫したものを提供するために、当社サイトを通じて収集した情報と、お客様に関して保持している他の情報 (当社の製品やサービスの利用に関する情報など) を組み合わせることがあります。

**当社が情報を処理する法的根拠**

法律で求められている場合、当社は、お客様の個人情報を処理する法的根拠があることを保証します。ほとんどの場合、当社の法的根拠は、当該個人情報と、それを収集する特定の状況により異なります。

* **契約：**処理は、当社がお客様に提供するサービスの実施のために、またはそうしたサービスの実施前に、その実施を見込んで (お客様の要求に応じて) 措置を講じるために必要です。
* **法的義務：**処理は、適用される法律、規制、政府および準政府の要求、裁判所命令または召喚状の遵守を含め、当社の法的義務を遵守するために必要です。
* **同意：**処理は、1 つ以上の特定の目的 (マーケティングなど) での個人情報の処理に対するお客様の同意に基づいています。
* **正当な利益：**処理は、当社の顧客の利益のために当社サイト、製品やサービスを開発および改善するなど、当社の正当な利益を満たすために必要です。
* **重大な利益：**処理は、お客様の重大な利益を保護するために必要です（例えば、ハネウェルの事業所での会議に出席する場合、安全衛生上の理由）。

当社がお客様の個人情報を収集および使用する法的根拠についてご質問がある場合、または詳細情報が必要な場合は、[HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com)までEメールでお問い合わせください。

**情報の匿名化**

適用法に従って、当社はお客様の個人情報を匿名化し、お客様の識別に使用できないようにする場合があります。匿名化された情報は個人情報とはみなされないため、本個人情報保護方針の対象ではありません。当社は、目的を問わず匿名化された情報を収集、使用、集約および共有することがあります。

**当社が情報を保持する期間**

当社がお客様の個人情報を保存する期間は、処理の目的によって異なります。例えば、当社は、お客様がハネウェルの顧客である限り、またはお客様が当社サイトを通して求人応募の申請を提出している限り、製品やサービスの提供または要請された取引を円滑に進めるために必要な個人情報を保存します。当社はお客様の申請に関連して、お客様が利用できるプライバシー通知に記載されているとおり、または法律で義務付けられているとおり、お客様による申請の詳細を保持します。その他すべての場合、当社は、このプライバシーに関する声明に記載されている目的を達成するために必要な場合に限り、お客様の個人情報を保存し、その目的の達成後、匿名化 (適用される法律で認められている場合)、削除または破棄します。

**情報の開示。**

当社は、下記を含め、適用される法律に従って、一部の第三者とお客様の個人情報を共有する場合があります。

* **当社のグループ会社**。本個人情報保護方針に記載されている目的のために合理的に必要な場合、当社はお客様の個人情報を当社の関連会社およびグループ会社と共有することがあります。
* **サービスプロバイダー。** 当社は、Webサイトのホスティング、アンケートの実施、取引の処理、当社サイトの分析、当社サイト、当社のビジネス、製品およびサービスの品質改善を目的とした分析の実施など、当社に代わってサービスを提供する契約を結んでいる企業とお客様の個人情報を共有する場合があります。当社は、これらのサービスプロバイダーに、お客様の個人情報の機密を保護するよう求めます。
* **販売代理店およびその他の信頼できるビジネスパートナー**。当社は、当社の製品を販売する第三者およびその他の信頼できるビジネスパートナーと、マーケティングコミュニケーションをお客様に送信することを当該第三者に許可するなどの目的で、お客様の個人情報を共有する場合があります。このようなマーケティング目的での個人情報の共有は、適用される法律および規制に従って行われます。
* **取引に関連する開示**。当社は、特定の取引に関連して、お客様の個人情報の一部またはすべてを、取引の履行に関係する金融機関、政府機関、および輸送会社または郵便サービス業者に開示する場合があります。
* **買収または売却に関連する開示**。戦略的またはその他のビジネス上の理由により、ハネウェルが一部の国で事業を売却、買収、処分、合併またはその他の方法で再編成することを決定した場合、開示が必要な状況が発生する場合があります。当社は、ハネウェルの資産の全部または一部の合併、買収、処分または売却の交渉または履行を進めるために合理的に必要な範囲で、お客様に関して保持している情報を開示することがあります。
* **他の理由による開示**。当社は、法律で求められているか認められている場合、または法的要件や当社に適用される法的手続きを遵守するため、当社の権利や財産を保護および防御するため、もしくは緊急事態において個人の安全を守るために、かかる行為が必要であるという誠実な信念を有している場合、個人情報を開示することがあります。

**国際的な転送**

ハネウェルはグローバルな組織であり、お客様の個人情報は、適用法に従って、米国、メキシコ、インド、その他の国など、世界中のさまざまな場所にて転送、保持、保存、または使用される場合があります。これにより、当社があなたの個人情報を収集すると、お客様の国の法律とは異なるデータ保護法がある国で処理される場合があります。ただし、ハネウェルは、お客様のプライバシーを保護し、お客様の居住国に相当する程度の個人情報保護を提供するために、合理的な措置を講じます。お客様の個人情報を保護するための適切な保護対策の詳細については、[Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com)までお問い合わせください。

**生体認証データに関する方針（イリノイ州居住者のみ）**

ハネウェルは、健康、安全、セキュリティ、その他の管理機能のために生体認証データを収集および使用する場合があります。例えば、当社施設でのウェルネスおよび健康のスクリーニングの実施、時間管理プログラムの実施、ハネウェルのコンピュータおよびその他の技術リソースに関する認証およびアクセス制御の実施、生体認証対応機能を備えたビデオ監視などのセキュリティ対策の実施などです。本個人情報保護方針にこれと異なる規定があっても、該当する個人と当社との間の最後のやり取りから1年以内に生体認証データを保持することがハネウェル方針です。ただし、当社は、適用される法律、または管轄権を有する裁判所が発行した有効な令状、召喚状、または命令を遵守するため、またはハネウェルが法的請求を確立、行使、または防御するために、許可されている、または別途要求されている場合、同じことを満たすために必要な最小限の期間、かかる生体認証データを保持することを条件に、この保持期間を超えてかかる生体認証データを保持する場合があります。ハネウェルは、その機密性を意図的に損なわない方法で、生体認証データを永久に破棄または廃棄するための商業的に合理的なプロトコルを導入し、維持しています。なお、本項は、ハネウェル従業員、請負業者、または臨時雇用者に関する生体認証データまたはその他の個人データの処理に関連するハネウェルの社内方針、手順、または記録の機密性を破棄するものではなく、また破棄することを意図するものでもありません。本項は、米国イリノイ州に居住し、ハネウェルに生体認証データを提供する個人にのみ適用されます。

**ワシントン在住者の場合**

あなたの個人データの処理およびプライバシー権に関する追加情報については[、ワシントン州消費者健康データプライバシー方針](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/washington-consumer-health-data-privacy-policy)をお読みください。 

**セキュリティ**

当社は個人情報のセキュリティ保護に努めています。当社は、個人情報を処理するリスクに適切なレベルのセキュリティを提供するために、技術的および組織的な措置を講じています。 ハネウェルの個人情保護の方法の詳細については、[Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com)までお問い合わせください。

**お客様の権利**

適用法によっては、個人情報に関する特定の権利があなたに付与される場合があります。

* あなたはご自身の個人情報に対し**アクセス、コピーの要求、修正、更新**または**削除の要求**をする権利を有します。
* お客様は、ご自身の個人情報の処理に**異議**を唱えること、個人情報の処理を**制限**するよう当社に依頼したり、個人情報の**ポータビリティ**を要求したりすることができます。
* 意思決定があなたに法的影響を与える場合、またはあなたに重大な影響を与える場合、**あなたについての説明を求める権利およびプロファイリングを含め、自動処理のみに基づいた意思決定を受け入れない**権利を有します。
* 同様に、当社がお客様の同意を得てお客様の個人情報を収集および処理した場合、**お客様はいつでも同意を撤回することができます**。同意の撤回は、撤回前に当社が行った処理の合法性に影響せず、同意以外の合法的な処理根拠に従って行われた個人情報の処理にも影響しません。
* お客様は、**お客様の個人情報の販売をオプトアウト**する権利を有します。ハネウェルは、お客様の個人情報を営利目的で第三者に販売することはありません。ただし、本個人情報保護方針と当社の[クッキーに関する通知](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice)に従って、お客様の個人情報を第三者と共有またはその他の方法で第三者に開示します。たとえば、当社は第三者と連携して当社の製品を販売したり、お客様に技術支援を提供したり、Webサイトの分析ツールと機能を運用したり、当社の製品とサービスのマーケティングと販売に従事したりします。こうした活動は、お客様の個人情報の第三者への開示が伴う場合があり、特定の (ただし、すべてではない) データ保護に関する法律の下でデータの「販売」とみなされる場合があります。
* お客様は、当社によるお客様の個人情報の処理がデータ保護法に準拠していないと考える場合、お客様の法域におけるデータ保護法の遵守について監督責任を負うデータ保護機関に、当社によるお客様の個人情報の収集および使用について**苦情を申し立てる**権利を有します。たとえば、EEAの個人には、管轄のデータ保護当局に苦情を申し立てる権利があります。データ保護当局のリストについては、[https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/board/members\_en](https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/board/members_en) を参照してください。 ただし、当社にお客様の懸念に対処する機会をいただければ幸いです。苦情がございましたら、お気軽に当社までお問い合わせください。 当社は、データプライバシー権を行使したことによって個人を差別することはありません。

当社は、適用される法律に従って、お客様に適用される権利が円滑に行使されるようにします。ただし、お客様の個人情報がデータ保護に関する法律に基づいて保護されていない場合、またはその他データ保護に関する法律の対象となっていない場合でも、当社のデータ処理活動に関するお客様からの要求やお問い合わせに対応するよう努めることがあります。ご自身の権利について質問がある場合、または権利の行使を希望される場合は、[Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com)までご連絡いただくか、以下のリンクにあるインタラクティブなWebフォームからプライバシーに関する質問を提出できます。  

**子供の情報**

当社サイトは、16歳未満の子供を対象としておらず、かかる子供が使用すべきではありません。当社は、かかる個人からそうと知りながら情報を収集、使用、販売することはありません。居住国の法律により未成年とみなされる方は、当社サイトを通じて個人情報を送信しないでください。

**他のWebサイトへのリンク**

当社サイトには、第三者のWebサイト、製品およびサービスへのリンクが含まれている場合があります。これらの Webサイト、製品およびサービス、当該Webサイトのポリシー、またはお客様の個人情報の収集もしくはその他の処理について、当社は一切責任を負いません。これらの第三者の慣行には、それぞれのプライバシーに関する方針適用されます。これらの第三者のプライバシーに関する方針を確認することをお勧めします。

**お問い合わせ**

本個人情報保護方針またはお客様の個人情報の取り扱いに関して質問がある場合、苦情を申し立てる場合、または当社にデータ保護責任者に問い合わせる場合は、下記の連絡先情報を使用して当社までお問い合わせください。当社は、お客様の懸念に速やかに対応し、満足する解決策に到達するよう努めます。 

インタラクティブなWebフォーム:   
  
Eメールアドレス：   
  
住所:   
ハネウェルのプライバシー   
4D5   
115 Tabor Road   
Morris Plains, NJ 07950  
  
米国内フリーダイヤル番号：   

**本個人情報保護方針の変更**

当社は、折に触れて本個人情報保護方針を更新する場合があります。その際、個人情報保護方針の冒頭にある「最終更新日」を変更し、法律で求められる場合は該当する追加措置を講じます。

**最終更新日：2024年4月29日**

**최종 개정일: 2021년 6월 11일**

**소개**

Honeywell International Inc.(“**Honeywell**”, “**당사**”, “**당사의**”, 또는 “**당사를**”)는 이용자가 당사 웹사이트 중 하나를 방문 또는 이용하거나, 본 개인정보 보호 정책에 연결되어 있는 제품, 서비스 및 애플리케이션(총칭 당사의 “사이트”)을 사용하는 경우 이용자에 관해 당사가 수집하는 개인 정보에 대한 "데이터 관리자"입니다. 본 개인정보 보호 정책에서는 당사가 이러한 방법으로 이용자의 개인 정보를 어떻게 수집, 공유 및 사용하며, 이용자는 어떻게 본인의 개인정보 보호 권리를 행사할 수 있는지에 대해 설명합니다.

당사는 이용자와 상호작용할 때 이용자에게 구체적인 처리 활동에 관한 추가적인 개인정보 보호 고지를 제공하거나, 특정 시점에 Honeywell이 이용자의 개인 정보를 처리하는 방법에 관해 추가적인 선택권을 제시합니다.

원하는 섹션으로 이동하려면 아래 링크 중 하나를 클릭하십시오.

**당사의 정보 수집**

* **이용자로부터 직접 수집하는 정보**. 당사는 이용자가 요청한 서비스를 제공하거나 트랜잭션을 수행하기 위해 개인 정보를 요청할 수 있습니다. 또한 이용자가 당사에 문의 또는 소통(예: 의견 제시, 문의, 고객 지원 요청, 사이트 방문자 등)하는 경우 또는 당사 사이트에서 계정을 등록할 때에도 당사에 개인 정보를 제공하게 될 수 있습니다. 이러한 개인 정보에는 다음 정보가 포함될 수 있습니다.
    * **신분 데이터,** 예를 들어 본인 이름, 직책, 회사/조직명, 이메일 주소, 전화번호 및 우편 주소(국가, 우편번호, 주/도, 시 및/또는 도로명 포함) 등.
    * **등록 데이터,** 사용자 이름과 암호를 포함해 이용자가 당사 사이트 이용을 위해 계정을 등록할 때 입력하는 정보.
    * **채용 데이터,** 입사 지원서 또는 문의와 관련해 제출하는 정보 포함(아래 설명 참조).
    * **업무상 연락처 데이터,** 다른 직원, 오너, 이사, 임원 또는 외부 조직(예: 기업, 회사, 파트너십, 자영업자, 비영리 또는 정부 기관)의 하청업체 등과 관련한 정보 등.
    * **마케팅 및 커뮤니케이션 데이터,** 이용자의 마케팅 설정 선택 및 당사 간행물에 대한 이용자의 구독 정보 포함.
    * **금융 정보,** 당사가 당사 사이트에서 판매될 수 있는 당사 제품 및 서비스에 대한 이용자 구매를 원활하게 진행하고자 하는 목적으로 수집하는 신용 카드 및 기타 금융 기관 계좌 정보 포함.
    * **수출 통제 정보,** 이용자의 국적, 시민권 및 거주 국가 등, 당사가 수출 통제 규정에 따라 특정 기술에 관한 정보를 받을 수 있는 이용자 적격성 여부를 판단하는 데 필요한 정보.
    * **트랜잭션 데이터,** 당사 제품 및 서비스에 관한 정보 및 주문 관련 문의, 이용자에 대한 대금 지급 및 이용자의 대금 결제에 관한 상세 정보(구매 주문 이력 및 결제 트랜잭션을 원활하게 진행하는 데 필요한 정보 포함) 포함.
    * **이벤트 등록 정보,** 이용자가 온라인 등록 양식을 작성하는 과정에서 입력하는 정보 포함. 그리고,
    * **이용자 피드백,** 당사 사이트 및 전반적으로 당사 제품과 서비스에 관한 이용자의 설문조사 응답, 추천 및 기타 피드백.

이용자가 요청하는 정보를 제공하지 않는 경우 당사는 요청 대상 서비스를 제공하거나 해당 트랜잭션을 완료하지 못할 수 있습니다.

* **당사가 이용자에 관해 자동으로 수집하는 정보**. 당사는 쿠키 및 유사 추적 기술을 사용해 이용자의 당사 사이트 방문에 관한 특정 정보를 수집합니다. 당사는 이러한 당사의 수집을 막을 수 있는 이용자의 법적 권리를 항상 존중할 것입니다. 이러한 방식으로 수집되는 데이터는 다음과 같습니다.
    * **사용 데이터,** 당사 사이트 사용 방법에 대한 정보를 포함하여 조회한 페이지, 전송된 바이트 수, 클릭한 링크, 액세스한 자료, 사이트에 액세스한 날짜 및 시간, 당사 사이트로 오기 위해 경유한 웹 사이트 및 해당 사이트 내에서 수행한 기타 작업 등. 그리고,
    * **기술 데이터,** 인터넷 프로토콜(IP) 주소, 브라우저 유형, 용량, 언어 및 운영 체제 등.

당사가 당사 사이트에서 사용하는 쿠키 및 기타 유사 추적 기술에 관한 정보는 당사의 [쿠키 고지](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#korean)를 참조하시기 바랍니다.

* **지리적 위치 정보**. 특정 사이트의 경우, 당사는 이용자의 동의 하에 이용자가 사용하는 모바일 기기의 정밀한 실시간 위치 정보(즉, 지리적 위치 정보)를 수집할 수 있습니다. 이러한 정보는 당사를 대신한 서비스 제공과 관련해 이러한 정보를 처리할 수 있는 당사 서비스 제공자에 의한 것을 포함해 이용자의 당사 사이트 이용을 원활하기 하는 목적에 한해 사용됩니다. 동의한 경우 이용자는 모바일 기기의 설정을 통해 본인의 위치 서비스(Location Service) 설정 선택을 이용해 이러한 동의를 변경할 수 있습니다.
* **제3자로부터 수집되는 정보**. 당사는 관련 법률에 따라, 당사 사이트를 이용자의 선호도에 맞게 개선 및 맞춤화 하거나 본 개인정보 보호 정책에서 정하는 기타 목적을 위해 소셜 미디어 웹사이트 및 애플리케이션 등 제3자로부터 이용자에 대한 개인 정보를 수집해 당사가 이미 보유하고 있는 정보와 결합할 수 있습니다. 당사는 또한 이용자의 직장 또는 그 외 제3자로부터 이용자의 업무상 연락 정보를 수집하거나 그 외에 기존 방식의 비즈니스 활동 및 유사 행정관리 업무를 진행할 수 있습니다.

**당사의 정보 사용**

당사는 당사 사이트에서, 또는 이용자가 다음과 같은 목적으로 당사에 문의할 때 수집된 개인 정보를 사용할 수 있습니다.

* **업무상 연락처 데이터**. Honeywell은 제품 또는 서비스와 관련한 실사를 실시하거나 제품 또는 서비스를 제공 또는 수령하는 것을 포함해 커뮤니케이션이나 트랜잭션을 실행하기 위해 업무상 연락처 데이터를 수집해 사용합니다. 예를 들어, Honeywell은 주문, 계약, 보증, 유지보수 및 유사한 업무상 기능을 실행 및 관리하기 위해, 신용 분석 및 수집 목적으로, 당사의 내부적 준수 및 법적 요건을 지원하기 위해, 그리고 (필요한 경우) 당사의 이해 관계 및 주장을 변호하기 위해 이러한 업무상 연락처 데이터를 수집 및 사용할 수 있습니다.
* **서비스 및 트랜잭션**.당사는 이용자의 개인 정보를 사용하여 서비스를 제공하거나 이용자가 요청한 트랜잭션을 수행합니다. 여기에는 이용자가 구입하거나 달리 사용하는 회사 제품이나 서비스에 대한 정보 제공, 구입한 제품 등록, 제품 주문 처리, 보증 클레임 처리, 제품 설명서 교체, 고객 서비스 요청 답변, 사이트 이용 활성화 등이 포함되나 이에 국한되지 않습니다.
* **당사 비즈니스 및 사이트 관리 및 보호**. 당사는 문제 해결, 시스템 유지 보수, 지원, 보고 및 데이터 호스팅과 같이 당사 비즈니스 및 사이트를 관리하고 보호하기 위해 이용자의 개인 정보를 사용할 수 있습니다.
* **당사 비즈니스, 사이트, 제품 및 서비스 개선**. 당사는 당사 사이트를 사용자의 특정한 기본 설정이나 관심사에 맞게 맞춤 설정함으로써 비즈니스 분석을 수행하거나, 비즈니스, 사이트, 제품 및 서비스(신제품이나 신규 서비스 포함)의 질을 개선하기 위한 기타 목적으로 이용자의 개인 정보를 사용할 수 있습니다.
* **마케팅**. 당사는 관련법 및 규정에 따라 이용자의 개인 정보를 사용하여 이용자가 관심을 가질 만한 제품 또는 서비스를 알리고, 제품, 이벤트 및 뉴스, 설문 조사, 특별 제안 및 관련 주제에 관해 이용자와 소통할 수 있습니다. 이용자는 당사에서 제공하는 이메일 마케팅 자료의 "수신 거부" 링크를 사용하거나 본 개인정보 보호 정책에 나와 있는 연락처 정보로 당사에 문의하여 언제든지 이메일을 통해 무료로 전송되는 마케팅 커뮤니케이션을 구독 거부할 수 있습니다. 이용자의 거주 국가에 따라 다른 유형의 마케팅 연락에 대해 옵트아웃(수신 동의 철회)할 수도 있습니다. 자세한 사항은 본 개인정보 보호 정책에 나와 있는 연락처 정보를 이용해 당사에 문의해 주시기 바랍니다. 사법 관할 지역에 따라 제3자의 직접 마케팅 목적으로 당사가 제3자에 개인 정보를 제공하는 것과 관련해 개인(예: 캘리포니아 주 주민)에게 특정 정보를 요청할 권리를 부여하는 곳도 있습니다. 당사의 마케팅 목적에 따른 데이터 제공 방식에 관한 자세한 정보는 아래에 나와 있는 안내에 따라 당사에 문의해 주시기 바랍니다.
* **관심 기반 광고**. 당사는 이용자에게 가장 관련성 있는 광고를 제공할 수 있도록 이용자의 온라인 활동에 관한 데이터를 수집하고 이용자의 관심 사항을 파악합니다. 이용자는 당사 [쿠키 고지](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#korean)에서 정하는 바에 따라 Honeywell이 보내는 관심 기반 광고 수신을 옵트아웃(수신 동의 철회)할 수 있습니다.
* **금전적 인센티브 및 상용고객 프로그램**. 당사는 당사의 금전적 인센티브와 상용고객 프로그램을 유지 및 실시하기 위해 개인 정보를 수집 및 사용합니다. 당사는 고유한 보상을 제공하고, 이용자의 프로그램 상태를 추적하고, 프로그램 포인트를 제품, 프로모션 자료, 교육 워크샵 및 기타 항목으로 교환 사용하는 것을 촉진하기 위해 이러한 프로그램에서 이용자가 제공하는 개인 정보를 이용합니다. 또한 당사는 법률이 허용하는 범위 내에서 본 개인정보 보호 정책에서 정하는 모든 다른 목적으로 금전적 인센티브 프로그램 맥락에서 이용자가 제공하는 개인 정보를 사용할 수 있습니다. 프로그램의 약관은 해당 프로그램에 맞춰 범위가 좁게 설정되어 있을 수 있는 만큼, 등록 또는 참여하고자 하는 각 금전적 인센티브 프로그램의 약관을 자세히 살펴보시기 바랍니다. 이러한 프로그램에 참여하는 데 동의하시는 경우, 본 개인정보 보호 정책의 끝 부분에 나와 있는 연락처 정보를 이용해 당사에 연락하거나 해당 프로그램의 약관에서 정하는 방법에 따라 언제든지 그러한 동의를 철회하실 수 있습니다.
* **입사 지원**. 이용자는 입사 지원이나 문의와 관련해 이력서, 추천인, 학력 및 경력 관련 정보, 직업적 교육 및 자격증 관련 정보 등, 자신에 관한 정보를 당사에 제공할 수 있습니다. 당사와 당사 그룹 계열사는 채용 심사, 신원 조회 및 채용 적격성 확인 목적, 그리고 별도의 개인정보 보호 정책 또는 그 외에 입사 지원과 관련해 확인 가능한 기타 고지에서 정하는 바에 따라 이러한 정보를 사용할 수 있습니다. 당사는 입사 지원을 요청, 수집 및 보관하기 위해 제3자(예: 채용업체) 또는 소셜 미디어 플랫폼을 이용할 수 있습니다. 자세한 사항은 당사의 [지원자 개인정보 보호 고지](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/applicant-privacy-notice#korean)를 참고하시기 바랍니다.
* **조사 및 분석**. 당사는 이용자의 개인 정보를 토대로 조사 및 분석을 실시하여 사용자의 구매 기본 설정을 분석하고, 이용자의 요구에 가장 잘 맞는 제품 및 서비스를 파악하고, 당사가 이용자에게 제공하는 광고의 효과를 측정할 수 있습니다.
* **법 집행**: 당사는 수집한 개인 정보를 사기, 지적재산권 침해, 당사의 약관 위반, 법률 위반, 당사 사이트의 악용을 탐지하고 방지하며 대응하기 위해 사용할 수 있습니다.

법률이 허용하는 한, 당사가 사이트를 통해 수집한 정보와 이용자에 대해 보유하고 있는 기타 정보(예: 당사 제품 및 서비스 이용에 대한 정보)를 결합하여 당사와 상호 작용할 때 또는 본 개인정보 보호 정책에 기술된 다른 용도를 위해 더 우수하고 일관된 고객 경험을 제공할 수 있습니다.

**당사가 정보를 처리하는 법적 근거**

법률에서 요구하는 경우, 당사는 이용자의 개인 정보 처리를 위한 법적 근거가 있음을 보장합니다. 대부분의 경우 당사의 법적 근거는 해당 개인 정보 및 당사가 그 정보를 수집하는 구체적인 맥락 상황에 따라 결정됩니다.

* **계약**: 당사가 이용자에게 제공하는 서비스의 수행을 위해, 또는 그러한 서비스의 수행 이전에, 그러한 서비스를 예상하고 (이용자의 요청에 따라) 조치를 취하기 위해서는 처리가 필요합니다.
* **법적 의무**: 관련 법률, 규정, 정부 및 준정부 요청, 법원 명령 또는 소환장 이행 등 당사의 법적 의무를 준수하기 위해 개인 정보를 처리해야 합니다.
* **동의**: 하나 이상의 지정된 목적(예: 마케팅)을 위해 처리하며 이용자의 개인 정보 처리에 대한 본인 동의를 근거로 처리합니다.
* **합법적 이해 관계**: 고객의 이익을 위해 당사 사이트, 제품 및/또는 서비스를 개발 및 개선하는 것과 같이 당사의 합법적인 이해 관계를 충족하기 위해 개인 정보 처리가 필요합니다. 또는,
* **생명에 직결되는 이해 관계**: 이용자의 생명에 직결되는 이해 관계를 보호하는 데 처리가 필요합니다(예를 들어, 이용자가 Honeywell 사업장에서 열리는 미팅에 참석하는 경우 건강 및 안전상의 이유로).

당사가 귀하의 개인 정보를 수집 및 사용하는 법적 근거와 관련해 궁금한 사항이 있거나 추가적인 정보가 필요하신 경우 [HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com)으로 이메일을 보내주시기 바랍니다.

**정보의 익명화**

해당 법률에 따라 이용자의 개인 정보를 익명화 하여 더 이상 이용자 신원을 확인하는 데 사용할 수 없도록 할 수 있습니다. 익명화된 정보는 개인 정보로 간주되지 않으며, 따라서 본 개인정보 보호 정책의 대상이 아닙니다. 당사는 익명의 정보를 모든 용도로 수집, 사용, 취합 및 공유할 수 있습니다.

**당사가 정보를 보유하는 기간**

당사가 이용자의 개인 정보를 보관하는 기간은 처리 목적에 따라 다릅니다. 예를 들어, 당사는 이용자가 Honeywell 고객으로 있는 한, 이용자에게 제품 및 서비스를 제공하거나 이용자가 요청한 트랜잭션을 원활하게 진행하기 위해 필요한 개인 정보를 보관하며, 이용자가 당사 사이트를 통해 입사 지원서를 제출하는 경우 해당 지원서와 관련해 이용자에게 제공되는 개인정보 고지에서 정하고 있거나 그 외 법률에서 정하는 요건에 따라 이용자의 지원서 세부 정보를 보관합니다. 그 외 다른 모든 경우 당사는 본 개인정보 보호 정책에 명시된 목적을 달성하는 데 필요한 기간 동안 이용자의 개인 정보를 보관하며 그 후에는 (관련법률에서 허용하는 경우) 익명화 하거나 삭제 또는 폐기합니다.

**정보의 공개**

당사는 아래에 명시된 내용을 포함하여 관련 법률에 따라 이용자의 개인 정보를 선택된 제3자와 공유할 수 있습니다.

* **당사 그룹 계열사**. 당사는 본 개인정보 보호 정책에 명시된 목적을 위해 합리적으로 필요한 경우 이용자의 개인 정보를 당사 계열사 및 그룹사와 공유할 수 있습니다.
* **서비스 제공업체**. 당사는 웹 사이트 호스팅, 설문 조사 수행, 트랜잭션 처리, 당사 사이트 분석 및 당사의 비즈니스, 사이트, 제품 및 서비스의 질을 향상하기 위한 분석 수행과 같이 당사를 대신하여 해당 서비스를 제공하기로 계약한 회사와 사용자의 개인 정보를 공유할 수 있습니다. 당사는 해당 서비스 제공업체에게 이용자의 개인 정보 기밀을 보호하도록 요구합니다.
* **유통사 및 기타 신뢰할 수 있는 비즈니스 파트너**. 당사는 제3자가 이용자에게 마케팅 커뮤니케이션을 보내는 것을 허용하는 목적으로 당사 제품을 유통하는 제3자 및 기타 신뢰할 수 있는 비즈니스 파트너와 이용자의 개인 정보를 공유할 수 있습니다. 마케팅 목적으로 개인 정보를 공유하는 경우 적용 가능한 법률 및 규정에 따라 수행됩니다.
* **트랜잭션과 관련한 공개**. 특정 트랜잭션과 관련하여 당사는 이용자의 개인 정보의 일부 또는 전부를 트랜잭션 이행에 연관된 금융 기관, 정부 기관, 운송 회사 또는 우편 서비스에 공개할 수 있습니다.
* **인수 또는 매각과 관련한 공개**. 전략적 이유 또는 그 외 사업상 이유로 Honeywell이 일부 국가에서 사업체를 매각, 인수, 처분, 합병 또는 그 외 다른 방법으로 조직 개편하는 상황이 발생할 수 있습니다. 당사는 Honeywell 자산의 전체 또는 일부에 대한 협상을 진행하거나 합병, 인수, 처분 또는 매각을 완료하기 위해 합리적으로 필요한 범위까지 당사가 보유하고 있는 이용자의 정보를 공개할 수 있습니다.
* **기타 사유에 따른 공개**. 당사는 법에서 요구하거나 허가하는 경우, 또는 법적 요건이나 당사에 적용된 법적 절차를 준수하기 위해 필요한 경우, 당사의 권리 또는 재산을 보호하고 변호하기 위해, 또는 비상시 개인의 안전을 보호하기 위해 정보 공개가 필요하다는 선의의 확신이 드는 경우 개인 정보를 공개할 수 있습니다.

**국가 간 이전**

Honeywell은 글로벌 조직이며, 이용자의 정보는 관련 법에 따라 미국, 멕시코, 인도 등 전 세계 다양한 장소에 걸쳐 이전, 보유, 저장 또는 사용될 수 있습니다. 따라서 당사가 이용자의 개인 정보를 수집했을 때 그 정보가 이용자 국가의 데이터 보호 법률과는 법률이 다른 국가에서 처리될 수 있다는 뜻입니다. 그러나 Honeywell은 항상 이용자의 개인 정보를 보호하고, 유럽 집행위원회(European Commission)의 표준 계약 조항(Standard Contractual Clauses)을 실시하는 것을 포함해, 이용자 거주 국가와 유사한 수준의 개인 정보 보호를 제공하기 위해 항상 합당한 조치를 취할 것입니다. 귀하의 개인 정보 보호를 위해 마련되어 있는 적절한 안전 장치에 관한 자세한 정보는 [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com)으로 문의해 주시기 바랍니다.

**보안**

당사는 이용자의 개인 정보 보안을 유지하기 위해 최선을 다합니다. 당사는 이용자의 개인 정보 처리에 따른 위험에 적합한 수준의 보안을 제공하기 위해 기술적 조치 및 조직 차원의 조치를 취하고 있습니다. Honeywell이 이용자의 개인 정보를 보호하는 방법에 관한 자세한 정보는 [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com)으로 문의해 주시기 바랍니다.

**이용자의 권리**

관련 법률에 따라 이용자에게는 본인의 개인 정보와 관련해 특정한 권리가 있을 수 있습니다.

* 이용자에게는 자신의 개인 정보에 대해 **열람, 정정, 수정** 또는 **삭제 요청**할 수 있는 권리가 있을 수 있습니다.
* 이용자는 자신의 개인 정보 처리에 **반대**하거나, 당사에 자신의 개인 정보 처리를 **제한**해 줄 것을 요청하거나, 본인 개인 정보의 **이동성**을 요청할 수 있습니다.
* 이용자에게는 자신에 대해 법적 효과를 갖거나 상당한 영향을 미치는 결정인 경우 **프로파일링을 포함해, 전적으로 자동 처리를 바탕으로 자신에 대해 그러한 결정이 이루어지지 않도록 할** 권리가 있습니다.
* 마찬가지로, 당사가 이용자의 동의 하에 이용자의 개인 정보를 수집 및 처리한 경우 **이용자는 언제든지 자신의 동의를 철회할 수 있습니다**. 동의를 철회하더라도 철회 전에 당사가 수행한 처리의 합법성에는 아무런 영향을 미치지 않으며, 동의를 제외한 합법적 처리 근거에 따라 수행한 이용자의 개인 정보 처리에도 영향을 미치지 않습니다.
* 이용자에게는 **자신의 개인 정보 판매에 대해 옵트아웃할 권리가 있을 수 있습니다**. Honeywell은 영리 목적으로 이용자의 개인 정보를 제3자에게 판매하지 않습니다. 그러나, 당사는 본 개인정보 보호 정책 및 당사의 [쿠키 고지](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#korean)에 따라 제3자와 이용자의 개인 정보를 공유하거나 그 외 다른 방법으로 제공합니다. 예를 들어, 당사는 당사 제품을 유통시키고, 이용자에게 기술 지원을 제공하며, 웹사이트 분석 도구 및 기능을 실행하고, 당사 제품 및 서비스의 마케팅 및 판매 활동을 수행하기 위해 제3자와 계약을 맺을 수 있습니다. 그러한 활동 과정에서 제3자에 대한 이용자의 개인 정보 제공이 발생할 수 있으며, 이는 (모두 그런 것은 아니지만) 특정 데이터 보호 법률에 따라 데이터 "판매"로 간주될 수 있습니다.
* 이용자에게는 당사에 의한 자신의 개인 정보 처리가 데이터 보호 법률에 부합되지 않는다고 판단되는 경우 당사의 개인 정보 수집 및 사용에 관해 자신이 속한 사법 관할권 내 데이터 보호 법률의 준수를 관할하는 데이터 보호 당국에 **민원을 제기**할 수 있습니다. 예를 들어, EEA(유럽경제지역) 내에 거주하는 개인의 경우 관할 데이터 보호 기관(Data Protection Authority)에 민원을 제기할 권리가 있으며, 데이터 보호 기관의 목록은 [https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/board/members\_en](https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/board/members_en)에서 확인할 수 있습니다. 하지만 우려되는 부분이 있으신 경우 당사가 해결해 드릴 수 있기를 바라며, 불만 사항이 있으시면 언제든지 당사에 직접 연락해 주시기 바랍니다. 당사는 자신이 가진 데이터 프라이버시 권리를 행사하는 개인을 차별하지 않습니다.

당사는 관련 법률에 따라 사용자에게 적용되는 권리 행사를 촉진합니다. 그러나 개인 정보가 데이터 보호 법률에 따른 보호 대상 또는 적용 대상이 아니라 하더라도 당사는 당사의 데이터 처리 활동과 관련한 이용자의 요청 또는 문의 사항을 수용하고자 할 수 있습니다. 본인의 권리에 관해 궁금한 사항이 있거나 본인이 가진 권리를 행사하고자 하시는 경우 [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com)으로 당사에 연락하시거나, 다음 링크를 이용해 당사의 대화형 웹 양식을 통해 개인정보 보호 관련 질문을 제출해 주시기 바랍니다.

**아동청소년의 정보**

당사 사이트는 십육(16) 세 미만 아동청소년을 대상으로 하지 않고 그러한 아동청소년이 사용해서는 안 되며, 그러한 아동청소년으로부터 의도적으로 정보를 수집해 사용하거나 판매해서는 안 됩니다. 귀하가 본인 국가의 법률 상 미성년자에 해당되는 경우 절대 당사 사이트를 통해 개인 정보를 제출해서는 안 됩니다.

**타 웹사이트 링크**

당사 사이트에는 제3자 웹사이트, 제품 및 서비스에 대한 링크가 포함될 수 있습니다. 당사는 제3자 웹사이트, 제품 및 서비스, 제3자 정책, 또는 제3자의 사용자 개인 정보 수집 또는 기타 처리에 대해 일체 책임지지 않습니다. 그러한 제3자의 정보 취급 방식에는 자체적인 개인정보 보호 정책이 적용됩니다. 이용자는 그러한 제3자의 개인정보 보호 정책에 대해 자세히 알아두는 것을 권장합니다.

**연락처**

본 개인정보 보호 정책 또는 당사의 이용자 개인 정보 처리와 관련하여 궁금한 사항이 있거나, 불만 사항을 제기하고자 하거나, 당사의 데이터 보호 담당자에게 문의하고자 하시는 경우 아래에 나와 있는 연락처 정보를 이용해 당사에 문의해 주시기 바랍니다. 당사는 지체 없이 우려 사항에 대응하고 만족스러운 해결책을 찾기 위해 노력할 것입니다.

대화형 웹 양식:  

이메일:  

우편 주소:  
Honeywell Privacy  
4D5  
115 Tabor Road  
Morris Plains, NJ 07950

무료 전화:  

**본 개인정보 보호 정책의 변경**

당사는 때때로 본 개인정보 보호 정책을 업데이트할 수 있습니다. 업데이트하는 경우 당사는 개인정보 보호 정책의 상단과 하단에 있는 "최종 수정일" 날짜를 수정하고, 법에서 정하고 있는 추가적 조치가 있는 경우 해당 조치를 취할 것입니다.

**최종 개정일: 2021년 6월 11일**

**Sist oppdatert 11. juni 2021**

**Introduksjon**

Honeywell International Inc. ("**Honeywell**", "**våre**", "**oss**" eller "**vi**”), er "behandlingsansvarlig" for personopplysningene vi samler inn om deg når du besøker eller bruker noen av våre nettsteder, eller bruker produkter, tjenester og programmer som er koblet til denne personvernerklæringen (samlet våre "**nettsteder**"). Denne personvernerklæringen forklarer hvordan vi samler inn, deler og bruker personopplysningene dine som er samlet inn på denne måten, og hvordan du kan utøve dine personvernrettigheter.

Når vi kommuniserer med deg, kan vi også gi deg ytterligere personvernerklæringer om spesifikke behandlingsaktiviteter eller tilby deg flere valg om hvordan Honeywell behandler personopplysningene dine på det aktuelle tidspunktet.

Klikk på en av koblingene nedenfor for å gå til avsnittet som du er interessert i:

**Vår innhenting av opplysninger**

* **Informasjon som samles inn direkte fra deg**. Vi kan be deg om personopplysninger for å yte en tjeneste eller utføre en transaksjon som du har bedt om. Du kan også gi oss personopplysninger når du tar kontakt med oss eller samhandler med oss (for eksempel med en kommentar, forespørsel eller kundesupportforespørsel, besøkende på nettsteder) eller registrerer deg for en konto for å bruke våre nettsteder. Disse personopplysningene kan omfatte:
    * **Identitetsdata,** for eksempel navn, tittel, firma/organisasjonsnavn, e-postadresse, telefonnummer og fysisk adresse (inkludert gate, by, postnummer og/eller land);
    * **Registreringsdata,** for eksempel informasjon gitt av deg når du registrerer deg for en konto for å bruke våre nettsteder, inkludert brukernavn og passord;
    * **Rekrutteringsopplysninger,** blant annet informasjon sendt inn i forbindelse med en søknad eller spørsmål om jobb (som beskrevet nedenfor);
    * **Bedriftskontaktdata,** for eksempel informasjon relatert til andre ansatte, eiere, styremedlemmer, funksjonærer eller leverandører i en tredjepartsorganisasjon (f.eks. virksomhet, selskap, partnerskap, enkeltmannsforetak, ideell organisasjon eller offentlig etat).
    * **Markedsførings- og kommunikasjonsdata,** inkludert markedsføringspreferanser og abonnementene i våre publikasjoner;
    * **Finansiell informasjon,** inkludert kredittkort eller annen finansiell kontoinformasjon, med det formål å gjøre det mulig for oss å legge til rette for kjøp av selskapets produkter og tjenester som kan være tilgjengelige på våre nettsteder;
    * **Informasjon om eksportkontroll,** for eksempel nasjonalitet, statsborgerskap og bostedsland, som gjør det mulig for oss å fastslå at du er kvalifisert under eksportkontrollforskrifter for å motta informasjon om visse teknologier;
    * **Transaksjonsdata,** blant annet henvendelser om og bestillinger for våre produkter og tjenester og detaljer om betalinger til og fra deg, inkludert innkjøpsordrehistorikk og informasjon som er nødvendig for å gjennomføre betalingstransaksjoner;
    * **Informasjon i forbindelse med hendelsesregistrering,** inkludert informasjon som du oppgir når du fyller ut e-registreringsskjemaer; og
    * **Din tilbakemelding,** inkludert tilbakemelding fra deg om nettstedet våre, samt produktene og tjenestene generelt.

Når du ikke oppgir forespurt informasjon, kan det hende vi ikke kan levere den tjenesten du ber om, eller utføre transaksjonen din.

* **Informasjon vi samler inn automatisk om deg**. Vi samler inn bestemt informasjon om ditt besøk på våre nettsteder ved hjelp av informasjonskapsler og lignende sporingsteknologier. Vi vil alltid respektere eventuelle juridiske rettigheter du måtte ha for å forhindre at vi gjør dette. Data som samles inn på denne måten, inkluderer:
    * **Bruksdata,** inkludert informasjon om hvordan du bruker våre nettsteder, hvilke sider du viser, antall byte som overføres, lenkene du klikker på, materialene du har tilgang til, datoen og klokkeslettet du får tilgang til nettstedet, nettstedet som du koblet videre til et av våre nettsteder fra, og andre handlinger på nettstedet; og
    * **Tekniske data,** for eksempel din IP-adresse, nettlesertype og -funksjoner og språk og operativsystem.

For informasjon om informasjonskapslene og andre lignende sporingsteknologier vi bruker på nettstedene våre, kan du se vår [merknad om informasjonskapsler](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#norwegian).

* **Geolokasjonsinformasjon**. For bestemte nettsteder kan vi med uttrykkelig samtykke fra deg samle inn nøyaktige posisjonsopplysninger i sanntid (dvs. geolokasjon) for mobilenheten din. Denne informasjonen brukes bare for å lette din bruk av nettstedene, inkludert av tjenesteleverandørene våre som kan behandle denne informasjonen i forbindelse med å tilby tjenester på våre vegne. Hvis du har gitt det, kan du justere dette samtykket ved å administrere preferansene dine for posisjonstjenester gjennom innstillingene på mobilenheten din.
* **Informasjon samlet inn fra tredjeparter**. I samsvar med gjeldende lov kan vi samle inn personopplysninger om deg fra tredjeparter, for eksempel nettsteder og apper på sosiale medier, og kombinere dem med informasjon vi allerede har, for å hjelpe oss med å forbedre og tilpasse nettstedene dine etter dine preferanser og for andre formål som er angitt i denne personvernerklæringen. Vi kan også samle virksomhetens kontaktinformasjon fra arbeidsgiveren din eller andre tredjeparter for å legge til rette for eller på annen måte delta i tradisjonelle forretningsaktiviteter og lignende administrative spørsmål.

**Vår bruk av opplysninger**

Vi kan bruke den personlige informasjonen som er samlet inn via våre nettsteder, eller når du kontakter oss for formål som inkluderer:

* **Forretningskontaktdata**. Honeywell samler inn og bruker forretningskontaktdata for å delta i kommunikasjon eller transaksjoner, inkludert for å utføre due diligence om, eller levere eller motta, et produkt eller en tjeneste. For eksempel kan Honeywell samle inn og bruke disse forretningskontaktopplysningene for å tilrettelegge for og administrere bestillinger, kontrakter, garantier, vedlikehold og lignende forretningsfunksjoner, for kredittanalyse- og innkrevingsformål, for å bistå med vårt eget interne samsvar og juridiske krav, og (om nødvendig) for å forsvare våre interesser og krav.
* **Tjenester og transaksjoner**. Vi kan bruke personopplysningene dine til å levere deg tjenester og utføre transaksjoner du har bedt om, inklusiv, men ikke begrenset til, å gi informasjon om selskapets produkter, eller tjenester som du har kjøpt eller på annen måte bruker, registrere kjøpte produkter, behandle produktbestillinger, behandle garantikrav, erstatte produkthåndbøker, svare på kundeservicehenvendelser og forenkle bruken av nettstedene våre.
* **Administrere og beskytte vår virksomhet og nettsteder**. Vi kan bruke dine personlige opplysninger til å administrere og beskytte vår virksomhet og våre nettsteder, inkludert feilsøking, systemvedlikehold, brukerstøtte, rapportering og hosting av data.
* **Forbedre vår forretningsvirksomhet, nettsteder, produkter og tjenester**. Vi kan bruke dine personlige opplysninger til å utføre forretningsanalyser eller til andre formål som hjelper oss med å utvikle og forbedre kvaliteten på virksomheten vår, nettsteder, produkter og tjenester (inkludert nye produkter og tjenester), for eksempel ved å tilpasse våre nettsteder til dine spesielle preferanser eller interesser.
* **Markedsføring**. I samsvar med gjeldende lover og forskrifter kan vi bruke dine personopplysninger til å informere deg om produkter eller tjenester som kan være av interesse for deg, og ellers kommunisere med deg om tilbud, hendelser og nyheter, undersøkelser, spesialtilbud og relaterte emner. Du kan når som helst melde deg fra markedsføringskommunikasjon sendt via e-post, gratis ved å bruke "unsubscribe"-lenken i e-postmarkedsføringsmateriell du mottar fra oss, eller ved å kontakte oss ved å bruke kontaktopplysningene som er oppført i denne personvernerklæringen. Avhengig av bostedsland kan du også velge bort andre typer markedsføringskommunikasjon; kontakt oss ved hjelp av kontaktinformasjonen som er oppført i personvernerklæringen for mer informasjon. Noen jurisdiksjoner gir enkeltpersoner (for eksempel innbyggere i California) rett til å be om bestemt informasjon om vår utlevering av personopplysninger til tredjeparter for tredjepartens direkte markedsføringsformål. For mer informasjon om vår datapubliseringspraksis for markedsføringsformål kan du kontakte oss i samsvar med instruksjonene som er oppført nedenfor.
* **Interessebasert reklame**. Vi samler inn data om aktivitetene dine på nettet og identifiserer interessene dine slik at vi kan tilby reklame som er mest relevant for deg. Du kan velge å motta interessebasert reklame fra Honeywell som beskrevet i vår [merknad om informasjonskapsler](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#norwegian).
* **Programmer for økonomisk insentiv og lojalitet**. Vi samler inn og bruker personopplysninger for å opprettholde og administrere våre programmer for økonomisk insentiv og lojalitet. Vi bruker personopplysningene du oppgir i disse programmene for å tilby unike belønninger, spore programstatusen din og for å tilrettelegge for utvekslingen av programpoeng i produkter, reklamemateriell, treningsverksteder og andre ting. I den grad loven tillater det, kan vi også bruke alle personopplysninger som du oppgir i forbindelse med et økonomisk insentivprogram til ethvert annet formål som er angitt i denne personvernerklæringen. Se gjennom vilkårene og betingelsene for hvert økonomisk insentivprogram du ønsker å registrere deg for eller delta i, ettersom slike vilkår kan være smalt tilpasset det aktuelle programmet. Hvis du samtykker i å delta i disse programmene, kan du når som helst trekke tilbake samtykket ved å kontakte oss ved å bruke kontaktinformasjonen på slutten av denne personvernerklæringen eller i samsvar med instruksjonene i det aktuelle programmets vilkår og betingelser.
* **Jobbsøknader**. I forbindelse med en jobbsøknad eller henvendelse kan du gi oss informasjon om deg selv, for eksempel CV, fagreferanser, informasjon om utdanning og jobbbakgrunn, og informasjon om fagopplæring og sertifiseringer. Vi og medlemmer av vår gruppe kan bruke denne informasjonen for å vurdere ansettelser, bakgrunnskontroll og ansettelseskvalifikasjon, og som det ellers er angitt i en hvilken som helst separat personvernerklæring eller annen merknad som er gjort tilgjengelig i forbindelse med søknaden din. Vi kan bruke en tredjepart (f.eks. rekrutteringsbyrå) eller plattform for sosiale medier for å be om, samle inn og beholde jobbsøknader. For mer informasjon kan du lese vår [Personvernerklæring for søkere](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/applicant-privacy-notice#norwegian).
* **Undersøkelser og analyser**. Vi kan bruke dine personopplysninger til å utføre forskning og analyse for å hjelpe oss med å analysere innkjøpspraksis, identifisere produktene og tjenestene som best passer dine krav, og måle effektiviteten av annonseringen vi leverer til deg.
* **Håndhevelse**: Vi kan bruke personopplysningene vi samler for å oppdage, forhindre og håndtere svindel, brudd på immaterielle rettigheter, brudd på våre vilkår og betingelser, lovbrudd eller annen misbruk av våre nettsteder.

Når loven tillater det, kan vi kombinere informasjonen vi samler inn via våre nettsteder med annen informasjon vi har om deg (for eksempel informasjon om din bruk av våre produkter og tjenester) for å tilby deg en bedre og konsistent kundeopplevelse når du samhandler med oss eller andre formål som er angitt i denne personvernerklæringen.

**Det rettslige grunnlaget for å behandle opplysninger**

Når loven krever det, sørger vi for at det er et rettslig grunnlag for behandlingen av dine personlige opplysninger. I de fleste tilfeller avhenger vårt juridiske grunnlag av de aktuelle personopplysningene og den spesifikke konteksten vi samler dem inn i.

* **Kontrakt**: behandlingen er nødvendig for utførelsen av tjenestene vi tilbyr deg, eller for å ta skritt (på din forespørsel) før utførelse av slike tjenester;
* **Juridisk forpliktelse**: behandlingen er nødvendig for å overholde våre juridiske forpliktelser, herunder overholdelse av gjeldende lover, forskrifter, statlige og kvasi-statlige forespørsler, rettsordre eller stevninger;
* **Samtykke**: behandlingen er basert på ditt samtykke til behandling av din personopplysninger for ett eller flere spesifiserte formål (for eksempel markedsføring);
* **Legitime interesser**: behandlingen er nødvendig for å møte våre legitime interesser, for eksempel for å utvikle og forbedre våre nettsteder, produkter og/eller tjenester til fordel for våre kunder; eller
* **Vitale interesser**: behandlingen er nødvendig for å beskytte dine vitale interesser (for eksempel helse- og sikkerhetsmessige grunner hvis du deltar på et møte på et Honeywell-sted).

Hvis du har spørsmål om eller trenger ytterligere informasjon om det juridiske grunnlaget som vi samler inn og bruker din personlige informasjon på, kan du sende en e-post til [HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com)

**Anonymisering av opplysninger**

I samsvar med gjeldende lov kan vi anonymisere dine personopplysninger slik at de ikke lenger kan brukes til å identifisere deg. Anonymisert informasjon anses ikke som personopplysninger og er derfor ikke underlagt denne personvernerklæringen. Vi kan samle inn, bruke, aggregere og dele anonymisert informasjon til ethvert formål.

**Hvor lenge vi lagrer opplysninger**

Perioden vi lagrer dine personopplysninger varierer avhengig av formålet med behandlingen. For eksempel lagrer vi personopplysninger som er nødvendige for å levere produkter og tjenester til deg, eller for å tilrettelegge for transaksjoner du har bedt om, så lenge du er kunde hos Honeywell, eller hvis du sender inn en jobbsøknad via våre nettsteder, vil vi beholde informasjon om søknaden din som beskrevet i personvernerklæringen som er tilgjengelig for deg i forbindelse med søknaden din eller som ellers kreves av loven. I alle andre tilfeller lagrer vi dine personlige opplysninger så lenge det er nødvendig for å oppfylle formålene som er angitt i denne personvernerklæringen, etter hvilken tid det er enten anonymisert (der det er tillatt ved gjeldende lov), slettet eller ødelagt.

**Utlevering av opplysninger**

Vi kan dele dine personopplysninger med utvalgte tredjeparter i samsvar med gjeldende lov, inkludert som angitt nedenfor:

* **Våre konsernselskaper**. Vi kan dele dine personopplysninger med våre tilknyttede selskaper og konsernselskaper som rimelig nødvendig for de formålene som er angitt i denne personvernerklæringen.
* **Tjenesteleverandører**. Vi kan dele dine personopplysninger med selskaper som vi har utkontraktert til å tilby tjenester på våre vegne, for eksempel hosting av nettsteder, gjennomføring av undersøkelser, behandlingstransaksjoner, analyse av våre nettsteder og utførelse av analyser for å forbedre kvaliteten på vår virksomhet, nettsteder, produkter og tjenester. Vi trenger disse tjenesteleverandørene for å beskytte konfidensialiteten til dine personopplysninger.
* **Distributører og andre pålitelige samarbeidspartnere**. Vi kan dele dine personlige opplysninger med tredjeparter som distribuerer våre produkter og andre pålitelige forretningspartnere til formål som inkluderer at disse tredjepartene kan sende markedsføringskommunikasjon til deg. Slik utveksling av personlig informasjon til markedsføringsformål blir utført i samsvar med gjeldende lover og forskrifter.
* **Utlevering i forbindelse med transaksjoner**. I forbindelse med visse transaksjoner kan det hende vi leverer videre noen av eller alle personopplysningene dine til finansinstitusjoner, myndighetsorganer og transport- eller postselskaper som er involvert i utførelsen av transaksjonen.
* **Opplysninger i forbindelse med oppkjøp eller frasalg**. Det kan oppstå forhold der Honeywell av strategiske eller andre forretningsgrunner bestemmer seg for å selge, kjøpe, selge, slå sammen eller på annen måte omorganisere virksomheter i noen land. Vi kan avsløre informasjon vi har om deg i den grad det er rimelig nødvendig for å fortsette med forhandling eller fullføring av fusjon, oppkjøp, avhendelse eller salg av hele eller deler av Honeywells eiendeler.
* **Utlevering av andre årsaker**. Det kan hende vi offentliggjør personopplysninger hvis nødvendig eller autorisert til å gjøre dette ifølge lov, eller når vi i god tro mener en slik handling er nødvendig for å etterleve juridiske krav, eller opptre riktig i forbindelse med søksmål mot oss, for å beskytte og forsvare våre rettigheter eller vår eiendom, eller for å beskytte den personlige sikkerheten til en person under presserende omstendigheter.

**Internasjonale overføringer**

Honeywell er en global organisasjon, og din personopplysningene dine kan overføres til, oppbevares, lagres eller brukes på forskjellige steder over hele verden som USA, Mexico og India i samsvar med gjeldende lov. Dette betyr at når vi samler inn personopplysningene dine, kan de bli behandlet i land som kan ha databeskyttelseslover som er forskjellige fra lovene i ditt land. Imidlertid vil Honeywell alltid ta rimelige tiltak for å beskytte personvernet ditt og for å gi et nivå av beskyttelse av personopplysninger som er sammenlignbar med den i bostedslandet ditt, inkludert implementering av EU-kommisjonens standardavtaleklausuler. For mer informasjon om hensiktsmessige tiltak for å beskytte personopplysningene dine kan du kontakte oss på [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com).

**Sikkerhet**

Vi er forpliktet til å verne personopplysninger om deg. Vi bruker tekniske og organisatoriske tiltak for å gi et sikkerhetsnivå som passer til risikoen for å behandle personopplysningene dine. For mer informasjon om hvordan Honeywell beskytter personopplysningene dine kan du kontakte oss på [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com)

**Dine rettigheter**

Avhengig av gjeldende lov kan du ha visse rettigheter med hensyn til personopplysningene dine.

* Du kan ha rett til å **få tilgang til, korrigere, oppdatere** eller **be om sletting** av personopplysningene dine.
* Du kan **protestere** mot behandlingen av personopplysningene dine, be oss om å **begrense** behandlingen av personopplysningene dine eller be om **portabilitet** av personopplysningene dine.
* Du kan ha rett **til at det ikke tas en beslutning om deg som bare er basert på automatisert behandling, inkludert profilering,** hvis avgjørelsen gir rettsvirkninger for deg eller påvirker deg betydelig.
* Tilsvarende, hvis vi har samlet inn og behandlet personopplysningene dine med ditt samtykke, **kan du når som helst trekke tilbake samtykket ditt**. Å trekke tilbake samtykket ditt vil ikke påvirke lovligheten av behandling vi har utført før du trakk det tilbake, og det vil heller ikke påvirke behandlingen av personopplysningene dine som er utført på annet lovlig behandlingsgrunnlag enn samtykke.
* Du kan ha rett til **å velge bort salg av personopplysningene dine**. Honeywell selger ikke personopplysningene dine til tredjeparter for fortjeneste. Imidlertid deler vi eller på annen måte avslører personopplysningene dine til tredjeparter i samsvar med denne personvernerklæringen og vår [Merknad om informasjonskapsler](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#norwegian). For eksempel samarbeider vi med tredjeparter for å distribuere våre produkter, gi deg teknisk assistanse, bruke analyseverktøy og -funksjoner på nettstedet og delta i markedsføring og salg av våre produkter og tjenester. Slike aktiviteter kan innebære utlevering av personopplysningene dine til tredjepart og kan betraktes som et "salg" av data under visse (men ikke alle) lover om databeskyttelse.
* Du har rett til å **klage** til en databeskyttelsesmyndighet som er ansvarlig for å overvåke overholdelse av databeskyttelsesloven i din jurisdiksjon om vår innsamling og bruk av personopplysningene dine hvis du mener at behandlingen av personopplysningene dine ikke er i samsvar med databeskyttelsesloven. For eksempel har personer i EØS rett til å inngi en klage til den kompetente datatilsynsmyndigheten. Det finnes en liste over slike myndigheter på: [https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/board/members\_en](https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/board/members_en). Vi vil imidlertid sette pris på muligheten til å løse dine bekymringer, så ikke nøl med å ta kontakt med oss hvis det er noe du vil klage på. Vi vil ikke diskriminere enkeltpersoner for å utøve sine personvernrettigheter.

Vi vil tilrettelegge utøvelsen av rettighetene som gjelder for deg i samsvar med gjeldende lov. Selv om personopplysningene dine ikke er gitt beskyttelse i henhold til eller på annen måte er underlagt en databeskyttelseslov, kan vi imidlertid søke å imøtekomme enhver forespørsel du måtte ha om våre databehandlingsaktiviteter. Hvis du har spørsmål om dine rettigheter eller ønsker å utøve dine rettigheter, kan du kontakte oss på [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com) eller sende personvernspørsmål via vårt interaktive webskjema på følgende lenke:

**Opplysninger fra barn**

Nettstedene våre er ikke rettet mot, og skal ikke brukes av, barn under seksten (16) år, og vi samler inn, bruker eller selger ikke bevisst informasjon fra slike personer. Hvis du er mindreårig i henhold til lovene i ditt land, må du ikke sende inn personopplysninger via våre nettsteder.

**Lenker til andre nettsteder**

Nettstedene våre kan inneholde lenker til tredjeparters nettsteder, produkter og tjenester. Vi har ikke noe erstatningsansvar eller annet ansvar for disse nettstedene, produktene og tjenestene, deres retningslinjer, eller deres samling eller annen behandling av dine personlige opplysninger. Fremgangsmåten til disse tredjepartene styres av deres egne personvernregler. Vi oppfordrer deg til å lære om personvernreglene til disse tredjepartene.

**Kontakt oss**

Hvis du har spørsmål om denne personvernerklæringen eller om vår håndtering av personopplysninger om deg, hvis du ønsker å levere en klage, eller hvis du ønsker å kontakte personvernombudet vårt, kan du kontakte oss via kontaktinformasjonen angitt nedenfor. Vi vil behandle spørsmålet ditt raskt og prøve å finne en tilfredsstillende løsning.

Interaktivt webskjema:  

E-post:  

Mailing Adresse:  
Honeywell Privacy  
4D5  
115 Tabor Road  
Morris Plains, NJ 07950

Grønt nummer:  

**Endringer i denne personvernerklæringen**

Vi kan av og til oppdatere personvernerklæringen. Når vi gjør det, vil vi revidere "sist oppdatert"-datoen øverst i personvernerklæringen og ta ytterligere skritt som kan være påkrevd i henhold til loven.

**Sist oppdatert 11. juni 2021**

**Ostatnia aktualizacja: 11 czerwca 2021 r.**

**Wprowadzenie**

Honeywell International Inc. („**Honeywell**”, „**nasz**”, “**nas**” lub „**my**”) jest „administratorem danych” osobowych, które gromadzimy na temat użytkownika podczas jego odwiedzin w naszych witrynach internetowych lub korzystania z nich bądź korzystania z produktów, usług i aplikacji powiązanych z niniejszym Oświadczeniem o ochronie prywatności (łącznie nasze „**Witryny**”). W tym Oświadczeniu o ochronie prywatności wyjaśniono, w jaki sposób gromadzimy, udostępniamy i wykorzystujemy zebrane w ten sposób dane osobowe i w jaki sposób użytkownik może korzystać ze swoich praw do ochrony prywatności.

Podczas interakcji z użytkownikiem możemy również przekazywać mu dodatkowe informacje dotyczące ochrony prywatności o określonych działaniach związanych z przetwarzaniem lub zaoferować dodatkowe możliwości wyboru sposobu przetwarzania danych osobowych przez firmę Honeywell w danym momencie.

Należy kliknąć jedno z łączy poniżej w celu przejścia do interesującej użytkownika sekcji:

**Gromadzenie danych**

* **Dane gromadzone bezpośrednio od użytkownika**. Możemy prosić użytkownika o udostępnienie danych osobowych w celu wykonania żądanej usługi lub przeprowadzenia żądanej transakcji. Użytkownik może również udostępniać nam niektóre dane osobowe, kiedy kontaktuje się z nami lub angażuje się w interakcję z nami w inny sposób (np. pisząc komentarz, przesyłając zapytanie lub zgłoszenie do działu pomocy technicznej, odwiedzając witrynę) bądź rejestruje konto w celu korzystania z naszych Witryn. Te dane osobowe mogą obejmować:
    * **dane tożsamości,** takie jak imię i nazwisko, stanowisko, nazwa firmy/organizacji, adres e-mail, numery telefonu i adres pocztowy (zawierający nazwę ulicy, miasto, województwo, kod pocztowy i/lub kraj);
    * **dane rejestracyjne** przekazane przez użytkownika podczas rejestracji konta w celu korzystania z naszych Witryn, w tym nazwy użytkownika i hasła;
    * **dane rekrutacyjne,** w tym informacje przekazywane w związku z podaniem lub zapytaniem o pracę (zgodnie z poniższym opisem);
    * **dane kontaktowe firmy,** takie jak informacje dotyczące innych pracowników, właścicieli, dyrektorów, członków zarządu lub wykonawców innej organizacji (np. firmy, spółki, spółki osobowej, jednoosobowej działalności gospodarczej, organizacji non-profit lub agencji rządowej);
    * **dane marketingowe i komunikacyjne,** w tym preferencje marketingowe i subskrypcje naszych publikacji;
    * **informacje finansowe,** w tym dane karty kredytowej lub innego rachunku finansowego, umożliwiające ułatwianie użytkownikowi dokonywania zakupu produktów i usług firmy, które mogą być dostępne w naszych Witrynach;
    * **dane dotyczące kontroli eksportu,** takie jak narodowość, obywatelstwo i kraj zamieszkania, które pozwalają nam ustalić, czy zgodnie z przepisami dotyczącymi kontroli eksportu użytkownik może otrzymywać informacje o niektórych technologiach;
    * **dane transakcji,** w tym zapytania o nasze produkty i usługi oraz zamówienia na nie, a także dane płatności na rzecz i od użytkownika, łącznie z historią zamówień i informacjami potrzebnymi do umożliwienia transakcji płatniczych;
    * **informacje o rejestracji udziału w określonych wydarzeniach,** w tym informacje podane przez użytkownika przy wypełnianiu formularzy e-rejestracji; oraz
    * **opinie użytkownika,** co obejmuje ankiety, zalecenia lub jego inne opinie dotyczące naszych Witryn, a także ogólnie oferowane przez nas produkty i usługi.

Jeśli użytkownik nie dostarczy nam wymaganych informacji, świadczenie na jego rzecz żądanej usługi lub zrealizowanie danej transakcji może być niemożliwe.

* **Informacje, które gromadzimy automatycznie o użytkowniku**. Gromadzimy pewne informacje o wizycie użytkownika w naszych Witrynach za pomocą plików cookie i podobnych technologii śledzenia. Zawsze będziemy przestrzegać wszelkich praw użytkownika, które mogą nam to uniemożliwiać. Dane gromadzone w ten sposób obejmują:
    * **dane dotyczące użytkowania,** w tym informacje na temat sposobu korzystania przez użytkownika z naszych Witryn i przeglądanych stron, a także liczby przesłanych bajtów, klikniętych łączy, wyświetlonych materiałów, daty i godziny wizyty w danej Witrynie, witryny internetowej, z której uzyskano dostęp do jednej z naszych Witryn, oraz innych działań podjętych w obrębie tych Witryn; oraz
    * **dane techniczne,** takie jak adres IP (Internet Protocol), typ i możliwości przeglądarki oraz język i system operacyjny.

Informacje na temat plików cookie i innych podobnych technologii śledzenia używanych w naszych Witrynach można znaleźć w naszych [Informacjach o plikach cookie](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#polish).

* **Informacje o geolokalizacji**. W niektórych Witrynach mogą być gromadzone w czasie rzeczywistym precyzyjne informacje o lokalizacji (geolokalizacji) urządzenia mobilnego użytkownika po uzyskaniu jego zgody. Informacje te będą wykorzystywane wyłącznie w celu ułatwienia użytkownikowi korzystania z Witryn, w tym przez naszych usługodawców, którzy mogą przetwarzać te dane w związku ze świadczeniem usług w naszym imieniu. Jeśli użytkownik udzieli wspomnianej zgody, może ją zmienić, zarządzając preferencjami usług lokalizacyjnych w ustawieniach urządzenia mobilnego.
* **Informacje zebrane od osób trzecich**. Zgodnie z obowiązującym prawem możemy gromadzić dane osobowe użytkownika od stron trzecich, takich jak witryny i aplikacje mediów społecznościowych, i łączyć je z informacjami, które już mamy, aby ulepszać nasze Witryny i dostosowywać je do preferencji użytkownika, a także w innych celach określonych w niniejszym Oświadczeniu o ochronie prywatności. Możemy również gromadzić dane kontaktowe firmy użytkownika od jego pracodawcy lub innych stron trzecich w celu ułatwienia prowadzenia tradycyjnej działalności gospodarczej i spraw administracyjnych o podobnym charakterze bądź angażowania się w nie w inny sposób.

**Wykorzystywanie danych**

Możemy wykorzystywać dane osobowe zgromadzone za pośrednictwem naszych Witryn lub podczas kontaktu użytkownika z nami w celach obejmujących:

* **Dane kontaktowe firmy**. Honeywell gromadzi i wykorzystuje dane kontaktowe firmy do komunikacji lub przeprowadzania transakcji, w tym w celu przeprowadzenia analizy due diligence w odniesieniu do produktu lub usługi bądź ich dostarczania lub uzyskania. Honeywell może na przykład gromadzić i wykorzystywać dane kontaktowe firmy w celu umożliwienia realizacji zamówień, umów, gwarancji, konserwacji i funkcji biznesowych o podobnym charakterze oraz zarządzania nimi, a także w celach analizy i windykacji kredytowej oraz wsparcia przestrzegania naszych wewnętrznych wymagań dotyczących zgodności z przepisami i wymogów prawnych oraz (jeśli to konieczne) obrony naszych interesów i roszczeń.
* **Usługi i transakcje**. Możemy używać danych osobowych użytkownika w celu dostarczania mu żądanych usług oraz realizacji żądanych transakcji, w tym w celu dostarczania informacji na temat produktów i usług firmy, które użytkownik zakupił lub z których korzysta w jakikolwiek inny sposób, a także rejestracji zakupionych produktów, przetwarzania zamówień, obsługi roszczeń gwarancyjnych, wymiany instrukcji obsługi produktów, odpowiadania na zgłoszenia przesłane do działu obsługi klienta oraz ułatwiania procesu korzystania z naszych Witryn.
* **Zarządzanie naszą działalnością i Witrynami oraz ich ochrona**. Możemy wykorzystywać dane osobowe użytkownika w celu zarządzania naszą działalnością i Witrynami oraz ich ochrony, w tym rozwiązywania problemów, konserwacji systemu, udzielania wsparcia, raportowania i hostingu danych.
* **Usprawnianie działalności oraz doskonalenie Witryn, produktów i usług**. Możemy wykorzystywać dane osobowe użytkownika do przeprowadzania analiz biznesowych lub w innych celach służących usprawnieniu naszej działalności oraz doskonaleniu Witryn, produktów i usług (w tym nowych produktów i usług), na przykład poprzez dostosowanie Witryn do indywidualnych preferencji lub zainteresowań użytkownika.
* **Marketing**. Zgodnie z obowiązującymi przepisami i regulacjami możemy wykorzystywać dane osobowe użytkownika w celu informowania go o produktach i usługach, którymi może być zainteresowany, oraz komunikowania się z nim w jakikolwiek inny sposób w sprawie naszych ofert, wydarzeń, aktualności, ankiet, ofert specjalnych i powiązanych tematów. Użytkownik może w dowolnym momencie bezpłatnie zrezygnować z otrzymywania wysyłanych pocztą e-mail materiałów marketingowych, klikając łącze rezygnacji z subskrypcji zamieszczone w otrzymanych od nas pocztą e-mail materiałach marketingowych lub kontaktując się z nami za pomocą informacji kontaktowych podanych w tym Oświadczeniu o ochronie prywatności. W zależności od kraju zamieszkania użytkownik może również zrezygnować z otrzymywania innych typów materiałów marketingowych; w celu uzyskania dalszych informacji prosimy o kontakt z nami za pomocą danych kontaktowych podanych w Oświadczeniu o ochronie prywatności. W niektórych jurysdykcjach osoby fizyczne (np. mieszkańcy Kalifornii) mają prawo żądać niektórych informacji dotyczących ujawniania danych osobowych osobom trzecim do celów ich marketingu bezpośredniego. Aby uzyskać więcej informacji na temat naszych praktyk w zakresie ujawniania danych w celach marketingowych, prosimy o kontakt z nami zgodnie z poniższymi instrukcjami.
* **Reklama oparta na zainteresowaniach**. Zbieramy dane o działaniach online użytkownika i ustalamy jego zainteresowania, aby móc mu udostępniać najbardziej odpowiednie dla niego reklamy. Użytkownik może zrezygnować z otrzymywania od firmy Honeywell reklam opartych na zainteresowaniach, jak opisano w naszych [Informacjach o plikach cookie](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#polish).
* **Programy zachęt finansowych i programy lojalnościowe**. Gromadzimy i wykorzystujemy dane osobowe w celu prowadzenia programów zachęt finansowych i programów lojalnościowych oraz zarządzania nimi. Wykorzystujemy dane osobowe podawane w tych programach, aby oferować wyjątkowe nagrody, śledzić status programu i umożliwiać wymianę punktów w ramach programów na produkty, materiały promocyjne, warsztaty szkoleniowe i inne elementy. W zakresie dozwolonym przez prawo możemy również wykorzystywać wszelkie dane osobowe podane przez użytkownika w kontekście programu zachęt finansowych w jakimkolwiek innym celu określonym w niniejszym Oświadczeniu o ochronie prywatności. Prosimy o zapoznanie się z warunkami każdego programu zachęt finansowych, w którym użytkownik chce się zarejestrować lub uczestniczyć, ponieważ takie warunki mogą być ściśle dostosowane do danego programu. Jeśli użytkownik wyrazi zgodę na udział w takich programach, może ją wycofać w każdej chwili, kontaktując się z nami za pomocą danych kontaktowych podanych na końcu tego Oświadczenia o ochronie prywatności lub zgodnie z instrukcjami podanymi w warunkach danego programu.
* **Podania o pracę**. W związku z podaniem lub zapytaniem o pracę użytkownik może przekazać nam informacje o sobie, takie jak życiorys (CV), referencje zawodowe, informacje na temat wykształcenia i historii zatrudnienia oraz szkoleń zawodowych i certyfikatów. My i członkowie naszej grupy możemy wykorzystywać te informacje w celu rozpatrywania podań o pracę, weryfikacji historii zatrudnienia i kwalifikowania się użytkownika do zatrudnienia, a także w inny sposób określony w każdym odrębnym oświadczeniu o ochronie prywatności lub innych informacjach udostępnionych w związku z podaniem użytkownika. Możemy korzystać z usług osoby trzeciej (np. agencji rekrutacyjnej) lub platformy mediów społecznościowych w celu pozyskiwania, gromadzenia i przechowywania podań o pracę. Więcej informacji można uzyskać w naszym [Oświadczeniu o ochronie prywatności dla kandydatów do pracy](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/applicant-privacy-notice#polish).
* **Badania i analizy**. Możemy wykorzystywać dane osobowe użytkownika do prowadzenia badań i analiz, które pomogą nam analizować jego preferencje zakupowe, identyfikować produkty i usługi najlepiej odpowiadające jego wymaganiom oraz mierzyć skuteczność wyświetlanych mu reklam.
* **Egzekwowanie**. Możemy wykorzystywać zebrane przez nas dane osobowe w celach wykrywania oszustw, naruszeń praw własności intelektualnej i postanowień naszych warunków, naruszeń prawa lub innych przypadków niewłaściwego korzystania z naszych Witryn, a także zapobiegania takim oszustwom, naruszeniom i niewłaściwemu korzystaniu oraz reagowania na nie.

W zakresie dozwolonym przez prawo możemy łączyć dane gromadzone za pośrednictwem naszych Witryn z naszymi innymi danymi o użytkowniku (takimi jak informacje o korzystaniu przez niego z naszych produktów i usług) w celu zapewnienia mu lepszej i bardziej spójnej obsługi podczas interakcji z nami lub w innych celach określonych w tym Oświadczeniu o ochronie prywatności.

**Podstawa prawna przetwarzania danych**

Jeśli jest to wymagane przez prawo, upewniamy się, że istnieje podstawa prawna przetwarzania danych osobowych użytkownika. W większości przypadków nasza podstawa prawna będzie zależeć od danych osobowych i konkretnego kontekstu, w jakim je gromadzimy.

* **Umowa**: przetwarzanie jest niezbędne w celu świadczenia usług, które realizujemy na rzecz użytkownika, lub w celu podjęcia kroków (na żądanie użytkownika) przed wykonaniem takich usług i przewidując takie wykonanie;
* **Obowiązek prawny**: przetwarzanie danych jest konieczne w celu wypełnienia naszych zobowiązań prawnych, w tym przestrzegania obowiązujących przepisów i regulacji, nakazów rządowych i quasi-rządowych oraz zarządzeń sądu lub wezwań sądowych;
* **Zgoda**: przetwarzanie odbywa się w oparciu o wyrażoną przez użytkownika zgodę na przetwarzanie jego danych osobowych w jednym lub kilku określonych celach (np. marketingowych);
* **Uzasadnione interesy**: przetwarzanie jest konieczne do realizacji naszych uzasadnionych interesów, na przykład w celu rozwoju i doskonalenia naszych Witryn, produktów i/lub usług na rzecz naszych klientów; lub
* **Żywotne interesy**: przetwarzanie jest niezbędne do ochrony żywotnych interesów użytkownika (na przykład ze względu na zdrowie i bezpieczeństwo, jeśli użytkownik uczestniczy w spotkaniu w lokalizacji firmy Honeywell).

W razie jakichkolwiek pytań lub potrzeby uzyskania dalszych informacji na temat podstawy prawnej zbierania i wykorzystywania przez nas danych osobowych prosimy o wysłanie wiadomości e-mail na adres: [HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com)

**Anonimizacja danych**

Zgodnie z obowiązującymi przepisami możemy przeprowadzić anonimizację danych osobowych użytkownika, aby nie mogły być już wykorzystywane do celów jego identyfikacji. Zanonimizowane dane nie są uznawane za dane osobowe i dlatego nie podlegają niniejszemu Oświadczeniu o ochronie prywatności. Możemy gromadzić, wykorzystywać, agregować i udostępniać zanonimizowane dane w dowolnym celu.

**Czas przechowywania danych**

Okres przechowywania danych osobowych użytkownika różni się w zależności od celu przetwarzania. Na przykład przechowujemy dane osobowe niezbędne do dostarczania produktów i świadczenia usług lub ułatwiania realizowania transakcji żądanych przez użytkownika tak długo, jak będzie on klientem firmy Honeywell, lub jeśli złoży on podanie o pracę za pośrednictwem naszych Witryn, zachowamy informacje na temat tego podania przez czas określony w informacji o ochronie prywatności udostępnionej mu w związku z podaniem lub zgodnie z innymi wymogami prawa. We wszystkich innych przypadkach przechowujemy dane osobowe użytkownika tak długo, jak to jest konieczne do realizacji celów określonych w tym Oświadczeniu o ochronie prywatności. Po tym czasie są one anonimizowane (jeśli jest to dozwolone przez obowiązujące prawo), usuwane lub niszczone.

**Ujawnianie danych**

Możemy udostępniać dane osobowe użytkownika wybranym osobom trzecim zgodnie z obowiązującym prawem, w tym w sposób opisany poniżej:

* **Spółki wchodzące w skład naszej grupy**. Możemy udostępniać dane osobowe użytkownika naszym podmiotom stowarzyszonym i firmom należącym do grupy, gdy będzie to w uzasadnionym zakresie niezbędne do celów określonych w tym Oświadczeniu o ochronie prywatności.
* **Usługodawcy**. Możemy udostępniać dane osobowe użytkownika firmom, którym zleciliśmy świadczenie w naszym imieniu takich usług, jak hosting witryn internetowych, przeprowadzanie ankiet, przetwarzanie transakcji, analiza naszych Witryn i przeprowadzanie analiz w celu usprawnienia naszej działalności oraz udoskonalenia Witryn, produktów i usług. Wymagamy od tych usługodawców ochrony poufności danych osobowych użytkownika.
* **Dystrybutorzy i inni zaufani partnerzy biznesowi**. Możemy udostępniać dane osobowe użytkownika osobom trzecim zajmującym się dystrybucją naszych produktów i innym zaufanym partnerom biznesowym w celu umożliwienia im wysyłania materiałów marketingowych do użytkownika. Ten proces udostępniania danych osobowych w celach marketingowych będzie odbywać się zgodnie z obowiązującymi przepisami i regulacjami prawnymi.
* **Ujawnianie danych w związku z transakcjami**. W związku z niektórymi transakcjami możemy ujawniać niektóre lub wszystkie dane osobowe użytkownika instytucjom finansowym, podmiotom rządowym oraz firmom wysyłkowym i poczcie, które biorą udział w realizacji transakcji.
* **Ujawnianie danych związane z transakcjami przejęcia lub zbycia**. W niektórych okolicznościach ze względów strategicznych lub innych powodów biznesowych firma Honeywell może podjąć decyzję o sprzedaży, zakupie, zbyciu, fuzji lub innej reorganizacji działalności w niektórych krajach. Możemy ujawniać przechowywane przez nas dane użytkownika w uzasadnionym zakresie koniecznym do prowadzenia negocjacji lub realizacji fuzji, przejęcia, zbycia lub sprzedaży całości bądź części aktywów firmy Honeywell.
* **Ujawnianie danych z innych powodów**. Możemy ujawniać dane osobowe, gdy wymaga tego prawo lub w dobrej wierze, że takie działanie jest niezbędne w celu przestrzegania wymogów prawnych lub prowadzonych wobec nas procesów prawnych, w celu ochrony i obrony naszych praw lub mienia, bądź w szczególnych okolicznościach w celu ochrony osobistego bezpieczeństwa dowolnej osoby.

**Międzynarodowe transfery danych**

Honeywell jest firmą globalną i dane osobowe użytkownika mogą być przekazywane do różnych krajów na całym świecie, takich jak Stany Zjednoczone, Meksyk i Indie, a także przechowywane lub wykorzystywane w takich krajach zgodnie z obowiązującym prawem. Oznacza to, że gdy gromadzimy dane osobowe użytkownika, mogą być one przetwarzane w krajach, w których mogą obowiązywać przepisy o ochronie danych różniące się od przepisów kraju użytkownika. Firma Honeywell zawsze podejmie jednak uzasadnione kroki w celu ochrony prywatności użytkownika i zapewnienia mu poziomu ochrony danych osobowych porównywalnego z poziomem ochrony w kraju jego zamieszkania, co obejmuje wdrożenie standardowych klauzul umownych Komisji Europejskiej. Aby uzyskać więcej informacji na temat odpowiednich zabezpieczeń stosowanych w celu ochrony danych osobowych, prosimy o skontaktowanie się z nami pod adresem: [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com).

**Bezpieczeństwo**

Zobowiązujemy się do ochrony bezpieczeństwa danych osobowych użytkowników. Stosujemy środki techniczne i organizacyjne, aby zapewnić poziom bezpieczeństwa odpowiedni do ryzyka przetwarzania danych osobowych użytkownika. Aby uzyskać więcej informacji na temat ochrony danych osobowych przez firmę Honeywell, prosimy o skontaktowanie się z nami pod adresem [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com)

**Prawa użytkownika**

W zależności od obowiązujących przepisów użytkownik może mieć określone prawa w odniesieniu do swoich danych osobowych.

* Użytkownik może mieć prawo **dostępu do swoich danych osobowych, ich poprawiania lub aktualizowania** lub **żądania ich usunięcia.**
* Użytkownik może **wyrazić sprzeciw** wobec przetwarzania swoich danych osobowych, zażądać od nas **ograniczenia** przetwarzania jego danych osobowych lub ich **przeniesienia**.
* Użytkownik może mieć prawo **do tego, aby nie podejmowano dotyczącej go decyzji w oparciu o wyłącznie zautomatyzowane przetwarzanie, w tym profilowanie,** jeśli taka decyzja wywołuje skutki prawne dotyczące użytkownika lub znacząco na niego wpływa.
* Podobnie, jeśli dane użytkownika zostały zebrane i są przetwarzane przez nas za jego zgodą, wówczas **może on w każdej chwili wycofać swoją zgodę**. Wycofanie zgody nie będzie miało wpływu na zgodność z prawem przetwarzania prowadzonego wcześniej ani nie wpłynie na przetwarzanie danych osobowych użytkownika w oparciu o zgodne z prawem podstawy przetwarzania inne niż zgoda.
* Użytkownik może mieć prawo do **rezygnacji ze sprzedaży swoich danych osobowych**. Firma Honeywell nie sprzedaje danych osobowych użytkowników osobom trzecim w celach zarobkowych. Udostępniamy jednak lub w inny sposób ujawniamy dane osobowe użytkowników osobom trzecim zgodnie z tym Oświadczeniem o ochronie prywatności i [Informacjami o plikach cookie](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#polish). Na przykład współpracujemy z osobami trzecimi w celu dystrybucji naszych produktów, świadczenia użytkownikom pomocy technicznej, obsługi narzędzi i funkcji analitycznych w witrynie internetowej, a także prowadzenia marketingu i sprzedaży naszych produktów i usług. Takie działania mogą wiązać się z ujawnianiem danych osobowych użytkownika osobom trzecim i zgodnie z niektórymi (ale nie wszystkimi) przepisami o ochronie danych mogą być uznawane za „sprzedaż” danych.
* Użytkownik ma prawo **złożyć skargę** do organu ds. ochrony danych odpowiedzialnego za nadzór nad przestrzeganiem przepisów o ochronie danych w jurysdykcji użytkownika w związku z gromadzeniem i wykorzystywaniem przez nas jego danych osobowych, jeśli uzna, że nie jest ono zgodne z przepisami o ochronie danych. Na przykład osoby fizyczne w EOG mają prawo złożyć skargę do właściwego organu ds. ochrony danych; wykaz takich organów jest dostępny pod adresem: [https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/board/members\_en](https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/board/members_en). Mamy jednak nadzieję, że zanim to nastąpi, użytkownik da nam szansę na rozwiązanie wszelkich zgłoszonych przez niego problemów, dlatego prosimy o kontakt w sprawie jakiejkolwiek ewentualnej skargi. Nie będziemy dyskryminować żadnych osób fizycznych w związku z korzystaniem przez nie z ich praw do ochrony danych.

Ułatwimy użytkownikowi korzystanie z praw, które mają do niego zastosowanie zgodnie z obowiązującym prawem. Jednak nawet jeśli dane osobowe użytkownika nie są chronione na mocy przepisów o ochronie danych lub nie podlegają im z innej przyczyny, możemy postarać się zrealizować wszelkie żądania lub zapytania, jakie użytkownik może mieć w związku z naszymi działaniami dotyczącymi przetwarzania danych. W razie pytań dotyczących praw użytkownika lub chęci ich wykonania prosimy o skontaktowanie się z nami pod adresem [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.co](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com)m lub o przesłanie pytań dotyczących prywatności za pośrednictwem naszego interaktywnego formularza online dostępnego po kliknięciu poniższego łącza:

**Dane dzieci**

Nasze Witryny nie są przeznaczone dla dzieci poniżej szesnastego (16.) roku życia i nie powinny one z nich korzystać, a my świadomie nie gromadzimy, nie wykorzystujemy ani nie sprzedajemy danych takich osób. Jeśli użytkownik jest osobą niepełnoletnią zgodnie z prawem obowiązującym w jego kraju, prosimy o nieprzekazywanie żadnych danych osobowych za pośrednictwem naszych Witryn.

**Łącza do innych witryn internetowych**

Nasze Witryny mogą zawierać łącza do witryn internetowych, produktów i usług osób trzecich. Nie ponosimy żadnej odpowiedzialności za te witryny internetowe, produkty, usługi i obowiązujące w nich zasady ani za gromadzenie w nich lub przetwarzanie w inny sposób danych osobowych użytkownika. Praktyki tych osób trzecich podlegają ich własnym zasadom ochrony prywatności. Zachęcamy do zapoznania się z zasadami ochrony prywatności tych osób trzecich.

**Kontakt z nami**

W razie pytań dotyczących tego Oświadczenia o ochronie prywatności lub naszego postępowania z danymi osobowymi, chęci złożenia skargi lub skontaktowania się z naszym inspektorem ochrony danych należy skontaktować się z nami za pomocą podanych niżej danych kontaktowych. Niezwłocznie odniesiemy się do zgłoszonych kwestii i będziemy dążyć do pomyślnego rozstrzygnięcia sprawy.

Interaktywny formularz online:  

E-mail:  

Adres do korespondencji:  
Honeywell Privacy  
4D5  
115 Tabor Road  
Morris Plains, NJ 07950

Bezpłatna infolinia:  

**Zmiany tego Oświadczenia o ochronie prywatności**

To Oświadczenie o ochronie prywatności może być okresowo aktualizowane. W takim przypadku zmienimy „datę ostatniej aktualizacji” na górze Oświadczenia o ochronie prywatności i podejmiemy wszelkie dodatkowe kroki, jakie mogą być wymagane przez prawo.

**Ostatnia aktualizacja: 11 czerwca 2021 r.**

**Última atualização: 11 de junho de 2021**

**Introdução**

Honeywell International Inc. ("**Honeywell**", "**nosso(a)**" ou "**nós**") é o "controlador de dados" das informações pessoais que recolhemos sobre o utilizador ao visitar ou utilizar qualquer um dos nossos websites, ou utilizar produtos, serviços e aplicações que estão associados à presente Declaração de Privacidade (coletivamente, os nossos "**Sites**"). Esta Declaração de Privacidade explica como recolhemos, partilhamos e utilizamos as suas informações pessoais recolhidas desta forma e como pode exercer os seus direitos de privacidade.

Quando interagimos consigo, podemos também fornecer-lhe avisos de privacidade adicionais sobre atividades de processamento específicas ou fornecer-lhe escolhas adicionais sobre a forma como a Honeywell processa as suas informações pessoais nesse momento específico.

Clique numa das ligações abaixo para aceder à secção que lhe interessa:

**A nossa recolha de informações**

* **Informações recolhidas diretamente do utilizador**. Poderemos pedir-lhe informações pessoais para fornecermos um serviço ou realizarmos uma transação que tenha solicitado. Também poderá fornecer-nos informações pessoais quando nos contacta ou interage connosco (por ex.: através de um comentário, uma consulta ou um pedido de suporte ao cliente, visitantes do site) ou registar uma conta para utilizar os nossos Sites. Estas informações pessoais podem incluir:
    * **Dados de identidade,** como o seu nome, cargo, nome da empresa/organização, endereço de e-mail, números de telefone e endereço físico (rua, cidade, localidade, distrito, código postal e/ou país);
    * **Dados de registo,** fornecidos por si quando regista uma conta para utilizar os nossos Sites, incluindo nomes de utilizador e palavras-passe;
    * **Dados de recrutamento,** incluindo informações fornecidas em associação com uma candidatura a emprego ou consulta (conforme descrito abaixo);
    * **Dados de contacto profissional,** como informações relacionadas com outros funcionários, proprietários, diretores, responsáveis ou contratantes de uma organização externa (por exemplo, empresa, sociedade, parceria, sociedade unipessoal, sem fins lucrativos ou agência governamental).
    * **Dados de marketing e comunicações,** incluindo preferências de marketing e subscrições das nossas publicações;
    * **Informações financeiras,** incluindo informações sobre cartões de crédito ou outras contas financeiras, com a finalidade de nos permitir proporcionar a compra de produtos e serviços da Empresa que poderão estar disponíveis nos nossos Sites;
    * **Informações de controlo de exportações,** como a sua nacionalidade, cidadania e país de residência, que nos permitem determinar a sua elegibilidade para receber informações sobre determinadas tecnologias, de acordo com os regulamentos de controlo de exportações;
    * **Dados de transações,** incluindo consultas e encomendas dos nossos produtos e serviços e detalhes de pagamento, incluindo histórico de ordens de compra e informações necessárias para facilitar as transações de pagamento;
    * **Informações de registo de eventos,** incluindo informações fornecidas por si durante o preenchimento de formulários de registo eletrónicos; e
    * **Os seus comentários,** incluindo inquéritos, recomendações ou outros comentários sobre os nossos Sites e os nossos produtos e serviços, de uma forma geral.

Se não nos fornecer as informações pedidas, poderemos não ser capazes de lhe proporcionar o serviço pedido ou concluir a transação.

* **Informações recolhidas automaticamente sobre o utilizador**. Recolhemos certas informações sobre a sua visita aos nossos Sites utilizando cookies e tecnologias de rastreio semelhantes. Respeitaremos sempre os direitos legais que o utilizador possa ter de nos impedir de fazê-lo. Os dados recolhidos desta forma incluem:
    * **Dados de utilização,** incluindo informações sobre a forma como utiliza os nossos Sites, as páginas visualizadas, o número de bytes transferidos, as ligações clicadas, os materiais acedidos, a data e hora de acesso ao Site, o site a partir do qual acedeu a um dos nossos Sites e outras ações realizadas nos Sites; e
    * **Dados técnicos,** como o seu endereço IP, tipo de browser, capacidades, idioma e sistema operativo.

Para obter informações sobre os cookies e outras tecnologias de rastreio semelhantes que utilizamos nos nossos Sites, consulte o nosso [Aviso de Cookies.](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#portuguese)

* **Informações de localização geográfica**. Para Sites específicos, com o seu consentimento, poderemos recolher a localização exata e em tempo real (ou seja, a localização geográfica) do seu dispositivo móvel. Estas informações serão utilizadas apenas para facilitar a sua utilização dos Sites, incluindo pelos nossos fornecedores de serviços, que poderão processar estas informações em associação com a prestação dos serviços em nosso nome. Se concedido, pode ajustar esta autorização gerindo as preferências dos Serviços de Localização através das definições do dispositivo móvel.
* **Informações recolhidas a partir de terceiros**. De acordo com a legislação aplicável, poderemos recolher informações pessoais suas a partir de terceiros, como aplicações e sites de redes sociais, que poderemos combinar com informações que já possuímos sobre si para nos ajudar a melhorar e personalizar os nossos Sites de acordo com as suas preferências e para outras finalidades dispostas na presente Declaração de Privacidade. Poderemos também recolher informações de contacto profissional do seu empregador ou de terceiros para facilitar ou participar em atividades comerciais tradicionais e assuntos administrativos semelhantes.

**A nossa utilização das informações**

Poderemos utilizar as informações pessoais recolhidas através dos nossos Sites ou quando nos contactar para finalidades que incluem:

* **Dados de contacto profissional**. A Honeywell recolhe e utiliza os dados de contacto profissional para efetuar comunicações ou transações, incluindo para efetuar a devida diligência relativamente a um produto ou serviço, ou para fornecer ou receber um produto ou serviço. Por exemplo, a Honeywell poderá recolher e utilizar estes dados de contacto profissional para facilitar e gerir encomendas, contratos, garantias, manutenção e funções profissionais semelhantes, para efeitos de análise e recolha de crédito, de modo a ajudar na nossa própria conformidade interna e requisitos legais, e (se necessário) para defender os nossos interesses e reivindicações.
* **Serviços e transações**. Poderemos utilizar as suas informações pessoais para lhe proporcionar serviços ou realizar transações que tenha solicitado, incluindo, sem limitações, o fornecimento de informações sobre produtos ou serviços da Empresa que tenha adquirido ou utilizado por qualquer outra forma, o registo de produtos adquiridos, o processamento de encomendas de produtos, o processamento de garantias, a substituição de manuais de produtos, a resposta a pedidos de suporte ao cliente e a utilização dos nossos Sites.
* **Administrar e proteger o nosso negócio e os nossos Sites**. Poderemos utilizar as suas informações pessoais para administrar e proteger o nosso negócio e os nossos Sites, incluindo tarefas de resolução de problemas, manutenção do sistema, suporte, geração de relatórios e alojamento de dados.
* **Melhorar o nosso negócio e os nossos Sites, produtos e serviços**. Poderemos utilizar as suas informações pessoais para realizar análises de negócio ou para outros fins que nos ajudem a desenvolver e melhorar a qualidade do nosso negócio e dos nossos Sites, produtos e serviços (incluindo produtos e serviços novos); por exemplo, personalizando os nossos Sites de acordo com as suas preferências ou interesses específicos.
* **Marketing**. De acordo com as leis e regulamentos aplicáveis, podemos utilizar as suas informações pessoais para informá-lo sobre produtos ou serviços que possam ser do seu interesse e para comunicar consigo sobre ofertas, eventos e notícias, pesquisas, ofertas especiais e tópicos relacionados. Pode cancelar a subscrição das comunicações de marketing enviadas por e-mail a qualquer momento, gratuitamente, através da ligação "Anular a subscrição" existente nos materiais de marketing por e-mail que recebe de nós ou contactando-nos utilizando as informações de contacto listadas na presente Declaração de Privacidade. Dependendo do seu país de residência, também poderá desativar outros tipos de comunicações de marketing; contacte-nos utilizando as informações de contacto listadas na Declaração de Privacidade para obter mais informações. Algumas jurisdições fornecem a pessoas (por exemplo, residentes na Califórnia) o direito de solicitar determinadas informações relativas à nossa divulgação de informações pessoais a terceiros para efeitos de marketing direto do terceiro. Para obter mais informações sobre as nossas práticas de divulgação de dados para efeitos de marketing, queira contactar-nos de acordo com as instruções indicadas abaixo.
* **Publicidade Baseada em Interesses**. Recolhemos dados sobre as suas atividades online e identificamos os seus interesses, para que possamos fornecer-lhe publicidade mais relevante. O utilizador pode optar por não receber publicidade baseada em interesses da Honeywell, conforme descrito no nosso [Aviso de Cookies](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#portuguese).
* **Programas de Fidelidade e Incentivos Financeiros**. Recolhemos e utilizamos informações pessoais para manter e administrar os nossos programas de fidelidade e incentivos financeiros. Utilizamos as informações pessoais que nos fornece nestes programas para proporcionar recompensas únicas, acompanhar o estado do programa e facilitar a troca de pontos do programa por produtos, materiais promocionais, workshops de formação e outros itens. Na extensão permitida por lei, podemos também utilizar quaisquer informações pessoais que nos forneça no contexto de um programa de incentivos financeiros para qualquer outro fim estabelecido na presente Declaração de Privacidade. Consulte os termos e condições de cada programa de incentivos financeiros no qual gostaria de registar-se ou participar, uma vez que esses termos e condições podem ser especificamente adaptados ao programa aplicável. Se consentir em participar nestes programas, poderá retirar esse consentimento em qualquer altura, ao contactar-nos utilizando os dados de contacto no final desta Declaração de Privacidade ou de acordo com as instruções estabelecidas nos termos e condições do programa aplicável.
* **Candidaturas de emprego**. Em associação a uma candidatura de emprego, poderá fornecer-nos informações sobre si, como um currículo, referências profissionais, informações sobre habilitações académicas e antecedentes profissionais e informações sobre formação profissional e certificações. Nós e membros do nosso grupo poderemos utilizar estas informações para efeitos de análise da candidatura, verificação de antecedentes e elegibilidade de emprego, e para outras finalidades dispostas numa declaração de privacidade separada ou noutro aviso disponibilizado em associação à sua candidatura. Poderemos utilizar um terceiro (por exemplo, recrutador de emprego) ou plataforma de rede social para solicitar, recolher e reter candidaturas de emprego. Para obter mais informações, leia o nosso [Aviso de Privacidade do Candidato](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/applicant-privacy-notice#portuguese).
* **Investigação e análise**. Podemos utilizar as suas informações pessoais para conduzir pesquisas e análises que nos ajudem a avaliar as suas preferências de compra, identificar os produtos e serviços que melhor atendam às suas necessidades e medir a eficácia da publicidade que lhe oferecemos.
* **Aplicação**. Poderemos utilizar as informações pessoais recolhidas para detetar, prevenir e reagir a fraude, violação propriedade intelectual, violação dos nossos termos e condições, violação da lei e outra utilização indevida dos nossos Sites.

Onde permitido por lei, poderemos combinar as informações recolhidas através dos nossos Sites com outras informações que tenhamos sobre si (como informações sobre a sua utilização dos nossos produtos e serviços) para lhe proporcionarmos uma experiência de cliente melhorada e consistente quando interage connosco para as finalidades estabelecidas na presente Declaração de Privacidade.

**A base jurídica pela qual processamos as informações**

Quando exigido por lei, garantiremos que existe uma base jurídica para o processamento das suas informações pessoais. Na maioria dos casos, a nossa base jurídica dependerá das informações pessoais em questão e do contexto específico em que as recolhermos.

* **Contrato**: o processamento é necessário para a execução dos serviços que lhe prestamos, ou para tomar medidas (a seu pedido) antes, em antecipação, da execução de tais serviços;
* **Obrigação legal**: o processamento é necessário para o cumprimento das nossas obrigações legais, incluindo o cumprimento das leis, regulamentações, pedidos governamentais e para-governamentais, ordem judicial ou intimação;
* **Consentimento**: o processamento é baseado no seu consentimento do processamento das suas informações pessoais para uma ou mais finalidades especificadas (por ex.: marketing);
* **Interesses legítimos**: o processamento é necessário para satisfazer os nossos interesses legítimos; por exemplo, para desenvolver e melhorar os nossos Sites, produtos e/ou serviços para o benefício dos nossos clientes; ou
* **Interesses vitais**: o processamento é necessário para proteger os seus interesses vitais (por exemplo, motivos de saúde e segurança se participar numa reunião numa localização da Honeywell).

Se tiver dúvidas ou necessitar de mais informações sobre a base jurídica pela qual recolhemos e utilizamos as suas informações pessoais, envie um e-mail para [HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com)

**Anonimização das informações**

De acordo com a legislação aplicável, poderemos anonimizar as suas informações pessoais para que estas não possam ser utilizadas para identificá-lo. As informações anonimizadas não são consideradas informações pessoais e, portanto, não estão sujeitas a esta Declaração de Privacidade. Podemos recolher, utilizar, agregar e partilhar informações anonimizadas para qualquer finalidade.

**Durante quanto tempo mantemos as informações**

O período durante o qual armazenamos as suas informações pessoais varia consoante a finalidade do processamento. Por exemplo, armazenamos as informações pessoais necessárias para lhe fornecer produtos e serviços ou para realizar transações que tenha solicitado enquanto cliente da Honeywell ou se submeter uma candidatura de emprego através dos nossos Sites, iremos reter os detalhes da candidatura conforme estabelecido na presente declaração de privacidade ou noutro aviso disponibilizado em associação à candidatura ou conforme exigido por lei. Em todos os outros casos, armazenamos as suas informações pessoais durante o período de tempo necessário para cumprir as finalidades descritas na presente Declaração de Privacidade, após o qual essas informações serão anonimizadas (quando permitido pela legislação aplicável), eliminadas ou destruídas.

**Divulgação de informações**

Poderemos partilhar as suas informações pessoais com terceiros selecionados, de acordo com a legislação aplicável, incluindo conforme disposto abaixo:

* **Empresas do nosso grupo**. Poderemos partilhar as suas informações pessoais com afiliadas e empresas do nosso grupo, conforme razoavelmente aceitável para as finalidades dispostas na presente Declaração de Privacidade.
* **Fornecedores de serviços**. Poderemos partilhar as suas informações pessoais com empresas que tenhamos contratado para o fornecimento de serviços em nosso nome, como o alojamento de sites, a realização de inquéritos, o processamento de transações, a análise dos nossos Sites e a realização de análise para o melhoramento da qualidade do nosso negócio e dos nossos Sites, produtos e serviços. Exigimos que estes fornecedores de serviços protejam a confidencialidade das suas informações pessoais.
* **Distribuidores e outros parceiros de negócio fidedignos**. Poderemos partilhar as suas informações pessoais com terceiros que distribuem os nossos produtos e outros parceiros de negócio fidedignos para finalidades que incluem permitir que estes terceiros lhe enviem comunicações de marketing. Esta partilha de informações pessoais para fins de marketing será realizada de acordo com as leis e regulamentos aplicáveis.
* **Divulgação associada a transações**. Em associação com determinadas transações, as suas informações pessoais podem ser total ou parcialmente divulgadas a instituições financeiras, entidades do Estado e empresas de transportes ou serviços postais envolvidos na transação.
* **Divulgações associadas a aquisições ou alienações**. Poderão surgir circunstâncias em que, por motivos estratégicos ou outros motivos de negócio, a Honeywell decida vender, comprar, alienar, fundir ou, por qualquer outra forma, reorganizar o negócio em alguns países. Podemos divulgar informações do utilizador na medida do razoavelmente necessário para proceder com a negociação ou conclusão de uma fusão, aquisição, alienação ou venda do total ou de uma parte dos bens da Honeywell.
* **Divulgação por outros motivos**. Poderemos divulgar Informações pessoais se tal for exigido ou autorizado por lei ou em crença de boa-fé de que tal ação é necessária para cumprir com requisitos ou processos legais impostos, para proteger e defender os nossos direitos ou propriedade ou, em circunstâncias urgentes, para proteger a segurança pessoal de qualquer indivíduo.

**Transferências internacionais**

A Honeywell é uma organização global e as suas informações pessoais podem ser transferidas para, mantidas, armazenadas ou utilizadas em várias localizações a nível mundial, tais como os EUA, o México e a Índia, de acordo com a lei aplicável. Isto significa que, quando recolhemos as suas informações pessoais, estas podem ser processadas em países que podem ter leis de proteção de dados diferentes das leis do seu país. No entanto, a Honeywell tomará sempre medidas razoáveis para proteger a sua privacidade e proporcionar um nível de proteção das informações pessoais que seja comparável à do seu país de residência, o que inclui a implementação das Cláusulas Contratuais Padrão da Comissão Europeia. Para obter mais informações sobre as salvaguardas adequadas em vigor para proteger as suas informações pessoais, contacte-nos em [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com).

**Segurança**

Estamos empenhados em proteger a segurança das suas informações pessoais. Utilizamos medidas técnicas e organizacionais para proporcionar um nível de segurança adequado ao risco de processamento das suas informações pessoais. Para obter mais informações sobre a forma como a Honeywell protege as suas informações pessoais, contacte-nos em [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com)

**Os seus direitos**

Dependendo da lei aplicável, poderá ter certos direitos no que diz respeito às suas informações pessoais.

* Pode ter o direito de **aceder, corrigir, atualizar** ou **solicitar a eliminação** das suas informações pessoais.
* Pode **opor-se** ao processamento das suas informações pessoais, solicitar-nos para **restringir** o processamento das suas informações pessoais ou solicitar a **portabilidade** das suas informações pessoais.
* Pode ter o direito **de não se tomar uma decisão sobre si que se baseie unicamente no processamento automatizado, incluindo a criação de perfis,** se essa decisão produzir efeitos legais sobre si ou o afetar significativamente.
* Da mesma forma, se tivermos recolhido e processado as suas informações pessoais com o seu consentimento, então **poderá retirar o seu consentimento em qualquer altura**. A revogação do seu consentimento não afetará a legalidade de qualquer processamento que tenhamos realizado antes da mesma, nem afetará o processamento das suas informações pessoais realizado com base em fundamentos de processamento legais além do consentimento.
* Pode ter o direito de **optar pela exclusão da venda das suas informações pessoais**. A Honeywell não vende as suas informações pessoais a terceiros com fins lucrativos. No entanto, partilhamos ou divulgamos as suas informações pessoais a terceiros, de acordo com a presente Declaração de Privacidade e o nosso [Aviso de Cookies](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#portuguese). Por exemplo, comprometemo-nos com terceiros para distribuir os nossos produtos, fornecer-lhe assistência técnica, operar ferramentas e funcionalidades analíticas do website, e envolver-nos no marketing e na venda dos nossos produtos e serviços. Tais atividades podem envolver a divulgação das suas informações pessoais a terceiros e podem ser consideradas uma "venda" de dados ao abrigo de certas (mas não todas) leis de proteção de dados.
* Tem o direito de **apresentar queixa** a uma autoridade de proteção de dados responsável pela supervisão do cumprimento da lei de proteção de dados na sua jurisdição sobre a nossa recolha e utilização das suas informações pessoais, se considerar que o nosso processamento das suas informações pessoais não cumpre a lei de proteção de dados. Por exemplo, os indivíduos no EEE têm o direito de apresentar uma queixa à Autoridade de Proteção de Dados competente, cuja lista pode ser consultada em: [https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/board/members\_en](https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/board/members_en). No entanto, gostaríamos que nos desse a oportunidade de resolver tais problemas. Portanto, não hesite em contactar-nos em relação a qualquer reclamação que possa ter. Não discriminaremos pessoas pelo exercício dos seus direitos de privacidade de dados.

Facilitaremos o exercício dos direitos que se aplicam a si, de acordo com a legislação aplicável. Contudo, mesmo que as suas informações pessoais não beneficiem de proteção ao abrigo de, ou de outra forma sujeitas a, uma lei de proteção de dados, poderemos procurar acomodar qualquer pedido ou inquérito que possa ter em relação às nossas atividades de processamento de dados. Se tiver quaisquer perguntas sobre os seus direitos, ou caso pretenda exercer os seus direitos, contacte-nos em [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com) ou submeta perguntas relacionadas com a privacidade através do nosso formulário Web interativo no seguinte link:

**Informações de menores**

Os nossos Sites não são dirigidos a, e não devem ser utilizados por, crianças menores de dezasseis (16) anos e não recolhemos, utilizamos ou vendemos intencionalmente informações de tais pessoas. Se for menor de idade, tal como entendido pela legislação do seu país, não submeta quaisquer informações pessoais através dos nossos Sites.

**Ligações para outros sites**

Os nossos Sites poderão conter ligações para sites, produtos e serviços de terceiros. Não temos qualquer responsabilidade relativamente a esses sites, produtos e serviços, às respetivas políticas, nem à recolha ou outro processamento das suas informações pessoais. As práticas destes terceiros são governadas por políticas de privacidade próprias. Encorajamo-lo a conhecer as políticas de privacidade desses terceiros.

**Contacte-nos**

Se tiver quaisquer perguntas relacionadas com a presente Declaração de Privacidade ou com o nosso processamento das suas informações pessoais, ou se quiser apresentar uma reclamação ou contactar o nosso Responsável pela Proteção de Dados, contacte-nos utilizando as informações listadas abaixo. Daremos toda a atenção à sua questão para obtermos uma resolução satisfatória.

Formulário Web interativo:  

E-mail:  

Endereço postal:  
Honeywell Privacy  
4D5  
115 Tabor Road  
Morris Plains, NJ 07950

Número gratuito:  

**Alterações a esta Declaração de Privacidade**

Poderemos ocasionalmente atualizar esta Declaração de Privacidade. Quando o fizermos, iremos rever a data de "última atualização" indicada na parte superior da Declaração de Privacidade e tomaremos os passos adicionais exigidos por lei.

**Última atualização: 11 de junho de 2021**

**Ultima actualizare la 11 iunie 2021**

**Introducere**

Honeywell International Inc. („**Honeywell**","**al nostru**", "**noi**", sau"**noi**"), este "controlorul de date" al informațiilor personale pe care le colectăm despre dvs. atunci când vizitați sau utilizați oricare dintre site-urile noastre web sau utilizați produse, servicii și aplicații care sunt legate de această Declarație de confidențialitate (colectiv, site-urile"**noastre**"). Această Declarație de confidențialitate explică modul în care colectăm, împărtășim și folosim informațiile dvs. personale colectate în acest mod și cum vă puteți exercita drepturile de confidențialitate.

Când interacționăm cu dvs., vă putem oferi, de asemenea, notificări de confidențialitate suplimentare despre activități de prelucrare specifice sau vă putem oferi opțiuni suplimentare despre modul în care Honeywell vă procesează informațiile personale în acel moment.

Faceți clic pe unul dintre linkurile de mai jos pentru a accesa secțiunea care vă interesează:

**Colecția noastră de informații**

* **Informații colectate direct de la dvs**. Este posibil să vă solicităm informații personale pentru furnizarea unui serviciu sau efectuarea unei tranzacții solicitate de dumneavoastră. Este posibil, de asemenea, să ne furnizați informații cu caracter personal atunci când ne contactați sau intrați în legătură cu noi (de ex., cu un comentariu, o întrebare sau o solicitare de asistență pentru clienți, vizitatorii site-ului) sau atunci când înregistrați un cont pentru a utiliza Site-urile noastre. Aceste informații personale pot include:
    * **Date referitoare la identitate,** cum ar fi numele dvs., funcția, numele companiei/organizației, adresa de e-mail, numărul de telefon și de fax și adresa fizică (inclusiv strada, orașul, statul, codul poștal și/sau țara);
    * **Datele de înregistrare,** furnizate de dvs. atunci când înregistrați un cont pentru utilizare pe Site-urile noastre, inclusiv numele de utilizator și parolele;
    * **Date privind recrutările,** inclusiv informațiile transmise în legătură cu o candidatură la un job sau o solicitare de informații (după cum se descrie mai jos);
    * **Date de contact despre afaceri,** cum ar fi informații legate de alți angajați, proprietari, directori, ofițeri sau contractori ai unei organizații terțe (de ex., afaceri, companii, parteneriate, întreprinderi individuale, non-profit sau agenții guvernamentale).
    * **Datele de marketing și comunicare,** inclusiv preferințele dvs. de marketing și abonamentele la publicațiile noastre;
    * **Informații financiare,** inclusiv informații despre cardul de credit sau alte informații despre conturi financiare, cu scopul de a ne permite să vă facilităm achiziția de produse și servicii oferite de Companie, care pot fi disponibile pe Site-urile noastre;
    * **Informații pentru controlul exporturilor,** cum ar fi naționalitatea, cetățenia și țara de reședință, care ne vor permite să stabilim eligibilitatea dumneavoastră pentru primirea de informații despre anumite tehnologii, în conformitate cu reglementările privind controlul exporturilor;
    * **Date legate de tranzacție,** inclusiv întrebări despre și comenzi pentru produsele și serviciile noastre și detalii privind plățile către și de la dvs., inclusiv istoricul comenzilor de achiziție și informațiile necesare pentru a facilita tranzacțiile de plată;
    * **Informații privind înregistrările la evenimente,** inclusiv informațiile pe care le furnizați atunci când completați formulare de înregistrare electronică; și
    * **Feedback-ul dumneavoastră,** inclusiv sondaje, recomandări sau alte feedback-uri de la dvs. despre site-urile noastre, precum și despre produsele și serviciile noastre în general.

Atunci când nu furnizați informațiile solicitate, este posibil să nu putem să vă furnizăm serviciul solicitat sau să vă finalizăm tranzacția.

* **Informații pe care le colectăm automat despre dvs**. Colectăm anumite informații despre vizita dvs. pe site-urile noastre utilizând cookie-uri și tehnologii similare de urmărire. Vom respecta întotdeauna orice drepturi legale pe care le aveți pentru a ne împiedica să facem acest lucru. Datele colectate în acest mod includ:
    * **Date despre utilizare,** inclusiv informații despre modul în care utilizați site-urile noastre, ce pagini vedeți, numărul de octeți transferați, linkurile pe care faceți clic, materialele pe care le accesați, data și ora la care accesați site-ul, site-ul web de la care v-ați conectat la unul dintre site-urile noastre și alte acțiuni întreprinse în cadrul Site-urilor; și
    * **Date tehnice,** cum ar fi adresa IP (Protocol internet), tipul și capacitățile browser-ului, limba și sistemul de operare.

Pentru informații despre cookie-uri și alte tehnologii similare de urmărire pe care le folosim pe site-urile noastre, vă rugăm să consultați site-ul nostru [Notificare cookie](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#romanian).

* **Informații de localizare geografică**. Pentru anumite site-uri, cu consimțământul dvs. expres, putem colecta locația exactă, în timp real (adică locația geografică) a dispozitivului dvs. mobil. Aceste informații vor fi utilizate numai în scopul facilitării utilizării de către dvs. a site-urilor, inclusiv de către furnizorii noștri de servicii care pot procesa aceste informații în legătură cu furnizarea de servicii în numele nostru. Dacă vi se oferă, puteți ajusta acest consimțământ gestionând preferințele Serviciilor de localizare prin setările dispozitivului dvs. mobil.
* **Informații colectate de la terțe părți**. În conformitate cu legislația aplicabilă, putem colecta informații personale despre dvs. de la terți, cum ar fi site-uri și aplicații de social media și le putem combina cu informații pe care le deținem deja, pentru a ne ajuta să îmbunătățim și să personalizăm site-urile noastre în funcție de preferințele dvs. și în alte scopuri stabilite în această Declarație de confidențialitate. Putem, de asemenea, să colectăm informațiile de contact ale companiei dvs. de la angajatorul dvs. sau de la alte terțe părți pentru a facilita sau a ne angaja în alt mod în activități comerciale tradiționale și în probleme administrative similare.

**Cum utilizăm informațiile**

Putem să utilizăm informațiile cu caracter personal colectate prin intermediul Site-urilor noastre sau atunci când ne contactați în diferite scopuri, printre care și următoarele:

* **Date de contact pentru afaceri**. Honeywell colectează și folosește date de contact pentru afaceri pentru a se angaja în comunicări sau tranzacții, inclusiv pentru efectuarea diligenței cu privire la sau furnizarea sau primirea unui produs sau serviciu. De exemplu, Honeywell poate colecta și utiliza aceste date de contact ale companiei pentru a facilita și gestiona comenzile, contractele, garanțiile, întreținerea și funcții comerciale similare, în scopuri de analiză și colectare a creditelor, pentru a ne ajuta cu propriile noastre cerințe legale de conformitate și (dacă este necesar) pentru a ne apăra interesele și revendicările.
* **Servicii și tranzacții**. Putem folosi informațiile dumneavoastră cu caracter personale pentru a presta servicii sau pentru a efectua tranzacții pe le-ați solicitat, care includ, dar nu se limitează la, oferirea de informații cu privire la produsele sau serviciile Companiei pe care le-ați achiziționat sau utilizat în alt mod, înregistrarea produselor achiziționate, procesarea comenzilor de produse, gestionarea solicitărilor de garanție, înlocuirea manualelor produselor, răspunsurile la solicitările de reparații ale clienților, facilitarea utilizării Site-urilor noastre.
* **Administrarea și protejarea afacerii și a site-urilor noastre**. Este posibil să utilizăm informațiile cu caracter personal pentru a ne administra și proteja afacerile și Site-urile, inclusiv prin depanare, întreținere de sistem, asistență, raportarea și găzduirea de date.
* **Îmbunătățirea afacerii, site-urilor, produselor și serviciilor noastre**. Este posibil să utilizăm informațiile dumneavoastră cu caracter personal pentru a efectua analize ale activității noastre sau în alte scopuri, care ne ajută să ne dezvoltăm și să ne îmbunătățim calitatea activității, a Site-urilor, produselor și serviciilor (inclusiv produsele și serviciile noi), de exemplu, prin personalizarea Site-urilor noastre în baza preferințelor sau intereselor dumneavoastră.
* **Marketing**. În conformitate cu legile și reglementările în vigoare, este posibil să utilizăm informațiile dumneavoastră cu caracter personal pentru a vă informa cu privire la produse sau servicii de care ați putea fi interesat și pentru a comunica în alte moduri cu dumneavoastră cu privire la evenimente, știri, chestionare, oferte speciale și subiecte asociate. Puteți să refuzați comunicările de marketing trimise prin e-mail în orice moment, gratuit, prin utilizarea linkului de „dezabonare” din materialele de marketing prin e-mail primite de la noi sau contactându-ne folosind informațiile de contact menționate în această Declarație de confidențialitate. În funcție de țara de reședință, este posibil să puteți renunța la alte tipuri de comunicări de marketing; vă rugăm să ne contactați folosind informațiile de contact enumerate în Declarația de confidențialitate pentru mai multe informații. Unele jurisdicții oferă persoanelor fizice (de exemplu, rezidenții din California) dreptul de a solicita anumite informații cu privire la divulgarea informațiilor personale către terți în scopuri de marketing direct ale terților. Pentru mai multe informații despre practicile noastre de divulgare a datelor în scopuri de marketing, vă rugăm să ne contactați în conformitate cu instrucțiunile enumerate mai jos.
* **Publicitate bazată pe interese**. Colectăm date despre activitățile dvs. online și vă identificăm interesele, astfel încât să vă putem oferi reclame care sunt cele mai relevante pentru dvs. Puteți renunța la primirea publicității bazate pe interese de la Honeywell așa cum este descris în documentul nostru [Notificare cookie](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#romanian).
* **Programele de stimulare financiară și de loialitate**. Colectăm și folosim informații personale pentru a menține și administra programele noastre de stimulare financiară și loialitate. Folosim informațiile personale pe care le furnizați în aceste programe pentru a oferi recompense unice, pentru a urmări starea programului dvs. și pentru a facilita schimbul de puncte de program pentru produse, materiale promoționale, ateliere de instruire și alte articole. În măsura permisă de lege, putem folosi, de asemenea, orice informație personală pe care o furnizați în contextul unui program de stimulare financiară pentru orice alt scop stabilit în această declarație de confidențialitate. Vă rugăm să consultați termenii și condițiile fiecărui program de stimulare financiară în care doriți să vă înregistrați sau să participați, deoarece astfel de termeni și condiții pot fi strict adaptate la programul aplicabil. Dacă sunteți de acord să participați la aceste programe, vă puteți retrage consimțământul în orice moment contactându-ne folosind datele de contact de la sfârșitul acestei Declarații de confidențialitate sau în conformitate cu instrucțiunile stabilite în termenii și condițiile programului aplicabil.
* **Cereri de angajare**. În legătură cu o cerere sau o solicitare de loc de muncă, ne puteți furniza informații despre dvs., cum ar fi un CV/curriculum vitae, referințe profesionale, informații despre educație și experiența profesională și informații despre pregătirea profesională și certificări. Noi și membrii grupului nostru putem folosi aceste informații în scopul luării în considerare a angajării, a face verificări de fond și eligibilitatea pentru angajare și, după cum se prevede în orice declarație de confidențialitate separată sau în altă notificare pusă la dispoziție în legătură cu cererea dvs. Putem folosi un terț (de exemplu, un recrutor de locuri de muncă) sau o platformă de socializare pentru a solicita, colecta și păstra cererile de angajare. Pentru mai multe informații, vă rugăm să citiți [Notificarea de confidențialitate a solicitantului](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/applicant-privacy-notice#romanian) .
* **Cercetare și analize**. Putem folosi informațiile dvs. personale pentru a efectua cercetări și analize care să ne ajute să analizăm preferințele dvs. de cumpărare, să identificăm produsele și serviciile care îndeplinesc cel mai bine cerințele dvs. și să măsurăm eficacitatea publicității pe care v-o servim.
* **Executare**: Este posibil să folosim informațiile cu caracter personal colectate pentru a detecta, preveni și reacționa la cazuri de fraudă, încălcări ale drepturilor de proprietate intelectuală, încălcări ale termenilor și condițiilor noastre sau ale legii, sau alte tipuri de utilizare abuzivă a Site-urilor.

Atunci când legea ne-o permite, este posibil să combinăm informațiile colectate prin Site-urile noastre cu alte informații pe care le deținem despre dumneavoastră (cum ar fi informațiile despre utilizarea produselor și serviciilor noastre) pentru a vă oferi o experiență îmbunătățită și constantă atunci când interacționați cu noi sau în alte scopuri prevăzute în această Declarație de confidențialitate.

**Temeiul juridic în baza căruia prelucrăm informațiile**

Atunci când legea o impune, ne vom asigura că există o bază legală pentru procesarea informațiilor dumneavoastră cu caracter personal. În majoritatea cazurilor, baza noastră juridică va depinde de informațiile personale în cauză și de contextul specific în care le colectăm.

* **Contract**: Prelucrarea este necesară pentru prestarea serviciilor pe care vi le oferim sau pentru a lua măsuri (la cererea dvs.) înainte și în anticiparea efectuării acestor servicii;
* **Obligație legală**: procesarea este necesară pentru a ne conforma cu obligațiile noastre legale, inclusiv conformitatea cu legile, reglementările, solicitărilor guvernamentale și cvasi-guvernamentale, ordinele judecătorești sau citațiile aplicabile;
* **Consimțământ**: procesarea se bazează pe consimțământul dumneavoastră pentru procesarea informațiilor cu caracter personal pentru unul sau mai multe scopuri specificate (de ex. marketing);
* **Interese legitime**: procesarea este necesară pentru interesele noastre legitime, de exemplu pentru dezvoltarea și îmbunătățirea Site-urilor, produselor și/sau serviciilor în beneficiul clienților; sau
* **Interese vitale**: prelucrarea este necesară pentru a vă proteja interesele vitale (de ex., motive de sănătate și siguranță dacă participați la o întâlnire într-o locație Honeywell).

Dacă aveți întrebări sau aveți nevoie de informații suplimentare cu privire la baza legală pe baza căreia colectăm și folosim informațiile dvs. personale, vă rugăm să trimiteți un e-mail la [HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com)

**Anonimizarea informațiilor**

În conformitate cu legile în vigoare, este posibil să anonimizăm informațiile dumneavoastră cu caracter personal, astfel încât să nu mai poată fi utilizate pentru identificare. Informațiile anonimizate nu sunt considerate informații cu caracter personal și, prin urmare, nu se supun acestei Declarații de confidențialitate. Este posibil să colectăm, să utilizăm, să agregăm și să distribuim informațiile anonimizate în orice scop.

**Cât timp păstrăm informațiile**

Perioada de păstrare a informațiilor dumneavoastră cu caracter personal depinde de scopul procesării. De exemplu, stocăm informațiile personale necesare pentru a vă oferi produse și servicii sau pentru a facilita tranzacțiile pe care le-ați solicitat, atâta timp cât sunteți client al Honeywell sau dacă trimiteți o cerere de angajare prin intermediul site-urilor noastre, vom păstra detalii despre cererea dvs. așa cum este stabilit în notificarea de confidențialitate care vă este pusă la dispoziție în legătură cu cererea dvs. sau după cum se impune altfel prin lege. În toate celelalte cazuri, stocăm informațiile dumneavoastră cu caracter personal atât timp cât este necesar pentru a îndeplini scopurile menționate în această declarație de confidențialitate, după care nu sunt nici anonimizate (acolo unde o permite legea în vigoare), nici șterse și nici distruse.

**Divulgarea informațiilor**

Este posibil să distribuim informațiile dumneavoastră cu caracter personal în conformitate cu legile în vigoare, inclusiv după cum se prevede mai jos:

* **Companiile din grupul nostru**. Este posibil să distribuim informațiile dumneavoastră cu caracter personal companiilor din grupul nostru, după cum este necesar în mod rezonabil pentru scopurile prevăzute în această Declarație de confidențialitate.
* **Prestatori de servicii**. Este posibil să distribuim informațiile dumneavoastră cu caracter personal companiilor contractate de noi, pentru ca acestea să presteze servicii în numele nostru, de exemplu pentru găzduirea site-urilor web, realizarea de sondaje, procesarea tranzacțiilor, analizarea Site-urilor noastre și efectuarea analizelor cu scopul de a îmbunătăți calitatea activității, Site-urilor și produselor și serviciilor noastre. Impunem acestor furnizori de servicii să protejeze confidențialitatea informațiilor dumneavoastră cu caracter personal.
* **Distribuitori și alți parteneri de afaceri de încredere**. Este posibil să distribuim informațiile dumneavoastră cu caracter personal terților care distribuie produsele noastre și altor parteneri de afaceri de încredere în scopuri care includ acordarea permisiunii respectivilor terți pentru a vă trimite comunicări de marketing. O astfel de distribuire a informațiilor dumneavoastră cu caracter personal va fi executată în conformitate cu legile și reglementările în vigoare.
* **Divulgarea în legătură cu tranzacțiile**. În contextul anumitor tranzacții, este posibil să divulgăm parțial sau în totalitate informațiile dumneavoastră cu caracter personal unor instituții financiare, entități guvernamentale și companii de expediere sau de servicii poștale implicate în ducerea la îndeplinire a tranzacției.
* **Dezvăluiri în legătură cu achiziții sau reducerea activelor**. Pot apărea circumstanțe în care, din motive strategice sau de altă natură, Honeywell decide să vândă, să cumpere, să cedeze, să fuzioneze sau să reorganizeze în alt mod afacerile din unele țări. Este posibil să divulgăm informații stocate cu privire la dvs., în măsura considerată rezonabilă și necesară pentru a avansa cu negocierile sau cu procedura de fuziune, achiziție, vânzare parțială sau totală a activelor Honeywell.
* **Dezvăluire din alte motive**. Este posibil să divulgăm informații cu caracter personal dacă acest lucru este impus sau autorizat prin lege, sau în situații în care considerăm, de bună-credință, că acest lucru este necesar pentru a respecta cerințele legale sau procedurile legale intentate împotriva noastră, pentru a ne proteja și apăra drepturile sau proprietățile sau, în situații urgente, pentru a proteja siguranța personală a oricărui individ.

**Transferuri internaționale**

Honeywell este o organizație globală, iar informațiile dvs. personale pot fi transferate, păstrate, stocate sau utilizate în diferite locații din întreaga lume, cum ar fi SUA, Mexic și India, în conformitate cu legislația aplicabilă. Aceasta înseamnă că, atunci când colectăm informațiile dvs. personale, acestea pot fi prelucrate în țări care pot avea legi privind protecția datelor care sunt diferite de legile țării dvs. Cu toate acestea, Honeywell va lua întotdeauna măsuri rezonabile pentru a vă proteja confidențialitatea și pentru a oferi un nivel de protecție a informațiilor personale care este comparabil cu cel al țării dvs. de reședință, care include punerea în aplicare a clauzelor contractuale standard ale Comisiei Europene. Pentru mai multe informații despre măsurile de protecție adecvate pentru a vă proteja informațiile personale, vă rugăm să ne contactați la [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com).

**Securitate**

Ne angajăm să protejăm securitatea informațiilor dvs. personale. Folosim măsuri tehnice și organizaționale pentru a oferi un nivel de securitate adecvat riscului de prelucrare a informațiilor dvs. personale. Pentru mai multe informații despre modul în care Honeywell vă protejează informațiile personale, vă rugăm să ne contactați la [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com)

**Drepturile dvs.**

În funcție de legislația aplicabilă, este posibil să aveți anumite drepturi cu privire la informațiile dvs. personale.

* Este posibil să aveți dreptul să **accesați, corectați, actualizați** sau **să solicitați ștergere**a informațiilor dvs. personale.
* Puteți **obiecta** la prelucrarea informațiilor dvs. personale, să ne cereți să **restricționăm** prelucrarea informațiilor dvs. personale sau să cereți **portabilitatea** informațiilor dvs. personale.
* Este posibil să aveți dreptul **să solicitați să nu se ia o decizie despre dvs. care se bazează exclusiv pe prelucrarea automată, inclusiv profilarea** dacă acea decizie produce efecte juridice despre dvs. sau vă afectează semnificativ.
* În mod similar, dacă am colectat și procesat informațiile dvs. personale cu acordul dvs., atunci **vă puteți retrage consimțământul în orice moment**. Retragerea consimțământului dvs. nu va afecta legalitatea oricărei prelucrări pe care am efectuat-o înainte de retragerea dvs. și nici nu va afecta prelucrarea informațiilor dvs. personale efectuate în baza unor motive de prelucrare legale, altele decât consimțământul.
* Este posibil să aveți dreptul să **renunțați la vânzarea informațiilor dvs. personale**. Honeywell nu vinde informațiile dvs. personale unor terțe părți pentru profit. Cu toate acestea, împărtășim sau dezvăluim informațiile dvs. personale unor terțe părți în conformitate cu această Declarație de confidențialitate și cu [Notificarea noastră cu privire la cookie](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#romanian). De exemplu, ne angajăm cu terțe părți pentru a distribui produsele noastre, pentru a vă oferi asistență tehnică, pentru a opera instrumente și caracteristici de analiză a site-ului web și pentru a ne angaja în marketing și vânzări ale produselor și serviciilor noastre. Aceste activități pot implica dezvăluirea informațiilor dvs. personale către terți și pot fi considerate o „vânzare” a datelor în conformitate cu anumite legi (dar nu toate) privind protecția datelor.
* Aveți dreptul să **vă plângeți** la o autoritate de protecție a datelor responsabilă cu supravegherea conformității cu legea privind protecția datelor din jurisdicția dvs. cu privire la colectarea și utilizarea informațiilor dvs. personale în cazul în care considerați că prelucrarea informațiilor dvs. personale nu este conformă cu legea privind protecția datelor. De exemplu, persoanele din SEE au dreptul de a depune o plângere la autoritatea competentă pentru protecția datelor, o listă care poate fi accesată la: [https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/board/members\_en](https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/board/members_en). Am aprecia, totuși, să ne dați șansa de a rezolva problemele dumneavoastră, de aceea vă rugăm să ne contactați oricând cu privire la orice plângere. Nu vom discrimina persoanele care își exercită drepturile de confidențialitate a datelor.

Vă vom facilita exercitarea drepturilor care vi se aplică, în conformitate cu legile în vigoare. Cu toate acestea, chiar dacă informațiile dvs. personale nu beneficiază de protecție în temeiul sau în orice alt mod supus unei legi de protecție a datelor, noi am putea dori să ne ocupăm de orice solicitare sau anchetă pe care o aveți cu privire la activitățile noastre de prelucrare a datelor. Dacă aveți întrebări cu privire la drepturile dvs. sau doriți să vă exercitați drepturile, ne puteți contacta la [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com) sau trimiteți întrebări despre confidențialitate prin intermediul formularului nostru web interactiv la următorul link:

**Informații despre copii**

Site-urile noastre nu sunt direcționate către și nu ar trebui să fie utilizate de copiii cu vârsta sub șaisprezece ani (16) și nu colectăm, folosim sau vindem cu bună știință informații de la astfel de persoane. Dacă sunteți minor, așa cum reglementează legile din țara dvs., vă rugăm să nu trimiteți informații personale prin intermediul site-urilor noastre.

**Linkuri către alte site-uri**

Site-urile noastre pot conține linkuri către site-uri web, produse și servicii ale unor terțe părți. Nu acceptăm nicio responsabilitate pentru site-urile web, produsele și serviciile respective, pentru politicile acestora sau pentru colectarea sau procesarea în alt mod de către acestea a informațiilor dumneavoastră cu caracter personal. Practicile acelor terțe părți sunt guvernate de propriile lor politici de confidențialitate. Vă încurajăm să vă informați în legătură cu politicile de confidențialitate ale respectivilor terți.

**Contactați-ne**

Dacă aveți întrebări cu privire la această declarație de confidențialitate sau manipularea de către noi datelor dvs. personale, dacă doriți să depuneți o plângere sau doriți să contactați responsabilul nostru cu protecția datelor, vă rugăm să ne contactați utilizând informațiile de contact enumerate mai jos. Vom acorda imediat atenție problemei dumneavoastră și vom face eforturi pentru a ajunge la o soluție satisfăcătoare.

Formular web interactiv:  

Email:  

Adresa poștală:  
Honeywell Privacy  
4D5  
115 Tabor Road  
Morris Plains, NJ 07950

Număr gratuit:  

**Modificări la această Declarație de confidențialitate**

Vom actualiza ocazional această Declarație de confidențialitate. Când facem acest lucru, revizuim data ultimei actualizări din partea de sus și de jos a Declarației de confidențialitate și luăm toate măsurile necesare impuse de lege.

**Последнее обновление: 11 июня 2021 г.**

**Введение**

Компания Honeywell International Inc. (далее **Honeywell**, **мы**, **нас** или **нам**) является контроллером персональных данных, собираемых во время посещения или использования вами любых из наших веб-сайтов или использования наших продуктов, сервисов и приложений, связанных с настоящим Заявлением о конфиденциальности (далее в совокупности **веб-сайты**). В настоящем Заявлении о конфиденциальности объясняется, как мы собираем, передаем и используем ваши персональные данные, собранные указанным образом, и как вы можете реализовывать свои права на конфиденциальность.

При взаимодействии с вами мы также можем предоставлять вам дополнительные уведомления о конфиденциальности в отношении конкретных действий по обработке данных или предлагать вам дополнительные варианты того, как Honeywell будет обрабатывать ваши персональные данные в конкретный момент времени.

Щелкните одну из приведенных ниже ссылок, чтобы перейти в интересующий вас раздел.

**Сбор данных**

* **Данные, которые мы получаем непосредственно от вас**. Мы можем попросить вас сообщить персональные данные, чтобы предоставить запрошенную услугу или совершить необходимую операцию. Некоторую информацию вы также можете предоставить при обращении к нам или взаимодействии с нами (например, оставив комментарий, запрос или обращение в службу поддержки клиентов, либо в качестве посетителя веб-сайта) или при регистрации учетной записи на наших веб-сайтах. Эти персональные данные могут включать в себя следующие данные.
    * **Идентификационные данные,** такие как ваше имя, должность, название компании или организации, адрес электронной почты, номера телефона и физический адрес (улица, город, область, почтовый индекс и (или) страна).
    * **Регистрационные данные,** предоставленные во время регистрации учетной записи для использования наших веб-сайтов, включая имена пользователей и пароли.
    * **Данные, связанные с трудоустройством,** включая информацию, предоставленную в связи с заявкой соискателя вакансии или запросом (см. определение, приведенное далее).
    * **Деловая контактная информация,** например информация, относящаяся к другим сотрудникам, владельцам, директорам, должностным лицам или подрядчикам сторонней организации (например к бизнесу, компании, партнерству, индивидуальному предпринимателю, некоммерческому или государственному учреждению).
    * **Маркетинговые и коммуникационные данные,** включая настройки рекламных рассылок и подписки на наши публикации.
    * **Финансовая информация,** включая данные о кредитных картах или другие финансовые данные, которые используются для упрощения процесса приобретения продуктов и услуг Компании, доступных на наших сайтах.
    * **Сведения для экспортного контроля,** такие как ваша национальность, гражданство и страна проживания, что позволяет нам определить, соответствуете ли вы требованиям нормативно-правовых актов о контроле экспорта для получения информации о тех или иных технологиях.
    * **Данные о сделках,** включая запросы и заказы наших продуктов и услуг, а также сведения о платежах, произведенных или полученных вами, включая историю заказов на покупки и сведения, необходимые для выполнения платежей.
    * **Сведения о регистрации на участие в мероприятиях,** включая информацию, предоставляемую при заполнении форм электронной регистрации.
    * **Ваши отзывы,** включая обзоры, рекомендации и другие отзывы о наших сайтах и продукции и услугах в целом.

Если вы не предоставите требуемую информацию, мы не сможем предоставить вам необходимые услуги или совершить сделку для выполнения вашего заказа.

* **Ваши данные, которые мы собираем автоматически**. Мы собираем определенную информацию о вашем посещении наших веб-сайтов с помощью файлов cookie и других технологий отслеживания. Мы всегда будем уважать все ваши законные права, позволяющие вам препятствовать нам в сборе данных. Собранные таким образом данные включают следующие данные.
    * **Данные об использовании**, включая информацию том, как вы используете наши сайты, просматриваемые вами страницы, количество переданных байтов, нажимаемые вами ссылки, просматриваемые вами материалы, дата и время доступа к сайту, веб-сайты, с которых вы перешли на наши сайты и другие действия, выполняемые вами на наших сайтах.
    * **Технические данные**, такие как IP-адрес, возможности и тип браузера, язык и операционная система.

Сведения о файлах cookie и других технологиях отслеживания, которые мы используем на наших веб-сайтах, см. в разделе [Уведомление о файлах cookie](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#russian).

* **Сведения геолокации**. С вашего явного согласия для определенных веб-сайтов мы можем производить сбор данных о точном местоположении в реальном времени (т. е. производить геолокацию) вашего мобильного устройства. Данная информация будет использоваться только для облегчения пользования нашими веб-сайтами, в том числе может быть предоставлена нашим поставщиками услуг, которые могут обрабатывать эту информацию в рамках предоставления услуг от нашего имени. Предоставив свое соглашение, вы можете изменить его, управляя службами геолокации с помощью настроек мобильного устройства.
* **Данные, полученные от третьих лиц**. В соответствии с применимым законодательством мы можем выполнять сбор персональных данных от третьих лиц, таких как веб-сайты и приложения социальных сетей. Эти данные мы можем объединять с уже имеющейся у нас информацией, чтобы оптимизировать и настраивать наши сайты с учетом ваших предпочтений, а также для других целей, указанных в настоящем Заявлении о конфиденциальности. Мы также можем получать вашу деловую контактную информацию от вашего работодателя или других третьих лиц, чтобы облегчить или иным образом вести традиционную деловую деятельность и решать иные подобные административные вопросы.

**Использование данных**

Мы можем использовать персональные данные, собранные при посещении наших веб-сайтов или при обращении к нам, которые могут включать следующие сведения.

* **Деловая контактная информация**. Компания Honeywell собирает и использует деловую контактную информацию для поддержания связи или транзакций, в том числе для проведения комплексных проверок в связи с предоставлением или получением продукта или услуги. Например, компания Honeywell может собирать и использовать деловую контактную информацию для оформления заказов и контрактов и управления ими, для предоставления гарантий, технического обслуживания и других подобных услуг, для анализа кредитоспособности, для обеспечения соответствия нашим собственным внутренним требованиям и требованиям законодательства, а также (при необходимости) для защиты наших интересов и претензий.
* **Услуги и сделки**. Мы можем использовать ваши персональные данные, чтобы предоставлять вам услуги или выполнять сделки, о совершении которых вы запрашивали, включая, помимо прочего, предоставление информации о продуктах или услугах Компании, которые вы приобрели или использовали иным образом, регистрацию купленных продуктов, обработку заказов на продукты, обработку гарантийных рекламаций, замену руководства по эксплуатации приобретенного продукта, ответы на запросы в службу поддержки клиентов и оптимизацию использования наших сайтов.
* **Администрирование и защита нашей коммерческой деятельности и сайтов**. Мы можем использовать персональные данные для администрирования и защиты нашей коммерческой деятельности и наших сайтов, включая поиск и устранение неполадок, обслуживание системы, поддержку, ведение отчетности и размещение данных.
* **Оптимизация работы нашей компании, сайтов и улучшение наших продуктов и услуг**. Мы можем использовать ваши персональные данные для выполнения бизнес-анализа или других целей, чтобы развивать наш бизнес и повышать качество нашей работы, сайтов, продуктов и услуг (включая новые продукты и услуги), например, настраивая сайт с учетом ваших предпочтений и интересов.
* **Маркетинг**. Согласно действующими законам и нормативам мы можем использовать ваши персональные данные, чтобы информировать вас о продуктах и услугах, в которых вы можете быть заинтересованы, а также отправлять вам предложения, анонсы событий, новости, опросные листы, специальные предложения и другие материалы. Вы в любое время можете бесплатно отказаться от рекламной рассылки по электронной почте. Для этого перейдите по ссылке «отписаться», указанной в любом полученном от нас сообщении с рекламными материалами, или свяжитесь с нами, используя контактные данные, указанные в Заявлении о конфиденциальности. В зависимости от страны проживания вы также можете отказаться от других типов рекламных рассылок. Для получения дополнительных сведений свяжитесь с нами, используя контактные данные, указанные в Заявлении о конфиденциальности. Некоторые юрисдикции предоставляют физическим лицам (например резидентам Калифорнии) право запрашивать определенную информацию, касающуюся раскрытия нами персональных данных третьим лицам для использования в целях прямого маркетинга. Для получения дополнительной информации о наших методах раскрытия данных в маркетинговых целях свяжитесь с нами в соответствии с приведенными далее инструкциями.
* **Реклама на основе интересов**. Мы собираем данные о ваших действиях в Интернете и определяем ваши интересы, чтобы предоставлять вам наиболее релевантную рекламу. Вы можете отказаться от получения рекламы на основе интересов от Honeywell, как описано в нашем [Уведомлении о файлах cookie](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#russian).
* **Программы финансового стимулирования и лояльности.** Мы собираем и используем персональные данные для реализации наших программ финансового стимулирования и лояльности и управления ими. Мы используем персональные данные, которые вы предоставляете в этих программах, чтобы предлагать уникальные вознаграждения, отслеживать статус вашей программы и содействовать обмену баллов программы на продукты, рекламные материалы, учебные семинары и другие предложения. В той степени, в которой это разрешено законодательством, мы также можем использовать любые персональные данные, которые вы предоставляете в контексте программы финансового стимулирования, для любых других целях, указанных в данном Заявлении о конфиденциальности. Ознакомьтесь с положениями и условиями каждой программы финансового стимулирования, в которой вы хотели бы зарегистрироваться или принять участие. Если вы даете согласие на участие в этих программах, вы можете отозвать свое согласие в любое время. Для этого свяжитесь с нами, используя контактные данные, указанные в конце настоящего Заявления о конфиденциальности, или в соответствии с инструкциями, изложенными в положениях и условиях соответствующей программы.
* **Заявление о приеме на работу**. В связи с подачей заявки на вакансию или запроса о наличии вакансии вы можете предоставить нам персональные данные, включая резюме и биографические данные, профессиональные рекомендации, сведения об образовании и опыте работы, а также информацию о профессиональной подготовке и сертификации. Мы и члены нашей группы можем использовать эту информацию для рассмотрения вопроса о приеме на работу, проверки биографических данных и определения права на трудоустройство, а также в иных случаях, указанных в отдельных заявлениях о конфиденциальности или других уведомлениях, применимых к данной ситуации. Мы можем прибегать к помощи третьих лиц (например агентства по трудоустройству) или пользоваться социальными сетями для запрашивания, сбора и хранения заявлений о приеме на работу. Дополнительные сведения см. в [Уведомлении о конфиденциальности данных кандидата](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/applicant-privacy-notice#russian).
* **Исследования и анализ**. Мы можем использовать ваши личные данные для проведения исследований и анализа, которые помогут нам проанализировать ваши предпочтения в покупках, определить продукты и услуги, максимально отвечающие вашим требованиям, и оценить эффективность рекламы, которую мы вам показываем.
* **Правоприменительные меры**. Мы можем использовать собранные персональные данные с целью выявления, предотвращения и реагирования на мошеннические действия, нарушение прав интеллектуальной собственности, неисполнение наших правил и условий, несоблюдение законов и другого неправомерного использования наших сайтов.

В случаях, разрешенных законом, мы можем объединять данные, собранные нами на наших сайтах, с другой имеющейся у нас информацией (такой как информация об использовании вами наших продуктов и услуг), чтобы повысить качество обслуживания клиентов, а также для других целей, указанных в настоящем Заявлении о конфиденциальности.

**Правовые основания для обработки данных**

В случаях, предусмотренных законом, мы обеспечим юридические основания для обработки ваших персональных данных. В большинстве случаев правовые основания будут зависеть от соответствующих персональных данных и конкретного контекста, в котором мы их собираем.

* **Договор**: обработка необходима для предоставления вам услуг или для принятия мер (по вашему запросу) до предоставления таких услуг.
* **Правовые обязательства**: обработка необходима для исполнения наших правовых обязательств, включая соблюдение применимых законов, нормативов, запросов государственных и иных органов, судебных распоряжений или вызовов в суд.
* **Согласие**: обработка выполняется по вашему разрешению на обработку персональных данных в одной или нескольких указанных целях (например для рекламы).
* **Законные интересы**: обработка необходима для удовлетворения наших законных интересов, например для разработки и оптимизации наших сайтов, продуктов и (или) услуг в интересах наших клиентов.
* **Жизненно важные интересы**: обработка необходима для защиты ваших жизненно важных интересов (например по соображениям здоровья и безопасности, если вы присутствуете на совещании в офисе компании Honeywell).

Если у вас есть какие-либо вопросы или вам нужна дополнительная информация о правовых основаниях, на которых мы собираем и используем ваши персональные данные, отправьте электронное письмо по адресу [HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com).

**Анонимизация данных**

В соответствии с применимым законодательством мы можем обеспечивать анонимность персональных данных, чтобы их невозможно было использовать для идентификации личности. Анонимизированные данные не считаются персональными данными и поэтому не попадают под действие настоящего Заявления о конфиденциальности. Мы можем собирать, использовать, объединять и передавать анонимную информацию в любых целях.

**Сроки хранения данных**

Период хранения персональных данных зависит от цели обработки. Например, мы храним персональные данные, необходимые для предоставления вам продуктов и услуг или для выполнения запрашиваемых вами транзакций, пока вы являетесь клиентом компании Honeywell. Если вы подаете заявление о приеме на работу через наши веб-сайты, мы будем хранить информацию о вашем заявлении, как указано в уведомлении о конфиденциальности, предоставленном вам в связи с вашим заявлением, или в соответствии с требованиями закона. Во всех других случаях мы храним персональные данные до тех пор, пока они необходимы для наших целей, изложенных в настоящем Заявлении о конфиденциальности, после чего мы либо анонимизируем данные (если это разрешено применимым законодательством), либо удаляем, либо уничтожаем их.

**Раскрытие данных**

Мы можем передавать ваши персональные данные выбранным третьим лицам в соответствии с применимым законодательством, в том числе, как указано ниже.

* **Наша группа компаний**. Мы также можем предоставлять ваши персональные данные своим аффилированным лицам и компаниям из нашей группы, когда это оправдано необходимо в целях, описанных в этом Заявлении о конфиденциальности.
* **Поставщики услуг**. Мы можем предоставлять персональные данные другим компаниям, с которыми у нас заключены договоры на предоставление услуг от нашего имени, таких как хостинг веб-сайтов, проведение опросов, обработка операций, анализ наших сайтов и выполнение анализа для улучшения качества нашей работы, сайтов, продуктов и услуг. Мы требуем, чтобы эти поставщики услуг обеспечивали конфиденциальность ваших персональных данных.
* **Дистрибьюторы и другие доверенные деловые партнеры**. Мы можем передавать ваши персональные данные третьим лицам, которые распространяют наши продукты, и другим доверенным деловым партнерам в целях, позволяющих этим третьим лицам отправлять вам рекламные материалы. Предоставление персональных данных в маркетинговых целях осуществляется в соответствии с применимыми законами и нормами.
* **Предоставление информации в связи со сделками**. В связи с некоторыми сделками мы можем сообщить некоторую часть или все ваши персональные данные финансовым учреждениям, правительственным организациям и транспортным компаниям, а также почтовым службам, привлеченным к осуществлению сделки.
* **Разглашение в связи с приобретением или ликвидацией компании**. В связи с обстоятельствами в стратегических целях или по иным деловым соображениям корпорация Honeywell может решить продать, купить, разделить, объединить посредством слияния или иначе реорганизовать свои предприятия в некоторых странах. Мы можем раскрыть имеющуюся о вас информацию до степени, достаточной для продолжения переговоров или завершения слияния, приобретения, разделения или продажи всех или части активов компании Honeywell.
* **Разглашение информации по другим причинам**. Мы можем раскрыть персональные данные, если это требуется или разрешено по закону или исходя из добросовестного предположения, что такое действие необходимо для соблюдения законных требований или врученного нам постановления суда, для защиты наших прав и имущества или в чрезвычайных обстоятельствах для защиты личной безопасности того или иного физического лица.

**Передача данных в другие страны**

Компания Honeywell является глобальной организацией, и ваши персональные данные могут передаваться, находиться, храниться или использоваться в различных регионах по всему миру, например в США, Мексике и Индии, в соответствии с действующим законодательством. Это означает, что когда мы собираем ваши персональные данные, они могут обрабатываться в странах, в которых законы о защите данных могут отличаться от законов вашей страны. Тем не менее, компания Honeywell всегда будет принимать разумные меры для защиты вашей конфиденциальности и обеспечения уровня защиты персональных данных, сопоставимого с уровнем защиты в вашей стране проживания, включая выполнение Стандартных договорных положений, утвержденных Европейской комиссией. Чтобы получить дополнительную информацию о соответствующих мерах защиты ваших персональных данных, свяжитесь с нами по адресу [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com).

**Безопасность**

Мы стремимся предпринять все возможные действия для защиты ваших персональных данных. Мы принимаем технические и организационные меры для обеспечения уровня безопасности, соответствующего риску, связанному с обработкой ваших персональных данных. Для получения дополнительной информации о том, как Honeywell защищает ваши персональные данные, свяжитесь с нами по адресу [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com).

**Ваши права**

В зависимости от применимого законодательства у вас могут быть определенные права в отношении ваших персональных данных.

* Вы можете иметь право **на доступ, исправление, обновление** или **удаление** ваших персональных данных.
* Вы можете **возражать** против обработки ваших персональных данных, просить нас **ограничит**ь обработку ваших персональных данных или требовать переноса ваших персональных данных.
* Вы можете иметь право **на то, чтобы в отношении вас не принимались решения, основанные исключительно на автоматической обработке, включая профилирование,** если эти решения создают для вас юридические последствия или оказывают иное значительное влияние на вас.
* Также, если мы собираем и обрабатываем ваши персональные данные с вашего согласия, **вы можете отозвать свое согласие в любое время**. Отзыв вашего согласия не повлияет на законность обработки, которую мы выполняли до отзыва согласия, а также не повлияет на обработку ваших персональных данных, проводимую на законных основаниях, отличных от согласия.
* Вы можете иметь право **отказаться от продажи ваших персональных данных**. Компания Honeywell не продает ваши персональные данные третьим лицам с целью получения прибыли. Однако мы передаем или иным образом раскрываем ваши персональные данные третьим лицам в соответствии с настоящим Заявлением о конфиденциальности и нашим [Уведомлением о файлах cookie](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#russian). Например, мы взаимодействуем с третьими лицами для распространения наших продуктов, предоставления вам технической помощи, использования аналитических инструментов и функций веб-сайта, а также маркетинга и продаж наших продуктов и услуг. Такие действия могут включать раскрытие ваших персональных данных третьим лицам и могут рассматриваться как «продажа» данных в соответствии с некоторыми (но не всеми) законами о защите данных.
* Вы имеете право **подавать жалобы** в органы власти, контролирующие соблюдение законов о защите данных в вашей юрисдикции, в отношении сбора и использования ваших персональных данных, если вы считаете, что обработка нами ваших персональных данных не соответствует закону о защите данных. Например, лица в ЕЭЗ имеют право подать жалобу в компетентный орган по защите данных, список которых можно найти по адресу: [https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/board/members\_en](https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/board/members_en). Тем не менее мы будет рады помочь вам решить ваши вопросы, поэтому не стесняйтесь обращаться к нам с любой жалобой. Мы не будем дискриминировать кого-либо за осуществление прав на конфиденциальность данных.

Мы будем обеспечивать соблюдение ваших прав в соответствии с применимым законодательством. Однако, даже если ваши персональные данные не защищены законом о защите данных или каким-либо иным образом не подпадают под его действие, мы будем стараться удовлетворить любой ваш запрос или требование в отношении нашей деятельности по обработке данных. Если у вас есть вопросы о ваших правах или вы хотите воспользоваться своими правами, свяжитесь с нами по адресу [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com) или отправьте вопросы о конфиденциальности через нашу интерактивную веб-форму по следующей ссылке:

**Персональные данные детей**

Наши веб-сайты не предназначены для детей младше шестнадцати (16) лет и не должны использоваться ими, и мы не собираем, не используем и не продаем данные таких лиц. Если вы являетесь несовершеннолетним в соответствии с законами вашей страны, пожалуйста, не сообщайте какие-либо персональные данные на наших веб-сайтах.

**Ссылки на другие веб-сайты**

Наши веб-сайты могут содержать ссылки на сторонние веб-сайты, продукты и услуги. Мы не несем ответственности за эти веб-сайты, продукты и услуги, их политику, условия сбора или обработки ваших персональных данных. Действия этих третьих лиц регулируются их собственными политиками конфиденциальности. Мы рекомендуем вам знакомиться с политиками конфиденциальности этих третьих лиц.

**Контакты**

Если у вас есть вопросы относительно настоящего Заявления о конфиденциальности или правил обработки ваших персональных данных, если вы хотите подать жалобу или обратиться к нашему специалисту по защите персональных данных, свяжитесь с нами, используя контактную информацию, указанную ниже. Мы незамедлительно изучим ваш вопрос и приложим усилия, чтобы найти удовлетворительное решение.

Интерактивная веб-форма:  

Электронная почта:  

Почтовый адрес:  
Honeywell Privacy  
4D5  
115 Tabor Road  
Morris Plains, NJ 07950.

Номер для бесплатных звонков:  
[844 774 8634](tel:8447748634).

**Изменения в этом Заявлении о конфиденциальности**

Мы вправе время от времени вносить изменения в настоящее Заявление о конфиденциальности. В случае внесения изменений мы исправим дату последнего обновления, указанную в верхней части Заявления о конфиденциальности, и предпримем дополнительные меры, предусмотренные законом.

**Последнее обновление: 11 июня 2021 г.**

**Posledná aktualizácia 11. júna 2021**

**Úvod**

Spoločnosť Honeywell International Inc. („**Honeywell**“, „**náš**“, „**nás**“ alebo „**my**“) je „správcom údajov“ osobných údajov, ktoré o vás zhromažďujeme, keď navštívite alebo použijete niektorú z našich webových lokalít alebo použijete produkty, služby a aplikácie, ktoré sú prepojené s týmto vyhlásením o ochrane osobných údajov (ďalej spoločne „**webové lokality**“). Toto vyhlásenie o ochrane osobných údajov vysvetľuje, ako zhromažďujeme, zdieľame a používame vaše osobné údaje zhromaždené týmto spôsobom a ako môžete uplatniť svoje práva na ochranu osobných údajov.

Keď s vami komunikujeme, môžeme vám tiež poskytnúť ďalšie oznámenia o ochrane osobných údajov týkajúce sa konkrétnych činností spracovania alebo vám ponúknuť ďalšie možnosti týkajúce sa spôsobu, akým spoločnosť Honeywell spracúva vaše osobné údaje v danom konkrétnom okamihu.

Kliknutím na jedno z nasledujúcich prepojení prejdite na časť, ktorá vás zaujíma:

**Zhromažďovanie údajov**

* **Údaje zhromaždené priamo od vás**. Môžeme vás požiadať o osobné údaje, aby sme vám mohli poskytnúť požadovanú službu alebo vykonať požadovanú transakciu. Osobné údaje nám môžete poskytnúť aj vtedy, keď nás kontaktujete alebo sa s nami spojíte (napr. keď nám pošlete komentár, otázku alebo žiadosť o zákaznícku podporu, návštevníkov) alebo keď si zaregistrujete konto na používanie našich webových lokalít. Tieto osobné údaje môžu obsahovať:
    * **údaje o identite,** ako napríklad vaše meno, titul, názov spoločnosti alebo organizácie, e-mailovú adresu, telefónne čísla a poštovú adresu (vrátane ulice, mesta, kraja, PSČ a/alebo krajiny);
    * **registračné údaje,** ktoré zadáte pri registrácii konta na používanie našich webových lokalít, vrátane mien používateľov a hesiel;
    * **náborové údaje** vrátane údajov poskytnutých v súvislosti so žiadosťou o zamestnanie alebo súvisiacou otázkou (v súlade s opisom uvedeným nižšie);
    * **Obchodné kontaktné údaje,** ako napríklad údaje týkajúce sa ďalších zamestnancov, vlastníkov, riaditeľov, riadiacich pracovníkov alebo zmluvných pracovníkov organizácie tretej strany (napr. podnik, spoločnosť, partnerstvo, živnostenský podnik, nezisková organizácia alebo vládna agentúra).
    * **marketingové a komunikačné údaje** vrátane vašich marketingových predvolieb a prihlásení na odber našich publikácií,
    * **finančné údaje** vrátane údajov o kreditných kartách alebo iných peňažných účtoch, aby sme vám mohli uľahčiť nákup našich produktov a služieb, ktoré sú dostupné na našich webových lokalitách;
    * **údaje na kontrolu vývozu,** ako napríklad údaje o vašej národnosti, občianstve a krajine trvalého pobytu, ktoré nám umožnia určiť, či ste podľa nariadení o kontrole vývozu oprávnení dostávať informácie o určitých technológiách;
    * **údaje o transakciách** vrátane objednávok a otázok týkajúcich sa našich produktov a služieb a podrobností o prichádzajúcich a odchádzajúcich platbách vrátane histórie nákupných objednávok a údajov potrebných na umožnenie platobných transakcií;
    * **údaje o registrácii** v rámci rôznych podujatí vrátane údajov, ktoré poskytnete pri vypĺňaní elektronických registračných formulárov; a
    * **vaše názory** vrátane prieskumov, odporúčaní a ďalšieho názoru na naše webové lokality, produkty a služby všeobecne.

Ak neposkytnete požadované údaje, môže sa stať, že vám nebudeme môcť poskytnúť požadovanú službu alebo vykonať požadovanú transakciu.

* **Údaje, ktoré o vás zhromažďujeme automaticky**. Pomocou súborov cookie a podobných technológií sledovania zhromažďujeme určité informácie o vašej návšteve našich webových lokalít. Vždy budeme rešpektovať všetky zákonné práva, ktorými nám môžete zabrániť tak urobiť. Údaje zhromaždené týmto spôsobom zahŕňajú:
    * **údaje o používaní** vrátane údajov o spôsobe používania našich webových lokalít, prezeraných webových stránkach, počte prenesených bajtov, prepojeniach, na ktoré kliknete, materiáloch, ku ktorým pristupujete, dátume a čase vášho prístupu k danej webovej lokalite, externej webovej lokalite, z ktorej ste prešli prostredníctvom prepojenia na jednu z našich webových lokalít, ako aj o ďalších činnostiach vykonávaných na našich webových lokalitách; a
    * **technické údaje,** ako napríklad údaje o adrese internetového protokolu (IP), type a možnostiach vášho prehliadača, nastavenom jazyku a používanom operačnom systéme.

Informácie o súboroch cookie a ďalších podobných technológiách sledovania, ktoré používame na našich webových lokalitách, nájdete v našom [oznámení o súboroch cookie](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#slovak).

* **Údaje o zemepisnej polohe**. Na niektorých webových lokalitách môžeme s vaším výslovným súhlasom zhromažďovať údaje o presnej aktuálnej polohe (t. j. zemepisnej polohe) vášho mobilného zariadenia. Tieto údaje budú použité iba na účely uľahčenia vášho používania webových lokalít, a to aj prostredníctvom našich poskytovateľov služieb, ktorí môžu tieto údaje spracovávať v súvislosti s poskytovaním služieb v našom mene. Ak bude udelený, svoj súhlas môžete neskôr zmeniť prostredníctvom predvolieb lokalizačných služieb, ktoré sú k dispozícii v nastaveniach mobilného zariadenia.
* **Údaje zhromaždené od tretích strán**. V súlade s platnými právnymi predpismi môžeme zhromažďovať vaše osobné údaje od tretích strán, ako sú napríklad webové lokality a aplikácie sociálnych médií, a kombinovať ich s údajmi, ktoré už máme, aby nám pomohli zlepšiť a prispôsobiť naše webové lokality vašim predvoľbám a na ďalšie účely uvedené v tomto vyhlásení o ochrane osobných údajov. Môžeme tiež zhromažďovať vaše obchodné kontaktné údaje od zamestnávateľa alebo iných tretích strán, aby sme umožnili alebo sa inak zapojili do tradičných obchodných činností a podobných administratívnych záležitostí.

**Používanie údajov**

Osobné údaje zhromaždené prostredníctvom našich webových lokalít alebo osobné údaje, ktoré nám poskytnete, keď nás kontaktujete, môžeme používať na nasledujúce účely:

* **Obchodné kontaktné údaje**. Spoločnosť Honeywell zhromažďuje a používa obchodné kontaktné údaje na zapojenie sa do komunikácií alebo transakcií a aj na vykonanie povinnej kontroly týkajúcej sa produktu alebo služby alebo ich poskytnutia či prijatia. Spoločnosť Honeywell môže napríklad zhromažďovať a používať tieto obchodné kontaktné údaje s cieľom umožniť a spravovať objednávky, zmluvy, záruky, údržby a podobné obchodné funkcie, na účely úverovej analýzy a zhromažďovania, na pomoc s našimi vlastnými internými zmluvnými a zákonnými požiadavkami a (ak je to potrebné) na obranu našich záujmov a nárokov.
* **Služby a transakcie**. Vaše osobné údaje môžeme používať na poskytovanie služieb pre vás alebo na vykonávanie transakcií, o ktoré požiadate, okrem iného napríklad na poskytovanie informácií o zakúpených alebo inak používaných produktoch či službách našej spoločnosti, registráciu zakúpených produktov, spracúvanie objednávok produktov, vybavovanie reklamácií, poskytovanie náhradných príručiek k produktom, vybavovanie žiadostí v rámci služieb zákazníkom a uľahčovanie používania našich webových lokalít.
* **Spravovanie a ochrana nášho podnikania a našich webových lokalít**. Vaše osobné údaje môžeme používať na spravovanie a ochranu nášho podnikania a našich webových lokalít vrátane riešenia problémov, údržby systémov, poskytovania podpory, poskytovania výkazov a hosťovania údajov.
* **Zlepšovanie nášho podnikania, webových lokalít, produktov a služieb**. Vaše osobné údaje môžeme používať na vykonávanie obchodných analýz a na iné účely, ktoré nám pomáhajú rozvíjať a zlepšovať kvalitu nášho podnikania a našich webových lokalít, produktov a služieb (vrátane nových produktov a služieb), napríklad prispôsobovaním našich webových lokalít vašim predvoľbám alebo záujmom.
* **Marketing**. V súlade s platnými právnymi predpismi a nariadeniami môžeme vaše osobné údaje používať na to, aby sme vás informovali o výrobkoch alebo službách, ktoré by vás mohli zaujímať, alebo na to, aby sme vás inými formami informovali o ponukách, podujatiach alebo novinkách, prieskumoch, osobitných ponukách a súvisiacich témach. Marketingovú komunikáciu zasielanú e-mailom môžete kedykoľvek bezplatne zrušiť prostredníctvom prepojenia na zrušenie jej odberu vo všetkých e-mailových marketingových materiáloch, ktoré od nás dostávate, prípadne nás môžete v tejto súvislosti kontaktovať prostredníctvom kontaktných údajov uvedených v tomto vyhlásení o ochrane osobných údajov. V závislosti od vašej krajiny pobytu môžete byť tiež schopní odhlásiť sa z iných typov marketingovej komunikácie. Pre viac informácií nás kontaktujte pomocou kontaktných údajov uvedených vo vyhlásení o ochrane osobných údajov. Niektoré jurisdikcie poskytujú jednotlivcom (napr. obyvateľom Kalifornie) právo požadovať určité informácie týkajúce sa nášho zverejňovania osobných údajov tretím stranám na účely priameho marketingu tretích strán. Ak chcete získať viac informácií o našich postupoch zverejňovania údajov na marketingové účely, kontaktujte nás v súlade s pokynmi uvedenými nižšie.
* **Záujmovo orientovaná reklama**. Zhromažďujeme údaje o vašich online aktivitách a identifikujeme vaše záujmy, aby sme mohli poskytovať reklamu, ktorá je pre vás najrelevantnejšia. Môžete sa odhlásiť z prijímania záujmovo orientovanej reklamy od spoločnosti Honeywell, ako je uvedené v našom [oznámení o súboroch cookie](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#slovak).
* **Finančné stimuly a vernostné programy**. Zhromažďujeme a používame osobné údaje na udržiavanie a spravovanie našich finančných stimulov a vernostných programov. Osobné údaje, ktoré poskytujete v týchto programoch, používame na ponúkanie jedinečných odmien, sledovanie stavu vášho programu a na umožnenie výmeny bodov programu za produkty, propagačné materiály, školiace semináre a ďalšie položky. V rozsahu povolenom právnymi predpismi môžeme tiež použiť akékoľvek osobné údaje, ktoré poskytnete v súvislosti s programom finančných stimulov, na akýkoľvek iný účel stanovený v tomto vyhlásení o ochrane osobných údajov. Prečítajte si podmienky každého programu finančných stimulov, do ktorého sa chcete zaregistrovať alebo sa ho zúčastniť, pretože tieto podmienky môžu byť úzko prispôsobené príslušnému programu. Ak súhlasíte s účasťou na týchto programoch, môžete tento súhlas kedykoľvek odvolať tak, že nás kontaktujete pomocou kontaktných údajov na konci tohto vyhlásenia o ochrane osobných údajov alebo v súlade s pokynmi uvedenými v podmienkach príslušného programu.
* **Žiadosti o zamestnanie**. V súvislosti so žiadosťou o zamestnanie alebo s požiadavkou na zamestnanie nám môžete poskytnúť informácie o sebe, ako napríklad životopis, profesijné referencie, informácie o vzdelaní a zamestnaní a informácie o odborných školeniach a certifikáciách. Naša spoločnosť a členovia našej skupiny môžu používať tieto údaje na účely zváženia zamestnania, previerok osoby a oprávnenosti na zamestnanie a iné účely stanovené v samostatnom vyhlásení o ochrane osobných údajov alebo v inom oznámení, ktoré je sprístupnené v súvislosti s vašou žiadosťou. Na vyžadovanie, zhromažďovanie a uchovávanie žiadostí o zamestnanie môžeme použiť tretiu stranu (napr. náborového pracovníka) alebo platformu sociálnych médií. Ďalšie informácie nájdete v našom dokumente [Oznámenie o ochrane osobných údajov žiadateľa](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/applicant-privacy-notice#slovak) .
* **Prieskum a analýza**. Vaše osobné údaje môžeme používať na vykonávanie prieskumov a analýz, ktoré nám pomáhajú analyzovať vaše nákupné predvoľby, identifikovať produkty a služby, ktoré najlepšie vyhovujú vašim požiadavkám, a merať efektívnosť zobrazovanej reklamy.
* **Presadzovanie právnych predpisov**: Zhromaždené osobné údaje môžeme používať na odhaľovanie, prevenciu a riešenie podvodov, porušení práv duševného vlastníctva, porušení našich podmienok, porušení právnych predpisov alebo iného zneužívania našich webových lokalít.

Ak to povoľujú platné právne predpisy, údaje zhromaždené prostredníctvom našich webových lokalít môžeme kombinovať s ostatnými údajmi, ktoré o vás evidujeme (napríklad s údajmi o tom, ako používate naše produkty a služby), aby sme vám mohli poskytovať lepšie a konzistentné možnosti pri interakciách s nami alebo na iné účely stanovené v tomto vyhlásení o ochrane osobných údajov.

**Právny základ nášho spracúvania údajov**

Ak to vyžadujú právne predpisy, budeme zaručovať, aby sa spracúvanie vašich osobných údajov vykonávalo na právnom základe. Náš právny základ bude vo väčšine prípadov závisieť od dotknutých osobných údajov a konkrétneho kontextu, v ktorom ich zhromažďujeme.

* **Zmluva**: spracovanie je nevyhnutné na výkon služieb, ktoré vám poskytujeme, alebo na účely podniknutia krokov (na vašu žiadosť) pred vykonaním a očakávaním týchto služieb;
* **Zákonná povinnosť**: spracúvanie je nevyhnutné na to, aby sme dodržiavali naše zákonné povinnosti vrátane dodržiavania platných právnych predpisov, nariadení, štátnych a obdobných požiadaviek, súdnych rozhodnutí alebo predvolaní;
* **Súhlas**: spracúvanie je založené na vašom súhlase so spracúvaním vašich osobných údajov na jeden alebo viacero zo stanovených účelov (napr. marketing);
* **Oprávnené záujmy**: spracúvanie je nevyhnutné na splnenie našich oprávnených záujmov, napríklad na vývoj a zdokonaľovanie našich webových lokalít, produktov a/alebo služieb v prospech našich zákazníkov; alebo
* **Životne dôležité záujmy**: spracúvanie je nevyhnutné na ochranu vašich životne dôležitých záujmov (napríklad z dôvodu ochrany zdravia a bezpečnosti, ak sa zúčastňujete stretnutia v sídle spoločnosti Honeywell).

Ak máte akékoľvek otázky alebo potrebujete ďalšie informácie týkajúce sa právneho základu, na ktorom zhromažďujeme a používame vaše osobné údaje, pošlite e-mail na adresu [HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com)

**Anonymizácia údajov**

V súlade s platnými právnymi predpismi môžeme anonymizovať vaše osobné údaje tak, aby ich nebolo možné použiť na vašu identifikáciu. Anonymizované údaje sa nepovažujú za osobné údaje, a preto sa na ne nevzťahuje toto vyhlásenie o ochrane osobných údajov. Anonymizované údaje môžeme zhromažďovať, používať, agregovať a zdieľať na akýkoľvek účel.

**Ako dlho uchovávame údaje**

Doba uchovávania vašich osobných údajov sa líši v závislosti od účelu ich spracúvania. Napríklad osobné údaje potrebné na to, aby sme vám mohli poskytovať produkty a služby alebo umožňovať vykonávanie požadovaných transakcií, uchovávame tak dlho, kým budete zákazníkmi spoločnosti Honeywell, alebo ak prostredníctvom našich webových lokalít podáte žiadosť o zamestnanie, podrobné informácie o vašej žiadosti budeme uchovávať po dobu stanovenú v tomto oznámení o ochrane osobných údajov, ktoré vám poskytneme v súvislosti s vašou žiadosťou alebo inak v súlade s právnymi predpismi. Vo všetkých ostatných prípadoch uchovávame vaše osobné údaje dovtedy, kým to bude potrebné na splnenie účelov uvedených v tomto vyhlásení o ochrane osobných údajov. Po uplynutí tejto doby budú buď anonymizované (ak to umožňujú platné právne predpisy), odstránené, alebo zničené.

**Zverejňovanie údajov**

Vaše osobné údaje môžeme zdieľať s vybratými tretími stranami v súlade s platnými právnymi predpismi vrátane podmienok stanovených nižšie:

* **Spoločnosti z našej skupiny**. Vaše osobné údaje môžeme zdieľať s našimi pridruženými spoločnosťami a spoločnosťami z našej skupiny, ak na to existujú primerané účely, ktoré sú stanovené v tomto vyhlásení o ochrane osobných údajov.
* **Poskytovatelia služieb**. Vaše osobné údaje môžeme zdieľať so spoločnosťami, s ktorými máme uzatvorenú zmluvu o poskytovaní služieb v našom mene, ako sú napríklad služby hosťovania webových lokalít, vykonávanie prieskumov, spracúvanie transakcií, analyzovanie našich webových lokalít a vykonávanie analýz na zlepšovanie kvality nášho podnikania, našich webových lokalít, produktov a služieb. Od týchto poskytovateľov služieb vyžadujeme, aby vaše osobné údaje chránili ako dôverné.
* **Distribútori a ďalší dôveryhodní obchodní partneri**. Vaše osobné údaje môžeme zdieľať s tretími stranami, ktoré distribuujú naše produkty, ako aj s ďalšími dôveryhodnými obchodnými partnermi, aby sme im umožnili napríklad posielať vám marketingové oznámenia. Takéto zdieľanie osobných údajov na marketingové účely sa bude vykonávať v súlade s platnými právnymi predpismi a nariadeniami.
* **Zverejňovanie v súvislosti s transakciami**. V spojení s určitými transakciami môžeme zverejniť časť alebo všetky osobné údaje finančným inštitúciám, štátnym subjektom, zásielkovým spoločnostiam alebo poštovým službám s cieľom uskutočnenia transakcie.
* **Zverejňovania v súvislosti s akvizíciami alebo odpredajmi**. Naša spoločnosť Honeywell sa za určitých okolností môže zo strategických alebo iných obchodných dôvodov rozhodnúť v niektorých krajinách predať, kúpiť, odpredať, vykonať zlúčenie alebo iným spôsobom reorganizovať svoje podniky. Informácie, ktoré o vás uchovávame, môžeme zverejniť v primeranom rozsahu potrebnom na vyjednanie alebo realizáciu zlúčenia, akvizície, odpredaja alebo predaja všetkého majetku spoločnosti Honeywell alebo jeho časti.
* **Zverejňovanie z iných dôvodov**. Osobné údaje môžeme zverejniť, ak to vyžadujú alebo ak nás k tomu oprávňujú právne predpisy, alebo ak to urobíme v dobrej viere, že je to nutné na splnenie zákonných požiadaviek alebo právneho procesu vedenému voči nám, na ochranu a obranu našich práv alebo majetku alebo v naliehavých prípadoch na ochranu bezpečnosti osôb.

**Medzinárodné prenosy**

Spoločnosť Honeywell je globálna organizácia a vaše osobné údaje môžu byť v súlade s platnými právnymi predpismi prenášané, uchovávané, ukladané alebo používané na rôznych miestach po celom svete, ako sú napríklad USA, Mexiko a India. To znamená, že keď zhromažďujeme vaše osobné údaje, môžu byť spracované v krajinách, ktorých právne predpisy o ochrane údajov sa môžu líšiť od právnych predpisov vo vašej krajine. Spoločnosť Honeywell však vždy podnikne primerané kroky na ochranu vášho súkromia a na zabezpečenie úrovne ochrany osobných údajov, ktorá je porovnateľná s úrovňou vo vašej krajine pobytu, ktoré zahŕňajú implementáciu štandardných zmluvných doložiek Európskej komisie. Ak chcete získať ďalšie informácie o príslušných uplatnených bezpečnostných opatreniach na ochranu vašich osobných údajov, kontaktujte nás na adrese [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com).

**Zabezpečenie**

Zaväzujeme sa chrániť vaše osobné údaje, aby boli v bezpečí. Používame technické a organizačné opatrenia na zabezpečenie úrovne bezpečnosti zodpovedajúcej riziku spracovania vašich osobných údajov. Ak chcete získať viac informácií o tom, ako spoločnosť Honeywell chráni vaše osobné údaje, kontaktujte nás na adrese [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com)

**Vaše práva**

V závislosti od platných právnych predpisov môžete mať určité práva týkajúce sa vašich osobných údajov.

* Môžete mať právo **pristupovať, kontrolovať, aktualizovať** alebo **požiadať o odstránenie** vašich osobných údajov.
* Môžete **namietať** proti spracovaniu vašich osobných údajov, požiadať nás **obmedziť** spracovanie vašich osobných údajov alebo požiadať **o prenosnosť** vašich osobných údajov.
* Môžete mať právo **nenechať o sebe rozhodovať výlučne na základe automatizovaného spracovania vrátane profilovania,** ak toto rozhodnutie vytvára o vás právne účinky alebo vás výrazne ovplyvňuje.
* Podobne, ak sme zhromaždili a spracovali vaše osobné údaje s vašim súhlasom, potom **svoj súhlas môžete kedykoľvek odvolať**. Odvolanie súhlasu neovplyvní zákonnosť spracovania, ktoré sme vykonali pred vašim odvolaním, ani to neovplyvní spracovanie vašich osobných údajov, ktoré sa vykonáva na základe iných zákonných dôvodov ako je súhlas.
* Môžete mať právo **odhlásiť sa z predaja vašich osobných údajov**. Spoločnosť Honeywell nepredáva vaše osobné údaje tretím stranám pre zisk. Vaše osobné údaje však zdieľame alebo inak poskytujeme tretím stranám v súlade s týmto vyhlásením o ochrane osobných údajov a naším [oznámením o súboroch cookie](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#slovak). S tretími stranami napríklad spolupracujeme pri distribúcii našich produktov, poskytovaní technickej pomoci pre vás, prevádzkovaní analytických nástrojov a funkcií webových lokalít a zaoberáme sa marketingom a predajom našich produktov a služieb. Takéto činnosti môžu zahŕňať zverejňovanie vašich osobných údajov tretím stranám a podľa určitých (ale nie všetkých) právnych predpisov na ochranu údajov sa môžu považovať za „predaj“ údajov.
* Máte právo **sťažovať sa** orgánu na ochranu údajov zodpovednému za dohľad nad dodržiavaním právnych predpisov o ochrane údajov vo vašej jurisdikcii na naše zhromažďovanie a používanie vašich osobných údajov, ak sa domnievate, že spracovanie vašich osobných údajov nie je v súlade s právnymi predpismi o ochrane údajov. Napríklad jednotlivci v EHP majú právo podať sťažnosť kompetentným orgánom na ochranu údajov, ktorých zoznam je dostupný na adrese: [https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/board/members\_en](https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/board/members_en). Veľmi by sme ocenili, keby ste nám umožnili vyriešiť vzniknutý problém, preto nás v prípade akýchkoľvek sťažností kontaktujte. Nebudeme diskriminovať jednotlivcov za uplatňovanie ich práv na ochranu osobných údajov.

Zabezpečíme, aby ste si mohli uplatňovať svoje práva v súlade s platnými právnymi predpismi. Aj keď sa na vaše osobné údaje neposkytuje ochrana podľa právnych predpisov o ochrane údajov alebo sa na ne nevzťahuje iný právny predpis, môžeme sa pokúsiť vyhovieť akejkoľvek žiadosti alebo otázke, ktoré môžete mať v súvislosti s našimi činnosťami v oblasti spracovania údajov. Ak máte otázky týkajúce sa vašich práv alebo ich chcete uplatniť, môžete nás kontaktovať na adrese [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com) alebo podajte otázky týkajúce sa ochrany osobných údajov prostredníctvom nášho interaktívneho webového formulára na nasledujúcom prepojení:

**Údaje detí**

Naše webové lokality nie sú zamerané na deti mladšie ako šestnásť (16) rokov a nemali by ich používať. Vedome nezhromažďujeme, nepoužívame ani nepredávame údaje týchto osôb. Ak ste podľa právnych predpisov vašej krajiny maloletí, nezadávajte žiadne osobné údaje prostredníctvom našich webových lokalít.

**Prepojenia na iné webové lokality**

Naše webové lokality môžu obsahovať prepojenia na webové lokality, produkty a služby tretích strán. Za tieto webové lokality, produkty a služby, ich zásady ani ich zhromažďovanie či iné spracúvanie vašich osobných údajov nenesieme žiadnu zodpovednosť. Postupy týchto tretích strán sa riadia ich vlastnými zásadami o ochrane osobných údajov. Odporúčame vám, aby ste sa oboznámili so zásadami ochrany osobných údajov týchto tretích strán.

**Kontaktujte nás**

Ak máte otázky týkajúce sa tohto vyhlásenia o ochrane osobných údajov alebo nášho spracúvania vašich osobných údajov, chcete podať sťažnosť alebo sa obrátiť na osobu zodpovednú za ochranu údajov, použite kontaktné údaje uvedené nižšie. Riešenie otázky s cieľom dosiahnuť uspokojivý výsledok sa bude hľadať v čo najkratšom čase.

Interaktívny webový formulár:  

E-mail:  

Poštová adresa:  
Ochrana osobných údajov spoločnosti Honeywell  
4D5  
115 Tabor Road  
Morris Plains, NJ 07950

Bezplatné číslo:  

**Zmeny tohto vyhlásenia o ochrane osobných údajov**

Toto vyhlásenie o ochrane osobných údajov môžeme príležitostne aktualizovať. V takom prípade sa zmení aj dátum „Posledná aktualizácia“ uvedený v hornej časti vyhlásenia o ochrane osobných údajov a podnikneme príslušné ďalšie kroky vyžadované platnými právnymi predpismi.

**Posledná aktualizácia 11. júna 2021**

**Última actualización: 11 de junio de 2021**

**Introducción**

Honeywell International Inc. ("**Honeywell**", "**nuestro**", "**nosotros**" o "**nos**"), es el "controlador de datos" de la información personal que recopilamos sobre usted cuando visita o utiliza alguno de nuestros sitios web, o usa alguno de nuestros productos, servicios o aplicaciones vinculados a esta declaración de privacidad (en conjunto, nuestros "**Sitios**"). Esta declaración de privacidad explica cómo recopilamos, compartimos y utilizamos su información personal de esta forma y cómo puede ejercer sus derechos de privacidad.

Cuando interactuamos con usted, también podemos proporcionarle avisos de privacidad adicionales sobre actividades de procesamiento específicas u ofrecerle opciones adicionales sobre cómo Honeywell procesa su información personal en ese momento en particular.

Haga clic en uno de los enlaces inferiores para ir a la sección que le interese:

**Cómo recopilamos la información**

* **Recopilamos la información directamente de usted.** Podemos pedirle información personal para prestarle un servicio o llevar a cabo una transacción que haya solicitado. También puede proporcionarnos información personal al contactar o interactuar con nosotros (por ejemplo, con un comentario, consulta o solicitud de atención al cliente cuando visita nuestro sitio web) o al registrar una cuenta para utilizar nuestros Sitios. Esta información personal puede incluir:
    * **Datos de identidad,** como su nombre, cargo, el nombre de su empresa/organización, dirección de correo electrónico, números de teléfono y dirección física (incluidos la calle, la ciudad, la provincia, el código postal y/o el país);
    * **Datos de registro,** proporcionados por usted cuando registra una cuenta para utilizar nuestros Sitios, incluidos los nombres de usuario y las contraseñas;
    * **Datos de contratación,** incluida información enviada en relación con una solicitud de empleo o consulta (como se explica a continuación);
    * **Datos de contacto empresariales,** como información relacionada con otros empleados, propietarios, directores, directivos o contratistas de organizaciones externas (por ejemplo, negocios, empresas, sociedades, propietarios únicos, organizaciones sin ánimo de lucro o agencias gubernamentales).
    * **Datos de marketing y de comunicación,** incluidas sus preferencias de marketing y sus suscripciones a nuestras publicaciones;
    * **Información financiera,** incluida la tarjeta de crédito u otros datos de la cuenta financiera que nos permita facilitarle la compra de productos y servicios de la empresa que puedan estar disponibles en nuestros Sitios;
    * **Información de control de las exportaciones,** como su nacionalidad, ciudadanía y país de residencia, que nos permita determinar su idoneidad bajo la normativa de control de exportaciones para recibir información sobre ciertas tecnologías;
    * **Información de transacciones,** incluidos pedidos y consultas sobre nuestros productos y servicios, así como detalles de pagos enviados y recibidos por usted, incluyendo el historial de órdenes de compra y la información necesaria para facilitar las transacciones de pago;
    * **Información de registro de eventos,** incluida la información que nos proporciona al rellenar formularios de inscripción electrónica; y
    * **Sus comentarios,** incluidas las encuestas, las recomendaciones u otros comentarios sobre nuestros Sitios, así como de nuestros productos y servicios en general.

Si no nos facilita la información solicitada, es posible que no podamos proporcionarle el servicio requerido ni completar su transacción.

* **Información que recopilamos automáticamente sobre usted.** Obtenemos cierta información sobre su visita a nuestros Sitios utilizando cookies y tecnologías de seguimiento similares. Siempre respetaremos cualquier derecho legal que pueda tener para evitar que lo hagamos. La información recopilada de esta forma incluye:
    * **Datos de uso,** incluida información sobre cómo utiliza nuestros Sitios, qué páginas visita, el número de bytes transferidos, los enlaces en los que hace clic, los materiales a los que accede, la fecha y la hora a las que accede al Sitio, el sitio web desde el que enlazó a uno de nuestros Sitios y otras acciones realizadas en los Sitios; y
    * **Datos técnicos,** como su dirección IP (Protocolo de Internet), el tipo, capacidad e idioma del navegador y su sistema operativo.

Para obtener más información sobre las cookies y otras tecnologías de seguimiento similares que utilizamos en nuestro Sitios, consulte nuestro [Aviso de cookies](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#spanish).

* **Información de geolocalización.** En determinados Sitios, con su consentimiento, podríamos recopilar la ubicación precisa y en tiempo real (es decir, la geolocalización) de su dispositivo móvil. Esta información se utilizará únicamente con el fin de facilitarle el uso de los Sitios, incluso por parte de nuestros proveedores de servicio, que podrían procesar esta información en relación con la prestación de servicios en nuestro nombre. Si se da el caso, podría ajustar este consentimiento gestionando sus preferencias de servicios de ubicación a través de la configuración de su dispositivo móvil.
* **Información recopilada por terceros.** De acuerdo con la legislación aplicable, podríamos recopilar información personal sobre usted de terceros, como sitios web y aplicaciones de redes sociales, y combinarla con la información sobre usted de la que ya disponemos para ayudarnos a mejorar y personalizar nuestros Sitios según sus preferencias y para otros fines establecidos en esta declaración de privacidad. También podríamos recopilar su información de contacto empresarial de su compañía o de otros terceros para facilitar o participar en actividades comerciales tradicionales y asuntos administrativos similares.

**Nuestro uso de la información**

Podríamos utilizar la información personal recopilada a través de nuestros Sitios o cuando contacta con nosotros para propósitos que incluyen:

* **Datos de contacto empresariales.** Honeywell recopila y utiliza datos de contacto empresariales para involucrarse en comunicaciones o transacciones, incluso para realizar la debida diligencia con respecto a un producto o servicio, o a su provisión o recepción. Por ejemplo, Honeywell podría recopilar y utilizar estos datos de contacto empresariales para facilitar y gestionar pedidos, contratos, garantías, mantenimiento y funciones comerciales similares, con fines de análisis y cobranza de crédito, para que nos ayuden con nuestros requisitos legales y de cumplimiento, y (si es necesario) para defender nuestros intereses y derechos.
* **Servicios y transacciones.** Podríamos usar su información personal para prestarle servicios o llevar a cabo transacciones que haya solicitado, entre las que se incluyen proporcionarle información sobre productos o servicios de la Empresa que haya adquirido o que utilice, registrar los productos adquiridos, procesar los pedidos de productos, gestionar reclamaciones de garantía, sustituir manuales de productos, responder a solicitudes de atención al cliente y facilitar el uso de nuestros Sitios.
* **Administración y protección de nuestra empresa y nuestros Sitios.** Podríamos utilizar su información personal para administrar y proteger nuestra empresa y nuestros Sitios, incluyendo la resolución de problemas, el mantenimiento del sistema, el servicio de asistencia técnica, las notificaciones y el alojamiento de datos.
* **Mejora de nuestra empresa, Sitios, productos y servicios.** Podríamos utilizar su información personal para llevar a cabo análisis empresariales o para otros fines que nos ayuden a desarrollar y mejorar la calidad de nuestra empresa, Sitios, productos y servicios (incluidos nuevos productos y servicios), por ejemplo, personalizando nuestros Sitios en función de sus preferencias o intereses particulares.
* **Marketing.** De acuerdo con las leyes y normativas aplicables, podríamos utilizar su información personal para informarle acerca de los productos o servicios que pudieran interesarle y para comunicarle ofertas, eventos y noticias, encuestas, ofertas especiales y temas relacionados. Tiene la posibilidad de darse de baja de las comunicaciones de marketing enviadas por correo electrónico en cualquier momento y de forma gratuita utilizando el enlace "Anular suscripción" de cualquier material de marketing que reciba por nuestra parte o bien poniéndose en contacto con nosotros a través de los datos de contacto incluidos en esta declaración de privacidad. En función de su país de residencia, también puede darse de baja de otros tipos de comunicaciones de marketing; póngase en contacto con nosotros utilizando los datos de contacto que se muestran en la declaración de privacidad para obtener más información. Algunas jurisdicciones brindan a las personas (por ejemplo, los residentes de California) el derecho a solicitar determinada información con respecto a nuestra divulgación de información personal a terceros para fines de marketing directo de terceros. Para obtener más información sobre nuestras prácticas de divulgación de datos con fines de marketing, póngase en contacto con nosotros siguiendo las instrucciones que se indican a continuación.
* **Publicidad personalizada.** Recopilamos datos sobre sus actividades en línea e identificamos sus intereses para poder mostrarle los anuncios que sean más relevantes para usted. Puede darse de baja de esta publicidad personalizada de Honeywell tal y como se explica en nuestro [Aviso de cookies](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#spanish).
* **Incentivos económicos y programas de fidelización.** Recopilamos y utilizamos información personal para mantener y administrar nuestros incentivos económicos y nuestros programas de fidelización. Utilizamos la información personal que usted nos facilita en esos programas para ofrecerle recompensas únicas, comprobar el estado de su programa y facilitar el intercambio de puntos del programa por productos, materiales promocionales, talleres de formación y otros artículos. En la medida en que lo permita la ley, también podemos utilizar cualquier información personal que nos facilite dentro del contexto de un programa de incentivo económico para cualquier otro propósito establecido en esta declaración de privacidad. Revise los términos y condiciones de cada programa de incentivo económico en los que quisiera registrarse o participar, ya que dichos términos y condiciones pueden estar estrictamente adaptados al programa correspondiente. Si acepta participar en estos programas, puede retirar ese consentimiento en cualquier momento poniéndose en contacto con nosotros utilizando los datos de contacto al final de esta declaración de privacidad o siguiendo las instrucciones establecidas en los términos y condiciones del programa correspondiente.
* **Solicitudes de empleo.** En relación con una consulta o una solicitud de empleo, puede facilitarnos información sobre usted como, por ejemplo, un currículum vitae, referencias profesionales, información sobre formación y trabajos anteriores, así como información sobre certificados y formación profesional. Nosotros y los miembros de nuestro grupo podríamos utilizar esta información para estudiar su solicitud de empleo, comprobar su experiencia y para la elegibilidad laboral, y como se establezca en cualquier declaración de privacidad independiente u otro aviso disponible en relación a su solicitud. Podríamos utilizar un tercero (por ejemplo, una empresa de selección de personal) o una plataforma de redes sociales para solicitar, recopilar y conservar solicitudes de empleo. Para obtener más información, lea nuestro [Aviso de privacidad del solicitante](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/applicant-privacy-notice#spanish).
* **Investigación y análisis.** Podríamos utilizar su información personal para llevar a cabo estudios y análisis que nos ayuden a analizar sus preferencias de compra, identificar los productos y servicios que mejor satisfagan sus necesidades y medir la eficacia de la publicidad que le ofrecemos.
* **Cumplimiento de normas:** podemos utilizar la información personal que recopilamos para detectar, prevenir y actuar contra el fraude, la vulneración de la propiedad intelectual, las infracciones de nuestros términos y condiciones, las infracciones de la ley u otros usos indebidos de nuestros Sitios.

En la medida en que lo permita la ley, podríamos combinar la información que recopilamos a través de nuestros Sitios con otra información que tengamos sobre usted (por ejemplo, información sobre el uso que hace de nuestros productos y servicios) para ofrecerle una experiencia de cliente mejorada y coherente al interactuar con nosotros o para otros fines establecidos en esta declaración de privacidad.

**La base legal sobre la que procesamos la información**

Si lo requiere la ley, nos aseguraremos de que haya una base legal para el procesamiento de su información personal. En la mayoría de los casos, nuestra base legal dependerá de la información personal en cuestión y del contexto específico en el que la recopilemos.

* **Contrato:** el procesamiento es necesario para el funcionamiento de los servicios que le proporcionamos, o para tomar medidas (si usted lo solicita) antes de, y anticipando, la realización de dichos servicios;
* **Obligación legal:** el procesamiento es necesario para cumplir con nuestras obligaciones legales, incluido el cumplimiento de las leyes, los reglamentos, las solicitudes gubernamentales y cuasi gubernamentales, las órdenes judiciales o las citaciones aplicables;
* **Consentimiento:** el procesamiento se basa en su consentimiento para el procesamiento de la información personal para uno o más propósitos especificados (por ejemplo, marketing);
* **Intereses legítimos:** el procesamiento es necesario para satisfacer nuestros intereses legítimos, por ejemplo, para desarrollar y mejorar nuestros Sitios, productos y/o servicios en beneficio de nuestros clientes; o
* **Intereses vitales:** el procesamiento es necesario para proteger sus intereses vitales (por ejemplo, motivos de salud y seguridad si asiste a una reunión en una ubicación de Honeywell).

Si tiene alguna duda o necesita más información acerca de la base legal sobre la que recopilamos y utilizamos su información personal, envíe un correo electrónico a [HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com)

**Anonimización de la información**

De acuerdo con la ley aplicable, podríamos anonimizar su información personal para que no pueda utilizarse en su identificación. La información anonimizada no se considera información personal y, por lo tanto, no está sujeta a esta declaración de privacidad. Podríamos recopilar, utilizar, agrupar y compartir información anonimizada para cualquier propósito.

**Cuánto tiempo almacenamos la información**

El periodo de tiempo durante el cual almacenamos su información personal puede variar en función de la finalidad del procesamiento. Por ejemplo, almacenamos información personal necesaria para proporcionarle productos y servicios o para facilitar transacciones que haya solicitado, durante tanto tiempo como sea cliente de Honeywell o, si envía una solicitud de empleo a través de nuestros Sitios, mantendremos los datos de su solicitud como se describe en el aviso de privacidad que se pone a su disposición en relación con su solicitud o según lo requiera la ley. En cualquier otro caso, almacenamos la información personal durante tanto tiempo como sea necesario para cumplir con los propósitos descritos en esta declaración de privacidad y, tras este tiempo, se anonimiza (donde lo permita la ley aplicable), se borra o se destruye.

**Divulgación de la información**

Podríamos compartir su información personal con terceros seleccionados de acuerdo con la legislación aplicable, incluyendo lo que se establece a continuación:

* **Empresas de nuestro grupo.** Podemos compartir su información personal con nuestras filiales y empresas del grupo en la medida en que sea razonablemente necesario para los fines establecidos en esta declaración de privacidad.
* **Proveedores de servicios.** Podemos compartir su información personal con empresas que hemos contratado para que presten servicios en nuestro nombre, por ejemplo, para que alojen sitios web, lleven a cabo encuestas, procesen transacciones, analicen nuestros Sitios y lleven a cabo análisis para mejorar la calidad de nuestro negocio, nuestros Sitios, los productos y los servicios. Exigimos a estos proveedores de servicio que protejan la confidencialidad de su información personal.
* **Distribuidores y otros socios empresariales de confianza.** Podemos compartir su información personal con terceros que distribuyen nuestros productos y con otros socios empresariales de confianza para diversos fines, entre los que se incluyen permitir a dichos terceros que le envíen comunicaciones de marketing. Este uso compartido de la información personal para fines de marketing se llevará a cabo de acuerdo con la legislación y reglamentos aplicables.
* **Revelación de información relacionada con las transacciones.** Con respecto a determinadas transacciones, podemos revelar parte o toda su información personal a las instituciones financieras, entidades gubernamentales y empresas de mensajería o servicios postales que participen en la realización de la transacción.
* **Revelación de información relacionada con las adquisiciones o desinversiones.** Pueden surgir circunstancias en las que, por razones estratégicas u otras razones comerciales, Honeywell decida vender, comprar, desinvertir, fusionar o reorganizar de otro modo sus negocios en algunos países. Podríamos divulgar información que conservamos de usted el tiempo que estimemos necesario para proseguir con la negociación o realización de una fusión, adquisición, desinversión o venta de todos o parte de los activos de Honeywell.
* **Revelación por otros motivos.** Podemos revelar su información personal si se nos autoriza o exige por ley o si creemos de buena fe que dicha acción es necesaria para cumplir con los requisitos legales o con procesos legales, para proteger y defender nuestros derechos o propiedades o, en circunstancias urgentes, para proteger la seguridad personal de cualquier persona.

**Transferencias internacionales**

Honeywell es una empresa global y su información personal puede ser transferida, conservada, almacenada y utilizada en diferentes ubicaciones de todo el mundo, como Estados Unidos, México y la India de acuerdo con la ley aplicable. Esto significa que cuando recopilamos su información personal, puede que sea procesada en países que tengan leyes de protección de datos distintas a las leyes de su país. No obstante, Honeywell siempre tomará medidas razonables para proteger su privacidad y para proporcionar un nivel de protección de la información personal que sea comparable a la de su país de residencia, lo que incluye la implementación de las cláusulas contractuales estándar de la Comisión Europea. Para obtener más información sobre los dispositivos de seguridad establecidos para proteger su información personal, contacte con nosotros a través de [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com).

**Seguridad**

Nos comprometemos a proteger la seguridad de su información personal. Utilizamos medidas técnicas y organizativas para proporcionar un nivel de seguridad adecuado al riesgo de procesar su información personal. Para obtener más información sobre cómo Honeywell protege su información personal, contacte con nosotros a través de [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com).

**Sus derechos**

En función de la ley aplicable, puede tener determinados derechos con respecto a su información personal.

* Puede tener derecho a **acceder, corregir, actualizar** o **solicitar la eliminación** de su información personal.
* Puede **oponerse** al procesamiento de su información personal, pedirnos que **restrinjamos** el procesamiento de su información personal o solicitar la **portabilidad** de su información personal.
* Podría tener derecho **a que no se tome una decisión sobre usted que se base únicamente en el procesamiento automatizado, incluida la elaboración de perfiles**, si esa decisión produce efectos legales sobre usted o le afecta significativamente.
* Del mismo modo, si hemos recopilado y procesado su información personal con su consentimiento, entonces **puede retirar su consentimiento en cualquier momento**. Retirar su consentimiento no afectará a la legalidad de ningún procesamiento que hubiéramos llevado a cabo antes de que lo retirara, ni afectará al procesamiento de su información personal que se haya llevado a cabo basándose en motivos legales de procesamiento distintos a los del consentimiento.
* Puede tener derecho a **rechazar la venta de su información personal**. Honeywell no vende su información personal a terceros con fines de lucro. No obstante, sí compartimos o revelamos su información personal a terceros de acuerdo con esta declaración de privacidad y nuestro [Aviso de cookies](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#spanish). Por ejemplo, nos relacionamos con terceros para distribuir nuestros productos, proporcionarle asistencia técnica, operar herramientas y funciones analíticas de sitios web, y participar en el marketing y las ventas de nuestros productos y servicios. Estas actividades pueden implicar la revelación de su información personal a terceros y puedes ser consideradas "ventas" de datos según ciertas (pero no todas) leyes de protección de datos.
* Tiene derecho a **reclamar** ante una autoridad de protección de datos responsable de supervisar el cumplimiento de la ley de protección de datos en su jurisdicción sobre nuestra recopilación y uso de su información personal si cree que nuestro procesamiento de su información personal no cumple con la ley de protección de datos. Por ejemplo, las personas del EEE tienen derecho a presentar una queja ante la autoridad de protección de datos competente, cuya lista se puede consultar en: [https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/board/members\_en](https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/board/members_en). Sin embargo, agradeceríamos la oportunidad de poder atender sus preocupaciones, así que, por favor, no dude en contactar con nosotros en relación con cualquier reclamación que pueda tener. No discriminaremos a las personas por ejercer sus derechos de privacidad de datos.

Le facilitaremos el ejercicio de los derechos que le corresponden de acuerdo con la ley aplicable. No obstante, incluso si su información personal no está protegida, o de otra manera sujeta, a una ley de protección de datos, podemos tratar de atender cualquier solicitud o consulta que pueda tener con respecto a nuestras actividades de procesamiento de datos. Si tiene dudas sobre sus derechos o quiere ejercerlos, puede contactar con nosotros a través de [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com) o enviar dudas relacionadas con la privacidad a través de nuestro formulario web interactivo en el siguiente enlace:

**Información sobre menores**

Nuestros Sitios no están dirigidos y no deberían ser utilizados por menores de dieciséis (16) años y no recopilamos, utilizamos ni vendemos información de dichas personas a sabiendas. Si es menor de edad según lo entienden las leyes de su país, no envíe ninguna información personal a través de nuestros Sitios.

**Enlaces a otros sitios web**

Nuestros Sitios pueden contener enlaces a páginas web, productos o servicios de terceros. No tenemos ninguna obligación o responsabilidad sobre esos sitios web, productos y servicios, sus políticas o su recopilación u otro procesamiento de su información personal. Las prácticas de esos terceros se rigen por sus propias políticas de privacidad. Le recomendamos que se informe sobre las políticas de privacidad de esos terceros.

**Contacte con nosotros**

Si tiene dudas en relación con esta declaración de privacidad o sobre el tratamiento de su información personal, quiere presentar una queja o desea contactar con nuestro delegado de protección de datos, póngase en contacto con nosotros utilizando la información de contacto que verá más abajo. Atenderemos su cuestión de inmediato y haremos todo lo posible por llegar a una resolución satisfactoria.

Formulario web interactivo:  
  
Correo electrónico:  
  
Dirección postal:  
Honeywell Privacy  
4D5  
115 Tabor Road  
Morris Plains, NJ 07950  
  
Número gratuito:  

**Cambios en esta declaración de privacidad**

En ocasiones, podemos actualizar esta declaración de privacidad. Cuando lo hagamos, revisaremos la fecha de "última actualización" del inicio de la declaración de privacidad y tomaremos las medidas adicionales que requiera la ley.

**Última actualización: 11 de junio de 2021**

**Senast uppdaterad den 11 juni 2021**

**Introduktion**

Honeywell International Inc. (”**Honeywell**”, ”**vår**”, ”**oss**” eller ”**vi**”) är den ”personuppgiftsansvarige” för den personliga informationen vi samlar in om dig när du besöker eller använder någon av våra webbplatser, eller använder produkter, tjänster och applikationer som är kopplade till denna sekretesspolicy (tillsammans, våra ”**webbplatser**”). Denna sekretesspolicy förklarar hur vi samlar in, delar och använder din personliga information som samlas in på detta sätt och hur du kan utöva dina integritetsrättigheter.

När vi interagerar med dig kan vi också ge dig ytterligare sekretessmeddelanden om specifika behandlingsaktiviteter eller erbjuda ytterligare valmöjligheter gällande hur Honeywell behandlar din personliga information vid den aktuella tidpunkten.

Klicka på någon av länkarna nedan för att gå till det avsnitt som intresserar dig:

**Insamling av information**

* **Information som samlas in direkt från dig.** Vi kan be dig om personlig information för att tillhandahålla en tjänst eller genomföra en transaktion som du har begärt. Du kan också tillhandahålla personlig information till oss när du kontaktar eller interagerar med oss (t.ex. i en kommentar, förfrågan eller kundsupportärende, webbplatsbesökare) eller registrerar ett konto för att använda våra webbplatser. Denna personliga information kan inkludera:
    * **Identitetsinformation,** så som ditt namn, titel, företags-/organisationsnamn, e-postadress, telefonnummer och fysisk adress (inklusive gata, stad, delstat, postnummer och/eller land);
    * **Uppgifter för registrering som** tillhandahålls av dig när du registrerar ett konto för att använda våra webbplatser, inklusive användarnamn och lösenord;
    * **Rekryteringsinformation,** inklusive information lämnad i samband med en jobbansökan eller förfrågan (enligt beskrivningen nedan);
    * **Kontaktuppgifter för företag**, så som information relaterad till andra anställda, ägare, styrelseledamöter, befattningshavare eller entreprenörer från en tredjepartsorganisation (t.ex. verksamhet, företag, partnerskap, enmansföretag, ideell verksamhet eller statlig myndighet).
    * **Marknadsförings- och kommunikationsdata,** inklusive dina marknadsföringspreferenser och dina prenumerationer på våra publikationer;
    * **Ekonomisk information,** inklusive kreditkorts- eller annan finansiell kontoinformation i syfte att göra det möjligt för oss att underlätta ditt köp av företagets produkter och tjänster som kan finnas tillgängliga på våra webbplatser;
    * **Exportkontrollinformation,** så som din nationalitet, medborgarskap och bosättningsland, som gör det möjligt för oss att avgöra din behörighet enligt exportkontrollbestämmelser att få information om vissa tekniker;
    * **Transaktionsdata,** inklusive förfrågningar om och beställningar av våra produkter och tjänster samt information om betalningar till och från dig, inklusive inköpsorderhistorik och information som behövs för att underlätta betalningstransaktioner;
    * **Registreringsinformation för evenemang,** inklusive information som du tillhandahåller när du fyller i registreringsformulär online; och
    * **Din feedback,** inklusive undersökningar, rekommendationer eller annan feedback från dig om våra webbplatser samt våra produkter och tjänster i allmänhet.

När du inte tillhandahåller efterfrågad information kanske vi inte kan tillhandahålla den begärda tjänsten eller genomföra din transaktion.

* **Information vi automatiskt samlar in om dig.** Vi samlar in viss information om ditt besök på våra webbplatser med hjälp av cookies och liknande spårningstekniker. Vi kommer alltid att respektera de rättigheter du har enligt lag att förhindra att vi gör detta. Uppgifter som samlas in på detta sätt inkluderar:
    * **Användningsdata,** inklusive information om hur du använder våra webbplatser, vilka sidor du visar, antalet byte som överförts, länkarna du klickar på, materialet du tillgår, datum och tid när du besöker webbplatsen, webbplatsen från vilken du länkat till någon av våra webbplatser samt andra åtgärder som vidtagits på webbplatserna; och
    * **Tekniska data,** så som din IP-adress (Internet Protocol), din webbläsartyp, dess funktioner, språk och ditt operativsystem.

För information om cookies och andra liknande spårningsteknologier som vi använder på våra webbplatser, se vårt [Meddelande om användning av cookies](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#swedish).

* **Information om geografisk plats.** På vissa webbplatser, med ditt samtycke, kan vi i realtid registrera den exakta platsen (dvs. geografisk plats) din mobila enhet befinner sig på. Denna information kommer endast att användas för att underlätta din användning av webbplatserna, inklusive våra tjänsteleverantörer som kan behandla denna information i samband med att de tillhandahåller tjänster för vår räkning. Om du har gett ditt samtycke kan du ändra detta genom att hantera dina inställningar för platstjänster via inställningarna på din mobila enhet.
* **Information som samlats in från tredje part.** I enlighet med tillämplig lag kan vi samla in personlig information om dig från tredje part, till exempel webbplatser och applikationer för sociala medier och kombinera den med information vi redan har, för att hjälpa oss att förbättra och anpassa våra webbplatser enligt dina preferenser och för andra ändamål som anges i denna sekretesspolicy. Vi kan också samla in din företagskontaktinformation via din arbetsgivare eller andra tredje parter för att underlätta eller på annat sätt delta i traditionell affärsverksamhet och liknande administrativa frågor.

**Användning av information**

Vi kan använda den personliga information som samlas in via våra webbplatser eller när du kontaktar oss för ändamål som inkluderar:

* **Företagskontaktinformation.** Honeywell samlar in och använder företagskontaktinformation för att delta i kommunikation eller transaktioner, inklusive för att vidta skälig aktsamhet avseende, eller vid tillhandahållandet eller mottagandet av, en produkt eller tjänst. Honeywell kan till exempel samla in och använda denna företagskontaktinformation för att underlätta och hantera beställningar, kontrakt, garantier, underhåll och liknande affärsfunktioner, för kreditanalys och insamlingsändamål, för att hjälpa till med vår egen interna efterlevnad och juridiska krav och (om nödvändigt) för att försvara våra intressen och anspråk.
* **Tjänster och transaktioner.** Vi kan använda din personliga information för att leverera tjänster till dig eller genomföra transaktioner du har begärt, inklusive, men inte begränsat till, tillhandahålla information om företagets produkter eller tjänster som du har köpt eller på annat sätt använder, registrera köpta produkter, behandla produktbeställningar, hantera garantianspråk, ersätta produktmanualer, svara på kundtjänstförfrågningar och underlätta användningen av våra webbplatser.
* **Administrera och skydda vår verksamhet och webbplatser.** Vi kan använda din personliga information för att administrera och skydda vår verksamhet och våra webbplatser, inklusive felsökning, systemunderhåll, support, rapportering och datavärdskap.
* **Förbättra vår verksamhet, webbplatser, produkter och tjänster.** Vi kan använda din personliga information för att utföra affärsanalyser eller för andra ändamål som hjälper oss att utveckla och förbättra kvaliteten på vår verksamhet, webbplatser, produkter och tjänster (inklusive nya produkter och tjänster), till exempel genom att anpassa våra webbplatser till dina specifika preferenser eller intressen.
* **Marknadsföring.** I enlighet med tillämpliga lagar och förordningar kan vi använda din personliga information för att informera dig om produkter eller tjänster som kan vara av intresse för dig och för att på annat sätt kommunicera med dig om erbjudanden, evenemang och nyheter, undersökningar, specialerbjudanden och relaterade ämnen. Du kan när som helst och utan kostnad välja bort marknadsföringskommunikation som skickas via e-post genom att använda länken ”avanmälan” i något av det marknadsföringsmaterial du får från oss via e-post, eller genom att kontakta oss med hjälp av kontaktinformationen som anges i denna sekretesspolicy. Beroende på i vilket land du bor kan du också välja bort andra typer av marknadsföringskommunikation; vänligen kontakta oss med hjälp av kontaktinformationen i sekretesspolicyn för mer information. Vissa jurisdiktioner ger individer (t.ex. invånare i Kalifornien) rätten att begära viss information om vår utlämning av personlig information till tredje part för tredje parts direkta marknadsföringsändamål. Kontakta oss enligt instruktionerna nedan för mer information om vår praxis gällande utlämning av uppgifter för marknadsföringsändamål.
* **Intressebaserad annonsering.** Vi samlar in data om dina aktiviteter online och identifierar dina intressen så att vi kan tillhandahålla annonsering som är mest relevant för dig. Du kan välja bort intressebaserad annonsering från Honeywell enligt beskrivningen i vårt [Meddelande om användning av cookies](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#swedish).
* **Ekonomiska incitament och lojalitetsprogram.** Vi samlar in och använder personlig information för att underhålla och administrera våra ekonomiska incitament och lojalitetsprogram. Vi använder den personliga informationen du tillhandahåller i dessa program för att erbjuda unika belöningar, spåra din programstatus och för att underlätta utbytet av programpoäng för produkter, reklammaterial, utbildningsworkshops och andra objekt. I den utsträckning som lagen tillåter kan vi också använda all personlig information som du tillhandahåller i samband med ett program med ekonomiska incitament för något annat syfte som anges i denna sekretesspolicy. Det är viktigt att du läser igenom villkoren för varje program med ekonomiska incitament som du vill registrera dig eller delta i eftersom dessa villkor kan vara mycket specifikt anpassade till det tillämpliga programmet. Om du samtycker till att delta i något av dessa program kan du när som helst dra tillbaka ditt samtycke genom att kontakta oss via kontaktuppgifterna i denna sekretesspolicy eller i enlighet med instruktionerna som anges i de tillämpliga villkoren.
* **Jobbansökningar.** I samband med en jobbansökan eller förfrågan kan du förse oss med information om dig själv, till exempel ett CV/meritförteckning, yrkesreferenser, information om utbildning och arbetsbakgrund samt information om yrkesutbildning och certifieringar. Vi och medlemmar i vår koncern kan använda denna information i syfte att överväga anställning, göra bakgrundskontroller och utvärdera anställningslämplighet och annat som anges i varje separat sekretesspolicy eller annat meddelande som görs tillgängligt i samband med din ansökan. Vi kan använda en tredje part (t.ex. jobbrekryterare) eller sociala medieplattformar för att värva, samla in och behålla jobbansökningar. För mer information, läs vårt [Meddelande om arbetssökandes sekretess](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/applicant-privacy-notice#swedish).
* **Forskning och analys.** Vi kan använda din personliga information för att utföra forskning och analys i syfte att hjälpa oss att analysera dina inköpspreferenser, identifiera de produkter och tjänster som bäst uppfyller dina krav och mäta effektiviteten av den annonsering vi erbjuder dig.
* **Tillämpning:** Vi kan använda den personliga informationen vi samlar in för att upptäcka, förhindra och svara på bedrägerier, intrång i immateriella rättigheter, brott mot våra villkor, överträdelser av lag eller annat missbruk av våra webbplatser.

Där lagen tillåter kan vi kombinera informationen som vi samlar in via våra webbplatser med annan information som vi har om dig (så som information om din användning av våra produkter och tjänster) för att erbjuda dig en förbättrad och konsekvent kundupplevelse när du interagerar med oss eller för andra ändamål som anges i denna sekretesspolicy.

**Den rättsliga grunden på vilken vi behandlar information**

Där det krävs enligt lag kommer vi att se till att det finns en rättslig grund för behandlingen av din personliga information. I de flesta fall beror vår rättsliga grund på berörd personlig information och det specifika sammanhang där vi samlar in den.

* **Kontrakt:** behandlingen är nödvändig för utförandet av de tjänster vi tillhandahåller dig, eller för att vidta åtgärder (på din begäran) före utförandet, och vid förväntan att utföra, sådana tjänster;
* **Juridisk skyldighet:** behandlingen är nödvändig för att uppfylla våra juridiska skyldigheter, inklusive efterlevnad av tillämpliga lagar, förordningar, statliga och kvasistatliga begäranden, domstolsbeslut eller stämningar;
* **Samtycke:** behandlingen baseras på ditt samtycke till behandlingen av din personliga information för ett eller flera specifika ändamål (t.ex. marknadsföring);
* **Legitima intressen:** behandlingen är nödvändig för att tillgodose våra legitima intressen, till exempel för att utveckla och förbättra våra webbplatser, produkter och/eller tjänster till förmån för våra kunder; eller
* **Vitala intressen:** behandlingen är nödvändig för att skydda dina vitala intressen (till exempel hälso- och säkerhetsskäl om du deltar i ett möte på en Honeywell-plats).

Om du har några frågor eller behöver ytterligare information om den rättsliga grund på vilken vi samlar in och använder din personliga information, skicka ett e-postmeddelande till [HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com).

**Anonymisering av information**

I enlighet med tillämplig lag kan vi anonymisera din personliga information så att den inte längre kan användas för att identifiera dig. Anonymiserad information anses inte vara personlig information och omfattas därför inte av denna sekretesspolicy. Vi kan samla in, använda, aggregera och dela anonymiserad information för alla syften.

**Hur länge vi behåller uppgifter**

Perioden under vilken vi lagrar din personliga information varierar beroende på syftet med behandlingen. Vi lagrar till exempel personlig information som behövs för att förse dig med produkter och tjänster, eller för att underlätta transaktioner du har begärt, så länge du är kund hos Honeywell eller om du skickar in en jobbansökan via våra webbplatser kommer vi att behålla information om din ansökan enligt beskrivningen i sekretessmeddelandet som görs tillgängligt för dig i samband med din ansökan eller på annat sätt krävs enligt lag. I alla andra fall lagrar vi din personliga information så länge som behövs för att uppfylla de syften som beskrivs i denna sekretesspolicy, varefter den antingen anonymiseras (där det är tillåtet enligt tillämplig lag), raderas eller förstörs.

**Utlämning av information**

Vi kan dela din personliga information med utvalda tredje parter i enlighet med tillämplig lag, inklusive enligt vad som anges nedan:

* **Våra koncernföretag.** Vi kan dela din personliga information med våra dotterbolag och koncernföretag enligt vad som är rimligt nödvändigt för de ändamål som anges i denna sekretesspolicy.
* **Tjänsteleverantörer.** Vi kan dela din personliga information med företag som vi har ingått avtal med att tillhandahålla tjänster för vår räkning, så som att vara värd för webbplatser, genomföra undersökningar, behandla transaktioner, analysera våra webbplatser och utföra analyser för att förbättra kvaliteten på vår verksamhet, webbplatser, produkter och tjänster. Vi kräver att dessa tjänsteleverantörer skyddar din personliga informations konfidentialitet.
* **Distributörer och andra betrodda affärspartner.** Vi kan dela din personliga information med tredje part som distribuerar våra produkter och andra betrodda affärspartner för ändamål som inkluderar att dessa tredje parter kan skicka marknadsföringskommunikation till dig. Sådan delning av personlig information för marknadsföringsändamål kommer att ske i enlighet med tillämpliga lagar och regler.
* **Utlämning i samband med transaktioner.** I samband med vissa transaktioner kan vi lämna ut någon eller all din personliga information till finansinstitut, statliga enheter och rederier eller posttjänster som är involverade i genomförandet av transaktionen.
* **Utlämningar i samband med förvärv eller avyttringar.** Omständigheter kan uppstå om Honeywell av strategiska eller andra affärsskäl beslutar att sälja, köpa, avyttra, slå samman eller på annat sätt omorganisera företag i vissa länder. Vi kan lämna ut information som vi har om dig i den utsträckning som är rimligt nödvändigt för att fortsätta med förhandlingarna eller slutförandet av en sammanslagning, förvärv, avyttring eller försäljning av hela eller en del av Honeywells tillgångar.
* **Utlämning av andra skäl.** Vi kan lämna ut personlig information om detta krävs eller bemyndigas enligt lag eller i god tro och det är nödvändigt för att följa rättsliga krav eller för en juridisk process som delges oss, för att skydda och försvara våra rättigheter eller egendom, under brådskande omständigheter, för att skydda varje individs personliga säkerhet.

**Internationella överföringar**

Honeywell är en global organisation och din personliga information kan överföras till, förvaras, lagras eller användas över olika platser världen över, så som USA, Mexiko och Indien i enlighet med tillämplig lag. Detta innebär att när vi samlar in din personliga information kan den behandlas i länder som kan ha dataskyddslagar som skiljer sig från lagarna i ditt land. Honeywell kommer dock alltid att vidta rimliga åtgärder för att skydda din integritet och för att tillhandahålla en skyddsnivå för personlig information som är jämförbar med den i ditt bosättningsland, inklusive implementering av Europeiska kommissionens standardavtalsklausuler. För mer information om lämpliga skyddsåtgärder för att skydda din personliga information, vänligen kontakta oss på [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com).

**Säkerhet**

Vi arbetar för att upprätthålla säkerheten för dina personuppgifter. Vi använder tekniska och organisatoriska åtgärder för att tillhandahålla en säkerhetsnivå som är lämplig för behandlingen av din personliga information. För mer information om hur Honeywell skyddar din personliga information, vänligen kontakta oss på [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com).

**Dina rättigheter**

Beroende på tillämplig lag kan du ha vissa rättigheter med avseende på din personliga information.

* Du kan ha rätt att **få tillgång till, korrigera, uppdatera** eller **begära radering** av din personliga information.
* Du kan **motsätta dig** behandlingen av din personliga information, be oss att **begränsa** behandlingen av din personliga information eller begära **flyttbarhet** av din personliga information.
* Du kan ha rätt **att inte få ett beslut fattat om dig som enbart baseras på automatiserad behandling, inklusive profilering** om beslutet i fråga leder till rättsliga effekter för dig eller påverkar dig på något väsentligt sätt.
* På samma sätt, om vi har samlat in och behandlat din personliga information med ditt samtycke, **kan du när som helst dra tillbaka ditt samtycke**. Tillbakadragande av ditt samtycke påverkar inte lagenligheten av all behandling som vi genomfört före ditt tillbakadragande och det kommer inte heller att påverka behandlingen av din personliga information som utförs beroende av andra lagliga behandlingsgrunder än samtycke.
* Du kan ha rätt att **välja bort försäljning av din personliga information**. Honeywell säljer inte din personliga information till tredje part för vinst. Vi delar eller lämnar dock ut din personliga information till tredje part i enlighet med denna sekretesspolicy och vårt [Meddelande om användning av cookies](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#swedish). Till exempel samarbetar vi med tredje part för att distribuera våra produkter, tillhandahålla teknisk hjälp, använda verktyg för analys av webbplatser och funktioner samt bedriva marknadsföring och försäljning av våra produkter och tjänster. Sådana aktiviteter kan innebära att din personliga information lämnas ut till tredje part och kan betraktas som en ”försäljning” av uppgifter enligt vissa (men inte alla) dataskyddslagar.
* Du har rätt att **lämna klagomål** till en dataskyddsmyndighet som ansvarar för att övervaka efterlevnaden av dataskyddslagen i din jurisdiktion gällande vår insamling och användning av din personliga information om du anser att vår behandling av din personliga information inte överensstämmer med dataskyddslagen. Till exempel har enskilda personer inom EES rätt att lämna in ett klagomål till den behöriga dataskyddsmyndigheten, vars lista kan nås på: [https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/board/members\_en](https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/board/members_en). Vi skulle dock uppskatta att få möjligheten att ta itu med dina frågor, så kontakta oss gärna angående eventuella klagomål. Vi diskriminerar inte individer för att de utövar sina dataskyddsrättigheter.

Vi kommer att underlätta ditt utövande av de rättigheter som gäller för dig i enlighet med tillämplig lag. Men även om din personliga information inte ges skydd enligt eller på annat sätt omfattas av en dataskyddslag kan vi försöka tillgodose de krav eller förfrågningar du har om vår databehandling. Om du har frågor om dina rättigheter eller vill utöva dina rättigheter kan du kontakta oss på [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com) eller skicka in dina frågor rörande sekretess via vårt interaktiva webbformulär på följande länk:

**Information för barn**

Våra webbplatser är inte riktade till och bör inte användas av barn under sexton (16) år och vi samlar inte medvetet in, använder eller säljer information från sådana individer. Om du är minderårig enligt lagarna i ditt land, vänligen lämna inte någon personlig information via våra webbplatser.

**Länkar till andra webbplatser**

Våra webbplatser kan innehålla länkar till webbplatser, produkter och tjänster tillhörande tredje part. Vi har ingen skyldighet eller ansvar för dessa webbplatser, produkter och tjänster, deras policyer, deras insamling eller annan behandling av din personliga information. Dessa tredje parters praxis styrs av deras egen sekretesspolicy. Vi uppmuntrar dig att ta reda på vad dessa tredje parter har för sekretesspolicyer.

**Kontakta oss**

Om du har frågor angående denna sekretesspolicy eller vår hantering av din personliga information, vill lämna ett klagomål eller komma i kontakt med vårt dataskyddsombud, kontakta oss med hjälp av kontaktinformationen nedan. Vi kommer omedelbart att ta itu med dina frågor och arbeta för att nå en tillfredsställande lösning.

Interaktivt webbformulär:  
  
E-post:  
  
Postadress:  
Honeywell Privacy  
4D5  
115 Tabor Road  
Morris Plains, NJ 07950  
  
Avgiftsfritt nummer:  

**Ändringar i denna sekretesspolicy**

Vi kan ibland göra uppdateringar i denna sekretesspolicy. När vi gör det kommer vi att revidera det ”senast uppdaterad”-datumet högst upp i sekretesspolicyn och vidta sådana ytterligare åtgärder som kan krävas enligt lag.

**Senast uppdaterad den 11 juni 2021**

**Son güncelleme: 11 Haziran 2021**

**Giriş**

Honeywell International Inc. ("**Honeywell**", "**bizim**", "**bize**" veya "**biz**"), web sitelerimizden herhangi birini ziyaret ettiğinizde veya kullandığınızda veya bu Gizlilik Bildirimi ile bağlantılı ürünleri, hizmetleri ve uygulamaları kullandığınızda (topluca "**Siteler**") hakkınızda topladığımız kişisel bilgilerin "veri denetleyicisidir". Bu Gizlilik Bildirimi, bu şekilde toplanan kişisel bilgilerinizi nasıl topladığımızı, paylaştığımızı ve kullandığımızı ve gizlilik haklarınızı nasıl kullanabileceğinizi açıklamaktadır.

Sizinle etkileşim kurduğumuzda, size belirli işleme faaliyetleri hakkında ek gizlilik bildirimleri sağlayabilir veya Honeywell'in belirli bir zamanda kişisel bilgilerinizi nasıl işlediği konusunda size ek seçenekler sunabiliriz.

İstediğiniz bölüme geçmek için aşağıdaki bağlantılardan birine tıklayın:

**Tarafımızdan bilgi toplanması**

* **Doğrudan sizden toplanan bilgiler.** Sitelerimizi ziyaret ettiğinizde talep ettiğiniz bir hizmeti vermek veya bir işlemi gerçekleştirmek için sizden kişisel bilgiler girmenizi isteyebiliriz. Ayrıca bizimle iletişime geçtiğinizde veya etkileşim kurduğunuzda (ör. bir yorum, soru veya müşteri destek talebi, site ziyaretçileri) veya Sitelerimizi kullanmak için bir hesap kaydı yaptığınızda da bize kişisel bilgiler verebilirsiniz. Bu kişisel bilgiler şunları içerebilir:
    * **Kimlik verileri,** isminiz, unvanınız, şirketinizin/kuruluşunuzun ismi, e-posta adresiniz, telefon numaralarınız ve posta adresiniz (sokak, şehir, eyalet, posta kodu veya bölge kodu ve/veya ülke dâhil olmak üzere) gibi veriler;
    * **Kayıt verileri,** Sitelerimizi kullanmak adına bir hesap için kaydolduğunuzda kullanıcı adları ve şifreler dahil olmak üzere sizin tarafınızdan sağlanan veriler;
    * **İşe alım verileri,** İş başvurusu veya işe almayla bağlantılı olarak sunulan bilgiler dahil olmak üzere veriler (aşağıda açıklandığı gibi);
    * **İş iletişim verileri,** bir üçüncü taraf kuruluşun (ör. işletme, şirket, ortaklık, şahıs şirketi, kar amacı gütmeyen kuruluş veya devlet kurumu) diğer çalışanları, sahipleri, yöneticileri, memurları veya yüklenicileriyle ilgili bilgiler gibi.
    * **Pazarlama ve iletişim verileri,** pazarlama konusundaki tercihlerinizi ve yayınlarımıza aboneliklerinizi içeren veriler;
    * **Finansal bilgiler,** Sitelerimizde bulunabilecek Şirket ürünlerini ve hizmetlerini satın almanızı kolaylaştırmamızı sağlamak amacıyla kredi kartı veya diğer banka hesap bilgilerini içeren bilgiler;
    * **İhracat denetleme bilgileri,** uyruğunuz, vatandaşlığınız ve ikamet ettiğiniz ülke gibi, ihracat yönetmelikleri uyarınca belirli teknolojiler hakkında bilgi almaya uygun olup olmadığınızı belirlememizi sağlayan bilgiler;
    * **İşlem verileri,** sipariş formu ve ödeme işlemlerini kolaylaştırmak için gereken bilgiler de dahil olmak üzere ürün ve hizmetlerimizle ilgili sorular ve siparişler ile sizden alınan ve size yapılan ödemelerin ayrıntıları;
    * **Etkinlik kayıt bilgileri,** e-kayıt formlarını doldururken sağladığınız bilgilerin dahil olduğu bilgiler ve
    * **Geri bildiriminiz,** anketler, öneriler veya genel olarak ürünlerimiz ve hizmetlerimizin yanı sıra Sitelerimiz hakkında sizden gelen diğer geri bildirimler.

İstenen bilgiyi sağlamadığınızda size istenen hizmeti sunamayabilir ya da işleminizi tamamlayamayabiliriz.

* **Hakkınızda otomatik olarak topladığımız bilgiler**. Çerezler ve benzer izleme teknolojileri kullanarak Sitelerimizi ziyaretiniz hakkında belirli bilgiler topluyoruz. Bunu yapmamızı engellemeniz konusunda sahip olabileceğiniz yasal haklara her zaman saygı duyarız. Bu şekilde toplanan veriler şunları içerir:
    * **Kullanım verileri,** Sitelerimizi nasıl kullandığınız, hangi sayfaları görüntülediğiniz, aktarılan bayt miktarı, tıkladığınız bağlantılar, eriştiğiniz materyaller, Siteye eriştiğiniz tarih ve saat, bağlantı aracılığıyla sizi Sitemize yönlendiren web sitesi ve Sitelerde gerçekleştirilen diğer eylemler hakkındaki bilgileri içeren veriler ve
    * **Teknik veriler,** İnternet Protokolü (IP) adresiniz, tarayıcınızın türü, yetenekleri ve dili ve işletim sisteminiz gibi veriler.

Sitelerimizde kullandığımız çerezler ve diğer benzer izleme teknolojileri hakkında bilgi için lütfen [Çerez Bildirimi](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#turkish) sayfamıza bakın.

* **Coğrafi konum bilgileri.** Belirli Siteler için, onayınızla birlikte, mobil cihazınızın kesin, gerçek zamanlı konumunu (yani coğrafi konumu) toplayabiliriz. Bu bilgiler yalnızca, bu bilgileri bizim adımıza hizmet sağlamakla bağlantılı olarak işleyebilecek hizmet sağlayıcılarımız da dahil olmak üzere, Siteleri kullanımınızı kolaylaştırmak amacıyla kullanılır. Onay verilmişse, mobil cihazınızın ayarları aracılığıyla Konum Servisleri tercihlerinizi yöneterek bu izni ayarlayabilirsiniz.
* **Üçüncü taraflardan toplanan bilgiler.** Yürürlükteki yasalara uygun olarak, Sitelerimizi tercihlerinize ve bu Gizlilik Bildiriminde belirtilen diğer amaçlara göre iyileştirmemize ve özelleştirmemize yardımcı olmak için sosyal medya web siteleri ve uygulamaları gibi üçüncü taraflardan hakkınızda kişisel bilgiler toplayabilir ve bunları halihazırda elimizde bulunan bilgilerle birleştirebiliriz. Ayrıca, geleneksel ticari faaliyetleri ve benzer idari konuları kolaylaştırmak veya bunlarla ilgilenmek için işvereninizden veya diğer üçüncü taraflardan iş iletişim bilgilerinizi toplayabiliriz.

**Tarafımızdan bilginin kullanılması**

Sitelerimiz aracılığıyla veya bizle iletişime geçtiğinizde toplanan kişisel bilgileri şu amaçlar için kullanabiliriz:

* **İş İletişim Verileri.** Honeywell, bir ürün veya hizmetle ilgili durum tespiti yapmak veya bir ürün veya hizmet sağlamak veya almak da dahil olmak üzere, iletişim veya işlemlerde bulunmak için iş iletişim verilerini toplar ve kullanır. Örneğin, Honeywell bu iş iletişim verilerini siparişleri, sözleşmeleri, garantileri, bakım ve benzeri iş fonksiyonlarını kolaylaştırmak ve yönetmek, kredi analizi ve tahsilat amaçlarıyla, kendi iç uyumumuza ve yasal gereksinimlerimize yardımcı olmak ve (gerekirse) çıkarlarımızı ve iddialarımızı savunmak için toplayabilir ve kullanabilir.
* **Hizmetler ve işlemler.** Kişisel bilgilerinizi, satın aldığınız veya başka şekilde kullandığınız Şirket ürünleri ve hizmetleri hakkında bilgi sağlamak, satın alınan ürünleri kaydetmek, ürün siparişlerini işlemek, teminat taleplerini işlemek, ürün el kitaplarını değiştirmek, müşteri hizmet taleplerine cevap vermek ve Sitelerimizin kullanımını kolaylaştırmak dâhil, ancak bunlarla sınırlı olmamak üzere, talep ettiğiniz hizmetleri vermek veya işlemleri gerçekleştirmek için kullanabiliriz.
* **İşletmemizin ve Sitelerimizin yönetilmesi ve korunması.** Kişisel bilgilerinizi; arıza arama, sistem bakımı, destek, raporlama ve verinin barındırılması dâhil olmak üzere işletmemizi ve Sitelerimizi yönetmek ve korumak için kullanabiliriz.
* **İşimizi, Sitelerimizi ve hizmetlerimizi iyileştirme.** Kişisel bilgilerinizi iş analizleri gerçekleştirmek veya Sitelerimizi belirli tercihlerinize ve ilgilerinize göre özelleştirmek gibi, işimizin, Sitelerimizin, ürünlerimizin ve hizmetlerinizin (yeni ürünler ve hizmetler dâhil) kalitesini geliştirmede ve iyileştirmede bize yardımcı olacak amaçlar için kullanabiliriz.
* **Pazarlama.** Yürürlükteki yasalara ve yönetmeliklere uygun olarak kişisel bilgilerinizi size ilgilenebileceğiniz ürünler ve hizmetler ile ilgili bilgi vermek veya teklifler, etkinlikler ve haberler, anketler, özel teklifler ve alakalı başlıklarla ilgili sizle iletişime geçmek için kullanabiliriz. Gönderdiğimiz e-posta pazarlama malzemelerindeki "aboneliği kaldır" bağlantısını kullanarak veya işbu Gizlilik Bildiriminde listelenen iletişim bilgileri ile bizimle iletişime geçerek e-posta ile gönderilen pazarlama iletişimlerini istediğiniz zaman ücretsiz olarak geri çevirebilirsiniz. İkamet ettiğiniz ülkeye bağlı olarak, diğer pazarlama iletişimi türlerini de devre dışı bırakabilirsiniz; daha fazla bilgi için lütfen Gizlilik Bildiriminde listelenen iletişim bilgilerini kullanarak bizimle iletişime geçin. Bazı yetki alanlarında, bireylere (örneğin, Kaliforniya'da ikamet edenlere) üçüncü tarafların doğrudan pazarlama amaçları için kişisel bilgileri üçüncü taraflara açıklamamızla ilgili belirli bilgileri talep etme hakkı verir. Pazarlama amaçlı veri açıklama uygulamalarımız hakkında daha fazla bilgi için lütfen aşağıda listelenen talimatlara uygun olarak bizimle iletişime geçin.
* **İlgi Alanına Dayalı Reklamcılık.** Sizinle en alakalı reklamları sunabilmemiz için çevrimiçi etkinlikleriniz hakkında veri topluyoruz ve ilgi alanlarınızı belirliyoruz. Honeywell'den ilgi alanına dayalı reklamları almayı [Çerez Bildirimi](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#turkish) sayfamızda açıklandığı şekilde devre dışı bırakabilirsiniz.
* **Finansal Teşvik ve Sadakat Programları.** Mali teşvik ve sadakat programlarımızı korumak ve yönetmek için kişisel bilgileri topluyor ve kullanıyoruz. Bu programlarda verdiğiniz kişisel bilgileri benzersiz ödüller sunmak, program durumunuzu izlemek ve ürünler, promosyon materyalleri, eğitim atölyeleri ve diğer ürünler için program puan değişimini kolaylaştırmak için kullanıyoruz. Yasaların izin verdiği ölçüde, bir finansal teşvik programı bağlamında sağladığınız tüm kişisel bilgileri, bu Gizlilik Bildiriminde belirtilen diğer herhangi bir amaç için de kullanabiliriz. Lütfen kaydolmak veya katılmak istediğiniz her bir finansal teşvik programının şart ve koşullarını gözden geçirin, çünkü bu şartlar ve koşullar geçerli programa hukuken uyacak şekilde uyarlanabilir. Bu programlara katılmayı kabul ederseniz, bu Gizlilik Bildiriminin sonundaki iletişim bilgilerini kullanarak veya geçerli programın hüküm ve koşullarında belirtilen talimatlara uygun olarak bizimle iletişime geçerek bu izni istediğiniz zaman geri çekebilirsiniz.
* **İş başvuruları.** Bir iş başvurusu veya iş aramayla bağlantılı olarak, bize kendiniz hakkında özgeçmiş veya mesleki geçmiş, profesyonel referanslar, eğitim ve kariyer geçmişine dair bilgiler ve mesleki eğitim ve sertifika bilgileri gibi bilgiler verebilirsiniz. Biz ve grubumuzun üyeleri bu bilgiyi işe alımı değerlendirme, geçmişe dönük kontroller ve işe uygunluk amacıyla veya başvurunuzla bağlantılı olarak sunulan herhangi ayrı bir gizlilik bildiriminde ya da diğer bildirimlerde belirtildiği şekilde kullanabiliriz. İş başvurularını istemek, toplamak ve saklamak için üçüncü bir taraf (ör. iş veren) veya sosyal medya platformunu kullanabiliriz. Daha fazla bilgi için, [Başvuru Sahibi Gizlilik Bildirimi](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/applicant-privacy-notice#turkish) sayfamızı okuyun.
* **Araştırma ve analiz.** Kişisel bilgilerinizi, satın alma tercihlerinizi analiz etmede, gereksinimlerinizi en iyi karşılayan ürünleri ve hizmetleri tanımlamada ve size sunduğumuz reklamların etkililiğini ölçmede bize yardımcı olması için araştırma veya analiz yapmak üzere kullanabiliriz.
* **Yürütme:** Topladığımız kişisel bilgileri sahteciliği, fikri mülkiyet haklarının çiğnenmesini, şartlar ve koşullarımızın veya yasaların ihlal edilmesini veya Sitelerimizin başka herhangi bir şekilde kötüye kullanılmasını saptamak, önlemek veya bunlara karşılık vermek için kullanabiliriz.

Yasaların izin verdiği durumlarda, bizle etkileşime geçtiğinizde size iyileştirilmiş ve tutarlı bir müşteri deneyimi sunmak için veya bu Gizlilik Bildiriminde belirtilen diğer amaçlarla, Sitelerimiz aracılığıyla topladığımız bilgileri sizin hakkınızda sahip olduğumuz diğer bilgilerle (ürünlerimizi ve hizmetlerimizi kullanımınız hakkındaki bilgiler gibi) birleştirebiliriz.

**Bilgilerinizi işlememizin yasal dayanağı**

Yasaların gerektirdiği durumlarda kişisel bilginizin işlenmesi için yasal bir dayanak olmasını sağlarız. Çoğu durumda yasal dayanağımız, ilgili kişisel bilgilere ve bunları topladığımız özel bağlama bağlı olur.

* **Sözleşme:** işleme, size sunduğumuz hizmetlerin yerine getirilmesi için veya bu tür hizmetleri gerçekleştirmeden önce ve bu tür hizmetleri gerçekleştirme beklentisiyle (isteğiniz üzerine) adımlar atmak için gereklidir;
* **Yasal zorunluluk:** işlemenin yürürlükteki yasalara, yönetmeliklere, hükümet ve hükümet benzeri kurum taleplerine, mahkeme emirlerine ve celplerine uymak da dahil olmak üzere, yükümlülüklerimize uymak için gereklidir;
* **Onay:** işlemenin belirtilen bir veya daha fazla amaç için (ör. pazarlama) kişisel bilgilerinizin işlenmesine verdiğiniz onaya dayalıdır;
* **Meşru menfaatler:** işlemenin meşru menfaatlerimizi karşılamak için, örneğin Sitelerimizi, ürünlerimizi ve/veya hizmetlerimizi müşterilerimizin yararına geliştirmek ve iyileştirmek için, gereklidir veya
* **Hayati çıkarlar:** işleme, hayati çıkarlarınızı korumak için gereklidir (örneğin, bir Honeywell konumunda bir toplantıya katılmanız durumunda sağlık ve güvenlik nedenleri).

Kişisel bilgilerinizi toplamamızın ve kullanmamızın yasal dayanağı hakkında herhangi bir sorunuz varsa veya daha fazla bilgiye ihtiyacınız varsa, [HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com) adresine e-posta gönderin.

**Bilgilerinizin anonimleştirilmesi**

Yürürlükteki yasalara uygun olarak kişisel bilgilerinizi sizi tanımlama amacıyla kullanılamaması için anonim hale getirebiliriz. Anonimleştirilmiş bilgiler kişisel bilgi olarak kabul edilmez ve bu nedenle bu Gizlilik Bildirimine tabi değildir. Anonimleştirilmiş bilgileri herhangi bir amaç için toplayabilir, kullanabilir, bir araya getirebilir ve paylaşabiliriz.

**Bilgilerinizi saklama süremiz**

Kişisel bilgilerinizi depoladığımız süre işlemenin amacına göre değişiklik gösterir. Örneğin, size ürünler veya hizmetler sunmak veya talep ettiğiniz işlemleri gerçekleştirmek için gereken kişisel bilgileri, Honeywell müşterisi olduğunuz süre boyunca depolarız veya Sitelerimiz üzerinden bir iş başvurusu göndermeniz halinde başvurunuzla bağlantılı olarak size sunulan gizlilik bildiriminde veya diğer bildirimlerde belirtildiği şekilde ya da yasaların gerektirdiği başka şekillerde başvurunuzun detaylarını tutarız. Diğer tüm durumlarda kişisel bilgilerinizi bu Gizlilik Bildiriminde belirtilen amaçları karşılamak için gereken süre boyunca depolarız, sonrasında bu bilgiler anonim hale getirilir (yürürlükteki yasaların izin verdiği durumlarda), silinir veya imha edilir.

**Bilgilerin açıklanması**

işisel bilgilerinizi yürürlükteki yasalara uygun olarak ve aşağıda belirtilen biçimlerin dahil olduğu şekillerde seçilmiş üçüncü taraflarla paylaşabiliriz:

* **Grup şirketlerimiz.** Kişisel bilgilerinizi bu Gizlilik Bildiriminde belirtilen amaçlar için makul ölçüde gerekli olduğu şekilde bağlı kuruluşlarımızla veya grup şirketlerimizle paylaşabiliriz.
* **Hizmet sağlayıcılar.** Kişisel bilgilerinizi bizim adımıza web sitelerini barındırma, anket yapma, işlem gerçekleştirme, Sitelerimizi analiz etme ve işimizin, Sitelerimizin, ürünlerimizin ve hizmetlerimizin kalitesini iyileştirmek için analizler gerçekleştirme gibi hizmetler sunmaları için sözleşme yaptığımız şirketlerle paylaşabiliriz. Bu hizmet sağlayıcıların kişisel bilgilerin gizliliğini korumalarını talep ederiz.
* **Dağıtımcılar ve diğer güvenilir iş ortakları.** Kişisel bilgilerinizi ürünlerimizi dağıtan üçünü taraflarla veya diğer güvenilir iş ortaklarıyla söz konusu üçüncü tarafların size pazarlama iletileri göndermesine olanak sağlamayı içeren amaçlarla paylaşabiliriz. Kişisel bilgilerin pazarlama amacıyla bu şekilde paylaşılması yürürlükteki yasalara ve yönetmeliklere uygun olarak gerçekleştirilir.
* **İşlemlerle bağlantılı olarak ifşa.** Belirli işlemlerle bağlantılı olarak kişisel bilgilerinizin bir kısmını veya tamamını işlemin yerine getirilmesinde rol oynayan mali kuruluşlara, kamu tüzel kişiliklerine ve taşımacılık şirketlerine veya posta hizmetlerine ifşa edebiliriz.
* **Satın almalar veya elden çıkarmalarla bağlantılı ifşa.** Honeywell'in stratejik veya diğer ticari nedenlerle bazı ülkelerde işletmeleri satmaya, satın almaya, elden çıkarmaya, birleştirmeye veya başka bir şekilde yeniden düzenlemeye karar verdiği durumlar ortaya çıkabilir. Hakkınızda tuttuğumuz bilgileri bir birleşmenin pazarlıklarının sürmesi veya tamamlanması, Honeywell'in varlıklarının bir kısmının veya tamamının alınması, elden çıkarılması veya satılması için gereken makul düzeyde ifşa edebiliriz.
* **Başka nedenlerle ifşa.** Yasaların zorunlu kılması ya da izin vermesi veya yasal gereklere ya da hakkımızdaki yasal bir sürece uymak, haklarımızı ya da mal ve mülkümüzü korumak ve savunmak veya acil durumlarda herhangi bir kimsenin kişisel emniyetini korumak için bunun gerekli olduğuna art niyetsiz olarak kani olunması durumunda kişisel bilgileri ifşa edebiliriz.

**Uluslararası aktarımlar**

Honeywell küresel bir kuruluştur ve kişisel bilgileriniz yürürlükteki yasalara uygun olarak ABD, Meksika ve Hindistan gibi dünyanın çeşitli yerlerinde aktarılabilir, tutulabilir, saklanabilir veya kullanılabilir. Bu, kişisel bilgilerinizi topladığımızda, ülkenizin yasalarından farklı veri koruma yasalarına sahip olabilecek ülkelerde işlenebileceği anlamına gelir. Ancak Honeywell, gizliliğinizi korumak ve Avrupa Komisyonu'nun Standart Sözleşme Maddelerinin uygulanmasını da içeren ikamet ettiğiniz ülkeyle karşılaştırılabilir düzeyde kişisel bilgilerin korunmasını sağlamak için her zaman makul adımlar atacaktır. Kişisel bilgilerinizi korumaya yönelik uygun önlemler hakkında daha fazla bilgi için lütfen [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com) adresinden bizimle iletişime geçin.

**Güvenlik**

Kişisel bilgilerinizin güvenliğini koruma kararlılığıyla çalışırız. Kişisel bilgilerinizin işlenmesi riskine uygun bir güvenlik düzeyi sağlamak için teknik ve organizasyonel önlemler alıyoruz. Honeywell'in kişisel bilgilerinizi nasıl koruduğu hakkında daha fazla bilgi için [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com) adresinden bizimle iletişime geçin.

**Haklarınız**

Yürürlükteki yasalara bağlı olarak, kişisel bilgilerinizle ilgili belirli haklara sahip olabilirsiniz.

* Kişisel bilgilerinize dair **erişim, düzeltme, güncelleme** veya **silme talebinde bulunma** hakkınız olabilir.
* Kişisel bilgilerinizin işlenmesine **itiraz edebilir**, kişisel bilgilerinizin işlenmesini **kısıtlamamızı** isteyebilir veya kişisel bilgilerinizin **taşınabilirliğini** talep edebilirsiniz.
* Bu kararın sizin hakkınızda yasal sonuçlar doğurması veya sizi önemli ölçüde etkilemesi durumunda, **profil çıkarma da dahil olmak üzere, yalnızca otomatik işlemeye dayalı bir karar vermeme** hakkına sahip olabilirsiniz.
* Benzer şekilde, kişisel bilgilerinizi sizin rızanızla toplamış ve işlemişsek, bu durumda **onayınızı istediğiniz zaman geri çekebilirsiniz**. Onayınızı geri çekmeniz, geri çekmenizden önce gerçekleştirdiğimiz herhangi bir işlemin yasallığını etkilemeyecek ve onay dışındaki yasal işleme gerekçelerine dayanarak yürütülen kişisel bilgilerinizin işlenmesini etkilemeyecektir.
* Kişisel bilgilerinizin satışını **devre dışı bırakma hakkına sahip olabilirsiniz**. Honeywell, kişisel bilgilerinizi kar amacıyla üçüncü taraflara satmaz. Ancak, bu Gizlilik Bildirimi ve [Çerez Bildirimimiz](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#turkish) uyarınca kişisel bilgilerinizi üçüncü taraflarla paylaşır veya başka bir şekilde ifşa ederiz. Örneğin, ürünlerimizi dağıtmak, size teknik yardım sağlamak, web sitesi analitik araçlarını ve özelliklerini çalıştırmak ve ürün ve hizmetlerimizin pazarlanması ve satışını yapmak için üçüncü taraflarla etkileşime gireriz. Bu tür faaliyetler, kişisel bilgilerinizin üçüncü taraflara ifşa edilmesini içerebilir ve belirli (ancak hepsi olmamak üzere) veri koruma yasaları uyarınca verilerin "satışı" olarak değerlendirilebilir.
* Kişisel bilgilerinizin işlenmesinin veri koruma yasasına uygun olmadığını düşünüyorsanız, kişisel bilgilerinizi toplamamız ve kullanmamız hakkında yargı bölgenizdeki veri koruma yasasına uyumu denetlemekten sorumlu bir veri koruma yetkilisine **şikayette bulunma** hakkınız vardır. Örneğin, AEA'daki bireyler, yetkili Veri Koruma Kurumu'na şikayette bulunma hakkına sahiptir. Bunların listesine şuradan erişebilirsiniz: [https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/board/members\_en](https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/board/members_en). Bununla birlikte, sorunlarınızın üzerine eğilmek istediğimizden, herhangi bir şikayetinizle ilgili olarak lütfen bizimle iletişime geçmekten çekinmeyin. Veri gizliliği haklarını kullandıkları için bireylere karşı ayrımcılık yapmayacağız.

Yürürlükteki yasalara uygun olarak, sizin için geçerli olan hakları kullanmanızı kolaylaştırırız. Bununla birlikte, kişisel bilgileriniz bir veri koruma yasası kapsamında koruma sağlamasa veya başka bir şekilde korunmasa bile, veri işleme faaliyetlerimizle ilgili olabilecek herhangi bir talep veya sorguyu yerine getirmeye çalışabiliriz. Haklarınızla ilgili sorularınız varsa veya haklarınızı kullanmak istiyorsanız, [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com) adresinden bizimle iletişime geçebilirsiniz veya aşağıdaki bağlantıdaki interaktif web formumuz aracılığıyla gizliliğe dair sorularınızı gönderebilirsiniz:

**Çocuklarla ilgili bilgiler**

Sitelerimiz on altı (16) yaşın altındaki çocuklara yönelik değildir ve bu çocuklar tarafından kullanılmamalıdır; bu tür bireylerden bilerek bilgi toplamaz, kullanmaz veya satmayız. Ülkenizin yasalarına göre reşit değilseniz, lütfen Sitelerimiz aracılığıyla herhangi bir kişisel bilgi göndermeyin.

**Diğer web sitelerine bağlantılar**

Sitelerimiz üçüncü taraf web sitelerine, ürünlere ve hizmetlere bağlantılar içerebilir. Bu web sitelerine, ürünler ve hizmetlere, bunların politikalarına veya kişisel bilgilerinizi toplamalarına ya da başka şekilde işlemelerine dair hiçbir sorumluluğumuz veya yükümlülüğümüz yoktur. Bu üçüncü tarafların uygulamaları kendi gizlilik politikalarına tabidir. Söz konusu üçüncü tarafların gizlilik politikaları hakkında bilgi edinmenizi öneririz.

**Bize ulaşın**

Bu Gizlilik Bildirimi veya kişisel bilgilerinizin ele alınmasıyla ilgili sorularınız varsa, bir şikayette bulunmak veya Veri Koruma Sorumlumuza başvurmak isterseniz, lütfen aşağıda belirtilen iletişim bilgilerini kullanarak bizimle iletişime geçin. Kaygılarınızı en kısa sürede ortadan kaldırmaya ve tatmin edici bir çözüme ulaşmaya çalışırız.

İnteraktif Web formu:  
  
E-posta:  
  
Posta Adresi:  
Honeywell Privacy  
4D5  
115 Tabor Road  
Morris Plains, NJ 07950  
  
Ücretsiz Hat:  

**İşbu Gizlilik Bildiriminde Yapılacak Değişiklikler**

Bu Gizlilik Bildirimini zaman zaman güncelleyebiliriz. Güncellediğimizde Gizlilik Bildiriminin üstündeki "son güncellenme tarihi"ni gözden geçirerek değiştiririz ve yasaların gerektirebileceği şekilde buna benzer ilave tedbirler alırız.

**Son güncelleme: 11 Haziran 2021**

English

**Last updated April 29, 2024**

**Introduction**

Honeywell International Inc. (“**Honeywell**”, “**our**”, “**us**”, or “**we**”), is the "data controller" of the personal information we collect about you when you visit or use any of our websites, or use products, services and applications that are linked to this Privacy Statement (collectively, our “**Sites**”).  This Privacy Statement explains how we collect, share and use your personal information collected in this way and how you can exercise your privacy rights.

When we interact with you, we may also provide you with additional privacy notices about specific processing activities or offer you additional choices about how Honeywell processes your personal information at that particular point in time.   

 Click on one of the links below to jump to the section that interests you:

**Our collection of information**

* **Information collected directly from you**. We may ask you for personal information to provide a service or carry out a transaction that you have requested. You may also provide personal information to us when you contact or engage with us (e.g., with a comment, inquiry or customer support request, site visitors) or register for an account to use our Sites. This personal information may include:
    * **Identity data,** such as your name, title, company/organization name, e-mail address, telephone numbers and physical address (including street, city, state, postal or zip code, and/or country);           
    * **Registration data,** provided by you when you register for an account to use our Sites, including usernames and passwords;  
        
    * **Recruitment data,** including information submitted in connection with a job application or inquiry (as described below); 
    * **Business contact data**, such as information related to other employees, owners, directors, officers, or contractors of a third-party organization (e.g., business, company, partnership, sole proprietorship, non-profit, or government agency);
    * **Biometric data**, such as facial recognition scanning, for health, safety, and security screening and other administrative functions;
    * **Marketing and communications data,** including your marketing preferences and your subscriptions to our publications;  
        
    * **Financial information,** including credit card or other financial account information for the purpose of enabling us to facilitate your purchase of Company products and services that may be available on our Sites;  
        
    * **Export control information,** such as your nationality, citizenship and country of residence, that allows us to determine your eligibility under export control regulations to receive information about certain technologies;  
        
    * **Transaction data,** including inquiries about and orders for our products and services and details of payments to and from you, including purchase order history and information needed to facilitate payment transactions;  
        
    * **Event registration information,** including information you provide when filling in e-registration forms; and  
        
    * **Your feedback,** including surveys, recommendations, or other feedback from you about our Sites as well as our products and services generally.

When you do not provide requested information, we may not be able to provide you the requested service or complete your transaction.

* **Information we collect automatically about you**. We collect certain information about your visit to our Sites using cookies and similar tracking technologies. We will always respect any legal rights you may have to prevent us doing this. Data collected in this way includes:
    * **Usage data,** including information about how you use our Sites, what pages you view, the number of bytes transferred, the links you click, the materials you access, the date and time you access the Site, the website from which you linked to one of our Sites and other actions taken within the Sites; and  
        
    * **Technical data,** such as your Internet Protocol (IP) address, your browser type and capabilities and language and your operating system.

For information about the cookies and other similar tracking technologies we use on our Sites, please refer to our [Cookie Notice](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice).

* **Geo-location information.** For certain Sites, with your consent, we may collect the precise, real-time location (i.e., geo-location) of your mobile device. This information will be used only for purposes of facilitating your use of the Sites including by our service providers who may process this information in connection with providing services on our behalf. If given, you may adjust this consent by managing your Location Services preferences through the settings of your mobile device.
* **Information collected from third parties.** In accordance with applicable law, we may collect personal information about you from third parties, such as social media websites and applications and combine it with information we already hold, to help us improve and customize our Sites to your preferences and for other purposes set forth in this Privacy Statement. We may also collect your business contact information from your employer or other third parties to facilitate or otherwise engage in traditional business activities and similar administrative matters.

**Our use of information**

We may use the personal information collected via our Sites or when you contact us for purposes that include:

* **Business Contact Data**. Honeywell collects and uses business contact data to engage in communications or transactions, including for conducting due diligence regarding, or providing or receiving, a product or service. For example, Honeywell may collect and use this business contact data in order to facilitate and manage orders, contracts, warranties, maintenance, and similar business functions, for credit analysis and collection purposes, to assist with our own internal compliance and legal requirements, and (if necessary) to defend our interests and claims.
* **Services and transactions.** We may use your personal information to deliver services to you or carry out transactions you have requested, including, but not limited to, providing information on Company products or services you have purchased or otherwise use, registering purchased products, processing product orders, handling warranty claims, replacing product manuals, answering customer service requests and facilitating the use of our Sites.
* **Administering and protecting our business and Sites.** We may use your personal information to administer and protect our business and our Sites, including troubleshooting, system maintenance, support, reporting and hosting of data.
* **Improving our business, Sites, products and services.** We may use your personal information to perform business analyses or for other purposes that help us to develop and improve the quality of our business, Sites, products and services (including new products and services), for example, by customizing our Sites to your particular preferences or interests.
* **Marketing.** In accordance with applicable laws and regulations, we may use your personal information to inform you of products or services which may be of interest to you, and to otherwise communicate with you about offerings, events and news, surveys, special offers, and related topics. You are able to opt-out from marketing communications sent via e-mail at any time, free of charge by using the “unsubscribe” link in any e-mail marketing materials you receive from us, or by contacting us using the contact information listed in this Privacy Statement. Depending on your country of residence, you may also be able to opt out of other types of marketing communications; please contact us using the contact information listed in the Privacy Statement for more information. Some jurisdictions provide individuals (e.g., California residents) with the right to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for the third party’s direct marketing purposes.  For more information on our data disclosure practices for marketing purposes, please contact us in accordance with the instructions listed below.
* **Interest-Based Advertising.** We collect data about your online activities and identify your interests so that we can provide advertising that is most relevant to you. You can opt out of receiving interest-based advertising from Honeywell as described in our [Cookie Notice](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice).
* **Financial Incentive and Loyalty Programs**. We collect and use personal information to maintain and administer our financial incentive and loyalty programs. We use the personal information you provide in these programs to offer unique rewards, track your program status, and to facilitate the exchange of program points for products, promotional materials, training workshops, and other items. To the extent permitted by law, we may also use any personal information that you provide in the context of a financial incentive program for any other purpose set forth in this Privacy Statement. Please review the terms and conditions of each financial incentive program in which you would like to register or participate as such terms and conditions may be narrowly tailored to the applicable program. If you consent to participate in these programs, you may withdrawal that consent at any time by contacting us using the contact details at the end of this Privacy Statement or in accordance with the instructions set forth in the applicable program’s terms and conditions.
* **Employment applications.** In connection with a job application or inquiry, you may provide us with information about yourself, such as a resume/curriculum vitae, professional references, information about education and job background, and information about professional training and certifications. We and members of our group may use this information for the purpose of employment consideration, background checks and employment eligibility, and as otherwise set forth in any separate privacy statement or other notice made available to in connection with your application. We may use a third party (e.g., job recruiter) or social media platform to solicit, collect, and retain employment applications. For more information, please read our [Applicant Privacy Notice](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/applicant-privacy-notice).
* **Research and analysis.** We may use your personal information to conduct research and analysis to help us analyse your purchasing preferences, identify the products and services that best meet your requirements and measure the effectiveness of the advertising we serve you.
* **Enforcement:** We may use the personal information we collect in order to detect, prevent and respond to fraud, intellectual property infringement, violations of our terms and conditions, violations of law or other misuse of our Sites.

Where permitted by law, we may combine the information that we collect via our Sites with other information we hold about you (such as information about your use of our products and services) in order to offer you an improved and consistent customer experience when interacting with us or for other purposes set forth in this Privacy Statement.

**The legal basis on which we process information**

Where required by law, we will ensure there is a legal basis for the processing of your personal information. In most cases our legal basis will depend on the personal information concerned and the specific context in which we collect it.

* **Contract**: the processing is necessary for the performance of the services we provide to you, or in order to take steps (at your request) prior to, and anticipation of, performing, such services;
* **Legal obligation**: the processing is necessary to comply with our legal obligations, including compliance with applicable laws, regulations, governmental and quasi-governmental requests, court orders or subpoenas;
* **Consent**: the processing is based on your consent to the processing of your personal information for one or more specified purposes (e.g. marketing);
* **Legitimate interests:** the processing is necessary to meet our legitimate interests, for example to develop and improve our Sites, products and/or services for the benefit of our customers; or
* **Vital interests**: the processing is necessary to protect your vital interests (for example, health and safety reasons if you attend a meeting at a Honeywell location).

If you have any questions about or need further information concerning the legal basis on which we collect and use your personal information, please send an email to [HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com).

**Anonymizing information**

In accordance with applicable law, we may anonymize your personal information so that it can no longer be used to identify you. Anonymized information is not considered personal information and is therefore not subject to this Privacy Statement. We may collect, use, aggregate and share anonymized information for any purpose.

**How long we keep information**

The period during which we store your personal information varies depending on the purpose for the processing. For example, we store personal information needed to provide you with products and services, or to facilitate transactions you have requested, for so long as you are a customer of Honeywell or if you submit an employment application via our Sites, we will retain details of your application as set forth in the privacy notice made available to you in connection with your application or as otherwise required by law. In all other cases, we store your personal information for as long as is needed to fulfil the purposes outlined in this Privacy Statement, following which time it is either anonymized (where permitted by applicable law), deleted or destroyed.

**Disclosure of information**

We may share your personal information with selected third parties in accordance with applicable law, including as set out below:

* **Our group companies.** We may share your personal information with our affiliates and group companies as reasonably necessary for the purposes set out in this Privacy Statement.
* **Service providers.** We may share your personal information with companies with which we have contracted to provide services on our behalf, such as hosting websites, conducting surveys, processing transactions, analyzing our Sites and performing analyses to improve the quality of our business, Sites, products and services. We require these service providers to protect the confidentiality of your personal information.
* **Distributors and other trusted business partners.** We may share your personal information with third parties that distribute our products and other trusted business partners for purposes that include allowing those third parties to send marketing communications to you. Such sharing of personal information for marketing purposes will be performed in accordance with applicable laws and regulations.
* **Disclosure in connection with transactions.** In connection with certain transactions, we may disclose some or all of your personal information to financial institutions, government entities and shipping companies or postal services involved in fulfilment of the transaction.
* **Disclosures in connection with acquisitions or divestitures.** Circumstances may arise where for strategic or other business reasons Honeywell decides to sell, buy, divest, merge or otherwise reorganize businesses in some countries. We may disclose information we maintain about you to the extent reasonably necessary to proceed with the negotiation or completion of a merger, acquisition, divestiture or sale of all or a portion of Honeywell’s assets.
* **Disclosure for other reasons.** We may disclose personal information if required or authorized to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with legal requirements or with legal process served on us, to protect and defend our rights or property or, in urgent circumstances, to protect the personal safety of any individual.

**International transfers**

Honeywell is a global organization and your personal information may be transferred to, held, stored or used across various locations worldwide such as the US, Mexico and India in accordance with applicable law. This means that when we collect your personal information it may be processed in countries that may have data protection laws that are different to the laws of your country. However, Honeywell will always take reasonable steps to protect your privacy and to provide a level of protection of personal information that is comparable to that of your country of residence which include implementing the European Commission's Standard Contractual Clauses. For more information on the appropriate safeguards in place to protect your personal information, please contact us at [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com).

**Biometric Data Policy (Illinois Residents Only)**

Honeywell may collect and use biometric data for health, safety, security, and other administrative functions, such as for performing wellness and health screening at our facilities, implementing timekeeping programs, implementing authentication and access controls with respect to Honeywell computers and other technology resources, and undertaking security measures, such as video surveillance with biometric-enabled features. Notwithstanding anything to the contrary in this Privacy Statement, it is Honeywell policy to retain biometric data for no longer than one (1) year following the last interaction between the applicable individual and us, provided however, we may retain such biometric data beyond this retention timeframe when permitted or otherwise required to comply with an applicable law, or a valid warrant, subpoena, or order issued by a court of competent jurisdiction, or for Honeywell to establish, exercise, or defend against, legal claims so long as we retain such biometric data for the minimum time necessary in order to satisfy the same. Honeywell has implemented and maintains commercially reasonable protocols for permanently destroying, or disposing of, biometric data in a manner that will not intentionally compromise its confidentiality. For the avoidance of doubt, this paragraph does not, and is not intended to, abrogate the confidential nature of any internal Honeywell policy, procedure, or record related to the processing of biometric data or other personal data concerning a Honeywell employee, contractor, or temporary worker. This paragraph only applies to individuals who reside in Illinois, United States and furnish their biometric data to Honeywell.

**Washington Residents Only**

Please read [the Washington State Consumer Health Data Privacy Policy](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/washington-consumer-health-data-privacy-policy) for additional information about the processing of your personal data and your privacy rights. 

**Security**

We are committed to protecting the security of your personal information. We use technical and organisational measures to provide a level of security appropriate to the risk of processing your personal information. For more information on how Honeywell protects your personal information please contact us at [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com).

**Your rights**

Depending on applicable law, you may have certain rights with respect to your personal information.

* You may have the right to **access, correct, update** or **request deletion** of your personal information.
* You can **object** to the processing of your personal information, ask us to **restrict** processing of your personal information or request **portability** of your personal information.
* You may have the right **not to have a decision made about you that is based solely on automated processing, including profiling** if that decision produces legal effects about you or significantly affects you.
* Similarly, if we have collected and process your personal information with your consent, then **you can withdraw your consent at any time**. Withdrawing your consent will not affect the lawfulness of any processing we conducted prior to your withdrawal, nor will it affect processing of your personal information conducted in reliance on lawful processing grounds other than consent.
* You may have the right to **opt-out of the sale of your personal information**. Honeywell does not sell your personal information to third parties for profit. However, we do share or otherwise disclose your personal information to third parties in accordance with this Privacy Statement and our [Cookie Notice](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice). For example, we engage with third parties to distribute our products, provide you with technical assistance, operate website analytical tools and features, and engage in marketing and sales of our products and services. Such activities may involve the disclosure of your personal information to third parties and may be considered a “sale” of data under certain (but not all) data protection laws.
* You have the right to **complain** to a data protection authority responsible for overseeing compliance with data protection law in your jurisdiction about our collection and use of your personal information if you believe our processing of your personal information does not comply with data protection law. For example, individuals in the EEA have the right to lodge a complaint with the competent Data Protection Authority, a list of which can be accessed at: [https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/board/members\_en](https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/board/members_en).  We would however appreciate the chance to address your concerns, so please feel free to contact us regarding any complaint you may have.  We will not discriminate against individuals for exercising their data privacy rights.

We will facilitate your exercise of the rights that apply to you in accordance with applicable law. However, even if your personal information is not afforded protection under, or otherwise subject to, a data protection law, we may seek to accommodate any request or inquiry you may have with regard to our data processing activities. If you have questions about your rights or wish to exercise your rights, you can contact us at [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com) or submit privacy questions via our interactive webform at the following link:  

**Children's information**

Our Sites are not directed to, and should not be used by, children under the age of sixteen (16) and we do not knowingly collect, use or sell information from such individuals. If you are a minor as understood by laws of your country, please do not submit any personal information through our Sites.

**Links to other websites**

Our Sites may contain links to third-party websites, products and services. We have no liability or responsibility for those websites, products and services, their policies, or their collection or other processing of your personal information. The practices of those third parties is governed by their own privacy policies. We encourage you to learn about the privacy policies of those third parties.

**Contact us**

If you have questions regarding this Privacy Statement or our handling of your personal information, would like to lodge a complaint, or wish to contact our Data Protection Officer, please contact us using the contact information listed below. We will promptly address your concern and strive to reach a satisfactory resolution. 

Interactive Webform:   
  
Email:   
  
Mailing Address:   
Honeywell Privacy   
4D5   
115 Tabor Road   
Morris Plains, NJ 07950  
  
Toll-Free Number:   

**Changes to this Privacy Statement**

We may occasionally update this Privacy Statement. When we do, we will revise the "last updated" date at the top of the Privacy Statement and take such additional steps as may be required by law.

**Last updated April 29, 2024**

Arabic

**آخر تحديث بتاريخ 11 يونيو 2021**

**مقدّمة**

تُعدّ شركة Honeywell International Inc. (المشار إليها باسم **"Honeywell"**، أو**"خاصتنا"،** أو**"الخاصة بنا"،** أو **"نحن**")، هي "المتحكم في البيانات" المتعلقة بالمعلومات الشخصية التي نجمعها عنك عندما تزور أيًّا من مواقعنا الإلكترونية أو تستخدمها، أو عندما تستخدم المنتجات، والخدمات، والتطبيقات المرتبطة ببيان الخصوصية هذا (ويشار إليها إجمالًا باسم **"المواقع").** يوضح بيان الخصوصية هذا كيفية جمعنا لمعلوماتك الشخصية المجمّعة بهذه الطريقة، وكيفية مشاركتها، واستخدامها، كما يوضّح كيفية ممارستك لحقوق الخصوصية الخاصة بك.

وعندما نتفاعل معك، فسيمكننا كذلك تزويدك بإشعارات إضافيةٍ تتعلق بالخصوصية حول أنشطة معالجةٍ معيّنةٍ أو نعرض عليك خياراتٍ إضافيةً حول طريقة معالجة Honeywell لمعلوماتك الشخصية في ذلك التوقيت الزمني المحدد.

انقر فوق أحد الروابط أدناه للانتقال إلى القسم الذي يلفت انتباهك:

**تجميعنا للمعلومات**

* **معلوماتٌ يتم تجميعُها منك بشكلٍ مباشر**. قد نطلب منك معلوماتٍ شخصيّة لتقديم خدمةٍ أو تنفيذ معاملةٍ قمت طلبتها. كما يمكنك تقديم معلوماتٍ شخصيةٍ إلينا عندما تتصل بنا أو تتواصل معنا (لذكر تعليقٍ -مثلًا- أو استفسارٍ ما، أو لطلب دعم العملاء، أو بخصوص زوار الموقع) أو التسجيل للحصول على حساب لاستخدام مواقعنا. وقد تتضمّن هذه المعلومات الشخصية ما يلي:  
    * **بيانات الهوية،** مثل الاسم، والمسمى الوظيفي، واسم الشركة/المؤسسة، وعنوان البريد الإلكتروني، وأرقام الهواتف، والعنوان الفعلي (وهذا يتضمّن اسم الشارع، و/أو المدينة، و/أو الولاية، و/أو الرمز البريدي، و/أو البلد)؛
    * **بيانات التسجيل،** والتّي تزوّدنا بها عند التسجيل للحصول على حسابٍ لاستخدام مواقعنا، بما في ذلك أسماء المستخدمين وكلمات المرور؛
    * **بيانات التوظيف،** بما في ذلك المعلومات المقدّمة حول التقدّم لوظيفة أو الاستفسار عنها (كما هو موضح أدناه)؛
    * **بيانات الاتصال الخاصة بالأعمال التجارية،** مثل المعلومات المتعلقة بالموظفين الآخرين، أو أصحاب العمل، أو المديرين، أو المسؤولين، أو المقاولين التابعين لمؤسسةٍ خارجية (على سبيل المثال: عمل تجاري، أو شركة، أو شراكة، أو ملكية فردية، أو جهة غير ربحية أو حكومية).
    * **بيانات التسويق والاتصالات،** بما في ذلك تفضيلاتك التسويقية واشتراكاتك في المنشورات الخاصة بنا؛
    * **المعلومات المالية،** بما في ذلك معلومات بطاقة الائتمان، أو معلومات الحسابات المالية الأخرى؛ لتمكيننا من تسهيل شرائك لمنتجات الشركة وخدماتها التي قد تكون متاحةً على مواقعنا؛
    * **معلومات مراقبة الصادرات،** مثل الجنسية، والمواطنة، وبلد الإقامة، ما يسمح لنا بتحديد أهليّتك لتلقّي معلوماتٍ حول تقنياتٍ معينةٍ بموجب لوائح مراقبة الصادرات؛
    * **بيانات المعاملات،** بما في ذلك الاستفسارات والأوامر ذات الصلة بمنتجاتنا وخدماتنا وتفاصيل المدفوعات الصادرة منك والواردة إليك، وهذا يشمل محفوظات أوامر الشراء والمعلومات اللازمة لتسهيل معاملات الدفع؛
    * **معلومات تسجيل الأحداث،** ويشمل ذلك المعلومات التي تقدّمها عند ملء استمارات التسجيل الإلكتروني؛ و
    * **ملاحظاتك،** بما في ذلك الاستطلاعات، أو التوصيات، أو ملاحظاتك الأخرى حول مواقعنا، وكذلك حول منتجاتنا، وخدماتنا بشكلٍ عام.

في حال لم تقم بتقديم المعلومات المطلوبة، فقد لا نتمكن إذًا من تزويدك بالخدمة المطلوبة أو من إكمال معاملتك.

* **معلوماتٌ حولك نجمعها تلقائيًا.** نعمل على جمع معلوماتٍ معينةٍ حول زيارتك لمواقعنا باستخدام ملفات تعريف الارتباط وتقنيات التتبع المماثلة. وسنراعي دائمًا أي حقوق قانونية يمكنك استخدامها لمنعنا من القيام بذلك. وتتضمن البيانات التي يتم جمعها بهذه الطريقة ما يلي:
    * **بيانات الاستخدام،** بما في ذلك المعلومات المتعلّقة بكيفية استخدامك لمواقعنا، والصفحات التي تشاهدها، وعدد وحدات البايت المنقولة، والروابط التي تنقر فوقها، والمواد التي تصل إليها، وتاريخ وصولك إلى الموقع ووقت وصولك إليه، والموقع الإلكتروني الذي قمت بربطه بأحد مواقعنا، وغير ذلك من الإجراءات المتَّخذة داخل المواقع؛ إلى جانب
    * **المعلومات الفنّية،** مثل عنوان بروتوكول الإنترنت (IP)، ونوع المتصفّح الخاص بك وإمكانياته واللغة المستخدمة فيه، ونظام التشغيل الخاص بك.

للحصول على معلوماتٍ حول ملفات تعريف الارتباط وتقنيات التتبع المماثلة الأخرى التي نستخدمها على مواقعنا، يُرجى الرجوع [إلى إشعار ملفات تعريف الارتباط لدينا](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#arabic).

* **معلومات الموقع الجغرافي.** بالنسبة لبعض المواقع، يمكننا -بموافقتك- جمع البيانات الدقيقة للموقع الفعليّ (أي الموقع الجغرافي) لجهازك المحمول. وسيكون الغرض الوحيد من استخدام هذه المعلومات هو تسهيل استخدامك للمواقع، وهذا يشمل استخدامها من قِبل مزودي الخدمة لدينا الذين قد يعالجون هذه المعلومات في سياق تقديم الخدمات نيابةً عنا. وفي حال موافقتك، يمكنك تعديل هذه الموافقة بإدارة تفضيلات خدمات الموقع من خلال الإعدادات الموجودة بجهازك المحمول.
* **المعلومات المُجمّعة من جهاتٍ خارجية.** طبقًا للقانون المعمول به، يُسمح لنا بجمع معلوماتٍ شخصيةٍ عنك من جهاتٍ خارجية -مثل المواقع والتطبيقات الخاصة بوسائل التواصل الاجتماعي- ودمجها مع المعلومات التي نحتفظ بها بالفعل؛ لمساعدتنا على تحسين مواقعنا وتخصيصها وفقًا لتفضيلاتك، وكذلك لأغراضٍ محددةٍ أخرى في بيان الخصوصية هذا. كما يُسمح لنا بجمع معلومات الاتصال التجارية الخاصة بك من صاحب العمل لديك أو من جهاتٍ خارجيةٍ أخرى؛ لتسهيل أنشطة الأعمال التقليدية والمسائل الإدارية المماثلة أو المشاركة فيها بطرقٍ أخرى.

**استخدامنا للمعلومات**

يُسمح لنا باستخدام المعلومات الشخصية التي يتم جمعها عبر مواقعنا أو أثناء اتصالك بنا لأغراضٍ تشمل ما يلي:

* بيانات الاتصال التجارية. تعمل شركة Honeywell على جمع **بيانات الاتصال التجارية** واستخدامها للمشاركة في الاتصالات أو المعاملات، بما في ذلك إجراء العناية الواجبة فيما يتعلق بمنتجٍ معيّنٍ أو خدمةٍ معيّنةٍ، أو توفيرها، أو الحصول عليها. فمثلًا، قد تقوم شركة Honeywell بجمع بيانات الاتصال التجارية هذه واستخدامها لتسهيل الأوامر، والعقود، والضمانات، والصيانة، والوظائف التجارية المشابهة وإدارتها، تحقيقًا لأغراض تحليل الائتمان والتّحصيل؛ للمساعدة في الامتثال الداخلي وتحقيق المتطلبات القانونية الخاصة بنا، وللدفاع عن مصالحنا ومطالباتنا (إذا لزم الأمر).
* **الخدمات والمعاملات.** يُسمح لنا باستخدام معلوماتك الشخصية لتزويدك بالخدمات أو تنفيذ المعاملات التي طلبتها، ومن ذلك -على سبيل المثال لا الحصر- تقديم معلوماتٍ عن منتجات الشركة أو خدماتها التي اشتريتها أو استخدمتها بأي طريقةٍ أخرى، إلى جانب تسجيل المنتجات التي اشتريتها، ومعالجة أوامر الشراء، والتعامل مع مطالبات الضمانات، واستبدال أدلّة استخدام المنتجات، والرد على طلبات خدمة العملاء، وتسهيل استخدام مواقعنا.
* **إدارة أعمالنا التجارية ومواقعنا وحمايتها.** يمكن أن نستخدم معلوماتك الشخصية لإدارة أعمالنا ومواقعنا وحمايتها، بما في ذلك استكشاف الأخطاء وإصلاحها، وصيانة النظام، والدعم، وإعداد التقارير، واستضافة البيانات.
* **تحسين أعمالنا التجارية، ومواقعنا، ومنتجاتنا، وخدماتنا.** قد نستخدم معلوماتك الشخصية لتحليل الأعمال، أو لأغراضٍ أخرى تساعدنا على تطوير جودة أعمالنا التجارية، ومواقعنا، ومنتجاتنا، وخدماتنا، وتحسينها (بما في ذلك المنتجات والخدمات الجديدة)، ويكون ذلك -على سبيل المثال- بتخصيص مواقعنا لتناسب تفضيلاتك الخاصة واهتماماتك.
* **التسويق.** طبقًا للقوانين واللوائح المعمول بها، قد نستخدم معلوماتك الشخصية لإبلاغك بالمنتجات أو الخدمات التي قد تهمك، أو للتواصل معك بشأن العروض، والأحداث، والأخبار، والاستطلاعات، والعروض الخاصة، والموضوعات ذات الصلة. ويمكنك إلغاء الاشتراك في المراسلات التسويقية المرسلة عبر البريد الإلكتروني في أي وقت، مجانًا، وذلك باستخدام رابط "إلغاء الاشتراك" في أي مواد تسويقية تتلقاها منا عبر البريد الإلكتروني، أو عن طريق الاتصال بنا باستخدام معلومات الاتصال المدرجة في بيان الخصوصية هذا. وحسب بلد إقامتك، قد تتمكن كذلك من إلغاء الاشتراك في أنواعٍ أخرى من المراسلات التسويقية؛ ولمزيدٍ من المعلومات، يُرجى الاتصال بنا باستخدام معلومات الاتصال المدرجة في بيان الخصوصية. كما تمنحُ بعض السلطات الحقَّ للأفراد (على سبيل المثال، سكان كاليفورنيا) في طلب معلوماتٍ معينةٍ بخصوص إفصاحنا عن المعلومات الشخصية لجهاتٍ خارجيةٍ لأغراض التسويق المباشر من جانب تلك الجهات. ولمزيدٍ من المعلومات حول ممارسات الإفصاح عن البيانات لأغراض التسويق لدينا، يُرجى الاتصال بنا وفقًا للتعليمات المذكورة أدناه.
* **الإعلانات القائمة على الاهتمامات.** نقوم بجمع بياناتٍ حول أنشطتك عبر الإنترنت ونحدّد اهتماماتك لنتمكن من أن نقدّم إليك الإعلانات الأكثر صلةً بك. يمكنك إلغاء الاشتراك في تلقي الإعلانات القائمة على الاهتمامات من شركة Honeywell كما هو موضّحٌ في [إشعار ملفات تعريف الارتباط الخاص بنا](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#arabic).
* **برامج الحوافز المالية والولاء.** نقوم بجمع المعلومات الشخصية واستخدامها للحفاظ على برامج الحوافز المالية والولاء وإدارتها. فنحن نستخدم المعلومات الشخصية التي تقدّمُها لنا في هذه البرامج لتقديم مكافآت فريدة، وتتبُّع حالة البرنامج لديك، وتسهيل تبديل نقاط البرنامج للمنتجات، والمواد الترويجية، وورش العمل التدريبية، وغيرها من العناصر. كما يُسمح لنا باستخدام أي معلومات شخصية تقدمها -بالحد الذي يسمح به القانون- في سياق برنامج الحوافز المالية لأي غرض آخر من الأغراض المنصوص عليها في بيان الخصوصية هذا. يُرجى مراجعة الشروط والأحكام الخاصة بكل برنامج من برامج الحوافز المالية التي ترغب في التسجيل فيها أو المشاركة فيها، فقد تكون هذه الشروط والأحكام موضوعةً بشكل حازمٍ حسب البرنامج المعمول به. في حال وافقت على المشاركة في هذه البرامج، يمكنك سحب هذه الموافقة في أي وقتٍ عن طريق الاتصال بنا باستخدام تفاصيل جهات الاتصال المدرجة في نهاية بيان الخصوصية هذا أو وفقًا للتعليمات المنصوص عليها في الشروط والأحكام الخاصة بالبرنامج المعمول به.
* **طلبات التوظيف.** فيما يتعلق بالتقدّم بطلبٍ لوظيفةٍ ما أو الاستفسار عنها، يمكنك تزويدنا بمعلوماتٍ عن نفسك، مثل بيان السيرة/السيرة الذاتية، والمراجع المهنية، ومعلوماتٍ حول مؤهلاتك التعليمية وخلفيتك الوظيفية، ومعلوماتٍ حول التدريب والشهادات المهنية. ويُسمح لنا ولأعضاء مجموعتنا باستخدام هذه المعلومات لغرض النّظر في طلبات التوظيف، والتحقق من الخلفية ومن الأهلية لشغل الوظيفة، كما يُسمح لنا باستخدامها على النحو المنصوص عليه بخلاف ذلك في أي بيان خصوصيةٍ منفصلٍ أو أي إشعارٍ آخر تتم إتاحته فيما يتعلق بطلبك الذي تقدّمه. قد نلجأ إلى استخدام جهةٍ خارجيةٍ (على سبيل المثال: مسؤول توظيف) أو استخدام منصةٍ من منصات وسائل التواصل الاجتماعي لاجتذاب طلبات التوظيف، وتجميعها، والاحتفاظ بها. لمزيدٍ من المعلومات، يُرجى قراءة إشعار [خصوصية مقدّم الطلب الخاص](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/applicant-privacy-notice) بنا.
* **البحث والتحليل.** يمكن أن نستخدم معلوماتك الشخصية لإجراء البحث والتحليل، وذلك لمساعدتنا في تحليل تفضيلات الشراء الخاصة بك، وتحديد المنتجات والخدمات التي تلبي متطلباتك على أفضل وجهٍ، وقياسِ فعالية الإعلانات التي نعرضها لك.
* **الاستخدام الإلزامي:** يمكن أن نستخدم المعلومات الشخصية التي نجمعها من أجل اكتشاف محاولات الاحتيال، أو انتهاكات الملكية الفكرية، أو انتهاكات الشروط والأحكام الخاصة بنا، أو انتهاكات القانون، أو أي إساءة استخدام أخرى لمواقعنا، إلى جانب منعها، والاستجابة لها.

قد نقوم بدمج المعلومات التي نجمعها عبر مواقعنا مع المعلومات الأخرى التي نحتفظ بها حولك (مثل المعلومات المتعلقة باستخدامك لمنتجاتنا وخدماتنا) -أينما سمح القانون بذلك- من أجل أن نقدم لك تجربة عملاءٍ محسّنةٍ ومتّسقةٍ عند التفاعل معنا أو لأغراض أخرى من المنصوص عليها في بيان الخصوصية هذا.

**الأساس القانوني الذي نستند إليه في معالجة المعلومات**

سنضمن وجود أساس قانوني لمعالجة معلوماتك الشخصية حيثما يقتضي القانون ذلك. يعتمد أساسنا القانوني -في معظم الحالات- على المعلومات الشخصية المعنيّة وعلى السياق المحدد الذي نجمعها فيه.

* **اتفاق:** تُعد المعالجة أمرًا ضروريًا لأداء الخدمات التي نقدمها لك، أو لاتخاذ خطوات (بناءً على طلبك) قبل تنفيذ هذه الخدمات، بالإضافة إلى توقّعها؛
* **الالتزام القانوني:** تُعد المعالجة أمرًا ضروريًا امتثالًا لالتزاماتنا القانونية، بما في ذلك الامتثال للقوانين واللوائح المعمول بها، أو الطلبات الحكومية، أو شبه الحكومية، أو الأحكام القضائية، أو مذكرات الإحضار؛
* **الموافقة:** تعتمد المعالجة على موافقتك على معالجة معلوماتك الشخصية لغرضٍ واحدٍ محددٍ أو أكثر من غرض (مثل التسويق)؛
* **المصالح المشروعة:** تُعد المعالجة أمرًا ضروريًا لتلبية مصالحنا المشروعة، ومن ذلك -على سبيل المثال- تطوير مواقعنا و/أو منتجاتنا و/أو خدماتنا وتحسينها لصالح عملائنا؛ أو
* **المصالح الحيوية:** تُعد المعالجة أمرًا ضروريًا لحماية مصالحك الحيوية (ومن ذلك على سبيل المثال: الأسباب المتعلّقة بالصحة والسلامة إذا كنت ستحضر اجتماعًا في موقع شركة Honeywell).

إذا كانت لديك أي أسئلةٍ أو كنت بحاجةٍ إلى مزيدٍ من المعلومات بشأن الأساس القانوني الذي نستند إليه في جمع معلوماتك الشخصية واستخدامها، فيُرجى إرسال رسالة إلكترونية عبر [HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com)

**إخفاء مصادر المعلومات**

يُسمح لنا -طبقًا للقانون المعمول به- بإخفاء مصادر معلوماتك الشخصية، بحيث لا يمكن استخدامها فيما بعد لتحديد هويتك. لا تُعدُّ المعلومات مجهولة المصدر معلوماتٍ شخصية، ومن ثمّ فهي لا تخضع لبيان الخصوصية هذا. يُسمح لنا بجمع المعلومات مجهولة المصدر، واستخدامها، وتجميعها، ومشاركتها لأي غرضٍ كان.

**مدّة احتفاظنا بالمعلومات**

تختلف الفترة التي نحتفظ فيها بمعلوماتك الشخصية باختلاف الغرض من المعالجة. فمثلًا، نحتفظ بالمعلومات الشخصية اللازمة لتزويدك بالمنتجات والخدمات، أو لتسهيل المعاملات التي طلبتها، طالما أنك عميلٌ لشركة Honeywell أو في حال تقدّمت بطلب توظيفٍ عبر مواقعنا، فسنحتفظ بتفاصيل طلبك على النحو المنصوص عليه في إشعار الخصوصية المتاح لك فيما يتعلق بهذا الطلب أو حسبما يقتضيه القانون. أمّا في جميع الحالات الأخرى، فإننا نحتفظ بمعلوماتك الشخصية طالما كانت ضروريةً لتحقيق الأغراض الموضّحة في بيان الخصوصية هذا، وبعد ذلك الوقت تكون هذه المعلومات مجهولة المصدر (حيثما يسمح القانون المعمول به) أو محذوفةً، أو تالفة.

**الإفصاح عن المعلومات**

يُسمح لنا بمشاركة معلوماتك الشخصية مع جهاتٍ خارجيةٍ محددةٍ طبقًا للقانون المعمول به، بما في ذلك مشاركتها على النحو الموضّح أدناه:

* **مجموعة شركاتنا.** يمكن أن نشارك معلوماتك الشخصية مع الشركات التابعة لنا ومجموعة الشركات حسبما تقتضيه الضرورة -بشكلٍ معقولٍ- تحقيقًا للأغراض المنصوص عليها في بيان الخصوصية هذا.
* **مقدمو الخدمة.** يمكن أن نشارك معلوماتك الشخصية مع الشركات التي تعاقدنا معها لتقديم الخدمات بالنيابة عنا، مثل استضافة مواقع الويب وإجراء الاستطلاعات، ومعالجة المعاملات، وتحليل مواقعنا، وإجراء التحليلات لتحسين جودة أعمالنا التجارية ومواقعنا، ومنتجاتنا وخدماتنا. ونحن نطلب من مزودي الخدمة هؤلاء حماية سرية معلوماتك الشخصية.
* **الموزعون والشركاء التجاريون الآخرون الموثوق بهم.** قد نشارك معلوماتك الشخصية مع جهاتٍ خارجيةٍ توزع منتجاتنا، ومع شركاء تجاريين موثوقين آخرين لأغراضٍ تشمل السماح لتلك الجهات الخارجية بإرسال مراسلاتٍ تسويقيةٍ إليك. وستتم مشاركة المعلومات الشخصية لأغراض التسويق على هذا النحو طبقًا للقوانين واللوائح المعمول بها.
* **الإفصاح المتعلق بالمعاملات.** قد نكشف عن بعض معلوماتك الشخصية أو كلها -فيما يتعلق بمعاملاتٍ معينةٍ- للمؤسسات المالية، أو الهيئات الحكومية، أو شركات الشحن، أو الخدمات البريدية، المتعلقة بتنفيذ المعاملة.
* **الإفصاحات المتعلقة بعمليات الاستحواذ أو التصفية.** قد تنشأ ظروف عندما تقرر شركة Honeywell -لأسبابٍ إستراتيجيةٍ أو لأسبابٍ تجاريةٍ أخرى- بيع الأعمال التجارية، أو شراءها، أو تجريدها، أو دمجها، أو إعادة تنظيمها بطريقةٍ أخرى في بعض البلدان. وقد نكشف عن المعلومات التي نحتفظ بها عنك بالقدر الضروري -وبشكلٍ معقول- للمضي قدمًا في التفاوض أو إكمال عملية الدمج لجميع أصول شركة Honeywell أو جزءٍ منها، أو الاستحواذ عليها، أو سحبها أو بيعها.
* **الإفصاح لأسبابٍ أخرى.** يُسمح لنا بالإفصاح عن المعلومات الشخصية إذا اقتضى الأمر ذلك بموجب القانون، أو عند الاعتقاد -بحسن نيةٍ- أن هذا الإجراء ضروري للامتثال للمتطلبات القانونية أو للإجراءات القانونية التي نخضع لها، وذلك بهدف حماية حقوقنا، أو ممتلكاتنا، والدفاع عنها، أو لحماية السلامة الشخصية -في حالات الطوارئ- لأي فردٍ.

**عمليات النقل الدولية**

شركة Honeywell هي مؤسسةٌ عالمية، ويمكن من خلالها نقل معلوماتك الشخصية، أو الاحتفاظ بها، أو تخزينها، أو استخدامها عبر مواقع مختلفةٍ في جميع أنحاء العالم، مثل الولايات المتحدة، والمكسيك، والهند، ويكون ذلك طبقًا للقانون المعمول به. ما يعني أنه حين نجمع معلوماتك الشخصية، فمن المحتمل أن تتم معالجتها في البلدان التي تُطبّق فيها قوانين مختلفةٌ عن قوانين بلدك فيما يخُصّ حماية البيانات. ومع ذلك، ستتخذ شركة Honeywell دائمًا خطواتٍ مقبولةٍ لحماية خصوصيتك، ولتوفير مستوى من الحماية للمعلومات الشخصية يمكن مقارنته بمستوى بلد إقامتك، والذي يتضمن تنفيذ البنود التعاقدية القياسية للمفوضية الأوروبية. لمزيدٍ من المعلومات حول الضمانات المناسبة المعمول بها لحماية معلوماتك الشخصية، يُرجى التواصل معنا عبر [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com).

**الأمان**

نحن ملتزمون بحماية أمان معلوماتك الشخصية. نستخدم التدابير الفنية والتنظيمية لتوفير مستوى من الأمان يتناسب مع المخاطر المتعلّقة بمعالجة معلوماتك الشخصية. ولمزيدٍ من المعلومات حول كيفية حماية شركة Honeywell لمعلوماتك الشخصية، يُرجى التواصل معنا عبر [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com)

**حقوقك**

طبقًا للقانون المعمول به، فإنك قد تتمتّع بحقوقٍ معينةٍ فيما يتعلق بمعلوماتك الشخصية.

* فقد يكون لك الحق في **الوصول إلى معلوماتك الشخصية أو تصحيحها، أو تحديثها، أو** طلب حذفها.
* ويمكنك **الاعتراض** على معالجة معلوماتك الشخصية، كما يمكنك أن تطلب منا **تقييد** عملية معالجة معلوماتك الشخصية أو أن تطلب **قابلية نقل** معلوماتك الشخصية.
* قد يكون لديك الحق **في عدم الالتزام بقرارٍ اتُّخذ بشأنك ويستند بالكامل إلى المعالجة الآلية، بما في ذلك جمع المعلومات** إذا كان هذا القرار تنتج عنه آثار قانونية تتعلق بك أو يؤثر عليك بشكلٍ كبير.
* وبالمثل، إذا قمنا بجمع معلوماتك الشخصية ومعالجتها بموافقتك، يمكنك حينها **سحب موافقتك في أي وقت.** لن يؤثر سحب موافقتك على شرعية أي معالجة أجريناها قبل انسحابك، ولن يؤثر على معالجة معلوماتك الشخصية التي تتم وفقًا لأسس معالجةٍ قانونيةٍ بخلاف الموافقة.
* قد يكون لك الحق في **اختيار عدم بيع معلوماتك الشخصية.** لا تبيع شركة Honeywell معلوماتك الشخصية لجهاتٍ خارجيةٍ بغرض الربح. ومع ذلك، فإننا نشارك معلوماتك الشخصية أو نكشف عنها بطريقةٍ أخرى لجهاتٍ خارجية بما يتوافق مع بيان الخصوصية هذا ومع [إشعار ملفات تعريف الارتباط](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#arabic) الخاص بنا. فنحن نتشارك -على سبيل المثال- مع جهاتٍ خارجيةٍ لتوزيع منتجاتنا، ونوفر لك المساعدة الفنية، ونقوم بتشغيل الأدوات التحليلية والمزايا لمواقع الويب، ونشارك في تسويق منتجاتنا، وخدماتنا، وبيعها. وقد تتضمّن هذه الأنشطة الكشف عن معلوماتك الشخصية لجهاتٍ خارجية، وقد تعتبر "عملية بيعٍ" للبيانات بموجب بعض القوانين المعنيّة بحماية البيانات (وليس كلّها).
* لديك الحق في **رفع شكوى** إلى سلطة حماية البيانات المسؤولة عن الإشراف على الامتثال لقانون حماية البيانات في ولايتك القضائية بشأن جمعنا لمعلوماتك الشخصية واستخدامها إذا كنت تعتقد أن معالجتنا لمعلوماتك الشخصية لا تتوافق مع قانون حماية البيانات. فيحقّ -على سبيل المثال- للأفراد في المنطقة الاقتصادية الأوروبية التقدّم بشكوى إلى هيئة حماية البيانات المختصة، والتي يمكن الوصول إلى قائمتها عبر: [https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/board/members\_en](https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/board/members_en). ومع ذلك، فإننا نقدّر منحك الفرصة لمواجهة مخاوفك، لذلك لا تتردد في الاتصال بنا بخصوص أي شكوى قد ترغب في التقدّم بها. ولن يصدر منّا أي شكل من أشكال التمييز ضد أي فردٍ من الأفراد لممارستهم حقوق خصوصية البيانات الخاصة بهم.

وسنعمل على تسهيل ممارسة الحقوق التي تنطبق عليك وفقًا للقانون المعمول به. وعلى أي حالٍ، فحتى إذا كانت معلوماتك الشخصية غير متاحةٍ للحماية بموجب قانون حماية البيانات، أو كانت لا تخضع له بأي شكلٍ آخر، فقد نسعى إلى تلبية أي طلبٍ أو استفسارٍ قد يكون لديك فيما يتعلق بأنشطة معالجة البيانات الخاصة بنا. وإذا كانت لديك أسئلةٌ حول حقوقك أو كنت ترغب في ممارستها، يمكنك التواصل معنا عبر [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com) أو إرسال أسئلة الخصوصية عبر نموذج الويب التفاعلي الخاص بنا من خلال الرابط التالي:

**المعلومات الخاصة بالأطفال**

لا تُوجَه مواقعنا إلى الأطفال الذين تقل أعمارهم عن ستة عشر (16) عامًا ولا ينبغي عليهم استخدامها، ونحن لا نقوم بجمع أي معلوماتٍ من هؤلاء الأفراد، أو بيعها، أو استخدامها عن قصد. وإذا كنت قاصرًا حسب ما تنصّ عليه قوانين بلدك، فيُرجى عدم إرسال أي معلوماتٍ شخصيةٍ عبر مواقعنا.

**روابط لمواقع ويب أخرى**

قد تحتوي مواقعنا على روابط لمواقع ويب، ومنتجاتٍ، وخدماتٍ تابعةٍ لجهات خارجية. نحن لا نتحمل أي التزامٍ أو مسؤوليةٍ تجاه تلك المواقع، أو المنتجات، أو الخدمات أو سياساتها، أو تجميعها لمعلوماتك الشخصية، أو سبل معالجتها الأخرى لمعلوماتك الشخصية. وتخضع ممارسات تلك الجهات الخارجية لسياسات الخصوصية الخاصة بها. ونحن نحثّك على التعرف على سياسات الخصوصية لتلك الجهات الخارجية.

**تواصل معنا**

إذا كانت لديك أي أسئلةٍ فيما يتعلق ببيان الخصوصية هذا أو بطريقة تعاملنا مع معلوماتك الشخصية، أو كنت ترغب في التقّدم بشكوى، أو في الاتصال بمسؤول حماية البيانات لدينا، فيُرجى الاتصال بنا باستخدام معلومات الاتصال المدرجة أدناه. سنتعامل مع مخاوفك على الفور وسنسعى للتوصل إلى حلٍّ مرضٍ.

نموذج الويب التفاعلي :  

البريد الإلكتروني :  

العنوان :  
Honeywell Privacy  
4D5  
115 Tabor Road  
Morris Plains, NJ 07950

رقم المكالمات المجانية :  

**التغييرات في بيان الخصوصية هذا**

قد نقوم بتحديث بيان الخصوصية هذا من حينٍ لآخر. وعندما نقوم بذلك، سنحرص على مراجعة تاريخ "آخر تحديث" في الجزء العلوي من بيان الخصوصية وسنراعي اتّخاذ الخطوات الإضافية التي قد يقتضيها القانون.

**آخر تحديث بتاريخ 11 يونيو 2021**

Chinese

**上次更新日期 2021年 12 月 02 日**

**简介**

当您访问或使用我们涉及隐私声明的任何网站、产品、服务和应用程序（统称为我们的“站点”）时，Honeywell International Inc.（**“霍尼韦尔”**或**“我们”**）会收集您的个人信息，并且是所收集信息的数据控制者。 本隐私声明说明了我们如何收集、共享和使用借此收集的您的个人信息，以及您可以如何行使您的隐私权。

当我们与您互动时，可能还会向您发布有关特定处理活动的其他隐私通知，或为您提供关于霍尼韦尔在该特定时间点如何处理您个人信息的其他选择。

单击下方的链接之一，跳转到您感兴趣的部分：

**信息的收集**

* **直接向您收集的信息**。为了按照您的请求提供服务或进行交易，我们可能会请您提供个人信息。 与我们联系或合作（例如提供意见、查询事宜、有客户支持请求或访问站点），或者为使用我们的站点而注册帐户时，也可能需要您向我们提供个人信息。 这些个人信息包括：
    * **身份数据，**例如您的姓名、职务、公司/组织名称、电子邮件地址、电话号码和实际地址（包括国家/地区、省/自治区/直辖市、市、街道和邮政编码）；
    * **注册数据，**您为使用我们的站点而注册帐户时提供的信息，包括用户名和密码；
    * **招聘数据，**包括在申请工作或查询时提交的信息（如下所述）；
    * **业务联系数据，**例如与第三方组织（如企业、公司、合伙企业、独资企业、非营利组织或政府机构）的其他员工、所有者、董事、高级职员或承包商相关的信息。
    * **营销和通讯数据，**包括您的购买偏好，以及您对我们出版物的订阅；
    * **财务信息，**包括信用卡或其他财务帐户信息，旨在方便您购买我们的站点上可能提供的公司产品和服务；
    * **出口管制信息，**例如您的国籍、公民身份以及所在国家/地区，以便我们可依据出口管制法规确定您是否有资格获知关于某些技术的信息；
    * **交易数据，**包括与我们的产品和服务相关的查询和订单，以及您的收付款详细信息，包括购买订单历史记录和促进付款交易所需的信息；
    * **活动注册信息，**包括您在填写电子注册表单时提供的信息；以及
    * **您的反馈，**包括您对我们的站点以及产品和服务整体上的调查结果、建议或其他反馈。

如果您没有提供请求的信息，我们可能无法为您提供请求的服务或完成您的交易。

* **我们自动收集的与您相关的信息**。我们会使用 Cookie 和类似跟踪技术来收集有关您访问我们站点的某些信息。 您有阻止我们收集这些信息的合法权利，我们将一直尊重您的此等权利。 以此方式收集的数据包括：
    * **使用数据，**包括以下相关信息：您如何使用我们的站点、查看的页面、传送的字节数、单击的链接、访问的资料、访问站点的日期和时间、您从哪个网站链接到我们的某个站点，以及在站点内执行的其他操作；以及
    * **技术数据，**例如 Internet 协议 (IP) 地址、浏览器类型、功能和语言，以及操作系统。

有关我们在霍尼韦尔站点上使用的 Cookie 和其他类似跟踪技术，请参阅我们的 [Cookie 声明](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#language3)。

* **地理位置信息**。对于某些站点，经您同意后，我们可能会收集您移动设备的准确、实时位置（即地理位置）。 此信息将仅用于方便您使用站点，包括我们的服务提供商可能会出于代表我们提供服务而处理此信息。 您给予同意后，也可以更改此同意，方法是在您移动设备的设置中，管理“定位服务”首选项。
* **从第三方收集的信息**。依据适用的法律，我们可能会从第三方（例如社交媒体网站和应用程序）处收集与您相关的个人信息，并将此类信息与我们已有的信息结合使用，来帮助我们根据您的偏好并出于本隐私声明中所列的其他目的，改进和定制我们的站点。我们还可能会从您的雇主或其他第三方处收集您的业务联系信息，以促进或参与传统业务活动和类似的管理事项。
* **敏感个人信息**。根据适用法律，我们收集的有关您的一些个人信息可能被视为“敏感”信息，视情况而定，**其中可能包括财务信息、交易信息和跟踪信息**。

**信息的使用**

通过霍尼韦尔站点或您联系我们时收集的个人信息，可能会用于以下目的，包括：

* **业务联系数据**。 霍尼韦尔将收集和使用业务联系数据进行沟通或交易，包括就产品或服务开展尽职调查，或者提供或接收产品或服务。 例如，霍尼韦尔可能会收集和使用此类业务联系数据来促进和管理订单、合同、保修、维护和类似业务职能；用于信用分析和收集；帮助达成我们自己内部的合规性和法律要求；以及（如有必要）捍卫我们的利益和主张。
* **服务和交易**。我们可能会使用您的个人信息按您的请求提供服务或进行交易，包括但不限于提供有关您已购买或以其他方式使用的公司产品或服务的信息、注册所购买的产品、处理产品订单、处理保修索赔、更换产品手册、回应客户服务请求以及方便使用我们的站点。
* **管理和保护我们的业务与站点**。我们可能会使用您的个人信息管理和保护我们的业务和站点，包括疑难解答、系统维护、支持以及数据的报告和托管。
* **改进我们的业务、站点、产品和服务**。我们可能会使用您的个人信息执行业务分析，或将其用于其他目的，来帮助我们发展业务、站点、产品和服务（包括新产品和服务）和改进其质量，例如根据您的特定偏好或兴趣定制我们的站点。
* **营销**。依据适用的法律和法规，我们可能会使用您的个人信息向您告知您可能感兴趣的产品或服务，或以其他方式向您告知产品和服务、活动和新闻、调查、特惠以及相关主题。 您可以随时选择不接收通过电子邮件发送的营销资讯，而无需承担任何费用，方法是使用我们发送给您的任何电子邮件营销资料中的“取消订阅”链接，或者使用本隐私声明中所列的联系信息联系我们。 根据您所在的国家/地区，您还可以选择不接收其他类型的营销资讯；有关详情，请使用本隐私声明中所列的联系信息联系我们。在某些司法管辖区，个人（如加利福尼亚州居民）有权请求有关我们向第三方披露个人信息以用于第三方直接营销的特定信息。 想了解更多我们出于营销目的而采取的数据披露做法，请按照下文的说明与我们联系。
* **根据兴趣推送广告**。 我们收集您的在线活动数据并明确您的兴趣所在，从而提供您最兴趣的广告。 您可以按照我们的 [Cookie 声明](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#language3)所述，选择不接收霍尼韦尔根据兴趣提供的广告。
* **财务激励和忠诚度计划**。 我们收集和使用个人信息来维护和管理我们的财务激励与忠诚度计划。 我们使用您在这些计划中提供的个人信息来提供特殊奖励、跟踪您的计划状态，并促进用计划积分兑换产品、促销材料、培训研讨会和其他项目。 在法律允许的范围内，我们还可能会出于本隐私声明中所列的任何其他目的，将您提供的任何个人信息用于财务激励计划。 请查看您要注册或参与的每个财务激励计划的条款和条件，因为这些条款和条件可能严格限于适用计划。 如果您同意参与此类计划，您可以随时撤销此项同意，方法是使用本隐私声明在末尾提供的详细联系信息或根据适用计划的条款和条件中所列的说明与我们联系。
* **就职申请**。在工作申请或查询中，您可能会向我们提供有关您自己的信息，例如简历、职业推荐信、有关教育和工作背景的信息以及有关职业培训和证书的信息。我们和我们集团的成员可能会将此类信息用于雇佣考虑、背景调查和就业资格认定，以及与您的申请相关的任何单独隐私声明或其他适用通知中所列的其他目的。 我们可能会使用第三方（例如招聘机构）或社交媒体平台来征集、收集和保留就职申请。 有关更多信息，请查看我们[的求职者隐私声明](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/applicant-privacy-notice#chinese)。
* **调查和分析**。我们可能会使用您的个人信息进行研究和分析，来帮助我们分析您的购买偏好、确定最能满足您要求的产品和服务，并衡量我们向您提供的广告的效果。
* **强制实施：**我们可能会将收集的个人信息用于检测、阻止和应对欺诈、知识产权侵犯、违反我们的条款和条件、违反法律或其他滥用我们站点的行为。

在法律允许的范围内，我们可能会将通过我们的站点收集的信息与我们拥有的与您相关的其他信息（例如与您使用我们的产品和服务相关的信息）结合使用，以在您与我们交互时为您提供改进的一致客户体验，或将其用于本隐私声明中所列的其他目的。

**我们处理信息的法律依据**

在法律要求的情况下，我们将会确保根据法律依据处理您的个人信息。 在大多数情况下，我们的法律依据取决于相关个人信息以及我们收集个人信息所在的特定环境。

* **合同：** 要正常使用我们为您提供的服务，或者在提供此类服务之前（应您请求）采取措施或预计将提供此类服务，则必需处理您的个人信息；
* **法律义务：** 我们出于履行法律义务（包括遵循适用的法律、法规、政府和准政府请求、法院命令或传票）而必需处理您的个人信息；
* **同意：** 处理建立在您同意出于一个或多个指定目的（例如营销）处理您的个人信息的基础之上；
* **合法利益：** 处理对于行使我们的合法利益是必需的，例如为了我们客户的利益，开发和改进我们的站点、产品和/或服务；或者
* **重要利益：** 处理对于保护您的重要利益是必需的（例如，如果您在霍尼韦尔地点参加会议，则我们可能出于保护您的健康和安全的原因来处理您的个人信息）。

如果您对我们收集和使用您的个人信息的法律依据有任何疑问或需要进一步的信息，请发送电子邮件至 [HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com)

**对信息进行匿名化处理**

依据适用的法律，我们可能会匿名处理您的个人信息，以便该信息不再能够用于识别您的身份。 匿名信息不属于个人信息，因此不受本隐私声明的制约。 我们可能会出于任何目的收集、使用、整合和共享匿名信息。

**我们保留信息的时长**

我们存储您的个人信息的时长因处理目的而异。 例如，在您作为霍尼韦尔客户的时间内，我们会一直存储您的个人信息，以便为您提供产品和服务，或为您请求的交易提供便利；或者如果您通过我们的站点提交求职申请，除非法律另有要求，否则我们将根据提供的与您的申请相关的隐私声明中的规定，保留您的申请详细信息。 在其他所有情况下，根据适用法律，我们会按照实现本隐私声明中所列的目的所需的时长存储您的个人信息，此后将匿名保存（在适用法律允许的范围内）、删除或销毁该信息。

**信息的披露**

我们可能会依据适用的法律与包括以下方在内的所选第三方共享您的个人信息：

* **我们的集团公司**。出于本隐私声明中所述的目的，我们可能会根据合理需要，与我们的关联公司和集团公司共享您的个人信息。
* **服务提供商**。我们可能会与签订了合同代表我们提供服务（例如托管网站、开展调查、处理交易、分析我们的站点和执行分析）的公司共享您的个人信息，以便提高我们的业务、站点、产品和服务的质量。 我们要求这些服务提供商保护您的个人信息的机密性。
* **分销商和其他可靠业务合作伙伴**。我们可能会与分销我们的产品的第三方以及其他可靠业务合作伙伴共享您的个人信息，以用于允许这些第三方向您发送营销资讯等目的。 出于营销目的进行的此类个人信息共享，将依据适用的法律和法规执行。
* **执行交易时披露**。在执行某些交易时，我们可能会向执行交易过程中涉及的金融机构、政府部门和运输公司或邮政机关披露您的部分或全部个人信息。
* **收购或资产剥离时披露**。出于战略原因或其他商业原因，可能会出现霍尼韦尔决定出售、购买、资产剥离、合并或以其他方式重组某些国家/地区内的企业的情况。 我们仅会披露我们所保留的有关您的合理必要信息，以便继续磋商或完成霍尼韦尔全部或部分资产的合并、收购、资产剥离或出售。
* **出于其他原因披露**。在以下情况下，我们可能会披露个人信息：法律规定或许可这么做；确信必须这么做才符合适用的法律规定或法律程序；保护和捍卫我们的权利或财产；在紧急情况下保护任何人的人身安全。

**跨国转移**

霍尼韦尔是一家全球性组织，因此可能会根据适用法律，将您的个人信息转移到世界各地或在这些地方保存、存储或使用您的个人信息，例如美国、墨西哥和印度等其他国家。 这意味着，当我们收集您的个人信息时，它可能会在其数据保护法律与您所在国家/地区的法律不同的国家/地区进行处理。 但是，霍尼韦尔将始终根据适用法律采取合理的措施来转移或处理您的个人信息，以保护您的隐私，并提供与您所在国家/地区同等水平的个人信息保护，其中包括执行相关监管部门批准的标准合同条款。

有关为保护您的个人信息所采取的相应安全保障措施的更多信息，请通过 [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com) 联系我们。

**安全性**

我们致力于保护您的个人信息的安全。 我们使用技术和组织措施来提供与处理您的个人信息的风险相适应的安全级别。有关霍尼韦尔如何保护您的个人信息的更多信息，请通过 [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com) 联系我们。

**您的权利**

根据适用法律，您对您的个人信息可能享有某些权利。

* 在适用及实际可行的情况下，您有权**访问、要求一份复印本、更正、更新**或要求**删除**您的个人信息。
* 您可以**反对**处理您的个人信息，要求我们**限制**处理您的个人信息或请求您的个人信息的**可移植性**。
* 您有权要求解释，并且要求**不完全基于自动化处理（包括分析）来做出有关您的、**会对您产生法律影响或对您有重大影响的决定。
* 同样，如果我们在征得您同意的情况下收集并处理了您的个人信息，**您可以随时撤销同意**。 撤销同意不会影响我们在您撤销之前进行的任何处理的合法性，也不会影响根据同意以外的合法处理理由对您个人信息的处理。
* 您有权**选择不出售您的个人信息**。 霍尼韦尔不会将您的个人信息出售给第三方以获取利润。 但是，我们会根据本隐私声明和我们的 [Cookie 声明](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#language3)，与第三方共享或以其他方式向第三方披露您的个人信息。 例如，我们会与第三方合作来分销我们的产品、向您提供技术帮助、运行网站分析工具和功能以及从事我们的产品和服务的营销与销售。 此类活动可能涉及向第三方披露您的个人信息，这些活动在某些（而非全部）数据保护法律下可能会被视为“出售”数据。
* 如果您认为我们在处理您的个人信息时未遵循数据保护法，您有权向您所在司法管辖区内负责监督数据保护法遵循情况的数据保护机构就我们收集和使用您的个人信息提出投诉。 例如，欧洲经济区的个人有权向主管的数据保护机构提出投诉，相关机构的列表可在以下位置访问： [https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/board/members\_en](https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/board/members_en)。 无论如何，我们都感谢您让我们有机会为您排忧解难，因此，敬请随时与我们联系，告知您可能提出的任何投诉。 我们不会因个人行使其数据隐私权而歧视他们。

我们将根据适用法律帮助您行使适用于您的权利。 不过，即使您的个人信息没有受到数据保护法的保护，我们也可能会力求满足您对我们的数据处理活动提出的任何请求或查询。 如果您对您的权利有疑问或希望行使您的权利，可以通过 [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com) 联系我们，或通过以下链接提供的交互式表单提交隐私问题：

**儿童的信息**

我们的站点不面向十六 (16) 周岁以下的儿童，也不应由他们使用，我们不会有意收集、使用或出售此类个人的信息。 如果您是您所在国家/地区的法律所理解的未成年人，请勿通过我们的站点提交任何个人信息。

**与其他网站的链接**

我们的站点可能包含指向第三方网站、产品和服务的链接。 对于这些网站、产品和服务及其政策，或它们对于您的个人信息的收集或以其他方式的处理，我们不负有任何义务或责任。 这些第三方的做法受其自己的隐私政策约束。 我们建议您了解这些第三方的隐私政策。

**联系我们**

如果您对本隐私声明或我们处理您的个人信息的方式有任何疑问，想要提出投诉，或希望联系我们的数据保护专员，请使用下面列出的联系信息与我们联系。 我们将立即着手解决您的问题并力争提供令您满意的解决方案。

交互式表单：  

电子邮件：  

邮寄地址：  
Honeywell Privacy  
4D5  
115 Tabor Road  
Morris Plains, NJ 07950

免费电话：  

**本隐私声明的变更**

我们有时可能会更新本隐私声明。 在更新时，我们将会修订本隐私声明顶部“上次更新”日期，并根据法律可能的要求采取此类其他措施。

**上次更新日期 2021 年 12月 02日**

Czech

**Naposledy aktualizováno 11. června 2021**

**Úvod**

Společnost Honeywell International Inc. (dále „**Honeywell**“, „**my**“, „**nás**“ nebo „**náš**“), je správcem údajů ve vztahu k osobním údajům, které o vás shromažďujeme, když navštívíte nebo používáte některý z našich webů, používáte naše produkty, služby a aplikace, jež jsou propojeny s tímto Prohlášením o ochraně soukromí (souhrnně dále „**weby**“). Toto Prohlášení o ochraně soukromí vysvětluje, jak shromažďujeme, sdílíme a používáme vaše osobní údaje, jež byly takto shromážděny, a jak můžete uplatnit svá práva z oblasti ochrany osobních údajů.

Při interakci s vámi vám můžeme poskytnout ještě další prohlášení o ochraně soukromí, jež se týkají konkrétních činností zpracování údajů, případně vám nabídnout další možnosti ohledně toho, jak bude společnost Honeywell v daném konkrétním čase zpracovávat vaše osobní údaje.

Kliknutím na některý z následujících odkazů přejdete na oddíl, který vás zajímá:

**Shromažďování údajů**

* **Údaje shromažďované přímo od vás**. Můžeme vás požádat o vaše osobní údaje, abychom mohli poskytnout službu nebo provést požadovanou transakci. Osobní údaje nám také můžete poskytnout, když nás kontaktujete nebo jste s námi v jiné interakci (např. nám pošlete komentář, dotaz, žádost o podporu, případně navštívíte náš web) nebo si zaregistrujete účet, abyste mohli používat naše weby. Mezi tyto osobní údaje se mohou řadit:
    * **údaje o identitě,** jako je vaše jméno, titul, název společnosti nebo organizace, e-mailová adresa, telefonní a faxové číslo a poštovní adresa (včetně ulice, obce, kraje, poštovního směrovacího čísla nebo země);
    * **registrační údaje,** které zadáte při registraci účtu, abyste mohli používat naše webové stránky, včetně uživatelských jmen a hesel;
    * **náborové údaje,** včetně údajů poskytnutých v souvislosti s žádostí o zaměstnání nebo dotazem na zaměstnání (viz níže);
    * **obchodní kontaktní údaje,** například údaje týkající se dalších zaměstnanců, vlastníků, ředitelů, představitelů nebo smluvních partnerů organizace, jež je třetí stranou (např. firmy, společnosti, partnerství, podniku s jediným majitelem, neziskové organizace nebo vládní agentury);
    * **marketingové a komunikační údaje,** včetně vašich marketingových předvoleb a přihlášení k odběru našich publikací;
    * **finanční údaje,** včetně informací o účtu platební karty nebo o jiném peněžním účtu pro účely nákupu produktů a služeb naší společnosti, které jsou dostupné na našich webových stránkách;
    * **údaje pro kontrolu vývozu,** například vaše národnost, občanství a země trvalého pobytu, které nám umožní rozhodnout, zda podle nařízení o kontrole vývozu smíte dostávat informace o určitých technologiích;
    * **údaje o transakcích,** včetně dotazů a objednávek našich produktů a služeb a podrobností o platbách vám a od vás, včetně historie objednávek a informací potřebných k provádění platebních transakcí;
    * **údaje o registraci na akce,** včetně informací, které poskytujete při vyplňování elektronických registračních formulářů; a
    * **vaše připomínky a názory,** včetně průzkumů, doporučení nebo jiných názorů na naše weby, případně obecných názorů a připomínek k našim produktům a službám.

Pokud nám požadované údaje neposkytnete, můžete se stát, že vám nebudeme moci poskytnout požadovanou službu nebo dokončit transakci.

* **Údaje, které o vás shromažďujeme automaticky**. Můžeme od vás automaticky shromažďovat určité informace o vaší návštěvě našich webů. K tomu slouží soubory cookie a dalších podobné sledovací technologie. Budeme vždy respektovat veškerá zákonná práva, jež nám v tomto počínání mohou bránit. Mezi údaje takto shromážděné se řadí:
    * **údaje o použití,** včetně údajů o způsobu použití našich webů, o prohlížených stránkách, o počtu přenesených bajtů, o odkazech, na které kliknete, o otevřených materiálech, o datu a času přístupu k webu, o webu s odkazem na náš web a o dalších akcích prováděných na našich webech; a
    * **technické údaje,** jako je IP adresa, typ a možnosti prohlížeče, váš jazyk a operační systém.

Informace o souborech cookie a dalších podobných sledovacích technologiích, které používáme na našich webech, najdete v [Prohlášení o používání souborů cookie](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#czech).

* **Údaje o zeměpisné poloze**. U některých webových stránek můžeme s vaším výslovným souhlasem shromažďovat údaje o přesné aktuální poloze (tzv. geografické poloze) vašeho mobilního zařízení. Tyto údaje využijeme pouze k tomu, abychom vám usnadnili používání webů, mj. prostřednictvím našich poskytovatelů služeb, kteří mohou tyto informace zpracovávat v souvislosti s poskytováním předmětných služeb naším jménem. Pokud takový souhlas udělíte, můžete jej spravovat spolu s předvolbami služeb zjišťování polohy v nastavení mobilního zařízení.
* **Informace shromážděné od třetích stran**. V souladu s platnou legislativou můžeme shromažďovat osobní údaje od třetích stran, jež se vás týkají, například z webů a aplikací sociálních médií, a spojovat je s informacemi, které již máme. Tento postup může sloužit vylepšení a přizpůsobení našich webů vašim předvolbám a dalším účelům stanoveným v tomto Prohlášení o ochraně soukromí. Můžeme také shromažďovat vaše obchodní kontaktní údaje od vašeho zaměstnavatele nebo jiných třetích stran, abychom mohli provádět běžné obchodní aktivity a podobné administrativní záležitosti nebo se do nich jiným způsobem zapojili.

**Používání údajů**

Osobní údaje shromážděné prostřednictvím našich webů nebo v případě, že nás kontaktujete, můžeme použít pro tyto účely:

* **Obchodní kontaktní údaje**. Společnost Honeywell shromažďuje a používá obchodní kontaktní údaje ke komunikaci nebo transakcím, včetně provádění due diligence ohledně produktů či služeb, případně poskytování nebo přijímání produktů či služeb. Společnost Honeywell může například shromažďovat a používat obchodní kontaktní údaje za účelem usnadnění a správy objednávek, smluv, záruk, údržby a podobných obchodních funkcí, za účelem posouzení úvěryschopnosti a pro účely inkasování prostředků, za účelem pomoci při vyřizování našich vlastních interních požadavků a právních požadavků a (pokud by to bylo nutné) k obraně našich zájmů a nároků.
* **Služby a transakce**. Vaše osobní údaje používáme k poskytování služeb nebo provádění požadovaných transakcí. Může se jednat například (ale nikoli výlučně) o poskytnutí informací o zakoupených nebo jinak používaných produktech či službách naší společnosti, registraci zakoupených produktů, zpracování objednávek produktů, vyřizování reklamací, poskytování náhradních příruček k produktům, vyřizování vašich požadavků v rámci služeb zákazníkům nebo o používání našich webů.
* **Správa a ochrana našeho podnikání a webů**. Vaše osobní údaje můžeme používat ke správě a ochraně naší obchodní činnosti a našich webů, včetně řešení potíží, údržby systémů, podpory, přípravy hlášení a hostování dat.
* **Zlepšování našeho podnikání, webů, produktů a služeb**. Vaše osobní údaje můžeme používat k obchodním analýzám a jiným účelům, které nám pomáhají rozvíjet naši obchodní činnost a zvyšovat její kvalitu, jakož i kvalitu našich webů, produktů a služeb (včetně nových produktů a služeb), například tím, že naše weby přizpůsobíme určitým preferencím nebo zájmům.
* **Marketing**. Podle platné legislativy a předpisů smíme používat vaše osobní údaje, abychom vás informovali o produktech nebo službách, které vás mohou zajímat, nebo s vámi jiným způsobem komunikovali o našich nabídkách, událostech a novinkách, průzkumech, speciálních nabídkách a souvisejících tématech. Marketingovou komunikaci zasílanou e-mailem můžete kdykoli bezplatně zrušit, když použijete odkaz pro zrušení odběru v kterémkoli z e-mailových marketingových materiálů, které od nás dostáváte, nebo když se na nás obrátíte prostřednictvím kontaktních údajů uvedených v tomto prohlášení. S ohledem na zemi vašeho pobytu můžete mít možnost odhlásit se z jiných typů marketingové komunikace. Máte-li zájem o více informací, kontaktujte nás s využitím kontaktních údajů uvedených v tomto Prohlášení o ochraně soukromí. V některých jurisdikcích náleží fyzickým osobám (např. obyvatelům Kalifornie) právo požadovat určité informace týkající se toho, jak sdělujeme osobní údaje třetím stranám pro účely přímého marketingu třetích stran. Chcete-li získat další informace o našich praktikách při poskytování údajů pro marketingové účely, kontaktujte nás v souladu s níže uvedenými pokyny.
* **Zájmově orientovaná reklama**. Shromažďujeme údaje o vašich online aktivitách a identifikujeme vaše zájmy, abychom vám mohli poskytovat nejrelevantnější reklamu. Přijímání zájmově orientované reklamy od společnosti Honeywell můžete odhlásit způsobem popsaným v našem [Prohlášení o používání souborů cookie](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#czech).
* **Finanční pobídkové a věrnostní programy**. Shromažďujeme a používáme osobní údaje k udržování a správě finančních pobídkových a věrnostních programů. Osobní údaje, které poskytujete v rámci těchto programů, využíváme k tomu, abychom vám nabízeli jedinečné odměny, sledovali váš stav v programu a umožnili výměnu programových bodů za produkty, propagační materiály, školicí semináře a další položky. V míře, do jaké to připouští zákon, můžeme také využít jakékoli osobní údaje, které nám poskytnete ve spojitosti s programem finančních pobídek, k jakémukoli jinému účelu uvedenému v tomto Prohlášení o ochraně soukromí. Prostudujte si podmínky každého finančního pobídkového programu, do něhož se chcete zaregistrovat nebo jehož se chcete účastnit, protože takové podmínky mohou být speciálně přizpůsobeny příslušnému programu. Pokud poskytnete souhlas s účastí v těchto programech, můžete jej kdykoli zrušit tak, že nás kontaktujete s využitím kontaktních údajů uvedených na konci tohoto Prohlášení o ochraně soukromí, případně v souladu s pokyny stanovenými v podmínkách příslušného programu.
* **Žádosti o zaměstnání**. V souvislosti s žádostí o zaměstnání nebo souvisejícími dotazy nám můžete poskytnout informace o sobě, například ve formě CV či životopisu, profesních referencí, informací o vzdělání a praxi, informací o odborných školeních a certifikacích. My a další členové naší skupiny můžeme tyto informace použít za účelem zvážení uzavření pracovního poměru, ověření vaší spolehlivosti či způsobilosti k výkonu práce, případně jak se uvádí jinak v jakémkoli samostatném prohlášení o ochraně soukromí nebo v jiném prohlášení, jež vám bude poskytnuto v souvislosti s vaší žádostí. K získávání, shromažďování a uchovávání žádostí o zaměstnání můžeme využívat třetí stranu (např. firmu zabývající se náborem pracovníků) nebo platformu sociálních médií. Další informace najdete v našem [Prohlášení o ochraně soukromí uchazečů o zaměstnání](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/applicant-privacy-notice#czech).
* **Průzkumy a analýzy**. Vaše osobní údaje můžeme používat k průzkumům a analýzám, které nám pomáhají analyzovat vaše nákupní preference, identifikovat produkty a služby, které nejlépe vyhovují vašim požadavkům, a měřit účinnost zobrazované reklamy.
* **Vynucování práva**. Shromažďované osobní údaje můžeme používat k odhalování, prevenci a řešení podvodů, porušování duševního vlastnictví, našich podmínek a ujednání, porušování zákona nebo jiného zneužití našich webů.

Pokud to zákon dovoluje, můžeme údaje shromažďované prostřednictvím našich webů spojovat s ostatními údaji, které o vás evidujeme (například s údaji o používání našich produktů a služeb), abychom vám nabídli dokonalejší a jednotnější prostředí určené ke spolupráci se zákazníky nebo k jiným účelům uvedeným v tomto prohlášení.

**Právní základ zpracování vašich údajů**

Pokud to vyžaduje zákon, zajistíme, aby zpracování vašich osobních údajů mělo právní základ. Ve většině případů bude právní základ záviset na příslušných osobních údajích a konkrétním kontextu, v němž je shromažďujeme.

* **Smlouva**: zpracování je nezbytné pro provádění služeb, jež vám poskytujeme, nebo za účelem realizace kroků (na vaši žádost) před provedením těchto služeb nebo v jejich očekávání.
* **Zákonná povinnost**: zpracování musíme provádět, abychom dostáli svým právním povinnostem, včetně dodržování platné legislativy, předpisů, státních a jiných obdobných požadavků, soudních rozhodnutí nebo předvolání.
* **Souhlas**: zpracování vychází z vašeho souhlasu se zpracováním osobních údajů k jednomu nebo více konkrétním účelům (např. marketing).
* **Oprávněné zájmy**: zpracování je nutné, protože na něm máme oprávněný zájem, například kvůli vývoji a zdokonalování našich webů, produktů nebo služeb k prospěchu našich zákazníků.
* **Životně důležité zájmy**: zpracování je nezbytné kvůli ochraně vašich životně důležitých zájmů (například ze zdravotních a bezpečnostních důvodů, pokud se zúčastníte schůzky na pracovišti společnosti Honeywell).

Pokud máte jakékoli dotazy nebo potřebujete další informace týkající se právního základu pro shromažďování a používání vašich osobních údajů, zašlete e-mail na adresu [HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com)

**Anonymizace údajů**

V souladu s platnou legislativou můžeme vaše osobní údaje anonymizovat, aby nebylo možné vás podle nich identifikovat. Anonymizované údaje se nepovažují za osobní údaje, a proto se na ně toto prohlášení nevztahuje. Anonymizované údaje můžeme shromažďovat, používat, agregovat a sdílet k jakýmkoli účelům.

**Jak dlouho údaje uchováváme**

Doba uložení vašich osobních údajů se liší podle účelu jejich zpracování. Například uchováváme osobní údaje potřebné k tomu, abychom vám mohli poskytovat produkty a služby nebo abychom mohli realizovat vámi požadované transakce, jste-li zákazníkem společnosti Honeywell nebo žádáte-li o zaměstnání prostřednictvím našich webů. V takovém případě budeme údaje z vaší žádosti uchovávat po takovou dobu, jak se uvádí v prohlášení o ochraně soukromí, jež vám je poskytnuto ve spojení s žádostí, případně jak to vyžaduje zákon. V ostatních případech uchováváme vaše osobní údaje tak dlouho, dokud jsou potřeba ke splnění účelu uvedeného v tomto prohlášení. Po uplynutí takové doby budou údaje anonymizovány (pokud to vyžaduje platná legislativa), odstraněny nebo zničeny.

**Sdělování údajů**

Podle platné legislativy smíme vaše osobní údaje sdílet s vybranými třetími stranami. Týká se to těchto třetích stran:

* **Společnosti naší skupiny**. Vaše osobní údaje můžeme sdílet s našimi přidruženými společnostmi a společnostmi naší skupiny, pokud k tomu existují přiměřené důvody, které jsou uvedeny v tomto prohlášení.
* **Poskytovatelé služeb**. Vaše osobní údaje můžeme sdílet se společnostmi, se kterými máme uzavřenou smlouvu o poskytování služeb naším jménem, jako je například hostování webů, provádění průzkumů, zpracování transakcí, analýza našich webů a další analýzy, které zvyšují kvalitu naší obchodní činnosti, webů, produktů a služeb. Od poskytovatelů služeb vyžadujeme, aby vaše osobní údaje chránili jako důvěrné.
* **Distributoři a jiní důvěryhodní obchodní partneři**. Vaše osobní údaje můžeme sdílet s třetími stranami, které distribuují naše produkty, a s dalšími důvěryhodnými obchodními partnery, abychom jim umožnili například posílat vám marketingové materiály. Sdílení osobních údajů k marketingovým účelům probíhá podle platné legislativy a předpisů.
* **Sdělování údajů ve spojitosti s transakcemi**. V souvislosti s určitými transakcemi můžeme sdělit některé nebo všechny vaše osobní údaje finančním institucím, státním úřadům a přepravním nebo poštovním společnostem, které se podílejí na uskutečnění transakce.
* **Sdělení údajů ve spojitosti s akvizicemi nebo odprodejem**. Mohou nastat okolnosti, kdy se společnost Honeywell ze strategických nebo jiných obchodních důvodů rozhodne v některých zemích prodat, koupit, odprodat, sloučit nebo jinak reorganizovat své podniky. Informace, které si o vás udržujeme, můžeme zpřístupnit do míry přiměřeně nezbytné k vyjednávání nebo provedení fúze, akvizice, odprodeje či prodeje části nebo veškerého majetku společnosti Honeywell.
* **Sdělení údajů z jiných důvodů**. Osobní údaje můžeme sdělit jiné straně, pokud to vyžaduje zákon (nebo nás k tomu opravňuje) nebo tak učiníme v dobré víře, že je to nutné ke splnění zákonných požadavků nebo kvůli dodržení právního procesu uplatňovaného vůči nám, dále k ochraně a obraně našich práv nebo majetku, v naléhavých případech a kvůli ochraně bezpečí osob.

**Mezinárodní přenosy**

Společnost Honeywell je globální organizace a vaše osobní údaje mohou být v souladu s platnou legislativou přenášeny, drženy, uchovávány nebo používány na různých místech po celém světě, například v USA, Mexiku a Indii. To znamená, že když shromažďujeme vaše osobní údaje, mohou být zpracovány v zemích, kde platí zákony na ochranu údajů, které se liší od zákonů vaší země. Společnost Honeywell však vždy přijme přiměřená opatření k ochraně vašeho soukromí a k zajištění úrovně ochrany osobních údajů, která je srovnatelná s úrovní vaší země pobytu, včetně implementace standardních smluvních doložek Evropské komise. Máte-li zájem o další informace o příslušných opatřeních na ochranu vašich osobních údajů, kontaktujte nás na adrese [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com).

**Zabezpečení**

Zavazujeme se chránit vaše osobní údaje, aby byly v bezpečí. Využíváme technická a organizační opatření k zajištění úrovně zabezpečení odpovídající riziku plynoucímu ze zpracování vašich osobních údajů. Máte-li zájem o další informace o postupech ochrany osobních údajů využívaných společností Honeywell, kontaktujte nás na adrese [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com)

**Vaše práva**

S ohledem na příslušnou legislativu můžete mít v souvislosti se svými osobními údaji určitá práva.

* Můžete mít právo na **přístup, opravu, aktualizaci** nebo **požádání o výmaz** svých osobních údajů.
* Můžete **vznést námitku** vůči zpracování svých osobních údajů, požádat nás o **omezení** zpracování osobních údajů nebo žádat o **přenositelnost** osobních údajů.
* Můžete mít právo požadovat, **aby se o vás nerozhodovalo pouze na základě automatického zpracování, včetně profilování**, pokud má takové rozhodnutí na vás právní dopady nebo se vás významně dotýká.
* Pokud shromažďujeme a zpracováváme vaše osobní údaje na základě uděleného souhlasu, **můžete svůj souhlas kdykoli odvolat**. Odvolání souhlasu nebude mít vliv na zákonnost jakéhokoli zpracování, které jsme provedli před odvoláním, ani to nebude mít vliv na zpracování vašich osobních údajů prováděné na základě jiných zákonných důvodů zpracování, než je souhlas.
* Můžete mít právo **odhlásit se z prodeje osobních údajů**. Společnost Honeywell neprodává vaše osobní údaje třetím stranám za účelem zisku. Vaše osobní údaje však sdílíme nebo jinak poskytujeme třetím stranám v souladu s tímto Prohlášením o ochraně soukromí a s naším [Prohlášením o používání souborů cookie](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#czech). Spolupracujeme například s třetími stranami při distribuci našich produktů, poskytování technické pomoci, používání analytických nástrojů a funkcí webů a při marketingových aktivitách a prodeji našich produktů a služeb. Takové aktivity mohou zahrnovat poskytnutí osobních údajů třetím stranám a podle některých (nikoli však všech) zákonů na ochranu osobních údajů mohou být považovány za „prodej“ údajů.
* Máte právo **vznést stížnost** úřadu pro ochranu údajů odpovědnému za dohled nad dodržováním zákonů o ochraně údajů ve vaší jurisdikci s ohledem na shromažďování a využívání vašich osobních údajů z naší strany, pokud se domníváte, že naše zpracování vašich osobních údajů není v souladu s právními předpisy o ochraně osobních údajů. Například fyzické osoby v EHP mají právo stěžovat si příslušnému úřadu pro ochranu údajů, jejichž seznam je k dispozici na adrese: [https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/board/members\_en](https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/board/members_en). Velice bychom ocenili, kdybyste nám dali příležitost problém vyřešit, a proto nás prosím v případě jakýchkoli stížností neváhejte kontaktovat. Nebudeme žádné fyzické osoby diskriminovat za to, že uplatňují svá práva na ochranu osobních údajů.

Uplatňování vašich práv zajistíme podle platné legislativy. I v případě, že vaše osobní údaje nejsou chráněny podle zákona o ochraně osobních údajů nebo se na ně tyto zákony jinak nevztahují, můžeme se pokusit vyhovět jakýmkoli požadavkům nebo dotazům, které můžete mít v souvislosti s našimi činnostmi v oblasti zpracování údajů. Pokud máte dotazy týkající se práv nebo si přejete svá práva uplatnit, můžete nás kontaktovat na adrese [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com) nebo můžete posílat dotazy týkající se ochrany osobních údajů prostřednictvím interaktivního webového formuláře na odkazu:

**Údaje dětí**

Naše weby nejsou zaměřeny na děti mladší šestnácti let (16) a neměly by být takovými dětmi používány. Vědomě neshromažďujeme, nepoužíváme ani neprodáváme informace od takových osob. Pokud jste nezletilí ve smyslu právních předpisů vaší země, žádné osobní údaje nám prostřednictvím našich webů neposkytujte.

**Odkazy na jiné weby**

Naše weby mohou obsahovat odkazy na webové stránky, produkty a služby třetích stran. Za jejich webové stránky, produkty a služby, zásady, shromažďování ani za jiné zpracování vašich osobních údajů neneseme žádnou odpovědnost. Postupy uplatňované těmito třetími stranami se řídí jejich vlastními zásadami ochrany osobních údajů. Proto vám doporučujeme, abyste se s těmito zásadami ochrany osobních údajů třetích stran seznámili.

**Kontaktujte nás**

Máte-li dotazy týkající se tohoto prohlášení nebo našeho zpracování vašich osobních údajů, chcete podat stížnost nebo se chcete obrátit na pověřence pro ochranu osobních údajů, použijte kontaktní údaje uvedené níže. Na váš dotaz budeme neprodleně reagovat a pokusíme se najít uspokojivé řešení.

Interaktivní webový formulář:  

E-mail:  

Poštovní adresa:  
Honeywell Privacy  
4D5  
115 Tabor Road  
Morris Plains, NJ 07950

Bezplatné telefonní číslo:  

**Změny tohoto prohlášení o ochraně soukromí**

Toto prohlášení o ochraně soukromí můžeme příležitostně aktualizovat. Pokud tak učiníme, opravíme datum poslední aktualizace uvedené nahoře v tomto prohlášení a případně podnikneme další kroky vyžadované zákonem.

**Naposledy aktualizováno 11. června 2021**

Danish

**Sidst opdateret den 11. juni 2021**

**Introduktion**

Honeywell International Inc. (»**Honeywell**«, »**vores**«, »**os**« eller »**vi**«), er »dataansvarlig« for de personlige oplysninger, vi indsamler om dig, når du besøger eller bruger enhver af vores hjemmesider, eller bruger produkter, tjenester og applikationer, der er knyttet til denne databeskyttelseserklæring (samlet vores »**sider**«). Denne databeskyttelseserklæring forklarer, hvordan vi indsamler, deler og bruger dine personlige oplysninger, der indsamles på denne måde, og hvordan du kan gøre brug af dine databeskyttelsesrettigheder.

Når vi interagerer med dig, kan vi også give dig yderligere databeskyttelseserklæringer om specifikke behandlingsaktiviteter eller tilbyde dig yderligere valg om, hvordan Honeywell behandler dine personlige oplysninger på det pågældende tidspunkt.

Klik på et af nedenstående links for at gå til den sektion, der interesserer dig:

**Vores indsamling af oplysninger**

* **Oplysninger, der indsamles direkte fra dig**. Vi kan bede dig om personlige oplysninger for at levere en tjeneste eller udføre en transaktion, som du har anmodet om. Du kan også give os personlige oplysninger, når du kontakter eller engagerer dig med os (f.eks. gennem en kommentar, forespørgsel eller kundesupportanmodning eller som besøgende på siden) eller når du tilmelder dig en konto for at bruge vores sider. Disse personlige oplysninger kan omfatte:
    * **Identitetsdata,** f.eks. dit navn, din titel, dit virksomhedsnavn/organisationsnavn, din e-mailadresse, dine telefonnumre og din fysiske adresse (herunder gade, by, stat, postnummer og/eller land);
    * **Tilmeldingsdata,** som du oplyser, når du tilmelder dig en konto for at bruge vores sider, herunder brugernavne og adgangskoder;
    * **Rekrutteringsdata,** herunder oplysninger, der er indsendt i forbindelse med en jobansøgning eller en forespørgsel (som beskrevet nedenfor);
    * **Virksomhedskontaktdata,** såsom oplysninger om andre medarbejdere, ejere, direktører, embedsmænd eller kontrahenter i en tredjepartsorganisation (f.eks. firma, virksomhed, partnerskab, enkeltmandsvirksomhed, nonprofitorganisation eller et statsligt agentur).
    * **Markedsførings- og kommunikationsdata,** herunder dine markedsføringsindstillinger og dine abonnementer på vores udgivelser;
    * **Finansielle oplysninger,** herunder kreditkortoplysninger eller andre finansielle kontooplysninger, som vi indsamler med henblik på at gøre det muligt for os at gennemføre dit køb af virksomhedens produkter og tjenester, der kan være tilgængelige på vores sider;
    * **Oplysninger om eksportkontrol,** såsom din nationalitet, dit statsborgerskab og dit bopælsland, der giver os mulighed for at afgøre din berettigelse til at modtage oplysninger om visse teknologier i henhold til eksportkontrolbestemmelser;
    * **Transaktionsdata,** herunder forespørgsler om og bestillinger af vores produkter og tjenester og oplysninger om betalinger til og fra dig, herunder købsordrehistorik og oplysninger, der er nødvendige for at udføre betalingstransaktioner;
    * **Tilmeldingsoplysninger for begivenheder,** herunder oplysninger, som du giver, når du udfylder tilmeldingsformularer online; og
    * **Din feedback,** herunder undersøgelser, anbefalinger eller anden feedback fra dig om vores sider samt vores produkter og tjenester generelt.

Når du ikke giver os de ønskede oplysninger, kan vi muligvis ikke levere den anmodede tjeneste eller gennemføre din transaktion.

* **Oplysninger, vi indsamler om dig automatisk**. Vi indsamler visse oplysninger om dit besøg på vores sider ved hjælp af cookies og lignende sporingsteknologier. Vi vil altid respektere de juridiske rettigheder, du måtte have for at forhindre os i at gøre dette. Data, der indsamles på denne måde omfatter:
    * **Brugsdata,** herunder oplysninger om, hvordan du bruger vores sider, hvilke websider du ser, antallet af overførte byte, de links, du klikker på, de materialer, du tilgår, datoen og tidspunktet for, hvornår du tilgår siden, hjemmesiden, hvorfra du blev forbundet til en af vores sider, og andre handlinger, der er foretaget inden for siderne; og
    * **Tekniske data,** såsom din internetprotokoladresse (IP), din browsertype og dine tilvalg og dit sprog samt dit operativsystem.

Find oplysninger om cookies og andre lignende sporingsteknologier, som vi bruger på vores sider i vores [cookieeklæring](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#danish).

* **Geo-placeringsoplysninger**. For visse sider, med dit samtykke, kan vi indsamle den præcise placering i realtid (dvs. geo-placering) for din mobile enhed. Disse oplysninger vil kun blive brugt til din brug af siderne, herunder af vores tjenesteleverandører, der kan behandle disse oplysninger i forbindelse med leveringen af tjenester på vegne af os. Hvis disse oplysninger gives, kan du ændre dette samtykke ved at administrere dine indstillinger for placeringstjenester via indstillingerne på din mobile enhed.
* **Oplysninger, der indsamles af tredjeparter**. I overensstemmelse med gældende lovgivning kan vi indsamle personlige oplysninger om dig fra tredjeparter, såsom sociale medier og applikationer, og kombinere dem med oplysninger, vi allerede har, for at hjælpe os med at forbedre og tilpasse vores sider til dine indstillinger og til andre formål, der er angivet i denne databeskyttelseserklæring. Vi kan også indsamle dine forretningskontaktoplysninger fra din arbejdsgiver eller andre tredjeparter for at muliggøre eller på anden måde engagere os i traditionelle forretningsaktiviteter og lignende administrative anliggender.

**Vores brug af oplysninger**

Vi kan bruge de personlige oplysninger, der indsamles via vores sider, eller når du kontakter os, til formål, der omfatter:

* **Forretningskontaktdata**. Honeywell indsamler og bruger forretningskontaktdata til at udføre kommunikation eller transaktioner, herunder til at udføre due diligence vedrørende, eller ved levering eller modtagelse af, et produkt eller en tjeneste. Honeywell kan for eksempel indsamle og bruge disse forretningskontaktoplysninger til at muliggøre og administrere ordrer, kontrakter, garantier, vedligeholdelse og lignende forretningsfunktioner med henblik på kreditanalyse og opkrævning, for at hjælpe vores egen interne overholdelse og juridiske krav og (om nødvendigt) til at forsvare vores interesser og krav.
* **Tjenester og transaktioner**. Vi kan bruge dine personlige oplysninger til at levere tjenester til dig eller udføre transaktioner, du har anmodet om, herunder, men ikke begrænset til, at levere oplysninger om virksomhedens produkter eller tjenester, som du har købt eller på anden måde bruger, registrere købte produkter, behandle produktordrer, håndtere garantikrav, udskifte produktmanualer, besvare kundeserviceanmodninger og muliggøre brugen af vores sider.
* **Administration og beskyttelse af vores forretning og sider**. Vi kan bruge dine personlige oplysninger til at administrere og beskytte vores virksomhed og vores sider, herunder til fejlfinding, systemvedligeholdelse, support, rapportering og datahosting.
* **Forbedring af vores forretning, sider, produkter og tjenester**. Vi kan bruge dine personlige oplysninger til at udføre forretningsanalyser eller til andre formål, der hjælper os med at udvikle og forbedre kvaliteten af vores forretning, sider, produkter og tjenester (herunder nye produkter og tjenester), f.eks. ved at tilpasse vores sider til dine specifikke indstillinger eller interesser.
* **Markedsføring**. I overensstemmelse med gældende love og bestemmelser kan vi bruge dine personlige oplysninger til at informere dig om produkter eller tjenester, der kan være af interesse for dig, og til på anden måde at kommunikere med dig om tilbud, begivenheder og nyheder, undersøgelser, særtilbud og relaterede emner. Du kan til enhver tid framelde dig markedsføringskommunikation, der sendes via e-mail gratis ved brug af linket »frameld« i det e-mailmarkedsføringsmateriale, du modtager fra os, eller ved at kontakte os gennem de kontaktoplysninger, der er angivet i denne databeskyttelseserklæring. Afhængigt af dit bopælsland kan du også fravælge andre former for markedsføringskommunikation; kontakt os ved hjælp af kontaktoplysningerne i databeskyttelseserklæringen for flere oplysninger. Nogle jurisdiktioner giver enkeltpersoner (f.eks. beboere i Californien) ret til at anmode om visse oplysninger vedrørende vores videregivelse af personoplysninger til tredjeparter, der bruges til tredjepartens direkte markedsføringsformål. Du kan få flere oplysninger om vores praksis for videregivelse af data til markedsføringsformål ved at kontakte os i overensstemmelse med instruktionerne nedenfor.
* **Interessebaseret annoncering**. Vi indsamler data om dine onlineaktiviteter og identificerer dine interesser, så vi kan levere de annoncer, der er mest relevante for dig. Du kan fravælge at modtage interessebaseret annoncering fra Honeywell i henhold til beskrivelsen i vores [cookieerklæring](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#danish).
* **Finansielle incitamenter og loyalitetsprogrammer**. Vi indsamler og bruger personlige oplysninger til at vedligeholde og administrere vores økonomiske incitaments- og loyalitetsprogrammer. Vi bruger de personlige oplysninger, du giver i disse programmer, til at tilbyde unikke belønninger, spore din programstatus og til at muliggøre udvekslingen af programpoint for produkter, reklamemateriale, træningsworkshops og andre ting. I det omfang loven tillader det, kan vi også bruge personlige oplysninger, som du giver i forbindelse med et økonomisk incitamentsprogram, til andre formål, der er angivet i denne databeskyttelseserklæring. Gennemgå vilkårene og betingelserne for hvert økonomisk incitamentsprogram, som du ønsker at tilmelde dig eller deltage i, da sådanne vilkår og betingelser kan være svært skræddersyede til det relevante program. Hvis du accepterer at deltage i disse programmer, kan du til enhver tid trække samtykket tilbage ved at kontakte os ved hjælp af kontaktoplysningerne i bunden af denne databeskyttelseserklæring eller i overensstemmelse med instruktionerne i de gældende vilkår og betingelser for programmet.
* **Jobansøgninger**. I forbindelse med en jobansøgning eller forespørgsel kan du give os oplysninger om dig selv, såsom et CV/curriculum vitae, faglige referencer, oplysninger om uddannelse og jobbaggrund, samt oplysninger om faglig uddannelse og certificeringer. Vi og medlemmer af vores koncern kan bruge disse oplysninger med henblik på ansættelsesovervejelser, baggrundstjek og ansættelsesberettigelse, og som ellers angivet i en separat databeskyttelseserklæring eller anden erklæring, der stilles til rådighed i forbindelse med din ansøgning. Vi kan bruge en tredjepart (f.eks. en rekrutteringsagent) eller en social medieplatform til at anmode om, indsamle og opbevare ansættelsesansøgninger. Du kan få flere oplysninger ved at læse vores [databeskyttelseserklæring for ansøgere](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/applicant-privacy-notice#danish).
* **Forskning og analyse**. Vi kan bruge dine personlige oplysninger til at udføre forskning og analyse for at hjælpe os med at analysere dine købspræferencer, identificere de produkter og tjenester, der bedst opfylder dine krav, og til at måle effektiviteten af den annoncering, vi viser for dig.
* **Håndhævelse**: Vi kan bruge de personlige oplysninger, vi indsamler, til at detektere, forhindre og reagere på svindel, brud på intellektuel ejendomsret, brud på vores vilkår og betingelser, brud på loven eller anden misbrug af vores sider.

Når det er tilladt ved lov, kan vi kombinere de oplysninger, vi indsamler via vores sider, med andre oplysninger, vi har om dig (såsom oplysninger om din brug af vores produkter og tjenester) for at tilbyde dig en forbedret og konsekvent kundeoplevelse, når du interagerer med os eller til andre formål, der er angivet i denne databeskyttelseserklæring.

**Det juridiske grundlag, hvorpå vi behandler oplysninger**

Når loven kræver det, vil vi sikre, at der er et retsgrundlag for behandlingen af dine personlige oplysninger. I de fleste tilfælde vil vores retsgrundlag afhænge af de pågældende personlige oplysninger og den specifikke kontekst, hvortil vi indsamler dem.

* **Kontrakt**: behandlingen er nødvendig for udførelsen af de tjenester, vi leverer til dig, eller for at tage skridt (efter din anmodning) forud for og i forventning om udførelsen af sådanne tjenester;
* **Juridisk forpligtelse**: behandlingen er nødvendig for at overholde vores juridiske forpligtelser, herunder overholdelse af gældende love, bestemmelser, statslige og kvasi-statslige anmodninger, retskendelser eller stævninger;
* **Samtykke**: behandlingen er baseret på dit samtykke til behandlingen af dine personlige oplysninger til et eller flere specifikke formål (f.eks. markedsføring);
* **Legitime interesser**: behandlingen er nødvendig for at opfylde vores legitime interesser, for eksempel for at udvikle og forbedre vores sider, produkter og/eller tjenester til gavn for vores kunder; eller
* **Vitale interesser**: behandlingen er nødvendig for at beskytte dine vitale interesser (f.eks. af sundheds- og sikkerhedsmæssige årsager, hvis du deltager i et møde på en Honeywell-lokation).

Hvis du har spørgsmål eller brug for yderligere oplysninger vedrørende det retsgrundlag, hvorpå vi indsamler og bruger dine personlige oplysninger, bedes du sende en e-mail til [HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com)

**Anonymisering af oplysninger**

I overensstemmelse med gældende lovgivning kan vi anonymisere dine personlige oplysninger, så de ikke længere kan bruges til at identificere dig. Anonymiserede oplysninger betragtes ikke som personlige oplysninger og er derfor ikke underlagt denne databeskyttelseserklæring. Vi kan indsamle, bruge, sammenlægge og dele anonymiserede oplysninger til ethvert formål.

**Opbevaringstiden for oplysninger**

Den periode, hvor vi gemmer dine personlige oplysninger, varierer afhængigt af formålet med behandlingen. For eksempel gemmer vi personlige oplysninger, der er nødvendige for at levere produkter og tjenester til dig, eller for at muliggøre transaktioner, du har anmodet om, så længe du er kunde hos Honeywell; eller hvis du indsender en jobansøgning via vores sider, vil vi opbevare oplysninger om din ansøgning som angivet i den databeskyttelseserklæring, der er gjort tilgængelig for dig i forbindelse med din ansøgning, eller som på anden måde krævet af loven. I alle andre tilfælde gemmer vi dine personlige oplysninger, så længe det er nødvendigt for at opfylde de formål, der er beskrevet i denne databeskyttelseserklæring, hvorefter de enten anonymiseres (hvor det er tilladt i henhold til gældende lovgivning), slettes eller destrueres.

**Videregivelse af oplysninger**

Vi kan dele dine personlige oplysninger med udvalgte tredjeparter i overensstemmelse med gældende lovgivning, herunder som angivet nedenfor:

* **Vores koncernselskaber**. Vi kan dele dine personlige oplysninger med vores datterselskaber og koncernselskaber, hvis det med rimelighed er nødvendigt til de formål, der er angivet i denne databeskyttelseserklæring.
* **Tjenesteleverandører**. Vi kan dele dine personlige oplysninger med virksomheder, som vi har indgået kontrakt med omkring levering tjenester på vegne af os, såsom hosting af hjemmesider, udførelse af undersøgelser, behandling af transaktioner, analyse af vores sider og udførelse af analyser for at forbedre kvaliteten af vores forretning, sider, produkter og tjenester. Vi kræver, at disse tjenesteleverandører beskytter fortroligheden af dine personlige oplysninger.
* **Distributører og andre betroede forretningspartnere**. Vi kan dele dine personlige oplysninger med tredjeparter, der distribuerer vores produkter og andre betroede forretningspartnere til formål, der omfatter at tillade disse tredjeparter at sende markedsføringskommunikation til dig. En sådan deling af personlige oplysninger til markedsføringsformål vil blive udført i overensstemmelse med gældende love og bestemmelser.
* **Oplysninger i forbindelse med transaktioner**. I forbindelse med visse transaktioner kan vi videregive nogle eller alle dine personlige oplysninger til finansielle institutioner, offentlige enheder og fragtvirksomheder eller posttjenester, der er involveret i gennemførelsen af transaktionen.
* **Oplysninger i forbindelse med erhvervelser eller afhændelser**. Der kan opstå omstændigheder, hvor Honeywell af strategiske eller andre forretningsmæssige årsager beslutter at sælge, købe, afhænde, fusionere eller på anden måde omorganisere virksomheder i nogle lande. Vi kan videregive oplysninger, vi opbevarer om dig, i det omfang det med rimelighed er nødvendigt for at fortsætte med forhandlingen eller gennemførelsen af en fusion, erhvervelse, afhændelse eller salg af alle eller en del af Honeywells aktiver.
* **Videregivelse af andre grunde**. Vi kan videregive personoplysninger, hvis det er påkrævet eller autoriseret i henhold til loven eller i god tro om, at en sådan handling er nødvendig for at overholde de juridiske krav eller den juridiske proces, der gælder for os, for at beskytte og forsvare vores rettigheder eller ejendom eller, i hastetilfælde, for at beskytte den enkeltes personlige sikkerhed.

**Internationale overførsler**

Honeywell er en global organisation, og dine personlige oplysninger kan overføres til, opbevares, lagres eller bruges på tværs af forskellige steder over hele verden, såsom USA, Mexico og Indien, i overensstemmelse med gældende lovgivning. Det betyder, at når vi indsamler dine personlige oplysninger, kan de blive behandlet i lande, der kan have databeskyttelseslove, der er forskellige fra lovene i dit land. Honeywell vil dog altid træffe rimelige foranstaltninger for at beskytte dine data og for at sikre et beskyttelsesniveau for personlige oplysninger, der kan sammenlignes med niveauet i dit bopælsland, herunder implementering af Europa-Kommissionens standardkontraktklausuler. Du kan få flere oplysninger om de passende sikkerhedsforanstaltninger omkring beskyttelse af personlige oplysninger ved at kontakte os på [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com).

**Sikkerhed**

Vi er dedikerede til at beskytte dine personlige oplysninger. Vi bruger tekniske og organisatoriske foranstaltninger til at levere et sikkerhedsniveau, der er passende i forhold til risikoen for at behandle dine personlige oplysninger. Du kan få flere oplysninger om, hvordan Honeywell beskytter dine personlige oplysninger, ved at kontakte os på [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com)

**Dine rettigheder**

Afhængigt af gældende lovgivning, kan du have visse rettigheder med hensyn til dine personlige oplysninger.

* Du har muligvis ret til at **tilgå, rette, opdatere** eller **anmode om sletning** af dine personlige oplysninger.
* Du kan **modsige** behandlingen af dine personlige oplysninger, bede os om at **begrænse**behandling af dine personlige oplysninger eller anmode om **flytning** af dine personlige oplysninger.
* Du kan have ret **til ikke at få truffet en beslutning om dig, der udelukkende er baseret på automatiseret behandling, herunder profilering,** hvis denne beslutning har juridisk effekt omkring dig eller påvirker dig i væsentlig grad.
* Similarly, if we have indsamlet and proces dit personal information with dit consent, then **du kan når som helst trække dit samtykke tilbage**. Tilbagetrækning af dit samtykke vil ikke påvirke lovligheden af enhver behandling, vi foretog før din tilbagetrækning, og det vil heller ikke påvirke behandlingen af dine personlige oplysninger, der udføres under andre lovlige behandlingsgrunde end samtykket.
* Du kan have retten til **at fravælge salg af dine personlige oplysninger**. Honeywell sælger ikke dine personlige oplysninger til tredjeparter med fortjeneste for øje. Vi deler eller videregiver dog på anden måde dine personlige oplysninger til tredjeparter i overensstemmelse med denne databeskyttelseserklæring og vores [cookieerklæring](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#danish). Vi samarbejder eksempelvis med tredjeparter om at distribuere vores produkter, give dig teknisk hjælp, drive hjemmesideanalytiske værktøjer og funktioner, og udføre markedsføring og salg af vores produkter og tjenester. Sådanne aktiviteter kan indebære videregivelse af dine personlige oplysninger til tredjeparter og kan betragtes som et »salg« af data i henhold til visse (men ikke alle) databeskyttelseslove.
* Du kan have ret til at **klage** til en databeskyttelsesmyndighed, der er ansvarlig for at overvåge overholdelse af databeskyttelseslovgivningen i din jurisdiktion om vores indsamling og brug af dine personlige oplysninger, hvis du mener, at vores behandling af dine personlige oplysninger ikke er i overensstemmelse med databeskyttelseslovgivningen. Personer i EØS har f.eks. ret til at indgive en klage til den kompetente databeskyttelsesmyndighed, som du kan få en liste over på: [https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/board/members\_en](https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/board/members_en). Vi vil dog sætte pris på muligheden for at løse dine problemer, så du er velkommen til at kontakte os vedrørende eventuelle klager, du måtte have. Vi vil ikke diskriminere mod enkeltpersoner, der udøver deres databeskyttelsesrettigheder.

Vi vil muliggøre din udøvelse af de rettigheder, der gælder for dig i overensstemmelse med gældende lovgivning. Men selvom dine personoplysninger ikke er beskyttet i henhold til, eller på anden måde er underlagt, en databeskyttelseslov, kan vi forsøge at imødekomme enhver anmodning eller forespørgsel, du måtte have i forbindelse med vores databehandlingsaktiviteter. Hvis du har spørgsmål om dine rettigheder eller ønsker at udøve dem, kan du kontakte os på [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com) eller indsende spørgsmål om databeskyttelse via vores interaktive webformular på følgende link:

**Børns oplysninger**

Vores sider er ikke rettet mod og bør ikke bruges af børn under seksten år (16), og vi indsamler, bruger eller sælger ikke bevidst oplysninger fra sådanne personer. Hvis du er mindreårig, som forstået i henhold til lovgivningen i dit land, må du ikke indsende personoplysninger via vores sider.

**Links til andre hjemmesider**

Vores sider kan indeholde links til tredjeparters hjemmesider, produkter og tjenester. Vi påtager os intet ansvar for disse hjemmesider, produkter og tjenester, deres politikker eller deres indsamling eller anden behandling af dine personlige oplysninger. Disse tredjeparters praksis er underlagt deres egne databeskyttelsespolitikker. Vi opfordrer dig til at læse disse tredjeparters databeskyttelsespolitikker.

**Kontakt os**

Hvis du har spørgsmål vedrørende denne databeskyttelseserklæring eller vores håndtering af dine personlige oplysninger, ønsker at indgive en klage, eller ønsker at kontakte vores databeskyttelsesansvarlige, bedes du kontakte os ved hjælp af nedenstående kontaktoplysninger. Vi vil straks håndtere din bekymring og bestræbe os på at nå frem til en tilfredsstillende løsning.

Interaktiv webformular:  

E-mail:  

Postadresse:  
Honeywell Privacy  
4D5  
115 Tabor Road  
Morris Plains, NJ 07950

Gebyrfrit nummer:  

**Ændringer af denne databeskyttelseserklæring**

Vi kan lejlighedsvis opdatere denne databeskyttelseserklæring. Når vi gør dette, vil vi revidere den »senest opdaterede« dato øverst i databeskyttelseserklæringen og tage de yderligere skridt, der måtte være påkrævet i henhold til loven.

**Sidst opdateret den 11. juni 2021**

Dutch

**Laatst bijgewerkt 11 juni 2021**

**Inleiding**

Honeywell International Inc. ("**Honeywell**", "**onze**", "**ons**", of "**wij/we**"), is de "gegevensbeheerder" van de persoonsgegevens die wij verzamelen over u wanneer u een van onze websites bezoekt of gebruikt, of producten, diensten en toepassingen gebruikt die zijn gekoppeld aan deze privacyverklaring (gezamenlijk onze "**sites**"). In deze privacyverklaring wordt uitgelegd hoe we uw op deze manier verzamelde persoonsgegevens verzamelen, delen en gebruiken en hoe u uw privacyrechten kunt uitoefenen.

Wanneer we met u communiceren, kunnen we u ook voorzien van aanvullende privacyverklaringen over specifieke verwerkingsactiviteiten of u aanvullende keuzes bieden over hoe Honeywell uw persoonsgegevens verwerkt op dat specifieke moment.

Klik op een van de onderstaande koppelingen om naar de paragraaf te gaan die u interesseert:

**Het verzamelen van gegevens door ons**

* **Direct van u verzamelde informatie**. We kunnen u vragen om persoonsgegevens voor het verlenen van diensten of transacties uit te voeren, waarom u hebt verzocht. U kunt ons ook persoonsgegevens verstrekken wanneer u contact opneemt met ons of ons benadert (bijvoorbeeld met een opmerking, vraag of verzoek om klantondersteuning) of wanneer u zich registreert voor een account voor gebruik van onze sites. Deze persoonsgegevens kunnen het volgende omvatten:
    * **Identiteitsgegevens,** zoals uw naam, functie, bedrijfs-/organisatienaam, e-mailadres, telefoon- en faxnummers en fysiek adres (inclusief straat, plaats, staat/provincie, postcode en/of land);
    * **Registratiegegevens,** die door u wordt verschaft wanneer u zich registreert voor een account voor het gebruik van onze sites, inclusief gebruikersnamen en wachtwoorden;
    * **Wervingsgegevens,** inclusief informatie die is verstrekt in verband met een sollicitatie of onderzoek (zoals hieronder beschreven);
    * **Zakelijke contactgegevens,** zoals informatie met betrekking tot andere werknemers, eigenaren, directeuren, functionarissen of contractanten van externe organisaties (bijvoorbeeld zaak, bedrijf, partnerschap, eenmanszaak, organisatie zonder winstoogmerk of overheidsinstantie).
    * **Marketing- en communicatiegegevens,** inclusief uw marketingvoorkeuren en uw abonnementen op onze publicaties;
    * **Financiële informatie,** inclusief creditcard- of andere financiële-rekeninginformatie, waarmee we uw aankoop mogelijk kunnen maken van producten en diensten van het Bedrijf die beschikbaar zijn op onze Sites;
    * **Informatie over exportcontrole,** zoals uw nationaliteit, burgerschap en land van verblijf, op basis waarvan wij kunnen beoordelen of u volgens de voorschriften voor exportcontrole in aanmerking komt voor het ontvangen van informatie over bepaalde technologieën;
    * **Transactiegegevens,** inclusief vragen over en bestellingen van onze producten en diensten en details van betalingen aan en van u, inclusief bestelgeschiedenis en informatie die nodig is om betalingstransacties te vergemakkelijken;
    * **Registratie-informatie voor evenementen,** inclusief informatie die u verstrekt bij het invullen van e-registratieformulieren; en
    * **Uw feedback,** inclusief enquêtes, aanbevelingen of andere feedback van u over onze sites, evenals onze producten en diensten in het algemeen.

Wanneer u de gevraagde informatie niet verstrekt, kunnen we u mogelijk niet de gevraagde dienst bieden of uw transactie voltooien.

* **Informatie over u die we automatisch verzamelen**. We verzamelen bepaalde informatie over uw bezoek aan onze sites met behulp van cookies en soortgelijke traceertechnologieën. We zullen altijd alle wettelijke rechten respecteren die u mogelijk hebt om ons hiervan te weerhouden. Op deze manier verzamelde gegevens omvatten:
    * **Gebruiksgegevens,** inclusief informatie over hoe u onze sites gebruikt, welke pagina's u bekijkt, het aantal overgedragen bytes, de koppelingen waarop u klikt, de materialen die u inziet, de datum en tijd waarop u de site bezoekt, de website waarvan u naar een van onze sites bent gekoppeld en andere acties die binnen de sites worden ondernomen; en
    * **Technische gegevens,** zoals uw IP-adres (Internet Protocol), uw browsertype en -capaciteiten en taal en uw besturingssysteem.

Voor informatie over de cookies en andere vergelijkbare volgtechnologieën die we op onze Sites gebruiken, verwijzen wij u naar onze [Kennisgeving over cookies](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice).

* **Geografische locatie-informatie**. Voor bepaalde sites kunnen we met uw toestemming de exacte, real time locatie (d.w.z. geografische locatie) van uw mobiele apparaat verzamelen. Deze informatie wordt alleen gebruikt om uw gebruik van de sites te vergemakkelijken, inclusief door onze serviceproviders die deze informatie kunnen verwerken in verband met het verlenen van diensten namens ons. Indien gegeven, kunt u deze toestemming aanpassen door uw voorkeuren voor locatieservices te beheren via de instellingen van uw mobiele apparaat.
* **Informatie verzameld van derden**. In overeenstemming met de toepasselijke wetgeving kunnen we persoonsgegevens over u verzamelen van derden, zoals sociale-mediawebsites en -toepassingen, en deze combineren met informatie die we al hebben, om ons te helpen onze sites te verbeteren en aan te passen aan uw voorkeuren en voor andere uiteengezette doeleinden in deze privacyverklaring. We kunnen ook uw zakelijke contactgegevens van uw werkgever of andere derde partijen verzamelen om traditionele zakelijke activiteiten en soortgelijke administratieve zaken te vergemakkelijken of anderszins uit te voeren.

**Ons gebruik van gegevens**

We kunnen de via onze sites of wanneer u contact met ons opneemt verzamelde persoonsgegevens gebruiken voor de volgende doeleinden:

* **Zakelijke contactgegevens**. Honeywell verzamelt en gebruikt zakelijke contactgegevens om communicatie of transacties aan te gaan, inclusief voor het uitvoeren van due diligence met betrekking tot, of het leveren of ontvangen van producten of diensten. Honeywell kan deze zakelijke contactgegevens bijvoorbeeld verzamelen en gebruiken om bestellingen, contracten, garanties, onderhoud en soortgelijke zakelijke functies te vergemakkelijken en te beheren, voor kredietanalyse en incassodoeleinden, om te helpen bij onze eigen interne nalevings- en wettelijke vereisten, en (indien nodig) om onze belangen en vorderingen te verdedigen.
* **Diensten en transacties**. We kunnen uw persoonsgegevens gebruiken voor het leveren van diensten aan u of voor het uitvoeren van door u aangevraagde transacties, inclusief, maar niet beperkt tot, het verstrekken van informatie over door u aangeschafte of anderszins gebruikte producten of diensten van het bedrijf, registratie van aangeschafte producten, verwerking van productbestellingen, afhandeling van garantieclaims, vervanging van producthandleidingen, het beantwoorden van klantenserviceverzoeken en ondersteuning van het gebruik van onze Sites.
* **Het beheren en beschermen van ons bedrijf en onze sites**. We kunnen uw persoonsgegevens gebruiken voor het beheer en de bescherming van ons bedrijf en onze sites, inclusief probleemoplossing, systeemonderhoud, ondersteuning, rapportage en hosting van gegevens.
* **Het verbeteren van onze zaken, sites, producten en services**. We kunnen uw persoonsgegevens mogelijk gebruiken voor het uitvoeren van zakelijke analyses of voor andere doeleinden die ons helpen bij het ontwikkelen en verbeteren van de kwaliteit van onze zaken, sites, producten en diensten (met inbegrip van nieuwe producten en diensten), bijvoorbeeld door het aanpassen van onze sites aan uw specifieke voorkeuren of interesses.
* **Marketing**. Overeenkomstig de toepasselijke wet- en regelgeving, kunnen wij uw persoonsgegevens gebruiken om u te informeren over producten of diensten die interessant kunnen zijn voor u en om anderszins met u te communiceren over aanbiedingen, evenementen en nieuws, enquêtes, speciale aanbiedingen en gerelateerde onderwerpen. U kunt zich op elk gewenst moment kosteloos uitschrijven voor het ontvangen van marketingberichten die per e-mail zijn verzonden via de koppeling "unsubscribe" (uitschrijven) in alle marketingmaterialen die u van ons per e-mail ontvangt of door contact met ons op te nemen via de contactgegevens die in deze privacyverklaring worden vermeld. Afhankelijk van uw land van verblijf, kunt u zich mogelijk ook uitschrijven voor andere soorten marketingcommunicatie; neem dan contact met ons op via de contactgegevens vermeld in de privacyverklaring voor meer informatie. Sommige rechtsgebieden bieden personen (bijvoorbeeld inwoners van Californië) het recht om bepaalde informatie op te vragen met betrekking tot onze openbaarmaking van persoonsgegevens aan derden voor doeleinden van directe marketing van deze derden. Neem contact met ons op in overeenstemming met de onderstaande instructies voor meer informatie over onze praktijken voor het vrijgeven van gegevens voor marketingdoeleinden.
* **Op interesses gebaseerde reclame**. We verzamelen gegevens over uw online activiteiten en identificeren uw interesses, zodat we advertenties kunnen aanbieden die het meest relevant zijn voor u. U kunt zich uitschrijven voor het ontvangen van op interesses gebaseerde reclame van Honeywell, zoals beschreven in onze [Kennisgeving over cookies](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice).
* **Financiële stimulerings- en loyaliteitsprogramma's**. We verzamelen en gebruiken persoonsgegevens voor het onderhouden en beheren van onze financiële stimulerings- en loyaliteitsprogramma's. We gebruiken de persoonsgegevens die u in deze programma's verstrekt om unieke beloningen aan te bieden, uw programmastatus bij te houden en om de uitwisseling van programmapunten voor producten, promotiemateriaal, trainingsworkshops en andere artikelen te vergemakkelijken. Voor zover wettelijk toegestaan, kunnen we ook gebruikmaken van alle persoonsgegevens die u verstrekt in het kader van een financieel stimuleringsprogramma voor elk ander doel dat wordt uiteengezet in deze privacyverklaring. Bestudeer de algemene voorwaarden van elk financieel stimuleringsprogramma waarvoor u zich wilt registreren of waaraan u wilt deelnemen, aangezien deze voorwaarden nauw kunnen zijn afgestemd op het toepasselijke programma. Als u ermee instemt om deel te nemen aan deze programma's, dan kunt u die toestemming op elk moment intrekken door contact met ons op te nemen via de contactgegevens aan het einde van deze privacyverklaring of in overeenstemming met de instructies in de toepasselijke algemene voorwaarden van het programma.
* **Sollicitaties voor werk**. U kunt ons, in verband met een sollicitatie of vraag voorzien van gegevens over uzelf, zoals een cv/curriculum vitae, professionele referenties, informatie over opleiding en werkachtergrond en informatie over beroepsopleidingen en certificeringen. Wij en leden van onze groep kunnen deze informatie gebruiken met het oog op tewerkstellingsoverwegingen, achtergrondonderzoeken en geschiktheid voor werk en zoals anders uiteengezet in een afzonderlijke privacyverklaring of andere kennisgeving die ter beschikking is gesteld in verband met uw sollicitatie. We kunnen gebruikmaken van een derde partij (bijv. recruiter) of een social-mediaplatform om sollicitaties te vragen, te verzamelen en te behouden. Lees voor meer informatie onze [Privacyverklaring voor sollicitanten](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/applicant-privacy-notice#dutch).
* **Onderzoek en analyse**. We kunnen uw persoonsgegevens gebruiken om onderzoek en analyse uit te voeren die ons kan helpen bij het analyseren van uw koopvoorkeuren, het identificeren van de producten en diensten die het beste in uw behoeften voorzien en het meten van de effectiviteit van de reclame die wij u aanbieden.
* **Handhaving**: We kunnen de persoonsgegevens die we verzamelen gebruiken voor het detecteren, voorkomen en aanpakken van fraude, inbreuken op intellectuele eigendomsrechten, schendingen van onze algemene voorwaarden, overtredingen van wetten of ander misbruik van onze sites.

Voor zover dit wettelijk is toegestaan, kunnen wij de via onze sites verzamelde informatie combineren met andere informatie die we over u aanhouden (zoals informatie over uw gebruik van onze producten en diensten) om u een betere en consistente klantervaring te bieden bij interacties met ons of voor andere doeleinden die worden uiteengezet in deze Privacyverklaring.

**De rechtsgrondslag voor het verwerken van gegevens**

Indien wettelijk vereist, verzekeren wij dat er een rechtsgrondslag is voor de verwerking van uw persoonsgegevens. In de meeste gevallen zal onze rechtsgrondslag afhangen van de betreffende persoonsgegevens en de specifieke context waarin we deze verzamelen.

* **Contract**: de verwerking is noodzakelijk voor de uitvoering van de diensten die wij aan u verlenen, of om (op uw verzoek) stappen te ondernemen voorafgaand aan en anticiperend op de uitvoering van dergelijke diensten;
* **Wettelijke verplichting**: de verwerking is noodzakelijk om te voldoen aan onze wettelijke verplichtingen, waaronder de naleving van toepasselijke wetgeving, voorschriften, verzoeken van overheids- en semi-overheidsinstanties, gerechtelijke bevelen of dagvaardingen;
* **Toestemming**: de verwerking is gebaseerd op uw toestemming voor de verwerking van uw persoonsgegevens voor een of meer gespecificeerde doeleinden (bijvoorbeeld marketing);
* **Legitieme belangen**: de verwerking is noodzakelijk om onze legitieme belangen te dienen, bijvoorbeeld voor het ontwikkelen en verbeteren van onze sites, producten en/of diensten ten behoeve van onze klanten; of
* **Vitale belangen**: De verwerking is noodzakelijk om uw vitale belangen te beschermen (bijvoorbeeld gezondheids- en veiligheidsredenen als u een vergadering bijwoont op een Honeywell-locatie).

Als u vragen hebt of meer informatie nodig hebt over de rechtsgrond waarop wij uw persoonsgegevens verzamelen en gebruiken, stuur dan een e-mail naar [HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com)

**Anonimisering van gegevens**

We kunnen uw persoonsgegevens anonimiseren, overeenkomstig toepasselijke wetgeving, zodat deze niet meer kunnen worden gebruikt om u te identificeren. Geanonimiseerde gegevens worden niet beschouwd als persoonsgegevens en zijn derhalve niet onderworpen aan deze privacyverklaring. We kunnen geanonimiseerde gegevens verzamelen, samenvoegen en delen voor elk gewenst doel.

**Bewaartermijnen voor gegevens**

De periode gedurende welke we uw persoonsgegevens opslaan, hangt af van het doel van de verwerking. We slaan bijvoorbeeld persoonsgegevens op die nodig zijn om u producten en diensten te leveren of om transacties te vergemakkelijken die u hebt aangevraagd, zolang u een klant van Honeywell bent; als u een sollicitatie indient via onze sites, bewaren wij details van uw sollicitatie zoals uiteengezet in de privacyverklaring die aan u ter beschikking is gesteld in verband met uw sollicitatie of zoals anderszins vereist door de wet. In alle andere gevallen bewaren we uw persoonsgegevens zolang als nodig is om de doeleinden te vervullen die worden uiteengezet in deze Privacyverklaring, waarna deze worden geanonimiseerd (waar toegestaan door toepasselijke wetgeving), verwijderd of vernietigd.

**Openbaarmaking van gegevens**

We kunnen uw persoonsgegevens delen met geselecteerde derden in overeenstemming met de toepasselijke wetgeving, inclusief zoals hieronder uiteengezet:

* **Bedrijven van onze groep**. We kunnen uw persoonsgegevens delen met onze verbonden ondernemingen en bedrijven van onze groep, voor zover redelijkerwijs noodzakelijk voor de doeleinden die worden uiteengezet in deze Privacyverklaring.
* **Dienstverleners**. We kunnen uw persoonsgegevens delen met bedrijven waarmee wij een contract zijn aangegaan om namens ons diensten te leveren, zoals het hosten van websites, het uitvoeren van enquêtes, het verwerken van transacties, het analyseren van onze sites en het uitvoeren van analyses om ter verbetering van de kwaliteit van onze onderneming, sites, producten en diensten. We vereisen de bescherming van de vertrouwelijkheid van uw persoonsgegevens van deze dienstverleners.
* **Distributeurs en andere vertrouwde zakenpartners**. We kunnen uw persoonsgegevens delen met derden die onze producten distribueren en andere vertrouwde zakenpartners voor doeleinden omvatten dat die derden toestemming hebben om marketingcommunicatie naar u te verzenden. Dergelijk delen van persoonsgegevens voor marketingdoeleinden wordt uitgevoerd in overeenstemming met de toepasselijke wet- en regelgeving.
* **Openbaarmaking in verband met transacties**. We kunnen in verband met bepaalde transacties sommige of alle persoonsgegevens van u openbaar maken aan financiële instellingen, overheidsinstellingen en transportbedrijven of postbedrijven die zijn betrokken bij de vervulling van de transactie.
* **Openbaarmakingen in verband met acquisities of desinvesteringen**. Er kunnen zich omstandigheden voordoen waarin Honeywell om strategische of andere zakelijke redenen besluit om bedrijven in sommige landen te verkopen, te kopen, af te stoten, te fuseren of anderszins te reorganiseren. We kunnen gegevens openbaar maken die we over u aanhouden, voor zover dat redelijkerwijs noodzakelijk is om door te gaan met onderhandelingen of voltooiing van een fusie, overname, afstoting of verkoop van een deel of het geheel van de activa van Honeywell.
* **Openbaarmaking om andere redenen**. We kunnen persoonsgegevens openbaar maken indien dit wordt vereist of toegestaan door wetgeving of indien we menen dat een dergelijke actie noodzakelijk is om aan wettelijke vereisten te voldoen of aan juridische actie mee te werken, om onze rechten of eigendommen te beschermen en te beveiligen of, in dringende omstandigheden, om de persoonlijke veiligheid van een persoon te beschermen.

**Internationale overdrachten**

Honeywell is een wereldwijde organisatie en uw persoonsgegevens kunnen worden overgedragen naar en bewaard, opgeslagen of gebruikt door verschillende locaties wereldwijd, zoals de VS, Mexico en India, in overeenstemming met toepasselijke wetgeving. Dit betekent dat, wanneer we uw persoonsgegevens verzamelen, deze kunnen worden verwerkt in landen met mogelijk wetten inzake gegevensbescherming die verschillen van de wetten van uw land. Honeywell zal echter altijd redelijke stappen ondernemen om uw privacy te beschermen en om een niveau van bescherming van persoonsgegevens te bieden dat vergelijkbaar is met dat van het land waar u woont, waaronder het implementeren van de standaardcontractbepalingen van de Europese Commissie. Neem contact met ons op via [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com) voor meer informatie over de passende veiligheidsmaatregelen voor de bescherming van uw persoonsgegevens.

**Beveiliging**

We doen onze uiterste best om de bescherming van uw persoonsgegevens te waarborgen. We gebruiken technische en organisatorische maatregelen om een beveiligingsniveau te bieden dat past bij het risico van het verwerken van uw persoonsgegevens. Neem contact met ons op via [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com), voor meer informatie over hoe Honeywell uw persoonsgegevens beschermt

**Uw rechten**

Afhankelijk van de toepasselijke wetgeving hebt u mogelijk bepaalde rechten met betrekking tot uw persoonsgegevens.

* U kunt het recht hebben op **toegang tot, correctie of bijwerking** van uw persoonsgegevens of **verzoeken om verwijdering** hiervan.
* U kunt **bezwaar maken** tegen de verwerking van uw persoonsgegevens, ons vragen om het verwerken van uw persoonsgegevens te **beperken** of verzoeken om **overdraagbaarheid** van uw persoonsgegevens.
* U kunt het recht hebben om **geen beslissing over u te laten nemen die uitsluitend is gebaseerd op geautomatiseerde verwerking, inclusief profilering**, als die beslissing juridische gevolgen voor u heeft of u aanzienlijk beïnvloedt.
* Evenzo, als we uw persoonsgegevens hebben verzameld en verwerkt met uw toestemming, dan **kunt u uw toestemming op elk moment intrekken**. Het intrekken van uw toestemming heeft geen invloed op de rechtmatigheid van enige verwerking die we voorafgaand aan uw intrekking hebben uitgevoerd, noch is dit van invloed op de verwerking van uw persoonsgegevens die wordt uitgevoerd op basis van andere rechtmatige verwerkingsgronden dan toestemming.
* U kunt het recht hebben om **uit te schrijven voor de verkoop van uw persoonsgegeven**s. Honeywell verkoopt uw persoonlijke gegevens niet aan derden met winstoogmerk. We delen uw persoonlijke gegevens echter wel of maken deze op een andere manieren bekend aan derden in overeenstemming met deze privacyverklaring en onze [Kennisgeving voor cookies](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice). We werken bijvoorbeeld samen met derden voor de distributie van onze producten, u te voorzien van technische ondersteuning, het gebruik van analytische hulpmiddelen en functies voor websites en het uitvoeren van marketing en verkoop van onze producten en diensten. Dergelijke activiteiten kunnen de openbaarmaking van uw persoonsgegevens aan derden inhouden en kunnen worden beschouwd als een "verkoop" van gegevens onder bepaalde (maar niet alle) wetten inzake gegevensbescherming.
* U hebt het recht om **in klacht in te dienen** bij een gegevensbeschermingsautoriteit die verantwoordelijk is voor het toezicht op de naleving van de wetgeving inzake gegevensbescherming in uw rechtsgebied over het verzamelen en gebruik van uw persoonsgegevens door ons, als u van mening bent dat onze verwerking van uw persoonsgegevens niet in overeenstemming is met de wetgeving inzake gegevensbescherming. Personen in de EER hebben bijvoorbeeld het recht om een klacht in te dienen bij de bevoegde gegevensbeschermingsautoriteit, waarvan een lijst beschikbaar is op: [https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/board/members\_en](https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/board/members_en). Wij zouden echter graag de kans krijgen uw punten van zorg aan te pakken, dus neem gerust contact met ons op betreffende eventuele klachten die u hebt. We discrimineren geen personen voor het uitoefenen van hun privacyrechten betreffende gegevens.

Wij zullen de uitoefening van de rechten die op u van toepassing zijn faciliteren in overeenstemming met de toepasselijke wetgeving. Maar zelfs als uw persoonlijke informatie geen bescherming biedt op grond van of anderszins onderworpen is aan een wet inzake gegevensbescherming, kunnen we proberen te voldoen aan elk verzoek dat u hebt met betrekking tot onze gegevensverwerkingsactiviteiten. Als u vragen hebt over uw rechten of uw rechten wilt uitoefenen, dan kunt u contact met ons opnemen via [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com) of stel privacyvragen via ons interactieve webformulier op de volgende koppeling:

**Gegevens van kinderen**

Onze sites zijn niet gericht op, en mogen niet worden gebruikt door, kinderen jonger dan zestien (16) en we verzamelen, gebruiken of verkopen niet bewust informatie van dergelijke personen. Als u minderjarig bent, zoals verstaan door de wetten van uw land, dient u geen persoonlijke informatie in te dienen via onze sites.

**Koppelingen naar andere websites**

Onze sites kunnen koppelingen bevatten naar websites, producten en diensten van derden. Wij zijn niet aansprakelijk of verantwoordelijk voor die websites, producten en diensten, hun beleid of hun verzameling of andere verwerking van uw persoonsgegevens. De praktijken van die derden worden beheerst door hun eigen privacybeleid. Wij moedigen u aan het privacybeleid van dergelijke derden te raadplegen.

**Neem contact met ons op**

Als u vragen hebt over deze Privacyverklaring of onze omgang met uw persoonsgegevens, een klacht wilt indienen of contact wilt opnemen met onze functionaris voor gegevensbescherming, kunt u contact met ons opnemen via onderstaande contactgegevens. We zullen spoedig op uw probleem antwoorden en streven ernaar een bevredigende oplossing te vinden.

Interactief webformulier:  

E-mail:  

Postadres:  
Honeywell Privacy  
4D5  
115 Tabor Road  
Morris Plains, NJ 07950

Gratis nummer:  

**Wijzigingen in deze Privacyverklaring**

We kunnen deze Privacyverklaring af en toe bij bijwerken. Wanneer we dit doen, herzien we de datum voor 'laatst bijgewerkt' boven en onder aan de Privacyverklaring en ondernemen we aanvullende stappen indien deze wettelijk zijn vereist.

**Laatst bijgewerkt 11 juni 2021**

Finnish

**Viimeksi päivitetty 11. kesäkuuta 2021**

**Johdanto**

Honeywell International Inc. (jäljempänä ”**Honeywell**” tai ”**me**”), on sinulta sivustoillamme käymisen tai niiden tai tähän Tietosuojalausuntoon liittyvien tuotteidemme, palveluidemme ja sovellustemme käytön yhteydessä keräämiemme henkilötietojen rekisterinpitäjä (yhdessä ”**Sivustomme**”). Tässä Tietosuojalausunnossa kerromme, miten keräämme, jaamme ja käytämme näin kerättyjä henkilötietojasi ja miten käytät oikeuttasi yksityisyyteen.

Eri alustoillamme saatat kohdata muitakin tietosuojailmoituksia yksittäisten toimintojen yhteydessä. Saatamme myös tarjota sinulle mahdollisuutta valita, miten Honeywell kulloinkin käsittelee henkilötietojasi.

Alla olevista linkeistä voit siirtyä suoraan itseäsi kiinnostavaan osioon:

**Tietojen kerääminen**

* **Suoraan sinulta kerätyt tiedot**. Saatamme pyytää sinulta henkilötietoja, jotta pyytämäsi palvelu tai tapahtuma voidaan suorittaa. Saatat lisäksi antaa meille henkilötietoja ollessasi meihin yhteydessä (esimerkiksi kommentin, tiedustelun, asiakastukipyynnön tai sivustokäynnin yhteydessä) tai rekisteröidessäsi tilin Sivustojamme käyttääksesi. Nämä henkilötiedot voivat sisältää
    * **tunnistetietoja,** kuten nimi, arvonimi, yrityksen tai organisaation nimi, sähköpostiosoite, puhelinnumerot ja postiosoite (katuosoite, postitoimipaikka, postinumero ja/tai maa)
    * **rekisteröitymistietoja,** jotka annat rekisteröityessäsi Sivustojemme käyttäjäksi (käyttäjätunnukset ja salasanat)
    * **rekrytointitietoja,** kuten (jäljempänä kuvatun) työhakemuksen tai työpaikkatiedustelun yhteydessä antamasi tiedot
    * **yritysyhteystietoja,** kuten tietoja kolmannen osapuolen (esim. yrityksen, osakeyhtiön, henkilöyhtiön, toiminimen, voittoa tavoittelemattoman organisaation tai valtion viraston) muista työntekijöistä, omistajista, hallituksen jäsenistä, toimihenkilöistä tai urakoitsijoista
    * **markkinointi- ja viestintätietoja,** kuten markkinointiasetuksesi ja tiedot julkaisujemme tilauksista
    * **taloustietoja,** kuten luottokortti- tai tilitiedot, joiden avulla voimme mahdollistaa sinulle Sivustoilla tarjoamiemme Yhtiön tuotteiden ja palveluiden oston
    * **vientivalvontatietoja,** kuten kansallisuus, kansalaisuus ja asuinmaa, joiden avulla voimme päätellä oikeutesi saada tietoa tietyistä teknologioista
    * **transaktiotietoja,** kuten tuotteita ja palveluita koskevat tiedustelut ja tilaukset sekä maksutiedot saamistasi ja suorittamistasi maksuista, näiden joukossa ostotilaushistoria ja maksutapahtumiin tarvittavat tiedot
    * **rekisteröitymistietoja tapahtumiin**, kuten sähköisillä rekisteröitymislomakkeilla antamasi tiedot
    * **antamaasi palautetta,** kuten kyselyissä, suosituksissa tai muutoin Sivustoistamme sekä tuotteistamme ja palveluistamme yleisesti antamasi palaute.

Jos et anna pyydettyjä tietoja, emme ehkä voi tarjota pyytämääsi palvelua tai suorittaa tiettyä transaktiota.

* **Automaattisesti sinusta kerätyt tiedot**. Keräämme tiettyjä tietoja käynneistäsi Sivustoillamme evästeiden ja vastaavien seurantatekniikoiden avulla. Kunnioitamme aina laillista oikeuttasi estää tietojen kerääminen. Näin kerätyt tiedot sisältävät
    * **käyttötietoja,** kuten miten käytät Sivustojamme, millä sivuilla käyt, siirretty tavumäärä, napsauttamasi linkit, avaamasi materiaalit, Sivustolla käyntisi ajankohta, sivusto, jolta tulet Sivustollemme sekä muut Sivustoilla suorittamasi toimet
    * **teknisiä tietoja,** kuten IP-osoitteesi, selaimen tyyppi ja valmiudet, laitteen kieli ja käyttöjärjestelmä.

Lisätietoja Sivustoillamme käytetyistä evästeistä ja muista seurantatekniikoista saat lukemalla [Evästeilmoituksemme](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#language6).

* **Maantieteelliset tiedot**. Tietyillä Sivustoilla voimme suostumuksellasi poimia tarkan, reaaliaikaisen sijaintisi mobiililaitteeltasi. Tätä tietoa käytetään vain Sivustojen käyttösi helpottamiseen meidän tai palveluntarjoajien toimesta. He saattavat käsitellä näitä tietoja palvelujen tarjoamiseksi sinulle puolestamme. Annettuasi suostumuksesi voit perua sen muuttamalla sijaintipalveluiden asetuksia mobiililaitteesi asetuksista.
* **Kolmansilta osapuolilta kerätyt tiedot**. Lain salliessa voimme kerätä henkilötietojasi kolmansilta osapuolilta, kuten sosiaalisen median sivustoilta ja sovelluksista, ja yhdistää ne jo hallussamme oleviin tietoihin parantaaksemme ja mukauttaaksemme Sivustoja mieltymystesi mukaisiksi sekä muita tässä Tietosuojalausunnossa ilmoitettuja tarkoituksia varten. Voimme myös kerätä yritysyhteystietoja työnantajaltasi tai muilta kolmansilta osapuolilta hyödyntääksemme niitä perinteiseen yritystoimintaan tai yrityksen hallinnollisiin tarkoituksiin.

**Tietojen käyttö**

Voimme käyttää Sivustojemme kautta tai yhteydenottosi yhteydessä keräämiämme henkilötietoja muun muassa seuraavia tarkoituksia varten:

* **Yritysyhteystiedot**. Honeywell kerää ja käyttää yritysyhteystietoja viestinnän tai transaktioiden tukena, kuten tuotteen tai palvelun tarjoamista tai hankintaa koskevaa asianmukaisuusvalvontaa varten. Honeywell voi kerätä ja käyttää näitä yritysyhteystietoja esimerkiksi sujuvoittaakseen ja hallinnoidakseen tilauksia, sopimuksia, takuita, huoltoa ja vastaavia liiketoimintoja, luottokelpoisuuden arviointiin ja perintään, sisäisiin compliance-tarkoituksiin ja juridisiin tarkoituksiin sekä (tarpeen vaatiessa) etujensa ja saataviensa ajamiseen.
* **Palvelut ja transaktiot**. Voimme käyttää henkilötietojasi palvelujen toimittamiseen sinulle tai pyytämiesi transaktioiden suorittamiseen, kuten tietojen toimitukseen hankkimistasi tai käytössäsi olevista Yhtiön tuotteista tai palveluista, hankittujen tuotteiden rekisteröintiin, tuotetilausten käsittelyyn, takuukorvausvaatimusten käsittelyyn, tuoteoppaiden päivitykseen, asiakaspalvelupyyntöihin vastaamiseen ja Sivustojemme käytön mahdollistamiseen.
* **Liiketoimintamme ja sivustojemme hallinnointi ja suojaaminen**. Voimme käyttää henkilötietojasi liiketoimintamme ja Sivustojemme hallinnointiin ja suojaamiseen, kuten vianmääritykseen, järjestelmän kunnossapitoon, tukeen, raportointiin ja tietojen säilyttämiseen palvelimilla.
* **Liiketoimintamme, Sivustojemme, tuotteidemme ja palveluidemme parantaminen**. Voimme käyttää henkilötietojasi liiketoiminta-analyysiin tai muihin tarkoituksiin, joilla kehitetään ja parannetaan liiketoimintamme, Sivustojemme ja tuotteidemme ja palveluittemme (myös uusien tuotteiden ja palveluiden) laatua esimerkiksi mukauttamalla Sivustoja mieltymystesi ja intressiesi mukaan.
* **Markkinointi**. Voimme käyttää henkilötietojasi lakien ja määräysten puitteissa informoidaksemme sinua tuotteista tai palveluista, jotka saattaisivat kiinnostaa sinua, sekä tuotteista, tapahtumista ja uutisista, kyselyistä, erikoistarjouksista ja näihin liittyvistä asioista. Voit kieltäytyä vastaanottamasta markkinointisähköpostiviestejä milloin tahansa kustakin viestistä löytyvää tilauksen peruutuslinkkiä käyttäen tai ottamalla meihin yhteyttä tässä Tietosuojalausunnossa annettujen yhteystietojen kautta. Asuinmaasta riippuen sinulla saattaa olla myös oikeus kieltäytyä muusta markkinointiviestinnästä. Lisätietoja saat ottamalla yhteyttä meihin Tietosuojalausunnossa mainittuja yhteystietoja käyttäen. Joillakin alueilla (esim. Kaliforniassa) yksityishenkilöillä on oikeus pyytää tietoja henkilötietojen luovuttamisesta kolmansille osapuolille suoramarkkinointitarkoituksiin. Jos haluat lisätietoa tietojen luovutusta markkinointitarkoituksiin koskevista käytännöistämme, ota meihin yhteyttä alla olevien ohjeiden mukaisesti.
* **Räätälöity mainonta**. Keräämme tietoja verkon käytöstäsi ja tunnistamme kiinnostuksesi kohteet, jotta voimme tarjota sinulle relevanttia mainontaa. Voit kieltäytyä vastaanottamasta räätälöityä mainontaa Honeywelliltä [Evästeilmoituksen](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#language6) mukaisesti.
* **Kannustin- ja kanta-asiakasohjelmat**. Keräämme ja käytämme henkilötietoja kannustin- ja kanta-asiakasohjelmiemme ylläpitoa ja hallinnointia varten. Käytämme näissä ohjelmissa antamiasi henkilötietoja yksilöllisten palkintojen tarjoamiseen, ohjelmastatuksesi seurantaan sekä ohjelmapisteiden tuotteisiin, mainosmateriaaleihin, työpajoihin ja muuhun sisältöön vaihdon mahdollistamiseen. Lain salliessa saatamme käyttää kannustinohjelman puitteissa antamiasi henkilötietoja myös muuta tähän Tietosuojalausuntoon kirjattua tarkoitusta varten. Perehdy kunkin kannustinohjelman nimenomaisiin ehtoihin ennen rekisteröitymistä tai osallistumista, koska ehdot on räätälöity ohjelmakohtaisesti. Jos annat suostumuksesi ohjelmaan osallistumiseen, voit perua sen milloin tahansa ottamalla meihin yhteyttä tämän Tietosuojalausunnon lopussa olevia yhteystietoja käyttäen tai ohjelman käyttöehtojen ohjeita noudattaen.
* **Työhakemukset**. Saatat antaa meille tietoja itsestäsi työhakemuksen tai -tiedustelun yhteydessä: ansioluettelon tai CV:n, referenssejä, tietoja koulutuksesta ja aiemmista työpaikoista sekä ammatillisista tutkinnoista. Me ja konsernin muut yhtiöt voimme käyttää näitä tietoja harkitessamme työn tarjoamista, tarkistaessamme taustoja ja muutoin haun yhteydessä annetun erillisen tietosuojaselosteen tai muun ilmoituksen mukaisesti. Voimme pyytää, kerätä ja tallentaa työhakemuksia kolmatta osapuolta (rekrytointiammattilaista) tai sosiaalisen median alustaa käyttäen. Lisätietoja saat [Työnhakijan tietosuojalausunnosta](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/applicant-privacy-notice#finnish).
* **Tutkimus ja analysointi**. Voimme käyttää henkilötietojasi tutkimuksessa ja analyyseissä, joilla analysoimme ostomieltymyksiäsi, määritämme tarpeisiisi parhaiten sopivat tuotteet ja palvelut ja mittaamme sinulle esittämämme mainonnan tehoa.
* **Lainmukaisuusvalvonta**. Voimme käyttää keräämiämme henkilötietoja petosten, immateriaalioikeusloukkausten, ehtojemme rikkomusten, lainvastaisen toiminnan tai muun Sivustojemme väärinkäytön havaitsemiseen ja ehkäisyyn sekä tällaiseen toimintaan reagointiin.

Saatamme lain salliessa yhdistää Sivustojemme kautta keräämiämme tietoja muihin sinusta säilyttämiimme tietoihin (esimerkiksi tuotteidemme ja palveluidemme käyttöäsi koskeviin tietoihin) tarjotaksemme sinulle paremman ja yhtenäisen asiakaskokemuksen tai muuta tähän Tietosuojalausuntoon kirjattua tarkoitusta varten.

**Tietojen käsittelyn oikeusperuste**

Varmistamme lain niin vaatiessa, että henkilötietojesi käsittelylle on oikeusperuste. Useimmissa tapauksissa oikeusperuste riippuu kerätyistä henkilötiedoista ja keruun kontekstista.

* **Sopimusperuste**: käsittely on välttämätöntä, jotta voimme suorittaa sinulle tarjoamamme palvelut tai toimet, joita vaaditaan (pyynnöstäsi) ennen palvelujen suorittamista niihin valmistautumiseksi
* **Laillinen velvoite**: käsittely on välttämätöntä, jotta voimme täyttää lakisääteiset velvoitteemme, kuten sovellettavien lakien, asetusten, viranomaisen tai viranomaistehtävää hoitavan yksityisen yrityksen vaatimusten tai oikeuden määräysten tai haasteiden noudattamiseksi
* **Suostumusperuste**: käsittely perustuu henkilötietojesi käsittelyyn antamaasi suostumukseen yhtä tai useampaa nimettyä tarkoitusta (esim. markkinointia) varten
* **Oikeutetut edut**: käsittely on välttämätöntä oikeutetun etumme toteuttamiseksi, kuten Sivustojemme, tuotteidemme ja/tai palveluidemme kehittämiseksi ja parantamiseksi asiakkaidemme hyväksi
* **Elintärkeät edut**: käsittely on välttämätöntä elintärkeän etusi suojaamiseksi (esimerkiksi terveys- ja turvallisuussyistä, jos osallistut tapaamiseen Honeywellin toimipisteessä).

Jos sinulla on kysyttävää tai haluat lisätietoja oikeusperusteesta, jonka nojalla keräämme ja käytämme henkilötietojasi, lähetä sähköpostia osoitteeseen [HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com)

**Tietojen anonymisointi**

Saatamme anonymisoida henkilötietojasi sovellettavan lain sallimissa rajoissa siten, ettei sinua voida enää tunnistaa kyseisten tietojen perusteella. Anonymisoitujen tietojen ei katsota olevan henkilötietoja, eikä niihin sen vuoksi sovelleta tätä Tietosuojalausuntoa. Voimme kerätä, käyttää, koostaa ja jakaa anonymisoituja tietoja missä tahansa tarkoituksessa.

**Kauanko tietoja säilytetään**

Henkilötietojesi säilytysaika vaihtelee sen mukaan, missä tarkoituksessa niitä käsitellään. Säilytämme esimerkiksi tuotteiden ja palvelujen tarjoamiseen tai pyytämiesi transaktioiden mahdollistamiseen tarvittavia henkilötietoja niin kauan kuin olet Honeywellin asiakas. Jos lähetät työhakemuksen Sivustojemme kautta, säilytämme hakemuksesi tietoja sinulle haun yhteydessä annetun tietosuojailmoituksen tai lain vaatimusten mukaisesti. Kaikissa muissa tapauksissa henkilötietojasi säilytetään niin kauan kuin se on tarpeen tässä Tietosuojalausunnossa määriteltyjen tarkoitusten toteuttamiseksi, minkä jälkeen ne joko anonymisoidaan (sovellettavan lain sen salliessa), poistetaan tai tuhotaan.

**Tietojen luovuttaminen**

Saatamme luovuttaa henkilötietojasi valituille kolmansille osapuolille sovellettavan lain sallimissa rajoissa muun muassa seuraavasti.

* **Konserniyhtiömme**. Voimme luovuttaa henkilötietojasi tytäryhtiöillemme ja konserniyhtiöillemme, kun se katsotaan kohtuudella välttämättömäksi tähän Tietosuojalausuntoon kirjattua tarkoitusta varten.
* **Palveluntuottajat**. Voimme luovuttaa henkilötietojasi yrityksille, jotka toimeksiannostamme tuottavat palveluita, kuten ylläpitävät verkkosivustojamme, suorittavat kyselyitä, käsittelevät transaktioita, analysoivat Sivustojamme ja suorittavat analyyseja liiketoimintamme, Sivustojemme ja tuotteidemme ja palveluidemme laadun parantamiseksi. Edellytämme, että nämä palveluntuottajat pitävät henkilötietosi salassa.
* **Jakelijat ja muut luotetut liiketoimintakumppanit**. Voimme luovuttaa henkilötietojasi kolmansille osapuolille, jotka jakelevat tuotteitamme, ja muille luotetuille liiketoimintakumppaneillemme muun muassa siinä tarkoituksessa, että kyseiset kolmannet osapuolet voivat lähettää sinulle markkinointiviestejä. Markkinointitarkoituksiin henkilötietoja luovutetaan sovellettavien lakien ja määräysten puitteissa.
* **Transaktioihin liittyvä tietojen luovuttaminen**. Joidenkin tapahtumien yhteydessä saatamme luovuttaa kaikki tai osan meillä olevista henkilötiedoistasi rahoituslaitoksille, viranomaisille ja kuljetusyrityksille tai postipalveluille, jotka osallistuvat transaktion toteutukseen.
* **Yritysostoon tai myyntiin liittyvä tietojen luovuttaminen**. Strategisista tai muista liiketoiminnallisista syistä Honeywell saattaa päätyä myymään, ostamaan, divestoimaan, yhdistämään tai uudelleenorganisoimaan yritystoimintaa joissakin maissa. Honeywell voi luovuttaa asiakastietoja kohtuudella tarpeellisessa määrin fuusioitumista, yritysostoa tai myyntiä tai yritystoimintojen osittaista tai täysimääräistä myyntiä koskevien neuvottelujen jatkamiseksi tai loppuunsaattamiseksi.
* **Tietojen luovuttaminen muista syistä**. Voimme luovuttaa henkilötietoja oikeuksiemme tai omaisuutemme suojaamiseksi ja puolustamiseksi tai hätätilanteessa henkilön turvallisuuden suojaamiseksi, mikäli laki sitä edellyttää tai sen sallii, kun luovuttamisen perustana on käsityksemme mukaan lakisääteinen velvoite tai laillinen kanne.

**Kansainväliset tiedonsiirrot**

Honeywell on globaali organisaatio, ja henkilötietojasi voidaan siirtää eri maihin, kuten Yhdysvaltoihin, Meksikoon tai Intiaan sovellettavan lain mukaisesti sekä säilyttää, tallettaa tai käyttää näissä maissa. Tämä tarkoittaa, että kun keräämme henkilötietojasi, niitä voidaan käsitellä maissa, joiden tietosuojalait poikkeavat oman maasi laeista. Honeywell pyrkii kuitenkin aina kohtuullisiin toimin turvaamaan yksityisyytesi ja tarjoamaan oman asuinmaasi tietosuojan tasoisen henkilötietojen suojan. Näihin toimiin kuuluu Euroopan komission vakiosopimuslausekkeiden käyttö. Jos haluat lisätietoja henkilötietojesi suojaamiseksi toteutetuista toimista, ota yhteyttä sähköpostitse osoitteeseen [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com).

**Turva**

Olemme sitoutuneet pitämään henkilötietosi turvassa. Turvaamme henkilötietojasi teknisin ja organisatorisin toimin taataksemme niille käsittelyn riskeihin nähden asianmukaisen suojan. Jos haluat lisätietoja siitä, miten Honeywell suojaa henkilötietojasi, ota yhteyttä sähköpostitse osoitteeseen [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com)

**Oikeutesi**

Kulloinkin sovellettavasta laista riippuen sinulla voi olla tiettyjä henkilötietoihisi liittyviä oikeuksia.

* Sinulla voi olla oikeus **tarkastaa, korjata ja päivittää** henkilötietosi tai **pyytää niiden poistoa**.
* Voit **vastustaa** henkilötietojesi käsittelyä, pyytää meitä **rajoittamaan** henkilötietojesi käsittelyä tai esittää henkilötietojesi **siirrettävyyttä** koskevan pyynnön.
* Sinulla voi olla oikeus **estää yksinomaan automatisoituun käsittelyyn perustuva itseäsi koskeva päätöksenteko, kuten profilointi,** jos päätöksellä on sinua koskevia oikeusvaikutuksia tai se vaikuttaa sinuun merkittävästi.
* Jos henkilötietojesi keruu ja käsittely on tapahtunut suostumuksellasi, **voit perua suostumuksesi milloin tahansa**. Suostumuksesi peruminen ei vaikuta ennen perumista suoritetun käsittelyn laillisuuteen. Se ei myöskään vaikuta henkilötietojesi käsittelyyn siltä osin kuin käsittelyn oikeusperuste on muu kuin suostumus.
* Sinulla voi olla oikeus kieltää **henkilötietojesi myynti edelleen**. Honeywell ei myy henkilötietojasi kolmansille osapuolille saadakseen taloudellista hyötyä. Me kuitenkin jaamme tai luovutamme henkilötietojasi kolmansille osapuolille tämän Tietosuojalausunnon ja [Evästeilmoituksemme](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#language6) rajauksin. Ulkoistamme kolmansille osapuolille esimerkiksi jälleenmyyntiä, teknisen tuen tarjoamista, verkkosivustojen analytiikkaa sekä tuotteiden ja palveluiden markkinointia ja myyntiä. Tällaiseen toimintaan voi liittyä henkilökohtaisten tietojesi luovuttaminen kolmansille osapuolille, joka voidaan katsoa tietojen myynniksi joidenkin (mutta ei kaikkien) tietosuojalakien nojalla.
* Sinulla on oikeus **tehdä valitus** sille tietosuojaviranomaiselle, joka vastaa henkilötietojen keruuta ja käyttöä koskevasta laillisuusvalvonnasta omassa maassasi, jos uskot meidän käsittelevän henkilötietojasi tietosuojalain vastaisesti. Esimerkiksi Euroopan talousalueella henkilö voi tehdä valituksen toimivaltaiselle tietosuojaviranomaiselle, jotka on listattu osoitteessa [https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/board/members\_fi](https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/board/members_fi). Toivomme kuitenkin, että keskustelet asiasta meidän kanssamme. Ota meihin yhteyttä, kun haluaisit valittaa. Emme syrji ketään siksi, että hän on ajanut tietosuojalakeihin perustuvia oikeuksiaan.

Olemme apuna lakisääteisten oikeuksiesi takaamisessa. Siinäkin tapauksessa, ettei tietosuojalaki suojaisi henkilötietojasi tietyssä tilanteessa, voimme kuitenkin pyrkiä vastaamaan tietojenkäsittelyämme koskeviin pyyntöihisi ja tiedusteluihisi. Jos sinulla on kysyttävää oikeuksistasi tai haluat käyttää niitä, ota meihin yhteyttä sähköpostitse osoitteeseen [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com) tai lähetä tietosuojakysymyksesi interaktiivisen verkkolomakkeemme kautta osoitteessa

**Lasten tiedot**

Sivustojamme ei ole suunnattu alle 16-vuotiaille lapsille. Heidän ei tulisi käyttää sivustoa, emmekä tietoisesti kerää, käytä tai myy alle 16-vuotiaiden tietoja. Jos olet oman maasi lainsäädännön nojalla alaikäinen, älä lähetä meille henkilötietoja Sivustojemme kautta.

**Linkit muihin sivustoihin**

Sivustomme saattavat sisältää linkkejä kolmansien osapuolten sivustoihin, tuotteisiin ja palveluihin. Emme ole vastuussa näistä sivustoista, tuotteista tai palveluista, niiden käytännöistä tai niiden henkilötietojesi keruusta tai muusta käsittelystä. Kolmansilla osapuolilla on omat tietosuojakäytäntönsä. Kehotamme sinua perehtymään näiden kolmansien osapuolten tietosuojakäytäntöihin.

**Ota yhteyttä**

Jos sinulla on kysyttävää tästä tietosuojalausunnosta tai henkilötietojesi käsittelystä, jos haluat tehdä valituksen tai saada yhteyden tietosuojavastaavaamme, ota meihin yhteys käyttäen seuraavia yhteystietoja. Perehdymme asiaasi viivytyksettä ja pyrimme pääsemään tyydyttävään ratkaisuun.

Interaktiivinen verkkolomake:  

Sähköposti:  

Postiosoite:  
Honeywell Privacy  
4D5  
115 Tabor Road  
Morris Plains, NJ 07950

Maksuton puhelin:  

**Tämän tietosuojalausunnon muutokset**

Tätä tietosuojalausuntoa voidaan päivittää ajoittain. Kun niin käy, muutamme Tietosuojalausunnon yläosassa olevaa ”Viimeksi päivitetty” -päiväystä ja ryhdymme muihin lainsäädännön mahdollisesti edellyttämiin lisätoimiin.

**Viimeksi päivitetty 11. kesäkuuta 2021**

French

**Dernière mise à jour le 11 juin 2021**

**Introduction**

Honeywell International Inc. (« **Honeywell** », « **notre** », « **nos** » ou « **nous** »), est le « responsable du traitement des données » des informations personnelles que nous collectons à votre sujet lorsque vous visitez ou utilisez l’un de nos sites Web, ou lorsque vous utilisez des produits, des services et des applications qui sont associés à la présente Déclaration de confidentialité (collectivement, nos « **Sites** »). La présente Déclaration de confidentialité explique comment nous collectons, partageons et utilisons vos informations personnelles collectées de cette façon et comment vous pouvez exercer vos droits à la confidentialité.

Lorsque nous interagissons avec vous, nous pouvons également vous fournir des notifications de confidentialité supplémentaires concernant des activités de traitement spécifiques ou vous proposer des options supplémentaires pour vous informer de la façon dont Honeywell traite vos informations personnelles à ce moment précis.

Cliquez sur l’un des liens ci-dessous pour accéder à la section qui vous intéresse :

[**La base juridique sur laquelle repose notre traitement des informations**](#fr-heading3)

**Notre collecte des informations**

* **Informations collectées directement auprès de vous**. Nous pouvons être amenés à vous demander des informations personnelles afin de pouvoir assurer le service ou la transaction que vous avez demandé. Vous pouvez également nous communiquer des informations personnelles lorsque vous nous contactez ou que vous collaborez avec nous (via un commentaire, une question ou une demande d’aide, en tant que visiteur de site), ou encore si vous créez un compte pour utiliser nos Sites. Ces informations personnelles peuvent comprendre :
    * **Les données relatives à votre identité** : votre nom, titre, le nom de votre société/organisation, votre adresse e-mail, vos numéros de téléphone et de télécopieur, votre adresse postale (y compris la rue, la ville, la région, le code postal et/ou le pays) ;
    * **Les données relatives à votre inscription** : les données que vous fournissez lorsque vous vous inscrivez à un compte pour utiliser nos Sites, y compris les noms d’utilisateur et les mots de passe ;
    * **Les données relatives à votre recrutement** : notamment les informations soumises dans le cadre d’une demande d’emploi ou d’une candidature à un emploi (voir ci-dessous) ;
    * **Les données relatives à vos informations professionnelles** : des informations relatives à d’autres employés, propriétaires, administrateurs, responsables ou sous-traitants d’une organisation tierce (par exemple, une entreprise, une société, un partenariat, un propriétaire unique, un organisme à but non lucratif ou gouvernemental).
    * **Les données relatives au marketing et aux communications** : vos préférences en matière de marketing et vos abonnements à nos publications ;
    * **Les données financières** : les informations relatives aux cartes de crédit ou autres comptes bancaires aux fins de faciliter vos achats de produits et de services de la Société disponibles sur nos Sites ;
    * **Les informations sur le contrôle des exportations** : les informations portant sur votre nationalité, votre citoyenneté et votre pays de résidence, qui nous permettent de déterminer si vous avez le droit de recevoir des informations au sujet de certaines technologies en vertu des lois en matière d’exportations ;
    * **Les données relatives aux transactions** : les demandes de renseignements et les commandes de nos produits et services, ainsi que les détails des paiements qui vous sont destinés et ceux que vous nous faites, y compris l’historique des commandes d’achat et les informations nécessaires pour faciliter les transactions de paiement ;
    * **Les données relatives à l’inscription à des évènements** : les renseignements que vous fournissez lorsque vous remplissez les formulaires d’inscription électronique ; ainsi que
    * **Vos commentaires** : vos commentaires concernant nos Sites ainsi que nos produits et services en général.

Lorsque vous ne fournissez pas les renseignements demandés, il ne nous est pas toujours possible de satisfaire vos demandes en matière de service ou de finaliser votre transaction.

* **Informations que nous collectons automatiquement à votre sujet**. Nous collectons certaines informations sur votre visite de nos Sites à l’aide de cookies et de technologies de suivi similaires. Nous respecterons toujours tous les droits légaux dont vous pourriez disposer pour nous en empêcher. Les données collectées de cette façon incluent :
    * **Données d’utilisation,** y compris les informations sur la manière dont vous utilisez nos Sites, les pages consultées, le nombre d’octets transférés, les liens sur lesquels vous cliquez, les documents auxquels vous accédez, la date et l’heure d’accès au site, le site à partir duquel vous avez accédé à l’un de nos Sites et d’autres actions effectuées sur les Sites ; et
    * **Données techniques,** telles que votre adresse IP (Internet Protocol), le type et les fonctionnalités de votre navigateur, votre langue et votre système d’exploitation.

Pour plus d’informations sur les cookies et d’autres technologies de suivi similaires que nous utilisons sur nos sites, veuillez consulter notre [Avis relatif aux cookies](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#french).

* **Informations sur la géolocalisation**. Pour certains Sites, avec votre consentement, nous pouvons collecter en temps réel l’emplacement précis (c’est-à-dire la géolocalisation) de votre appareil mobile. Ces informations ne seront utilisées que dans le but de faciliter votre utilisation des Sites, et pourront notamment être utilisées par nos fournisseurs de services, qui pourront traiter ces informations en relation avec la prestation de services en notre nom. Si vous accordez votre consentement, vous pouvez modifier celui-ci en gérant vos préférences de Services de localisation dans les paramètres de votre appareil mobile.
* **Informations provenant de tiers**. Conformément à la législation en vigueur, nous pouvons collecter des informations personnelles à votre sujet auprès de tiers, comme des sites de réseaux sociaux ou des applications, et les combiner avec des informations que nous détenons déjà, afin de nous aider à améliorer et à personnaliser nos Sites en fonction de vos préférences et à d’autres fins définies dans la présente Déclaration de confidentialité. Nous pouvons également collecter vos coordonnées professionnelles auprès de votre organisation ou d’autres tiers afin de faciliter ou d’exercer des activités commerciales classiques et des tâches administratives similaires.

**Notre utilisation des informations**

Nous pouvons utiliser les informations personnelles collectées via nos Sites ou lorsque vous nous contactez à des fins qui incluent les suivantes :

* **Coordonnées professionnelles**. Honeywell collecte et utilise les coordonnées professionnelles afin d’effectuer des communications ou des transactions, y compris pour réaliser une vérification au préalable sur, ou fournir ou recevoir, un produit ou un service. Par exemple, Honeywell peut collecter et utiliser ces coordonnées professionnelles afin de faciliter et de gérer les commandes, les contrats, les garanties, la maintenance et des fonctions professionnelles similaires, à des fins d’analyse du crédit et de collecte, pour nous assister dans le cadre de nos obligations juridiques et de conformité internes, et (si nécessaire) de défendre nos intérêts et nos demandes.
* **Services and transactions**. Nous pouvons utiliser vos informations personnelles pour vous fournir les services ou réaliser les opérations que vous avez demandées, y compris, mais sans s’y limiter, l’envoi d’informations sur les produits ou services de la Société que vous avez achetés ou que vous utilisez par ailleurs, l’enregistrement des produits achetés, le traitement des commandes, la gestion des réclamations liées à la garantie, le remplacement des manuels de référence des produits, le traitement des demandes de service client, l’aide à l’utilisation de nos Sites.
* **Administration et protection de nos activités et de nos Sites**. Nous pouvons utiliser vos informations personnelles pour administrer et protéger notre entreprise et nos Sites, y compris le dépannage, la maintenance du système, l’assistance, le reporting et l’hébergement des données.
* **Amélioration de nos activités, de nos Sites, de nos produits et de nos services**. Nous pouvons utiliser vos informations personnelles pour effectuer des analyses commerciales ou à d’autres fins pouvant nous aider à développer et améliorer la qualité de nos activités, Sites, produits et services (y compris les nouveaux produits et services), par exemple en personnalisant nos Sites selon vos préférences ou centres d’intérêts.
* **Marketing**. Conformément aux lois et réglementations applicables, nous pouvons utiliser vos informations personnelles pour vous informer des produits ou services susceptibles de vous intéresser, mais aussi pour communiquer avec vous concernant des offres, événements et actualités, sondages, offres spéciales et sujets connexes. Vous pouvez à tout moment vous désabonner des communications marketing envoyées par e-mail en utilisant le lien « Désabonnement » contenu dans nos e-mails de marketing, ou en nous contactant avec les coordonnées présentes dans cette Déclaration de confidentialité. En fonction de votre pays de résidence, vous pouvez également désactiver d’autres types de communications marketing. Pour plus d’informations, veuillez nous contacter en utilisant les coordonnées répertoriées dans la présente Déclaration de confidentialité. Certaines juridictions donnent le droit à des individus (par exemple, les résidents de la Californie) de demander certaines informations concernant la divulgation de leurs informations personnelles à des tiers dans le cadre des objectifs de marketing direct du tiers. Pour de plus amples informations sur nos pratiques en matière de divulgation de données à des fins de marketing, veuillez nous contacter en suivant les instructions énumérées ci-dessous.
* **Publicités ciblées par centre d’intérêt**. Nous collectons des données sur vos activités en ligne et identifions vos centres d’intérêt afin de pouvoir vous proposer les publicités les plus pertinentes pour votre profil. Vous pouvez refuser de recevoir de la part de Honeywell des publicités ciblées par centre d’intérêt, comme décrit dans notre [Avis relatif aux cookies](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#french).
* **Programmes d’incitation financière et de fidélité**. Nous collectons et utilisons des informations personnelles pour gérer et administrer nos programmes d’incitation financière et de fidélité. Nous utilisons les informations personnelles que vous fournissez dans le cadre de ces programmes pour offrir des récompenses uniques, suivre l’état de votre programme et faciliter l’échange de points de programme pour des produits, du matériel promotionnel, des ateliers de formation et d’autres articles. Dans la mesure permise par la loi, nous pouvons également utiliser les informations personnelles que vous fournissez dans le cadre d’un programme d’incitation financière pour toute autre fin énoncée dans la présente Déclaration de confidentialité. Veuillez consulter les conditions générales de chaque programme d’incitation financière dans lequel vous souhaitez vous inscrire ou auquel vous souhaitez participer, car ces conditions générales peuvent être adaptées avec précision au programme applicable. Si vous acceptez de participer à ces programmes, vous pouvez à tout moment nous contacter en utilisant les coordonnées à la fin de la présente Déclaration de confidentialité ou en suivant les instructions détaillées des conditions générales du programme en vigueur.
* **Demandes d’emploi**. Dans le cadre d’une demande d’emploi ou d’une requête, vous pouvez nous fournir des informations sur vous-même, par exemple un CV, des références professionnelles, des informations sur votre niveau d’éducation et vos antécédents professionnels, ainsi que des informations sur vos formations et certifications professionnelles. Les membres de notre groupe et nous-même pouvons utiliser ces informations à des fins de recrutement, de contrôle des antécédents et d’éligibilité à l’emploi, et tel qu’établi dans toute Déclaration de confidentialité ou tout autre avis distinct disponible en relation avec votre demande. Nous pouvons faire appel à un tiers (par exemple, un recruteur) ou utiliser une plateforme de réseaux sociaux pour solliciter, collecter et conserver des demandes d’emploi. Pour plus d’informations, veuillez lire notre [Avis de confidentialité des candidats à un emploi](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/applicant-privacy-notice#french).
* **Recherche et analyse**. Nous pouvons utiliser vos informations personnelles pour effectuer des recherches et des analyses afin de nous aider à analyser vos préférences d’achat, d’identifier les produits et services qui répondent le mieux à vos besoins, mais aussi pour mesurer l’efficacité des publicités que nous vous proposons.
* **Application** : nous nous réservons le droit d’utiliser les informations personnelles recueillies afin de détecter et prévenir des fraudes ou de réagir si elles sont avérées, des violations de la propriété intellectuelle, tout non-respect de nos Conditions d’utilisation ou de la loi ainsi que toute autre utilisation non appropriée de nos Sites.

Lorsque la loi l’autorise, nous pouvons combiner les données que nous collectons via nos Sites avec d’autres informations que nous détenons à votre sujet (telles que des informations sur votre utilisation de nos produits et services) afin de vous offrir une expérience client améliorée et cohérente lorsque vous interagissez avec nous ou à d’autres fins énoncées dans la présente Déclaration de confidentialité.

**La base juridique sur laquelle repose notre traitement des informations**

Lorsque cela est requis par la loi, nous nous assurons qu’il existe une base juridique pour le traitement de vos informations personnelles. Dans la plupart des cas, notre base juridique dépend de la protection des informations personnelles et du contexte spécifique dans lequel nous les collectons.

* **Contrat** : le traitement est nécessaire pour l’exécution des services que nous vous fournissons, ou afin de prendre les mesures (à votre demande) avant et en prévision de l’exécution de ces services ;
* **Obligation juridique** : le traitement est nécessaire pour nous conformer à nos obligations légales, y compris le respect des lois, règlements, demandes gouvernementales et paragouvernementales, ordonnances des tribunaux ou assignations à comparaître ;
* **Consentement** : le traitement se base sur votre consentement au traitement de vos informations personnelles à une ou plusieurs fins spécifiées (par exemple, le marketing) ;
* **Intérêts légitimes** : le traitement est nécessaire pour répondre à nos intérêts légitimes, par exemple pour développer et améliorer nos Sites, produits et/ou services au bénéfice de nos clients ; ou
* **Intérêts vitaux** : le traitement est nécessaire pour protéger vos intérêts vitaux (par exemple, pour des raisons de santé et de sécurité si vous assistez à une réunion sur un site Honeywell).

Si vous avez des questions ou si vous avez besoin d’informations complémentaires relatives à la base juridique sur laquelle nous recueillons et utilisons vos informations personnelles, veuillez envoyer un e-mail à l’adresse [HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com).

**Anonymisation des informations**

Conformément à la législation applicable, nous pouvons anonymiser vos informations personnelles afin qu’elles ne puissent plus être utilisées pour vous identifier. Les informations anonymisées ne sont pas considérées comme des informations personnelles et ne sont donc pas soumises à cette Déclaration de confidentialité. Nous pouvons collecter, utiliser, regrouper et partager des informations anonymisées à n’importe quelle fin.

**Combien de temps conservons-nous les informations ?**

La période durant laquelle nous stockons vos informations personnelles varie en fonction de l’objectif du traitement. Par exemple, nous stockons les informations personnelles nécessaires pour vous fournir des produits et des services, ou pour faciliter les transactions que vous avez demandées, tant que vous êtes client de Honeywell ou si vous envoyez une candidature à un poste via nos Sites, nous conserverons les détails de votre demande tel que défini dans l’avis de confidentialité qui vous est fourni en lien avec votre candidature ou tel qu’exigé par la loi. Dans tous les autres cas, nous conservons vos informations personnelles aussi longtemps que nécessaire pour atteindre les objectifs énoncés dans la présente Déclaration de confidentialité, après quoi elles seront anonymisées (lorsque la loi l’autorise), supprimées ou détruites.

**Divulgation des informations**

Conformément à la législation applicable, nous pouvons partager vos informations personnelles avec des tiers sélectionnés, y compris de la manière indiquée ci-dessous :

* **Les sociétés du groupe**. Nous pouvons partager vos informations personnelles avec les filiales et sociétés du groupe dans la mesure où cela est raisonnablement nécessaire aux fins énoncées dans la présente Déclaration de confidentialité.
* **Prestataires de services**. Nous pouvons partager vos informations personnelles avec des entreprises avec lesquelles nous sommes sous contrat afin de leur permettre de fournir des services en notre nom, tels que l’hébergement de sites Web, la réalisation de sondages, le traitement des transactions, l’analyse de nos Sites ainsi que l’exécution d’analyses pour améliorer la qualité de nos activités, Sites, produits et services. Nous demandons à ces prestataires de services de protéger la confidentialité de vos informations personnelles.
* **Distributeurs et autres partenaires commerciaux de confiance**. Nous pouvons partager vos informations personnelles avec des tiers qui distribuent nos produits, mais aussi avec d’autres partenaires commerciaux de confiance dans le but de permettre à ces tiers de vous envoyer des e-mails de marketing. Un tel partage d’informations personnelles à des fins de marketing sera effectué conformément aux législations et règlements applicables.
* **Divulgation en rapport avec des transactions**. Dans le cadre de certaines transactions, nous nous réservons le droit de divulguer tout ou partie de vos informations personnelles à des institutions financières, à des organismes publics et à des sociétés assurant des services de livraison ou postaux, qui en auraient besoin pour mener à bien la transaction en question.
* **Divulgations en lien avec des acquisitions ou des cessions**. Dans certains cas, Honeywell peut décider pour des raisons stratégiques ou d’autres motifs d’affaires de vendre, d’acheter, de fusionner ou de réorganiser des activités dans certains pays. Nous nous réservons le droit de dévoiler certaines informations vous concernant et dont nous disposons, uniquement si c’est nécessaire, au cours de négociations dans le cadre d’une fusion, d’une acquisition, d’une cession ou d’une vente de tout ou partie des actifs de Honeywell.
* **Divulgation pour d’autres motifs**. Nous pouvons divulguer des informations personnelles dans le cas où la loi l’exige/l’autorise ou si nous jugeons, en toute bonne foi, que cela est indispensable pour nous conformer aux obligations légales ou aux réglementations qui nous sont imposées, pour défendre et faire valoir nos droits de propriété ou autres, ou dans des cas d’urgence en vue de garantir la sécurité des individus.

**Transferts internationaux**

Honeywell est une société mondiale et vos informations personnelles peuvent être transmises, conservées, stockées ou utilisées dans diverses implantations du monde entier, tel qu’aux États-Unis, au Mexique et en Inde conformément à la législation en vigueur. Cela signifie que lorsque nous recueillons vos informations personnelles, elles peuvent être traitées dans des pays qui peuvent disposer de lois sur la protection des données qui sont différentes des lois de votre pays. Cependant, Honeywell prendra toujours des mesures raisonnables pour protéger votre vie privée et fournir un niveau de protection des informations personnelles comparable à celui de votre pays de résidence, ce qui inclut la mise en œuvre des Clauses contractuelles types de la Commission européenne. Pour de plus amples informations sur les mesures de protection appropriées qui ont été mises en place pour protéger vos informations personnelles, veuillez nous contacter à l’adresse [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com).

**Sécurité**

Nous nous engageons à assurer la protection de vos informations personnelles. Nous avons recours à des mesures techniques et organisationnelles pour fournir un niveau de sécurité adapté au risque de traitement de vos informations personnelles. Pour plus d’informations sur la façon dont Honeywell protège vos informations personnelles, veuillez nous contacter à l’adresse [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com).

**Vos droits**

Selon la loi en vigueur, vous pouvez disposer de certains droits quant à vos informations personnelles.

* Vous pouvez disposer du droit de **consulter, corriger, mettre à jour** ou **demander la suppression** de vos informations personnelles.
* Vous pouvez **vous opposer** au traitement de vos informations personnelles, nous demander de **restreindre** le traitement de vos informations personnelles ou demander la **portabilité** de vos informations personnelles.
* Vous disposez du droit **de refuser qu’une décision soit prise uniquement sur la base d’un traitement automatisé, y compris le profilage,** si cette décision génère des effets juridiques à votre encontre ou vous affecte de manière significative.
* De même, si nous avons recueilli et traité vos informations personnelles avec votre consentement, **vous pouvez retirer votre consentement à tout moment**. Le retrait de votre consentement n’affectera en rien la légalité des traitements que nous avons effectués avant votre retrait, et cela n’affectera pas le traitement de vos informations personnelles effectué en se fondant sur des motifs de traitement licites autres que le consentement.
* Vous pouvez avoir le droit de **refuser la vente de vos informations personnelles**. Honeywell ne vend pas vos informations personnelles à des tiers afin d’en tirer profit. Toutefois, nous partageons ou divulguons vos informations personnelles à des tiers conformément à la présente Déclaration de confidentialité et à notre [Avis relatif aux cookies](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#french). Par exemple, nous collaborons avec des tiers pour distribuer nos produits, vous fournir une assistance technique, exploiter des outils et des fonctionnalités analytiques du site Web, et procéder à la commercialisation et à la vente de nos produits et services. Ces activités peuvent impliquer la divulgation de vos informations personnelles à des tiers et peuvent être considérées comme une « vente » de données en vertu de certaines lois (mais pas toutes) sur la protection des données.
* Vous avez le droit de **porter plainte auprès** d’une autorité de protection des données responsable de l’application de la loi sur la protection des données dans votre juridiction concernant la collecte et l’utilisation de vos données personnelles si vous pensez que le traitement de vos données personnelles ne respecte pas la loi sur la protection des données. Par exemple, les personnes de l’EEE ont le droit de déposer une plainte auprès de l’autorité compétente en matière de protection des données, dont la liste est accessible à l’adresse suivante : [https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/board/members\_en](https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/board/members_en). Nous serions toutefois heureux de pouvoir répondre à vos préoccupations, alors n’hésitez pas à nous contacter pour toute plainte que vous pourriez avoir. Nous n’exercerons aucune discrimination à l’encontre de personnes ayant exercé leurs droits à la confidentialité des données.

Nous faciliterons l’exercice des droits qui vous sont applicables conformément à la législation en vigueur. Cependant, même si vos informations personnelles ne sont pas protégées par une loi sur la protection des données, ou autrement assujetties à cette législation, nous pouvons nous efforcer de répondre à toute demande ou requête que vous pourriez avoir en ce qui concerne nos activités de traitement de données. Si vous avez des questions sur vos droits ou souhaitez exercer vos droits, vous pouvez nous contacter à l’adresse [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com) ou soumettre des questions relatives à la confidentialité en utilisant notre formulaire Web interactif disponible via le lien suivant :

**Informations relatives aux enfants**

Nos Sites ne sont pas destinés aux enfants de moins de seize (16) ans et ne doivent pas être utilisés par ceux-ci, et nous ne recueillons pas, n’utilisons pas ou ne vendons pas volontairement des informations relatives à ces personnes. Si vous êtes mineur au sens des lois de votre pays, veuillez ne pas soumettre d’informations personnelles via nos Sites.

**Liens vers d’autres sites Web**

Nos Sites peuvent contenir des liens vers des sites Web, produits et services de tiers. Nous n’avons aucune responsabilité ou obligation envers ces sites, produits et services, leurs politiques, leur collecte ou tout autre traitement de vos informations personnelles. Les pratiques de ces tiers sont régies par leurs propres politiques de confidentialité. Nous vous encourageons à vous familiariser avec les politiques de confidentialité de ces tiers.

**Nous contacter**

Si vous avez des questions concernant cette Déclaration de confidentialité ou notre traitement de vos informations personnelles, si vous souhaitez déposer une plainte ou contacter notre agent de protection des données, veuillez nous contacter en utilisant les coordonnées ci-dessous. Nous ferons tout ce qui est en notre pouvoir pour répondre rapidement à votre requête et trouver une juste issue au problème.

Formulaire Web interactif:  

E-mail:  

Adresse postale:  
Honeywell Privacy  
4D5  
115 Tabor Road  
Morris Plains, NJ 07950

Numéro gratuit:  

**Modification de la Déclaration de confidentialité**

Nous pouvons de temps à autre mettre à jour la présente déclaration de confidentialité. Dans un tel cas, nous actualiserons la date de la « dernière mise à jour » en haut de la Déclaration de confidentialité et prendrons les mesures supplémentaires requises par la loi.

**Dernière mise à jour le 11 juin 2021**

French - Canadian

**Dernière mise à jour le 11 juin 2021**

**Introduction**

Honeywell International Inc. (« **Honeywell** », « **notre** », « **nos** » ou « **nous** »), est le « contrôleur des données » pour les renseignements personnels que nous recueillons à votre sujet lorsque vous visitez ou utilisez l’un de nos Sites Web, ou lorsque vous utilisez des produits, des services et des applications qui sont associés à la présente Déclaration de confidentialité (collectivement, nos « **Sites** »). La présente Déclaration de confidentialité explique comment nous recueillons, partageons et utilisons vos renseignements personnels recueillis de cette façon et comment vous pouvez exercer vos droits à la confidentialité.

Lorsque nous interagissons avec vous, nous pouvons également vous fournir des notifications de confidentialité supplémentaires concernant des activités de traitement spécifiques ou vous proposer des options supplémentaires pour vous informer de la façon dont Honeywell traite vos renseignements personnels à ce moment précis.

Cliquez sur l’un des liens ci-dessous pour accéder à la section qui vous intéresse :

[**Le fondement juridique sur lequel s’appuie notre traitement des renseignements**](#fr-ca-heading3)

**Notre procédure de collecte de renseignements**

* **Informations recueillies directement auprès de vous**. Nous pourrions vous demander des renseignements personnels afin de vous fournir un service ou d’effectuer une transaction que vous avez demandée. Il se peut également que vous fournissiez des renseignements personnels lorsque vous communiquez avec nous (par exemple, pour envoyer un commentaire, une demande de renseignements ou une demande de soutien à la clientèle, visiter un site) ou que vous créiez un compte pour utiliser nos Sites. Ces renseignements personnels peuvent comprendre :
    * **Des données d’identification,** comme votre nom, titre, nom d’entreprise ou d’organisation, adresse courriel, numéros de téléphone, adresse postale ou code postal (y compris la rue, la ville, la province, le code postal ou le pays);
    * **Des données d’enregistrement,** comme les renseignements que vous nous fournissez lorsque vous créez un compte pour utiliser nos Sites, y compris les noms d’utilisateur et les mots de passe;
    * **Des données de recrutement,** y compris les renseignements soumis associés à une demande d’emploi ou de renseignements (comme décrit ci-dessous);
    * **Des coordonnées professionnelles,** comme des informations relatives à d’autres employés, propriétaires, administrateurs, responsables ou sous-traitants d’une organisation tierce (par exemple, une entreprise, une société, un partenariat, un propriétaire unique, un organisme à but non lucratif ou gouvernemental).
    * **De données de marketing et de communication,** y compris vos préférences marketing et vos abonnements à nos publications;
    * **Des données financières,** y compris des renseignements de carte de crédit ou d’autres renseignements financiers afin de nous permettre de faciliter votre achat de produits et services de la Société pouvant être offerts sur nos Sites;
    * **Des renseignements pour les contrôles des exportations,** comme votre nationalité et votre pays de résidence pour nous permettre de déterminer, conformément aux contrôles des exportations, votre admissibilité à recevoir des renseignements au sujet de certaines technologies;
    * **Des données de transaction,** y compris les demandes de renseignements et les commandes pour nos produits et services ainsi que les détails des paiements que vous recevez et que vous effectuez, dont l’historique des commandes et les informations nécessaires pour faciliter les transactions de paiement;
    * **Des renseignements d’inscription aux événements,** y compris les renseignements que vous fournissez lorsque vous remplissez des formulaires d’inscription en ligne;
    * **Vos commentaires, y compris des sondages,** des recommandations ou d’autres commentaires généraux que vous transmettez concernant nos Sites et nos produits et services.

Si ne vous ne communiquez pas les renseignements demandés, nous pourrions ne pas être en mesure de vous fournir le service demandé ou d’effectuer votre transaction.

* **Les renseignements que nous recueillons automatiquement sur vous**. Nous recueillons automatiquement certaines informations vous concernant lors de votre visite sur nos Sites à l’aide de témoins et d’autres technologies de suivi similaires. Nous respecterons toujours tous les droits légaux dont vous pourriez disposer et qui nous empêcheraient de le faire. Les données collectées de cette façon comprennent :
    * **Des données sur l’utilisation,** y compris des renseignements sur l’utilisation que vous faites de nos Sites, les pages affichées, la quantité d’octets transférés, les liens visités, le contenu consulté, la date et l’heure auxquelles vous avez accédé au site, le site Web à partir duquel vous avez été redirigé vers l’un de nos Sites ainsi que toute autre activité effectuée sur les sites;
    * **Des données techniques,** comme votre adresse IP (Internet Protocol), le type et les capacités de votre navigateur, votre langue et votre système d’exploitation.

Pour plus d’informations sur les témoins et d’autres technologies de suivi similaires que nous utilisons sur nos Sites, veuillez consulter notre [Avis relatif aux témoins](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#french-canadian).

* **Des données de géolocalisation**.Sur certains sites, avec votre consentement, nous pourrions collecter avec précision l’emplacement exact en temps réel de votre appareil mobile (c.-à-d. la géolocalisation). Ces informations ne seront utilisées que dans le but de faciliter votre utilisation des Sites, et pourront notamment être utilisées par nos fournisseurs de services, qui pourront traiter ces informations en relation avec la prestation de services en notre nom. Si vous accordez votre consentement, vous pouvez modifier celui-ci en gérant vos préférences de Services de localisation dans les paramètres de votre appareil mobile.
* **Renseignements recueillis auprès de tiers**. Conformément à la loi applicable, nous pouvons recueillir des renseignements personnels vous concernant auprès de tiers, comme des sites Web ou des applications de médias sociaux, et les combiner aux renseignements que nous détenons déjà afin de nous aider à améliorer et à personnaliser nos Sites selon vos préférences ainsi qu’à d’autres fins indiquées dans cet énoncé de confidentialité. Nous pouvons également recueillir vos coordonnées professionnelles auprès de votre employeur ou d’autres tiers afin de faciliter ou d’entreprendre des activités commerciales traditionnelles et des questions administratives similaires.

**La façon dont nous utilisons l’information**

Nous pouvons utiliser les renseignements personnels recueillis sur nos Sites ou lorsque vous communiquez avec nous aux fins suivantes :

* **Coordonnées professionnelles**. Honeywell collecte et utilise les coordonnées professionnelles afin d’effectuer des communications ou des transactions, y compris pour réaliser une vérification au préalable sur un produit ou un service ou la prestation ou réception d’un produit ou d’un service. Par exemple, Honeywell peut collecter et utiliser ces coordonnées professionnelles afin de faciliter et de gérer les commandes, les contrats, les garanties, la maintenance et des fonctions professionnelles similaires à des fins d’analyse du crédit et de collecte, pour nous assister dans le cadre de nos obligations juridiques et de conformité internes, et, si nécessaire, de défendre nos intérêts et nos demandes.
* **Services et transactions**. Nous pouvons utiliser vos renseignements personnels pour vous fournir des services ou effectuer des transactions que vous avez demandées, y compris, mais sans s’y limiter, pour vous fournir des informations sur des produits ou des services de la Société que vous avez achetés ou que vous utilisez, enregistrer des produits achetés, traiter des commandes de produits, traiter des réclamations sous garantie, remplacer des manuels des produits, répondre aux questions adressées au service à la clientèle et faciliter l’utilisation de nos Sites.
* **Gestion et protection de notre entreprise et de nos Sites**. Nous pouvons utiliser vos renseignements personnels pour gérer et protéger nos activités et nos Sites, y compris le dépannage, la maintenance du système, le soutien, la production de rapport et l’hébergement des données.
* **Amélioration de notre entreprise, de nos Sites, de nos produits et de nos services**. Nous pouvons utiliser vos renseignements personnels aux fins d’analyses commerciales ou à d’autres fins qui nous aident à développer et à améliorer la qualité de divers aspects de notre entreprise, de nos Sites et de nos produits et services (y compris les nouveaux produits et services), par exemple en adaptant nos Sites à vos préférences et à vos champs d’intérêt.
* **Marketing**. Conformément aux lois et réglementations applicables, nous pouvons utiliser vos renseignements personnels pour vous informer des produits ou des services susceptibles de vous intéresser et pour communiquer avec vous concernant des offres, des événements, des nouvelles, des sondages, des offres spéciales et des sujets connexes. Vous pouvez vous désabonner des communications marketing envoyées par courriel en tout temps en cliquant sur le lien de désabonnement figurant dans tout matériel de marketing par courriel que nous vous envoyons ou en communiquant avec nous à l’aide des coordonnées indiquées dans cet énoncé de confidentialité. Selon votre pays de résidence, vous pouvez également vous désabonner d’autres types de communications marketing; veuillez communiquer avec nous à l’aide des coordonnées indiquées dans l’énoncé de confidentialité pour plus d’informations. Certaines administrations (p. ex. les résidents de Californie) donnent aux personnes le droit de demander certaines informations concernant notre divulgation de renseignements personnels à des tiers à des fins de marketing direct. Pour de plus amples informations sur nos pratiques en matière de divulgation de données à des fins de marketing, veuillez nous contacter en suivant les directives ci-dessous.
* **Publicités ciblées par centre d’intérêt**. Nous collectons des données sur vos activités en ligne et déterminons vos centres d’intérêt afin de pouvoir vous proposer les publicités les plus pertinentes pour votre profil. Vous pouvez refuser de recevoir de la part de Honeywell des publicités ciblées par centre d’intérêt, comme décrit dans notre [Avis relatif aux témoins](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#french-canadian).
* **Programmes d’incitation financière et de fidélité**. Nous collectons et utilisons des renseignements personnels pour gérer et administrer nos programmes d’incitation financière et de fidélité. Nous utilisons les renseignements personnels que vous fournissez dans le cadre de ces programmes pour offrir des récompenses uniques, suivre l’état de votre programme et faciliter l’échange de points de programme pour des produits, du matériel promotionnel, des ateliers de formation et d’autres articles. Dans la mesure permise par la loi, nous pouvons également utiliser les renseignements personnels que vous fournissez dans le cadre d’un programme d’incitation financière pour toute autre fin énoncée dans la présente Déclaration de confidentialité. Veuillez consulter les conditions générales de chaque programme d’incitation financière dans lequel vous souhaitez vous inscrire ou auquel vous souhaitez participer, car ces conditions générales peuvent être adaptées avec précision au programme applicable. Si vous acceptez de participer à ces programmes, vous pouvez à tout moment communiquer avec nous en utilisant les coordonnées à la fin de la présente Déclaration de confidentialité ou en suivant les instructions détaillées des conditions générales du programme en vigueur.
* **Demandes d’emploi**. Dans le cadre d’un renseignement ou d’une demande d’emploi, vous pourriez nous fournir des renseignements personnels, comme votre CV, des références professionnelles, des renseignements sur votre scolarité et vos antécédents d’emploi, ainsi que des renseignements sur vos formations ou certifications professionnelles. Les membres de notre groupe et nous-mêmes pouvons utiliser ces renseignements à des fins de recrutement, de vérification des antécédents et d’admissibilité à l’emploi, et tel qu’établi dans toute Déclaration de confidentialité ou tout autre avis distinct disponible en relation avec votre demande. Nous pouvons utiliser un tiers (p. ex. un recruteur) ou une plateforme de médias sociaux pour solliciter, collecter et conserver les demandes d’emploi. Pour plus d’informations, veuillez lire notre [Avis de confidentialité du candidat](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/applicant-privacy-notice#french-canadian).
* **Recherche et analyse**. Nous pouvons utiliser vos renseignements personnels pour effectuer des recherches et des analyses afin de nous aider à examiner vos préférences d’achat, à déterminer les produits et services qui répondent le mieux à vos besoins et à mesurer l’efficacité de la publicité que nous vous présentons.
* **Application**: Nous pouvons utiliser les renseignements personnels que nous recueillons afin de détecter, de prévenir et de combattre la fraude, l’utilisation abusive de nos Sites et la violation de la propriété intellectuelle, de nos conditions générales et des lois.

Si la loi le permet, nous pouvons combiner les renseignements que nous recueillons sur nos Sites à d’autres renseignements vous concernant que nous détenons (comme des renseignements sur votre utilisation de nos produits et services) afin de vous offrir une expérience client améliorée et cohérente lorsque vous interagissez avec nous ou à d’autres fins indiquées dans cet énoncé de confidentialité.

**Le fondement juridique sur lequel s’appuie notre traitement des renseignements**

Lorsque la loi l’exige, nous nous assurons qu’il existe un fondement juridique pour le traitement de vos renseignements personnels. Dans la plupart des cas, notre fondement juridique pour la collecte et l’utilisation des renseignements personnels décrits dans le présent Avis de confidentialité dépendra des renseignements personnels applicables et du contexte spécifique dans lequel nous les recueillons.

* **Contrat** : le traitement est nécessaire pour l’exécution des services que nous vous fournissons ou afin de prendre les mesures (à votre demande) avant et en prévision de l’exécution de ces services;
* **Obligation juridique** : le traitement est nécessaire pour nous conformer à nos obligations légales, y compris le respect des lois, des règlements, des demandes gouvernementales et quasi gouvernementales, des ordonnances ou des citations à comparaître applicables;
* **Consentement** : le traitement est fondé sur votre consentement au traitement de vos renseignements personnels à une ou plusieurs fins précisées (par exemple, à des fins de marketing);
* **Intérêts légitimes** : le traitement est nécessaire pour répondre à nos intérêts légitimes, par exemple pour développer et améliorer nos Sites, nos produits ou nos services au profit de nos clients.
* **Intérêts vitaux** : le traitement est nécessaire pour protéger vos intérêts vitaux (par exemple, pour des raisons de santé et de sécurité si vous assistez à une réunion dans un établissement Honeywell).

Si vous avez des questions ou avez besoin d’autres renseignements en ce qui concerne le fondement juridique de notre collecte et de notre utilisation de vos renseignements personnels, veuillez envoyer un courriel à [HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com).

**L’anonymisation des informations**

Conformément à la loi applicable, nous pouvons anonymiser vos renseignements personnels afin qu’ils ne puissent plus être utilisés pour vous identifier. Les renseignements anonymisés ne sont pas considérés comme des renseignements personnels; ils ne sont donc pas assujettis à cet énoncé de confidentialité. Nous pouvons recueillir, utiliser, regrouper et partager des renseignements anonymisés à n’importe quelle fin.

**Durée de conservation des renseignements**

La période durant laquelle nous conservons vos renseignements personnels varie en fonction de l’objectif de traitement. Par exemple, nous conservons les renseignements personnels nécessaires pour vous fournir des produits et des services ou pour faciliter les transactions que vous avez demandées aussi longtemps que vous êtes un client de Honeywell ou si vous soumettez une demande d’emploi sur nos Sites, nous conserverons les détails de votre demande comme l’indique l’énoncé de confidentialité ou tout autre avis mis à votre disposition dans le cadre de votre demande ou comme la loi l’exige. Dans tous les autres cas, nous conservons vos renseignements personnels aussi longtemps que nécessaire aux fins décrites dans cet énoncé de confidentialité, après quoi ils sont anonymisés (lorsque la loi applicable le permet), supprimés ou détruits.

**Divulgation des informations**

Nous pouvons partager vos renseignements personnels avec des tiers sélectionnés conformément à la loi applicable, y compris comme indiqué ci-dessous :

* **Les sociétés de notre groupe**. Nous pouvons partager vos renseignements personnels avec nos sociétés affiliées et les sociétés de notre groupe pour des utilisations raisonnablement nécessaires aux fins décrites dans le présent énoncé de confidentialité.
* **Les fournisseurs de services**. Nous pouvons partager vos renseignements personnels avec des entreprises que nous avons engagées pour la prestation de services pour notre compte, comme l’hébergement de sites Web, la réalisation de sondages, le traitement de transactions, l’analyse de nos Sites et la production d’analyses pour améliorer la qualité de divers aspects de notre entreprise, de nos Sites et de nos produits et services. Nous exigeons que ces fournisseurs de services protègent la confidentialité de vos renseignements personnels.
* **Les distributeurs et autres partenaires commerciaux de confiance**. Nous pourrions partager vos renseignements personnels avec des tiers qui distribuent nos produits et avec d’autres partenaires commerciaux de confiance à des fins comprenant la possibilité que ces tiers communiquent avec vous à des fins de marketing. Le partage de renseignements personnels à des fins de marketing sera effectué conformément aux lois et règlements applicables.
* **Divulgation de renseignements dans le contexte d’une transaction**. Dans le cadre de certaines transactions, nous pourrions divulguer une partie ou l’intégralité de vos renseignements personnels aux institutions financières, entités gouvernementales et sociétés d’expédition ou services postaux qui participent à l’exécution de la transaction.
* **Divulgation en lien avec des acquisitions ou des cessions**. Dans certaines circonstances, il est possible que la Société décide, pour des questions stratégiques ou d’autres raisons professionnelles, de vendre, d’acheter, de désinvestir, de fusionner ou de réorganiser autrement les activités dans certains pays ou de se départir de ces activités. Il se peut que nous divulguions des renseignements à votre sujet dans la mesure nécessaire à juste titre afin de mener les négociations, voire de procéder à la fusion, à l’acquisition, au désinvestissement ou à la vente des actifs de Honeywell en tout ou en partie.
* **Divulgation pour d’autres motifs**. Nous pouvons divulguer des renseignements personnels si la loi l’exige ou l’autorise ou si nous jugeons en toute bonne foi qu’une telle action est nécessaire pour nous conformer à des obligations légales ou à des recours en droit exercés à notre égard, pour protéger et défendre nos droits et nos biens, ou dans des circonstances urgentes de protection de la sécurité personnelle de tout individu.

**Transferts internationaux**

Compte tenu du fait que Honeywell est une organisation internationale, vos renseignements personnels peuvent être transférés, détenus, conservés ou utilisés sur différentes plateformes à travers le monde, par exemple aux États-Unis, au Mexique et en Inde conformément aux lois applicables. Cela signifie que lorsque nous recueillons vos renseignements, ceux-ci peuvent être traités dans des pays appliquant des lois sur la protection des données différentes des lois de votre pays. Toutefois, Honeywell prendra toujours des mesures raisonnables pour protéger votre vie privée et pour assurer un niveau de protection des renseignements personnels comparable à celui de votre pays de résidence, y compris par la mise en œuvre des clauses contractuelles standard de la Commission européenne. Pour de plus amples informations sur les mesures de protection appropriées qui ont été mises en place pour protéger vos renseignements personnels, veuillez nous contacter à l’adresse [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com).

**Sécurité**

Nous nous engageons à protéger la sécurité de vos renseignements personnels. Nous avons recours à des mesures techniques et organisationnelles pour fournir un niveau de sécurité adapté au risque de traitement de vos renseignements personnels. Pour plus d’informations sur la façon dont Honeywell protège vos renseignements personnels, veuillez nous contacter à l’adresse [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com).

**Vos droits**

Selon la loi en vigueur, vous pouvez disposer de certains droits quant à vos renseignements personnels.

* Vous pouvez avoir le droit **d’accéder, de corriger, de mettre à jour** ou **de demander la suppression** de vos renseignements personnels.
* Vous pouvez vous **opposer** au traitement de vos renseignements personnels, nous demander de **restreindre** le traitement de vos renseignements personnels ou demander la **transférabilité** de vos renseignements personnels.
* Vous disposez du droit **de refuser qu’une décision soit prise uniquement sur la base d’un traitement automatisé, y compris le profilage,** si cette décision génère des effets juridiques à votre encontre ou vous affecte de manière significative.
* De la même façon, si nous avons recueilli et traité vos renseignements personnels avec votre consentement, **vous pouvez retirer votre consentement en tout temps**. Le retrait de votre consentement n’aura aucune incidence sur la légalité de tout traitement que nous avons effectué avant votre retrait, et cela n’affectera pas le traitement de vos renseignements personnels reposant sur des motifs de traitement licites autres que le consentement.
* Vous pouvez avoir le droit de **refuser la vente de vos renseignements personnels**. Honeywell ne vend pas vos renseignements personnels à des tiers afin d’en tirer profit. Toutefois, nous partageons ou divulguons vos renseignements personnels à des tiers conformément à la présente Déclaration de confidentialité et à notre [Avis relatif aux témoins](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#french-canadian). Par exemple, nous collaborons avec des tiers pour distribuer nos produits, vous fournir une assistance technique, exploiter des outils et des fonctionnalités analytiques du site Web, et procéder à la commercialisation et à la vente de nos produits et services. Ces activités peuvent impliquer la divulgation de vos renseignements personnels à des tiers et peuvent être considérées comme une « vente » de données en vertu de certaines lois (mais pas toutes) sur la protection des données.
* Vous avez le droit de **porter plainte auprès** d’une autorité de protection des données responsable de l’application de la loi sur la protection des données dans votre juridiction concernant la collecte et l’utilisation de vos renseignements personnels si vous pensez que le traitement de vos renseignements personnels ne respecte pas la loi sur la protection des données. Par exemple, les personnes de l’EEE ont le droit de déposer une plainte auprès de l’autorité compétente en matière de protection des données, dont la liste est accessible à l’adresse suivante : [https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/board/members\_en](https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/board/members_en). Nous serions toutefois reconnaissants d’avoir l’occasion de répondre à vos préoccupations, alors n’hésitez pas à communiquer avec nous pour toute plainte que vous pourriez avoir. Nous n’exercerons aucune discrimination à l’encontre de personnes ayant exercé leurs droits à la confidentialité des données.

Nous faciliterons l’exercice des droits qui s’appliquent à vous conformément aux lois applicables. Cependant, même si vos renseignements personnels ne sont pas protégés par une loi sur la protection des données, ou autrement assujettis à cette législation, nous pouvons nous efforcer de répondre à toute demande ou requête que vous pourriez avoir en ce qui concerne nos activités de traitement de données. Si vous avez des questions concernant vos droits ou souhaitez exercer vos droits, vous pouvez communiquer avec nous à l’adresse [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com) ou envoyer des questions relatives à la confidentialité en utilisant notre formulaire Web interactif en cliquant sur lien suivant :

**Renseignements sur les enfants**

Nos Sites ne sont pas destinés aux enfants de moins de seize (16) ans et ne doivent pas être utilisés par ceux-ci, et nous ne recueillons pas, n’utilisons pas ou ne vendons pas volontairement des informations relatives à ces personnes. Si vous êtes mineur au sens des lois de votre pays, veuillez ne pas transmettre de renseignements personnels sur nos Sites.

**Liens vers d’autres sites Web**

Nos sites peuvent contenir des liens vers des sites Web, des produits et des services de tiers. Nous n’assumons aucune responsabilité relativement à ces sites Web, produits ou services ni à leurs politiques et à leur collecte ou à leur traitement de vos renseignements personnels. Les pratiques de ces tiers sont régies par leurs propres politiques de confidentialité. Nous vous invitons à vous informer sur les politiques de confidentialité de ces tiers.

**Communiquer avec nous**

Si vous avez des questions concernant cette Déclaration de confidentialité ou notre traitement de vos renseignements personnels, si vous souhaitez déposer une plainte ou contacter notre agent de protection des données, veuillez nous contacter en utilisant les coordonnées ci-dessous. Nous traiterons dans les plus brefs délais votre problème et chercherons à parvenir à une résolution satisfaisante.

Formulaire Web interactif:  

Courriel:  

Adresse postale:  
Honeywell Privacy  
4D5  
115 Tabor Road  
Morris Plains, NJ 07950

Numéro sans frais:  

**Modification de la Déclaration de confidentialité**

Nous pourrions de temps à autre mettre cette déclaration de confidentialité à jour. Lorsque nous le ferons, nous modifierons la date de la dernière mise à jour au haut de l’énoncé de confidentialité et prendrons toute autre mesure exigée par la loi.

**Dernière mise à jour le 11 juin 2021**

German

**Zuletzt aktualisiert am 11. Juni 2021**

**Einführung**

Honeywell International Inc. („**Honeywell**“, „**unser**“, „**uns**“ oder „**wir**“) ist der „Verantwortliche“ für die personenbezogenen Daten, die wir über Sie erheben, wenn Sie eine unserer Websites besuchen oder nutzen oder Produkte, Dienstleistungen und Anwendungen verwenden, die mit dieser Datenschutzerklärung verknüpft sind (gemeinsam unsere „**Sites**“). In dieser Datenschutzerklärung wird erläutert, wie wir Ihre personenbezogenen Daten erheben und die auf diese Weise erhobenen Daten weitergeben und nutzen und wie Sie Ihre Datenschutzrechte ausüben können.

Bei der Interaktion mit Ihnen können wir Ihnen auch zusätzliche Datenschutzhinweise zu bestimmten Verarbeitungsaktivitäten erteilen oder Ihnen zusätzliche Wahlmöglichkeiten bezüglich der Verarbeitung Ihrer personenbezogenen Daten durch Honeywell zu dem betreffenden Zeitpunkt bieten.

Klicken Sie auf einen der folgenden Links, um direkt zu dem für Sie interessanten Abschnitt zu gelangen:

[**Rechtliche Grundlage für die Verarbeitung von Informationen**](#ps-german-heading3)

**Unsere Datenerhebung**

* **Direkt von Ihnen erhobene Informationen**. Es kann sein, dass wir Sie nach personenbezogenen Daten fragen, um eine Dienstleistung zu erbringen oder eine von Ihnen angeforderte Transaktion auszuführen. Möglicherweise stellen Sie uns auch personenbezogene Daten bereit, wenn Sie Kontakt mit uns aufnehmen oder mit uns interagieren (beispielsweise in Form eines Kommentars, einer Anfrage oder einer Kundensupportanforderung, als Besucher unserer Website) oder wenn Sie ein Konto registrieren, um unsere Sites zu nutzen. Zu diesen personenbezogenen Daten können folgende Daten gehören:
    * **Identitätsdaten,** beispielsweise Ihr Name, Ihr Titel, der Name Ihres Unternehmens/Ihrer Organisation, Ihre E-Mail-Adresse, Ihre Telefonnummern und Ihre Postanschrift (einschließlich Straße, Ort, Postleitzahl und/oder Land);
    * **Registrierungsdaten**, die Sie bei der Registrierung eines Kontos bereitgestellt haben, um unsere Sites zu nutzen, einschließlich Benutzernamen und Kennwörtern;
    * **Einstellungsdaten,** einschließlich Informationen, die Sie in Verbindung mit einer Bewerbung oder Stellenanfrage übermittelt haben (wie unten beschrieben);
    * **Geschäftskontaktdaten,** beispielsweise Informationen zu anderen Mitarbeitern, Eigentümern, Direktoren, leitenden Angestellten oder Auftragnehmern einer Drittorganisation (z. B. Geschäft, Firma, Partnerschaft, Einzelunternehmen, gemeinnützige Organisation oder Behörde);
    * **Marketing- und Kommunikationsdaten,** einschließlich Ihrer Marketingpräferenzen und Ihrer Abonnements unserer Veröffentlichungen;
    * **Finanzdaten,** einschließlich Kreditkarteninformationen oder sonstiger Kontoinformationen, die Sie uns zur Abwicklung Ihres Kaufs von Produkten und Dienstleistungen bereitstellen, die möglicherweise auf unseren Sites verfügbar sind;
    * **Informationen im Zusammenhang mit Ausfuhrbestimmungen,** beispielsweise Angaben zu Ihrer Nationalität, zu Ihrer Staatsangehörigkeit und zu Ihrem Wohnsitzland, die es uns ermöglichen, Ihre Berechtigung zum Erhalt von Informationen zu bestimmten Technologien gemäß den Ausfuhrbestimmungen zu ermitteln;
    * **Transaktionsdaten,** beispielsweise Anfragen und Bestellungen für unsere Produkte und Dienstleistungen sowie Details zu den an Sie und von Ihnen geleisteten Zahlungen, einschließlich der Bestellhistorie und der für die Durchführung von Zahlungen erforderlichen Informationen;
    * **Informationen zu Registrierungen für Veranstaltungen,** einschließlich Informationen, die Sie beim Ausfüllen elektronischer Registrierungsformulare bereitstellen; und
    * **Ihr Feedback**, einschließlich Umfragen, Empfehlungen oder sonstigen Feedbacks, das Sie uns allgemein zu unseren Sites sowie zu unseren Produkten und Dienstleistungen bereitstellen.

Wenn Sie die angeforderten Informationen nicht zur Verfügung stellen, sind wir möglicherweise nicht in der Lage, Ihnen die angeforderte Leistung zu erbringen oder Ihre Transaktion abzuschließen.

* **Informationen, die wir automatisch über Sie erfassen**. Mithilfe von Cookies und ähnlichen Nachverfolgungstechnologien erfassen wir bestimmte Informationen zu Ihrem Besuch unserer Sites. Wir respektieren stets alle Ihnen möglicherweise gesetzlich zustehenden Rechte, uns daran zu hindern. Zu den auf diese Weise erhobenen Daten gehören:
    * **Nutzungsdaten,** einschließlich Informationen zu Ihrer Verwendung unserer Sites, zu den aufgerufenen Seiten, zur Anzahl der übertragenen Bytes, zu den angeklickten Links, zu den Materialien, auf die Sie zugreifen, zum Datum und zur Uhrzeit Ihres Zugriffs auf die Website, von der Sie zu einer unserer Sites gelangt sind, sowie zu anderen Aktionen innerhalb der Sites; und
    * **Technische Daten,** wie beispielsweise Ihre Internetprotokolladresse (IP-Adresse), Typ, Funktionalität und Sprache Ihres Browsers und Ihr Betriebssystem.

Informationen zu Cookies und anderen ähnlichen Nachverfolgungstechnologien, die wir auf unseren Sites verwenden, finden Sie in unserem [Hinweis zu Cookies](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#german).

* **Geo-Standortdaten**. Für bestimmte Sites können wir mit Ihrer Zustimmung den genauen Echtzeit-Standort (d. h. die Geolokalisierung) Ihres mobilen Geräts erfassen. Diese Informationen werden ausschließlich zu dem Zweck verwendet, Ihre Nutzung der Sites zu erleichtern. Dies gilt auch für unsere Dienstleister, die diese Informationen möglicherweise im Zusammenhang mit der Erbringung von Dienstleistungen in unserem Namen verarbeiten. Nachdem Sie uns Ihre Zustimmung erteilt haben, können Sie diese Zustimmung jederzeit über die Einstellungen für Standortservices Ihres Mobilgeräts ändern.
* **Informationen, die wir von Dritten erheben**. In Übereinstimmung mit geltendem Recht können wir personenbezogene Daten über Sie von Dritten, beispielsweise Social-Media-Websites und Anwendungen, erheben und mit unseren bereits vorhandenen Informationen kombinieren, um unsere Sites zu verbessern und an Ihre Präferenzen anzupassen, sowie zu anderen in dieser Datenschutzerklärung dargelegten Zwecken. Wir können Ihre Geschäftskontaktinformationen auch von Ihrem Arbeitgeber oder anderen Dritten erheben, um traditionelle Geschäftsaktivitäten und ähnliche Verwaltungsangelegenheiten zu ermöglichen oder anderweitig durchzuführen.

**Unsere Nutzung von Informationen**

Wir können die personenbezogenen Daten, die wir über unsere Sites oder bei Ihrer Kontaktaufnahme erheben, u. a. zu folgenden Zwecken verwenden:

* **Geschäftskontaktdaten**. Honeywell erhebt und verwendet Geschäftskontaktdaten für Kommunikationen oder Transaktionen. Hierzu gehören u. a. Due-Diligence-Prüfungen in Bezug auf ein Produkt oder eine Dienstleistung bzw. die Bereitstellung oder der Erhalt eines Produkts oder einer Dienstleistung. Honeywell kann diese Geschäftskontaktdaten beispielsweise zur Unterstützung und Verwaltung von Bestellungen, Verträgen, Garantien, Wartungsarbeiten und ähnlichen Geschäftsfunktionen, für Kreditanalysen und Inkassozwecke, zur Unterstützung unserer internen Compliance-Anforderungen und gesetzlicher Bestimmungen sowie (falls erforderlich) zur Verteidigung unserer Interessen und Ansprüche erheben und verwenden.
* **Dienstleistungen und Transaktionen** Wir können Ihre personenbezogenen Daten verwenden, um Dienstleistungen für Sie bereitzustellen oder von Ihnen angeforderte Transaktionen auszuführen. Hierzu zählen, ohne hierauf beschränkt zu sein, die Bereitstellung von Informationen zu Produkten oder Dienstleistungen des Unternehmens, die Sie erworben haben oder anderweitig verwenden, die Registrierung erworbener Produkte, die Verarbeitung von Produktbestellungen, die Bearbeitung von Garantieansprüchen, die Ersetzung von Produkthandbüchern, die Beantwortung von Kundendienstanfragen und die Unterstützung der Verwendung unserer Sites.
* **Verwaltung und Schutz unseres Geschäfts und unserer Sites**. Wir können Ihre personenbezogenen Daten verwenden, um unser Geschäft und unsere Sites zu verwalten und zu schützen, einschließlich Fehlerbehebung, Systemwartung, Support, Berichterstellung und Hosting von Daten.
* **Verbesserung unseres Geschäfts sowie unserer Sites, Produkte und Dienstleistungen**. Wir können Ihre personenbezogenen Daten zur Ausführung geschäftlicher Analysen oder zu anderen Zwecken verwenden, die uns helfen, die Qualität unseres Geschäfts, unserer Sites, unserer Produkte und Dienstleistungen (einschließlich neuer Produkte und Dienstleistungen) weiterzuentwickeln und zu verbessern, indem wir beispielsweise unsere Sites an Ihre spezifischen Präferenzen oder Interessen anpassen.
* **Marketing**. Soweit nach geltenden Gesetzen und Vorschriften zulässig, können wir Ihre personenbezogenen Daten verwenden, um Sie über Produkte oder Dienstleistungen zu informieren, die für Sie möglicherweise von Interesse sind, und um auf andere Weise mit Ihnen über Angebote, Veranstaltungen und Neuigkeiten, Umfragen, Sonderangebote und verwandte Themen zu kommunizieren. Sie können Marketingmitteilungen, die Sie per E-Mail erhalten, jederzeit kostenlos abbestellen, indem Sie auf den Link „Abbestellen“ klicken. Dieser Link ist in allen Marketing-E-Mails enthalten, die Sie von uns erhalten. Sie können sich auch über die in dieser Datenschutzerklärung enthaltenen Kontaktinformationen an uns wenden. Je nach Wohnsitzland können Sie sich auch von anderen Arten von Marketingmitteilungen abmelden. Bitte kontaktieren Sie uns unter Verwendung der in der Datenschutzerklärung aufgeführten Kontaktinformationen, um weitere Informationen zu erhalten. Einige Rechtsräume geben Einzelpersonen das Recht, bestimmte Informationen über unsere Offenlegung personenbezogener Daten gegenüber Dritten für Direktmarketingzwecke dieser Dritten anzufordern (dies gilt beispielsweise für die Einwohner von Kalifornien). Wenn Sie weitere Informationen über unsere Vorgehensweisen zur Offenlegung von Daten zu Marketingzwecken wünschen, kontaktieren Sie uns bitte unter Berücksichtigung der unten aufgeführten Anweisungen.
* **Interessenbezogene Werbung**. Wir erheben Daten über Ihre Online-Aktivitäten und ermitteln Ihre Interessen, damit wir Ihnen für Sie besonders relevante Werbung bereitstellen können. Sie können den Erhalt von interessenbezogener Werbung von Honeywell deaktivieren, wie in unserem [Hinweis zu Cookies](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#german) beschrieben.
* **Finanzielle Anreiz- und Treueprogramme**. Wir erheben und verwenden personenbezogene Daten, um unsere finanziellen Anreiz- und Treueprogramme zu verwalten und zu organisieren. Unter Verwendung der im Rahmen dieser Programme bereitgestellten personenbezogenen Daten bieten wir besondere Belohnungen, verfolgen den Status Ihres Programms und ermöglichen den Austausch von Programmpunkten gegen Produkte, Werbematerialien, Schulungsworkshops und mehr. Soweit gesetzlich zulässig, können wir personenbezogene Daten, die Sie im Rahmen eines finanziellen Anreizprogramms angeben, auch für andere in dieser Datenschutzerklärung dargelegte Zwecke verwenden. Bitte überprüfen Sie die Bedingungen für jedes finanzielle Anreizprogramm, für das Sie sich registrieren oder an dem Sie teilnehmen möchten, da diese Bedingungen stark auf das jeweilige Programm zugeschnitten sein können. Wenn Sie in die Teilnahme an diesen Programmen eingewilligt haben, können Sie diese Einwilligung jederzeit widerrufen, indem Sie uns über die Kontaktdaten am Ende dieser Datenschutzerklärung oder gemäß den Anweisungen in den Bedingungen des jeweiligen Programms kontaktieren.
* **Bewerbungen**. Im Zusammenhang mit einer Bewerbung oder Stellenanfrage können Sie uns Informationen über sich selbst zur Verfügung stellen, beispielsweise einen Lebenslauf, berufliche Referenzen, Informationen über Ihre Schulbildung und Ihren beruflichen Hintergrund sowie Informationen zu Ihrer Berufsausbildung und zu Zertifizierungen. Wir und die Mitglieder unserer Gruppe können diese Informationen zum Zwecke der Prüfung einer möglichen Beschäftigung, der Überprüfung Ihres Hintergrunds und Ihrer Eignung für eine Anstellung sowie zu anderen Zwecken verwenden, die in einer separaten Datenschutzerklärung oder einem anderen Hinweis in Verbindung mit Ihrer Bewerbung dargelegt sind. Wir können auf Dritte (beispielsweise Personalvermittler) oder Social-Media-Plattformen zurückgreifen, um Bewerbungen einzuholen, zu sammeln und einzubehalten. Weitere Informationen finden Sie in unserer [Datenschutzerklärung für Bewerber](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/applicant-privacy-notice#german).
* **Forschung und Analyse**. Wir können Ihre personenbezogenen Daten verwenden, um Studien und Analysen auszuführen, die uns helfen, Ihre Kaufpräferenzen zu analysieren, die Produkte und Dienstleistungen zu identifizieren, die Ihre Anforderungen am besten erfüllen, und die Effektivität der Werbung zu ermitteln, die wir Ihnen bereitstellen.
* **Durchsetzung**: Wir können die von uns erhobenen personenbezogenen Daten verwenden, um Betrugsfälle, Verletzungen von Rechten an geistigem Eigentum, Verstöße gegen unsere Geschäftsbedingungen, Verstöße gegen Gesetze oder andere missbräuchliche Verwendungen unserer Sites zu entdecken, zu verhindern und entsprechend zu reagieren.

Soweit gesetzlich zulässig, können wir die über unsere Sites erhobenen Informationen mit anderen Informationen kombinieren, die wir über Sie besitzen (beispielsweise Informationen zu Ihrer Verwendung unserer Produkte und Dienstleistungen), um Ihnen eine verbesserte und konsistente Kundenerfahrung zu bieten, wenn Sie mit uns interagieren, oder zu anderen, in dieser Datenschutzerklärung beschriebenen Zwecken.

**Rechtliche Grundlage für die Verarbeitung von Informationen**

Wenn gesetzlich vorgeschrieben, stellen wir sicher, dass es eine rechtliche Grundlage für die Verarbeitung Ihrer personenbezogenen Daten gibt. In den meisten Fällen ist unsere Rechtsgrundlage von den betreffenden personenbezogenen Daten und dem spezifischen Kontext abhängig, in dem wir die Daten erheben.

* **Vertrag**: Die Verarbeitung ist für die Dienstleistungen, die wir für Sie erbringen, oder für (auf Ihre Anfrage) zu ergreifende Maßnahmen vor und in Erwartung der Erbringung dieser Dienstleistungen erforderlich;
* **Gesetzliche Verpflichtungen**: Die Verarbeitung ist notwendig, um unsere gesetzlichen Verpflichtungen einzuhalten, einschließlich der Einhaltung geltender Gesetze und Vorschriften, der Erfüllung behördlicher und offizieller Auflagen, gerichtlicher Anordnungen oder Verfügungen;
* **Zustimmung**: Die Verarbeitung basiert auf Ihrer Zustimmung zur Verarbeitung Ihrer personenbezogenen Daten zu mindestens einem angegebenen Zweck (z. B. Marketing);
* **Legitime Interessen**: Die Verarbeitung ist notwendig, um unsere legitimen Interessen zu verfolgen, beispielsweise die Entwicklung und Verbesserung unserer Sites, Produkte und/oder Dienstleistungen zum Vorteil unserer Kunden; oder
* **Essenzielle Interessen**: Die Verarbeitung ist notwendig, um Ihre essenziellen Interessen zu schützen (z. B. aus Gesundheits- und Sicherheitsgründen, wenn Sie an einem Meeting an einem Honeywell-Standort teilnehmen).

Wenn Sie Fragen haben oder weitere Informationen zur Rechtsgrundlage benötigen, anhand derer wir Ihre personenbezogenen Daten erfassen und verwenden, senden Sie bitte eine E-Mail an [HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com)

**Anonymisierung von Informationen**

Gemäß geltendem Recht kann es sein, dass wir Ihre personenbezogenen Daten anonymisieren, sodass sie nicht mehr verwendet werden können, um Sie zu identifizieren. Anonymisierte Informationen gelten nicht als personenbezogene Daten und unterliegen daher nicht dieser Datenschutzerklärung. Wir können anonymisierte Informationen zu jedem Zweck erheben, verwenden, aggregieren und weitergeben.

**Dauer der Aufbewahrung von Informationen**

Der Zeitraum, über den wir Ihre personenbezogenen Daten speichern, ist vom Zweck der Verarbeitung abhängig. Personenbezogene Daten, die wir benötigen, um Ihnen Produkte und Dienstleistungen zur Verfügung zu stellen oder um Transaktionen zu ermöglichen, die Sie angefordert haben, speichern wir beispielsweise, solange Sie Kunde von Honeywell sind. Wenn Sie eine Bewerbung über unsere Sites einreichen, bewahren wir Informationen über Ihre Bewerbung wie in der Datenschutzerklärung, die Ihnen im Zusammenhang mit Ihrer Bewerbung zur Verfügung gestellt wurde, dargelegt oder wie anderweitig gesetzlich vorgeschrieben auf. In allen anderen Fällen speichern wir Ihre personenbezogenen Daten solange wie notwendig, um die in dieser Datenschutzerklärung beschriebenen Zwecke zu erfüllen. Anschließend werden sie entweder anonymisiert (soweit gesetzlich zulässig), gelöscht oder vernichtet.

**Offenlegung von Informationen**

Gemäß geltendem Gesetz geben wir Ihre personenbezogenen Daten möglicherweise an ausgewählte Dritte weiter, einschließlich der im Folgenden beschriebenen Dritten:

* **Unternehmen unserer Gruppe**. Möglicherweise geben wir Ihre personenbezogenen Daten an unsere Tochterunternehmen und Unternehmen der Gruppe weiter, wie angemessenerweise für die in dieser Datenschutzerklärung beschriebenen Zwecke notwendig.
* **Dienstanbieter**. Möglicherweise geben wir Ihre personenbezogenen Daten an Unternehmen weiter, die wir mit der Bereitstellung von Dienstleistungen in unserem Namen beauftragt haben, beispielsweise dem Hosten von Websites, der Durchführung von Umfragen, der Verarbeitung von Transaktionen, der Analyse unserer Sites und der Durchführung von Analysen zur Verbesserung der Qualität unseres Geschäfts, unserer Sites, Produkte und Dienstleistungen. Diese Dienstanbieter müssen die Vertraulichkeit Ihrer personenbezogenen Daten sicherstellen.
* **Vertriebspartner und andere vertrauenswürdige Geschäftspartner**. Möglicherweise geben wir Ihre personenbezogenen Daten an Dritte, die unsere Produkte vertreiben, und andere vertrauenswürdige Geschäftspartner weiter. Dies dient möglicherweise auch dem Zweck, dass diese Dritten Ihnen Marketingmitteilungen senden. Die Weitergabe personenbezogener Daten zu Marketingzwecken erfolgt gemäß geltenden Gesetzen und Vorschriften.
* **Offenlegung in Verbindung mit Transaktionen**. In Verbindung mit bestimmten Transaktionen kann es vorkommen, dass wir Ihre persönlichen Daten oder einen Teil davon Geldinstituten, Regierungsbehörden, Frachtunternehmen oder Postbehörden offenlegen, die an der Transaktionsabwicklung beteiligt sind.
* **Offenlegung von Informationen in Verbindung mit Akquisitionen oder Veräußerungen**. Es kann Situationen geben, in denen Honeywell aus strategischen oder anderen geschäftlichen Gründen beschließt, Unternehmen in einigen Ländern zu verkaufen, zu kaufen, zu veräußern, zu fusionieren oder anderweitig neu zu organisieren. Wir können Informationen, die wir über Sie aufbewahren, in dem Umfang offenlegen, der vernünftigerweise notwendig ist, um einen Zusammenschluss, eine Akquisition, eine Veräußerung oder einen Verkauf von Honeywell-Vermögen oder -Teilvermögen aushandeln und durchführen zu können.
* **Offenlegung von Informationen aus anderen Gründen**. Wir können personenbezogene Daten offenlegen, sofern dies im Rahmen von Gesetzesvorschriften bzw. im Vertrauen darauf erfolgt, dass diese Maßnahme aus einem der folgenden Gründe erforderlich ist: Einhaltung gesetzlicher Verpflichtungen oder Anordnungen, Schutz unserer Rechte und unseres Eigentums oder in dringenden Fällen Schutz der persönlichen Sicherheit einer Person.

**Internationale Datenübermittlungen**

Honeywell ist ein weltweit tätiges Unternehmen. Daher werden Ihre personenbezogenen Daten möglicherweise gemäß geltendem Recht an verschiedene Standorte weltweit – beispielsweise die USA, Mexiko und Indien – übermittelt und dort aufbewahrt, gespeichert oder verwendet. Das bedeutet, dass die von uns erhobenen personenbezogenen Daten möglicherweise in Ländern verarbeitet werden, deren Datenschutzgesetze sich von den Datenschutzgesetzen Ihres Landes unterscheiden. Honeywell wird jedoch stets angemessene Schritte unternehmen, um Ihre Privatsphäre zu schützen und einen Grad an Schutz für Ihre personenbezogene Daten zu bieten, der mit dem Grad an Schutz in Ihrem Wohnsitzland vergleichbar ist. Dies umfasst auch die Implementierung der Standardvertragsklauseln der Europäischen Kommission. Wenn Sie weitere Informationen über die geeigneten Sicherheitsvorkehrungen zum Schutz Ihrer personenbezogenen Daten wünschen, kontaktieren Sie uns bitte unter [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com).

**Sicherheit**

Wir sind bestrebt, die Sicherheit Ihrer personenbezogenen Daten zu schützen. Wir setzen technische und organisatorische Maßnahmen ein, um ein Sicherheitsniveau zu bieten, das dem mit der Verarbeitung Ihrer personenbezogenen Daten verbundenen Risiko angemessen ist. Wenn Sie weitere Informationen darüber wünschen, wie Honeywell Ihre personenbezogenen Daten schützt, kontaktieren Sie uns bitte unter [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com)

**Ihre Rechte**

Abhängig von den geltenden Gesetzen haben Sie möglicherweise bestimmte Rechte in Bezug auf Ihre personenbezogenen Daten.

* Sie haben möglicherweise das Recht, auf Ihre personenbezogenen Daten **zuzugreifen, diese zu korrigieren, zu aktualisieren** oder **ihre Löschung zu beantragen**.
* Sie können der Verarbeitung Ihrer personenbezogenen Daten **widersprechen**, uns auffordern, die Verarbeitung Ihrer personenbezogenen Daten **einzuschränken** oder die **Übertragbarkeit** Ihrer personenbezogenen Daten anfordern.
* Möglicherweise haben Sie ein Recht darauf, **dass keine Entscheidung über Sie getroffen wird, die ausschließlich auf einer automatisierten Verarbeitung basiert, einschließlich Profilierung,** wenn eine solche Entscheidung rechtliche Folgen für Sie hat oder Sie erheblich beeinträchtigt.
* Wenn wir Ihre personenbezogenen Daten mit Ihrer Zustimmung erfasst und verarbeitet haben, **können Sie Ihre Zustimmung jederzeit zurückziehen**. Die Zurückziehung Ihrer Zustimmung hat keinen Einfluss auf die Gesetzlichkeit einer Verarbeitung, die wir vor dieser Zurückziehung ausgeführt haben. Sie hat auch keinen Einfluss auf eine Verarbeitung Ihrer personenbezogenen Daten, die auf anderen gesetzlichen Grundlagen als Ihrer Zustimmung basiert.
* Sie haben möglicherweise das Recht, dem **Verkauf Ihrer personenbezogenen Daten zu widersprechen**. Honeywell verkauft Ihre personenbezogenen Daten nicht gewinnbringend an Dritte. Allerdings geben wir Ihre personenbezogenen Daten in Übereinstimmung mit dieser Datenschutzerklärung und unserem [Hinweis zu Cookies](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#german) an Dritte weiter oder legen sie anderweitig Dritten gegenüber offen. So beauftragen wir beispielsweise Drittanbieter, unsere Produkte zu vertreiben, Ihnen technische Unterstützung zu bieten, analytische Tools und Funktionen für die Website zu betreiben und unsere Produkte und Dienstleistungen zu vermarkten und zu verkaufen. Solche Aktivitäten können die Offenlegung Ihrer personenbezogenen Daten gegenüber Dritten beinhalten und gemäß bestimmten (jedoch nicht allen) Datenschutzgesetzen als „Verkauf“ von Daten angesehen werden.
* Sie haben das Recht, sich bei einer Datenschutzbehörde, die für die Überwachung der Einhaltung der Datenschutzgesetze in Ihrem Rechtsraum zuständig ist, über unsere Erhebung und Verwendung Ihrer personenbezogenen Daten zu **beschweren**, wenn Sie der Meinung sind, dass unsere Verarbeitung Ihrer personenbezogenen Daten nicht den Datenschutzgesetzen entspricht. Personen im EWR haben beispielsweise das Recht, bei der zuständigen Datenschutzbehörde eine Beschwerde einzureichen. Eine Liste dieser Datenschutzbehörden finden Sie unter folgendem Link: [https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/board/members\_en](https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/board/members_en). Wir würden es jedoch schätzen, wenn wir Gelegenheit erhielten, auf Ihre Bedenken zu reagieren. Bitte nehmen Sie daher im Fall einer Beschwerde Kontakt mit uns auf. Wir werden Einzelpersonen nicht diskriminieren, wenn sie ihre Datenschutzrechte ausüben.

Wir unterstützen Sie bei der Ausübung Ihrer Rechte entsprechend den geltenden Gesetzen. Doch auch wenn Ihre personenbezogenen Daten nicht durch ein Datenschutzgesetz geschützt sind und auch nicht anderweitig unter ein Datenschutzgesetz fallen, werden wir versuchen, Ihren Wünschen oder Anfragen in Bezug auf unsere Datenverarbeitung nachzukommen. Wenn Sie Fragen zu Ihren Rechten haben oder Ihre Rechte ausüben möchten, können Sie uns unter [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com) kontaktieren oder Datenschutzfragen über unser interaktives Webformular unter folgendem Link einreichen:

**Informationen von Kindern**

Unsere Sites richten sich nicht an Kinder unter sechzehn (16) Jahren und sollten von diesen nicht genutzt werden. Wir werden nicht wissentlich Informationen von solchen Personen erheben, verwenden oder verkaufen. Wenn Sie nach den Gesetzen Ihres Landes minderjährig sind, übermitteln Sie bitte keine personenbezogenen Daten über unsere Sites.

**Links zu anderen Websites**

Unsere Sites enthalten möglicherweise Links zu Websites, Produkten und Services Dritter. Wir sind für diese Websites, Produkte und Services, ihre Richtlinien und ihre Erfassungs- oder anderen Verarbeitungsaktivitäten in Bezug auf Ihre personenbezogenen Daten nicht haftbar oder verantwortlich. Die Verfahren dieser Dritten unterliegen ihren eigenen Datenschutzrichtlinien. Wir empfehlen Ihnen, sich über die Datenschutzrichtlinien dieser Dritten zu informieren.

**Kontakt**

Wenn Sie Fragen zu dieser Datenschutzerklärung oder zu unserer Verarbeitung Ihrer personenbezogenen Daten haben, eine Beschwerde einreichen möchten oder sich an unseren Datenschutzbeauftragten wenden möchten, nehmen Sie bitte unter Verwendung der folgenden Kontaktdaten Kontakt mit uns auf. Wir werden uns umgehend mit der von Ihnen vorgebrachten Angelegenheit auseinandersetzen und uns bemühen, eine zufriedenstellende Lösung zu finden.

Interaktives Webformular:  

E-Mail:  

Postanschrift:  
Honeywell Privacy  
4D5  
115 Tabor Road  
Morris Plains, NJ 07950

Gebührenfreie Rufnummer:  

**Änderungen dieser Datenschutzerklärung**

Wir können diese Datenschutzerklärung von Zeit zu Zeit aktualisieren. Wen wir dies tun, ändern wir das Datum für die letzte Aktualisierung oben in der Datenschutzerklärung und unternehmen alle weiteren möglicherweise gesetzlich vorgeschriebenen Schritte.

**Zuletzt aktualisiert am 11. Juni 2021**

Hungarian

**Utolsó módosítás: 2021. június 11.**

**Bevezetés**

A Honeywell International Inc. (a továbbiakban „**Honeywell**” vagy „**mi**”) adatkezelőként jár el azoknak az adatoknak az esetében, amelyeket akkor gyűjtünk, amikor Ön felkeresi vagy használja bármelyik webhelyünket, vagy amikor a jelen Adatvédelmi nyilatkozat hatálya alá eső termékeket, szolgáltatásokat és alkalmazásokat használ (együttesen: „**Webhelyeink**”). A jelen Adatvédelmi nyilatkozat ismerteti, hogyan gyűjtjük, osztjuk meg és használjuk fel a fent ismertetett módon gyűjtött személyes adatokat, és leírja, hogyan gyakorolhatja Ön az adatvédelemhez fűződő jogait.

Amikor kapcsolatba lépünk Önnel, további adatvédelmi tájékoztatókat is küldhetünk az egyes konkrét adatkezelési tevékenységekre vonatkozóan, vagy további választási lehetőségeket kínálhatunk a Honeywell által az Ön adatain az adott esetben végzett adatkezelési tevékenységek kapcsán.

Kattintson az alábbi hivatkozások egyikére a megtekinteni kívánt fejezet megnyitásához:

**Az általunk végzett adatgyűjtés**

* **Közvetlenül Öntől gyűjtött adatok**. A szolgáltatások biztosításához, valamint a kért tranzakciók végrehajtásához szükség esetén személyes adatokat kérünk Öntől. Emellett akkor is megadhat nekünk személyes adatokat, amikor Ön veszi fel velünk a kapcsolatot vagy valamilyen interakcióba lép velünk (például kommentet ír, érdeklődést vagy ügyfélszolgálati megkeresést küld be, esetleg felkeresi az oldalainkat), vagy felhasználói fiókot hoz létre Webhelyeink használatához. Ezeknek a személyes adatoknak a körébe az alábbiak tartoznak:
    * **Személyazonosító adatok,** például név, cím, vállalat/szervezet neve, e-mail-cím, telefon- és faxszám és postacím (utca, település, állam, irányítószám és/vagy ország);
    * **Regisztrációs adatok**, azaz a webhelyeink használatához szükséges fiók regisztrálása során megadott adatok, például felhasználónév és jelszó;
    * **Munkaerő-felvétellel kapcsolatos adatok,** ideértve a meghirdetett állásokkal vagy a beküldött érdeklődésekkel kapcsolatban megadott információkat (ezeket alább ismertetjük);
    * **Üzleti kapcsolattartási adatok,** például egy harmadik szervezet (például vállalkozás, cég, társaság, egyéni vállalkozás, nonprofit szervezet vagy kormányzati szerv) alkalmazottjaira, tulajdonosaira, igazgatóira, tisztségviselőire vagy alvállalkozóira vonatkozó információk,
    * **Marketing- és kommunikációs adatok,** ideértve a marketingpreferenciákat és a kiadványainkra vonatkozó előfizetéseket;
    * **Pénzügyi adatok,** például bankkártya- és egyéb számlaadatok a webhelyeinken elérhető termékek és szolgáltatások megvásárlásának elősegítése érdekében;
    * **Exportellenőrzési adatok,** például nemzetiség, állampolgárság és lakhely szerinti ország, amelyek segítségével meghatározhatjuk, hogy az exportellenőrzési rendeletek értelmében küldhetünk-e Önnek információkat bizonyos technológiákról;
    * **Tranzakciós adatok,** ideértve a termékeinkkel és a szolgáltatásainkkal kapcsolatos érdeklődések, megrendelések és az Önnek küldött, valamint az Öntől fogadott kifizetések részleteit, valamint a megrendelési előzményeket és a fizetési tranzakciók lebonyolításához szükséges információkat;
    * **Eseményregisztrációval kapcsolatos adatok,** többek között az e-regisztrációs űrlapok kitöltése során megadott adatok; és
    * **Az Ön visszajelzései,** beleértve a felméréseket, az ajánlásokat és más, a Webhelyeinkkel, valamint a termékeinkkel és szolgáltatásainkkal kapcsolatos általános visszajelzéseket.

Ha nem adja meg a kért adatokat, előfordulhat, hogy nem tudjuk Önnek biztosítani a kért szolgáltatást, vagy nem tudjuk teljesíteni tranzakcióit.

* **Az Önről automatikusan gyűjtött adatok**. Bizonyos információkat cookie-k és hasonló nyomkövető technológiák segítségével rögzítünk a Webhelyeinken tett látogatásáról. Ha Önnek joga van letiltani az ilyen adatgyűjtést, ezt a kérését minden esetben tiszteletben tartjuk. Az ilyen módon gyűjtött adatok közé a következők tartoznak:
    * **Használati adatok,** például azzal kapcsolatos adatok, hogy Ön hogyan használja a Webhelyeket, a megtekintett oldalak, az átvitt bájtok száma, a megnyitott hivatkozások, a megtekintett anyagok, a Webhely megnyitásának dátuma és időpontja, a webhely, amelyről a mi Webhelyünkre érkezett, valamint a Webhelyen végzett egyéb műveletek; és
    * **Technikai adatok,** például IP-cím, a böngésző típusa, valamint az operációs rendszer jellemzői és nyelve.

A Webhelyeinken használt cookie-król és más hasonló nyomkövető technológiákról a [Cookie-kkal kapcsolatos közleményben](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#hungarian) olvashat.

* **Földrajzi helyekkel kapcsolatos adatok**. Egyes Webhelyek esetén az Ön hozzájárulásával rögzíthetjük a mobileszköz pontos, valós idejű helyét (azaz az eszköz helyadatait). Ezeket az adatokat kizárólag arra használjuk fel, hogy lehetővé tegyük Önnek a Webhelyek használatát. Az általunk különböző szolgáltatások biztosításával megbízott partnerek is kizárólag ebből a célból dolgozzák fel ezeket az adatokat. A hozzájárulást a későbbiekben a mobileszköz helyadatokkal kapcsolatos beállításaiban módosíthatja.
* **Harmadik felektől gyűjtött adatok**. A hatályos törvények betartásával harmadik felektől, például közösségimédia-webhelyekről és -alkalmazásokból is gyűjthetünk adatokat Önről, amlyeket az Önről más forrásokból gyűjtött információkkal kombinálhatunk. Ezekat az adatokat Webhelyeink fejlesztésére és az Ön igényei szerinti személyre szabására, valamint a jelen Adatvédelmi nyilatkozatban meghatározott egyéb célokra használhatjuk fel. Emellett az Ön munkáltatójától vagy más harmadik felektől is gyűjthetünk üzleti kapcsolattartási adatokat Önről, amelyeket a szokásos üzleti tevékenységek és adminisztratív feladatok elvégzésére használunk fel.

**Az adatok felhasználása**

A Webhelyeinken keresztül, valamint a velünk való kapcsolatfelvétel során gyűjtött személyes adatokat többek között az alábbi célokra használhatjuk fel:

* **Üzleti kapcsolattartási adatok**. A Honeywell a kapcsolat felvétele vagy tranzakciók lebonyolítása céljából gyűjti össze és használja fel az üzleti kapcsolattartási adatokat. Ilyen tevékenység lehet például a termék vagy szolgáltatások biztosításával vagy fogadásával kapcsolatos átvilágítás. A Honeywell például összegyűjtheti és felhasználhatja az üzleti kapcsolattartási adatokat a megrendelések, a szerződések, a jótállások, a karbantartási tevékenységek és más, hasonló üzleti feladatkörök elvégzése és kezelése érdekében, hitelelemzési és behajtási célokra, saját belső megfelelőségi és jogi követelményeink teljesítése érdekében, valamint (szükség esetén) érdekeink és követeléseink védelmére.
* **Szolgáltatások és tranzakciók**. Személyes adatait felhasználhatjuk az Ön által kért szolgáltatások biztosítására és tranzakciók lebonyolítására, ideértve többek között a következőket: a megvásárolt vagy használt vállalati termékekkel és szolgáltatásokkal kapcsolatos tájékoztatás, megvásárolt termékek regisztrálása, megrendelések feldolgozása, jótállási igények kezelése, kézikönyvek cseréje, ügyfélszolgálati kérések megválaszolása és a Webhelyeink használatának elősegítése.
* **Üzleti tevékenységünk és Webhelyeink kezelése és védelme** Személyes adatait felhasználhatjuk üzleti tevékenységünk és Webhelyeink kezelésére és védelmére, ideértve többek között a hibaelhárítást, a rendszerkarbantartást, a támogatást, a jelentések készítését és az adatok hosztolását.
* **Üzleti tevékenységünk, Webhelyeink, termékeink és szolgáltatásaink fejlesztése**. Személyes adatait felhasználhatjuk üzleti elemzések készítéséhez, valamint üzleti tevékenységünk, Webhelyeink, termékeink és szolgáltatásaink minőségének fejlesztését szolgáló további célokra (az új termékeket és szolgáltatásokat is beleértve), például arra, hogy Webhelyeinket az Ön preferenciáinak és érdeklődési körének megfelelően személyre szabjuk.
* **Marketing**. A hatályos törvényeknek és rendeleteknek megfelelően személyes adatait felhasználhatjuk arra, hogy tájékoztassuk azokról a termékekről és szolgáltatásokról, amelyek érdekelhetik Önt, és más módokon is megkeressük Önt különböző ajánlatok, események, hírek, felmérések, különleges ajánlatok és más, hasonló témák kapcsán. Az e-mailben kapott marketingkommunikációs anyagokról bármikor díjmentesen leiratkozhat. Ehhez kattintson a tőlünk kapott e-marketing anyagokban található „Leiratkozás” hivatkozásra, vagy vegye fel velünk a kapcsolatot a jelen Adatvédelmi nyilatkozatban felsorolt elérhetőségek egyikén. A lakóhelye szerinti országtól függően előfordulhat, hogy más típusú marketingkommunikációs anyagokról is leiratkozhat; további információért vegye fel velünk a kapcsolatot a jelen Adatvédelmi nyilatkozatban felsorolt elérhetőségek egyikén. Egyes joghatóságok (például Kalifornia) lehetővé teszik, hogy polgáraik tájékoztatást kérjenek tőlünk arról, hogy milyen személyes adataikat adjuk át harmadik feleknek közvetlen üzletszerzési célokra. Ha szeretne többet tudni az adatok marketingcélú továbbítására vonatkozó gyakorlatunkról, vegye fel velünk a kapcsolatot az alábbiakban olvasható utasításokat követve.
* **Érdeklődésen alapuló hirdetések**. Adatokat gyűjtünk az interneten Ön által végzett tevékenységekről, és ezek alapján azonosítjuk az érdeklődési köreit, hogy így relevánsabb hirdetéseket tudjunk megjeleníteni Önnek. A Honeywell érdeklődésen alapuló hirdetéseiről a [Cookie-kkal kapcsolatos közleményben](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#hungarian) leírtak szerint iratkozhat le.
* **Pénzügyi ösztönzők és hűségprogramok**. Pénzügyi ösztönzőink és hűségprogramjaink működtetéséhez és kezeléséhez is személyes adatokat gyűjtünk és használunk fel. Az Ön által e programok kapcsán megadott személyes adatokat arra használjuk fel, hogy egyedi jutalmakat ajánljunk fel, nyomon kövessük a program státuszát, és lehetővé tegyük a programban szerzett pontok termékekre, promóciós anyagokra, képzésekre és másokra való beváltását. A jogszabályok által megengedett mértékben a pénzügyi ösztönzőprogramok keretében megadott személyes adatokat a jelen Adatvédelmi nyilatkozatban meghatározott egyéb célokra is felhasználhatjuk. Ha szeretne regisztrálni egy ilyen pénzügyi ösztönzőprogramra, vagy részt venni valamelyik programban, olvassa el a program feltételeit, mivel bizonyos esetekben ezek a feltételek kizárólag az adott programra vonatkozó információkat tartalmaznak. Ha vállalja, hogy részt vesz egy ilyen programban, bármikor visszavonhatja ezt a hozzájárulását. Ehhez lépjen kapcsolatba velünk a jelen Adatvédelmi nyilatkozat végén megadott elérhetőségeken keresztül, vagy kövesse az adott program feltételeiben meghatározott utasításokat.
* **Álláspályázatok**. Álláspályázata vagy hasonló megkeresése kapcsán is személyes adatokat adhat át nekünk, ilyen például az önéletrajza, a szakmai referenciái, a végzettségével és a szakmai hátterével, valamint a szakmai képzettségével és bizonyítványaival kapcsolatos információk. Mi és vállalatcsoportunk tagjai felhasználhatjuk ezeket az adatokat az állás betöltéséhez, a háttérellenőrzések elvégzéséhez és a munkavállalásra való alkalmasság ellenőrzéséhez, valamint a jelentkezése kapcsán rendelkezésre bocsátott külön adatvédelmi nyilatkozatban vagy más tájékoztatóban foglalt további célokra. Bizonyos esetben harmadik feleket (például állásközvetítő céget) vagy közösségimédia-platformokat is igénybe vehetünk az álláspályázatok bekéréséhez, összegyűjtéséhez és megőrzéséhez. További információkért olvassa el az [állásra jelentkezőkre vonatkozó adatvédelmi nyilatkozatunka](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/applicant-privacy-notice#hungarian)t.
* **Kutatás és elemzések**. Személyes adatait felhasználhatjuk különböző kutatások és elemzések elvégzésére, amelyek célja a vásárlási preferenciák vizsgálata, az Ön igényeinek leginkább megfelelő termékek és szolgáltatások megkeresése, valamint az Önnek megjelenített hirdetések hatékonyságának felmérése.
* **Végrehajtás**: Az Önről gyűjtött személyes adatokat felhasználhatjuk a csalások, a szerzői jogsértések, a törvénysértések, a felhasználási feltételeink megsértésének, valamint a Webhelyeink egyéb helytelen használatának észlelésére, megelőzésére és kezelésére.

Ha a jogszabályok megengedik, a Webhelyeinken gyűjtött információkat az Önről tárolt egyéb adatokkal (például a termékek és szolgáltatások használatával kapcsolatos adatokkal) kombinálva felhasználhatjuk a jelen Adatvédelmi nyilatkozatban meghatározott célokra és arra, hogy jobb és egységesebb ügyfélélményt biztosítsunk Önnek a velünk folytatott interakciók során.

**Az adatkezelés jogalapja**

Ha a jogszabályok előírják, gondoskodunk arról, hogy személyes adatai feldolgozásának megfelelő jogalapja legyen. A legtöbb esetben a hivatkozott jogalap az érintett személyes adatoktól és ezek begyűjtésének konkrét körülményeitől függ.

* **Szerződés**: az adatkezelés az általunk Önnek nyújtott szolgáltatások biztosításához szükséges, vagy ahhoz, hogy (az Ön kérésére) megtegyük az ilyen szolgáltatások teljesítését megelőzően szükséges lépéseket;
* **Jogi kötelezettség**: az adatok kezelésére jogi kötelezettségeinknek, többek között a hatályos törvényeknek, jogszabályoknak, kormányzati és ezzel egyenértékű kérelmeknek, bírósági rendeleteknek vagy idézéseknek való megfelelés érdekében van szükség;
* **Hozzájárulás**: az adatkezelés alapja, hogy Ön hozzájárult személyes adatai egy vagy több célra (például marketingcélokra) való kezeléséhez;
* **Jogos érdek**: az adatkezelésre jogos érdekből, például Webhelyeink, termékeink és/vagy szolgáltatásaink ügyfeleink érdekében történő fejlesztéséhez és javításához van szükség; vagy
* **Létfontosságú érdek**: az adatkezelés az Ön létfontosságú érdekeinek védelméhez szükséges (például egészségügyi és biztonsági okokból, ha Ön a Honeywell egyik telephelyén vesz részt egy megbeszélésen).

Ha bármilyen kérdése van, vagy további információra van szüksége a személyes adatok gyűjtésének és felhasználásának jogalapjáról, írjon nekünk a következő e-mail-címre: [HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com)

**Az adatok névtelenítése**

A hatályos jogszabályoknak megfelelően bizonyos esetekben anonimizáljuk személyes adatait, amelyek ezt követően nem lesznek alkalmasak az Ön azonosítására. A névtelenített adatok nem számítanak személyes adatoknak, azért ezekre a jelen Adatvédelmi nyilatkozat nem vonatkozik. Névtelen adatokat bármilyen célból gyűjthetünk, felhasználhatunk, összesíthetünk és megoszthatunk.

**Az adatok megőrzésének időtartama**

A személyes adatok megőrzésének időtartama a feldolgozás céljától függően eltérő lehet. Például az Ön által kért termékek és szolgáltatások biztosításához vagy a tranzakciók teljesítéséhez szükséges személyes adatokat mindaddig megőrizzük, amíg Ön a Honeywell ügyfele. Továbbá ha Ön a Webhelyeinken keresztül állásra jelentkezik nálunk, a jelentkezés kapcsán átadott adatvédelmi tájékoztatóban vagy a jogszabályokban előírtaknak megfelelően őrizzük meg a jelentkezéséhez kapcsolódó adatokat. A személyes adatokat minden más esetben a jelen Adatvédelmi nyilatkozatban meghatározott célok teljesítéséhez szükséges ideig őrizzük meg, amelyet követően az adatokat névtelenítjük (ha a hatályos jogszabályok ezt lehetővé teszik), töröljük vagy megsemmisítjük.

**Az adatok továbbítása**

A hatályos törvényeknek megfelelően személyes adatait bizonyos harmadik felekkel is megoszthatjuk. Ezeket a harmadik feleket az alábbiakban ismertetjük:

* **Vállalatcsoportunkhoz tartozó társaságok**. Személyes adatait a jelen Adatvédelmi nyilatkozatban meghatározott célokhoz szükséges mértékben megoszthatjuk társvállalatainkkal és a csoporthoz tartozó vállalatokkal.
* **Szolgáltatók**. Személyes adatait megoszthatjuk a megbízásunkból szerződéses alapon különböző szolgáltatásokat nyújtó vállalatokkal, amelyek például webhelyeinket üzemeltetik, felméréseket végeznek, tranzakciókat dolgoznak fel, elemzéseket végeznek Webhelyeinken, valamint üzleti tevékenységünk, Webhelyeink, termékeink és szolgáltatásaink minőségének javítását célzó elemzéseket végeznek. E szolgáltatók számára előírjuk, hogy minden esetben bizalmasan kezeljék az Ön személyes adatait.
* **Forgalmazók és más megbízható üzleti partnerek**. Személyes adatait megoszthatjuk a termékeinket forgalmazó harmadik felekkel és más megbízható üzleti partnerekkel, és többek között engedélyezhetjük az ilyen harmadik feleknek, hogy marketinganyagokat küldjenek Önnek. A személyes adatok marketingcélokból történő megosztása során mindig a hatályos törvényeknek és jogszabályoknak megfelelően járunk el.
* **Tranzakciókkal kapcsolatos adattovábbítás**. Bizonyos tranzakciók során pénzügyi intézményekkel, kormányzati szervekkel, valamint a tranzakciók végrehajtásában érintett szállítmányozási vállalatokkal és postai szolgáltatókkal is megoszthatjuk az Ön egyes személyes adatait vagy valamennyi személyes adatát.
* **Felvásárlással vagy vállalatrész eladásával kapcsolatos adattovábbítás**. Előfordulhat, hogy a Honeywell stratégiai vagy üzleti célokból úgy dönt, hogy bizonyos országokban elad, megvásárol, leválaszt, egybeolvaszt vagy más módon átszervez egyes alvállalatokat. Ebben az esetben a Honeywell-vállalat eszközeinek egy részének vagy egészének egybeeolvasztásával, felvásárlásával, leválasztásával vagy eladásával járó tevékenységekkel kapcsolatos tárgyalások lebonyolításához, valamint az ilyen tevékenységek elvégzéséhez szükséges mértékben megoszthatjuk az Önről tárolt adatokat.
* **Adattovábbítás más okból**. Személyes adatait abban az esetben is továbbíthatjuk, ha ezt a törvények előírják vagy lehetővé teszik, valamint ha jóhiszeműen úgy véljük, hogy az adatok továbbítására törvényi kötelezettségeknek vagy jogi eljárásban született döntésnek való megfelelés, jogaink vagy vagyonunk védelme, valamint sürgős esetekben egy személy biztonságának védelme érdekében van szükség.

**Nemzetközi adattovábbítás**

A Honeywell globális vállalat, ezért az Ön személyes adatait a hatályos jogszabályoknak megfelelően világszerte különböző helyszínekre, például az Amerikai Egyesült Államokba, Mexikóba és Indiába továbbíthatjuk, így az Ön adatait ezekben az országokban is tárolhatjuk és felhasználhatjuk. Tehát az Öntől gyűjtött személyes adatokat olyan országokban is kezelhetjük, amelyek adatvédelmi jogszabályai eltérhetnek az Ön országában hatályos törvényektől. A Honeywell minden észszerűen elvárható lépést megtesz az Ön magánéletének és személyes adatainak megóvása érdekében, valamint hogy az Ön lakóhelye szerinti országhoz hasonló szintű védelmet biztosítson adatainak. Ennek részeként az Európai Bizottság által jóváhagyott általános szerződési feltételeket is alkalmazunk. A személyes adatok védelmét szolgáló intézkedésekkel kapcsolatos további tájékoztatásért írjon nekünk a [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com) e-mail-címre.

**Biztonság**

Elkötelezettek vagyunk személyes adatai védelme mellett. Technikai és szervezési intézkedéseket vezettünk be annak érdekében, hogy az adatkezelésben rejlő kockázatokhoz mérten megfelelő szintű biztonságot érjünk el. Ha szeretne többet megtudni arról, hogyan védi a Honeywell az Ön személyes adatait, írjon nekünk a [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com) e-mail-címre.

**Az Ön jogai**

A hatályos jogszabályoktól függően Önt bizonyos jogok illethetik meg személyes adataival kapcsolatban.

* Például jogosult lehet arra, hogy **hozzáférjen személyes adataihoz, valamint helyesbítse és frissítse őket**, vagy kérelmezze a **törlésüket**.
* Emellett **tiltakozhat** személyes adatainak feldolgozása ellen, kérheti, hogy **korlátozzuk** személyes adatainak feldolgozását, valamint az adatok **hordozhatóságával** kapcsolatos kérelmet is küldhet nekünk.
* Emellett joga lehet ahhoz, **hogy ne hozzanak Önről kizárólag automatizált adatkezelésen, például profilalkotáson alapuló döntést,** ha ez a döntés joghatással bír Önre, vagy jelentős mértékben érinti Önt.
* Emellett ha személyes adatait az Ön hozzájárulása alapján gyűjtöttük össze és kezeljük, akkor **Ön bármikor visszavonhatja a hozzájárulását**. A hozzájárulás visszavonása nem érinti a korábban végzett adatkezelés jogszerűségét, valamint nem befolyásolja azokat az adatkezelési tevékenységeket, amelyeket nem az Ön hozzájárulása alapján, hanem más jogalappal végzünk.
* Jogában áll úgy dönteni, hogy **nem engedélyezi személyes adatainak értékesítését**. A Honeywell nem értékesíti az Ön személyes adatait harmadik feleknek nyereség céljából Az Ön személyes adatait azonban bizonyos, a jelen Adatvédelmi nyilatkozatban és a [Cookie-kkal kapcsolatos közleményben](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#hungarian) megadott esetekben megoszthatjuk harmadik felekkel, valamint harmadik feleknek továbbíthatjuk. Például harmadik felekkel együttműködve forgalmazzuk a termékeinket, műszaki segítséget nyújtunk Önnek, webhelyelemző eszközöket és funkciókat használunk, valamint különböző módszerekkel népszerűsítjük és értékesítjük termékeinket és szolgáltatásainkat. E tevékenységek során előfordulhat, hogy harmadik feleknek kell továbbítanunk az Ön személyes adatait, és egyes adatvédelmi törvények értelmében ez az adatok „értékesítésének” minősülhet.
* Önnek joga van **panaszt tenni** a joghatóságában hatályos adatvédelmi törvények betartásának felügyeletéért felelős adatvédelmi hatóságnál személyes adatainak gyűjtésével és felhasználásával kapcsolatban, ha úgy véli, hogy az adatkezelés során nem tartottuk be az adatvédelmi jogszabályokat. Az EGT területén élő magánszemélyek például panaszt tehetnek az illetékes adatvédelmi hatóságnál. E hatóságok listája a következő címen érhető el: [https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/board/members\_en](https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/board/members_en). Nagyra értékelnénk azonban, ha lehetőséget adna nekünk, hogy mi foglalkozzunk az aggályaival. Ha panasza merül fel, vegye fel velünk bátran a kapcsolatot! Nem alkalmazunk hátrányos megkülönböztetést az adatvédelmi jogaikat gyakorló magánszemélyekkel szemben.

Minden esetben lehetővé tesszük, hogy Ön élhessen a hatályos törvények értelmében fennálló jogaival. Bizonyos esetekben még akkor is megpróbálunk eleget tenni az Ön adatkezelési tevékenységeinkkel kapcsolatos kéréséinek, ha az Ön személyes adatait nem védik az adatvédelmi törvények, vagy nem tartoznak az adatvédelmi törvények hatálya alá. Ha kérdése merül fel a jogaival kapcsolatban, vagy szeretné gyakorolni a jogait, írjon nekünk a [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com) e-mail-címre, vagy küldje el adatvédelemmel kapcsolatos kérdéseit az alábbi hivatkozáson elérhető interaktív webes űrlapon keresztül:

**Gyermekek adatai**

Webhelyeink nem tizenhat (16) éven aluli gyermekek számára készültek, és tudatosan nem gyűjtünk és nem is használunk fel adatokat ilyen személyekről, és nem értékesítjük ilyen személyek adatait. Ha Ön az országa törvényei szerint kiskorúnak minősül, ne adjon meg személyes adatokat a Webhelyeinken keresztül.

**Más webhelyekre mutató hivatkozások**

Webhelyeink harmadik felek webhelyeire, termékeire és szolgáltatásaira mutató hivatkozásokat tartalmazhatnak. Az ilyen webhelyekért, termékekért és szolgáltatásokért, valamint az általuk végzett adatgyűjtésért és -kezelésért nem vállalunk felelősséget. Az ilyen harmadik felek gyakorlatait saját adatvédelmi szabályzataik határozzák meg. Javasoljuk, hogy tájékozódjon e harmadik felek adatvédelmi gyakorlatairól.

**Kapcsolatfelvétel**

Ha kérdése merül fel a jelen Adatvédelmi nyilatkozattal vagy személyes adatai kezelésével kapcsolatban, szeretne panaszt benyújtani, vagy kapcsolatba lépni adatvédelmi tisztségviselővel, keressen meg minket az alábbi elérhetőségek valamelyikén keresztül. A lehető leghamarabb válaszolunk kérdéseire, és arra törekszünk, hogy minden problémára kielégítő megoldást találjunk.

Interaktív webes űrlap:  

E-mail:  

Levelezési cím:  
Honeywell Privacy  
4D5  
115 Tabor Road  
Morris Plains, NJ 07950

Ingyenes hívható telefonszám:  

**A jelen Adatvédelmi nyilatkozat módosításai**

Időről időre módosíthatjuk a jelen Adatvédelmi nyilatkozatot. Az Adatvédelmi nyilatkozat módosítása esetén megváltoztatjuk az Adatvédelmi nyilatkozat tetején olvasható „utolsó módosítás” dátumát, és megtesszük a törvények által előírt további lépéseket.

**Utolsó módosítás: 2021. június 11.**

Italian

**Ultimo aggiornamento in data: 11 giugno 2021**

**Introduzione**

Honeywell International Inc. (“**Honeywell**”, “**nostro**”, “**noi**”, o “**ci**”), è il "titolare del trattamento" dei dati personali che acquisiamo sugli utenti quando visitano o utilizzano i nostri siti web o i prodotti, i servizi e le applicazioni collegati alla presente Informativa sulla privacy (collettivamente, i nostri “**siti**”). La presente Informativa sulla privacy illustra le modalità con cui acquisiamo, condividiamo e utilizziamo i dati personali ottenuti in questo modo e come è possibile esercitare i propri diritti di tutela della privacy.

Quando interagiamo con gli utenti, possiamo anche fornire loro ulteriori informazioni sulla privacy in merito a specifiche attività di trattamento o offrir loro ulteriori alternative sul modo in cui Honeywell tratta i loro dati personali in un determinato momento.

Fare clic su uno dei collegamenti di seguito per andare direttamente alla sezione di interesse:

**Acquisizione dei dati**

* **Informazioni ottenute direttamente dall'utente**. È possibile che siano richiesti dati personali per fornire il servizio o effettuare la transazione che l'utente ha specificato. L'utente può inoltre fornire alcuni dati personali quando contatta o si rivolge a noi (per esempio, quando invia un commento, un quesito o una richiesta di assistenza cliente, visitatori del sito) o creare un account per utilizzare i nostri siti. Tali dati personali possono includere:
    * **Dati identificativi,** come il nome, il titolo, la ragione sociale dell'azienda/organizzazione, l'indirizzo e-mail, i numeri di telefono e l'indirizzo postale (inclusi via, città, provincia, codice postale e/o paese);
    * **Dati di registrazione,** forniti dall'utente al momento della creazione di un account per poter accedere ai nostri siti, inclusi nomi utente e password;
    * **Dati di selezione,** incluse le informazioni fornite in relazione a una candidatura o richiesta di lavoro (come di seguito illustrato);
    * **Dati di contatti aziendali,** come informazioni relative ad altri dipendenti, proprietari, dirigenti, funzionari o fornitori di organizzazioni terze (per esempio, aziende, società, partnership, imprese individuali, no-profit o agenzie governative).
    * **Dati relativi al marketing e alle comunicazioni,** compresi le preferenze di marketing e gli abbonamenti alle nostre pubblicazioni;
    * **Informazioni finanziarie,** incluse le informazioni relative alle carte di credito o ad altri conti finanziari al fine di agevolare l'acquisto da parte dell'utente di prodotti e servizi Honeywell disponibili sui nostri siti;
    * **Informazioni sul controllo delle esportazioni,** come la nazionalità, la cittadinanza e il paese di residenza, che ci consentono di determinare se l'utente è idoneo a ricevere informazioni relative a determinate tecnologie in base alle normative sul controllo delle esportazioni;
    * **Dati sulle transazioni,** compresi richieste e ordini per i nostri prodotti e servizi e i dettagli dei pagamenti da e verso l'utente, compresa la cronologia degli ordini di acquisto e le informazioni necessarie per agevolare le transazioni di pagamento;
    * **Informazioni relative alla registrazione a eventi,** inclusi i dati forniti dall'utente durante la compilazione di moduli di registrazione online; e
    * **Feedback dell'utente,** inclusi sondaggi, raccomandazioni o altri feedback ricevuti dagli utenti in merito ai nostri siti e ai nostri prodotti e servizi in generale.

Nel caso in cui l'utente non fornisca le informazioni previste, potremmo non essere in grado di fornire il servizio richiesto o di completare la transazione.

* **Informazioni che acquisiamo automaticamente sui nostri utenti**. Raccogliamo alcune informazioni sulle visite ai nostri siti utilizzando cookie e tecnologie di tracciamento assimilabili. Rispetteremo in ogni caso qualsiasi diritto legale che l'utente possa vantare per impedirci di farlo. I dati in tal modo acquisiti includono:
    * **Dati di utilizzo,** incluse le informazioni relative all'utilizzo dei nostri siti da parte dall'utente, tra cui le pagine visualizzate, il numero di byte trasferiti, i collegamenti aperti, il materiale consultato, la data e l'ora di accesso al sito, il sito dal quale l'utente è stato rimandato a uno dei nostri siti e ulteriori azioni intraprese nei siti Honeywell; e
    * **Dati tecnici,** come l'indirizzo IP (Internet Protocol) dell'utente, il tipo di browser utilizzato, le funzionalità e la lingua, nonché il sistema operativo in uso.

Per informazioni sui cookie e altre tecnologie di tracciamento assimilabili che utilizziamo sui nostri siti, si rimanda alla nostra [Informativa sui cookie](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#italian).

* **Informazioni di geo-localizzazione**. Per alcuni siti, previo consenso dell'utente, potremmo acquisire la posizione precisa e in tempo reale (ovvero, la geolocalizzazione) del suo dispositivo mobile. Queste informazioni saranno utilizzate solo per agevolare l'uso dei siti da parte degli utenti, compresi i nostri fornitori di servizi che possono elaborare tali dati in relazione alla fornitura di servizi per nostro conto. Se si decide di autorizzare questa operazione, l'utente può adeguare il proprio consenso gestendo le preferenze dei Servizi di localizzazione attraverso le impostazioni del dispositivo mobile.
* **Informazioni acquisite da terze parti**. In conformità con la legge applicabile, possiamo acquisire dati personali sugli utenti tramite terze parti, come siti web e applicazioni di social media, e associarli con le informazioni già in nostro possesso, al fine di migliorare e personalizzare i nostri siti in base alle preferenze degli utenti e per altri scopi indicati nella presente Informativa sulla privacy. Possiamo inoltre acquisire informazioni di contatto aziendali dal datore di lavoro o da altre terze parti per favorire o altrimenti intraprendere attività commerciali tradizionali e questioni amministrative di tipo analogo.

**Utilizzo delle informazioni**

Le informazioni personali acquisite da Honeywell attraverso i nostri siti o quando l'utente ci contatta possono essere utilizzate per i seguenti scopi:

* **Dati di contatto aziendali**. Honeywell acquisisce e utilizza i dati di contatto aziendali per effettuare comunicazioni o transazioni, anche per condurre attività di due diligence, o fornire o ricevere, un prodotto o un servizio. Per esempio, Honeywell può acquisire e utilizzare questi dati di contatto aziendali per agevolare e gestire ordini, contratti, garanzie, interventi di manutenzione e funzioni aziendali analoghe, per finalità di analisi e riscossione dei crediti, per contribuire alla nostra conformità interna e soddisfare i requisiti legali e (se necessario) per difendere i nostri interessi e diritti.
* **Servizi e transazioni**. Ci riserviamo il diritto di utilizzare le informazioni personali per offrire servizi o effettuare transazioni richieste dall'utente, come per esempio la fornitura di informazioni su prodotti e servizi Honeywell acquistati o altrimenti utilizzati dall'utente, la registrazione dei prodotti acquistati, il monitoraggio degli ordini di prodotti, la gestione delle richieste di garanzia, la sostituzione di manuali dei prodotti, le risposte alle richieste effettuate al servizio clienti, l'assistenza nell'utilizzo dei nostri siti web e così via.
* **Amministrazione e tutela della nostra attività e dei nostri siti**. Ci riserviamo il diritto di utilizzare i dati personali dell'utente allo scopo di gestire e proteggere l'azienda e i nostri siti, incluse la risoluzione dei problemi, la manutenzione del sistema, l'assistenza, la segnalazione e la conservazione di dati.
* **Miglioramento di attività, siti, prodotti e servizi**. Ci riserviamo il diritto di utilizzare i dati personali dell'utente per eseguire business analysis o per altri scopi che ci consentano di sviluppare e migliorare la qualità dell'attività aziendale, dei nostri siti e dei prodotti e servizi offerti (inclusi i nuovi prodotti e servizi), ad esempio, personalizzando i siti in base alle preferenze e agli interessi specifici dell'utente.
* **Marketing**. In accordo con le leggi e le normative applicabili, ci riserviamo il diritto di utilizzare i dati personali dell'utente per informarlo di prodotti o servizi a cui l'utente potrebbe essere interessato e per comunicazioni di altro genere in relazione a promozioni, eventi e novità, sondaggi, offerte speciali e temi correlati. L'utente ha il diritto di revocare il consenso alla ricezione di comunicazioni di marketing via e-mail in qualsiasi momento, gratuitamente, mediante il link "annulla iscrizione" presente in tutte le e-mail contenenti materiale di marketing ricevute da Honeywell o contattandoci attraverso le informazioni di contatto contenute nella presente Informativa sulla privacy. In base al paese di residenza, l'utente può scegliere di annullare la ricezione anche di altri tipi di comunicazioni di marketing; per ulteriori informazioni, è possibile contattarci utilizzando le informazioni riportate nella presente Informativa sulla privacy. Alcune giurisdizioni forniscono ai singoli (per esempio, i residenti in California) il diritto di richiedere specifiche informazioni riguardanti la nostra divulgazione di dati personali a terzi per scopi di marketing diretto degli stessi. Per ricevere maggiori informazioni sulle nostre pratiche di divulgazione dei dati per scopi di marketing, è possibile contattarci secondo le istruzioni elencate di seguito.
* **Pubblicità basata sugli interessi dell'utente**. Acquisiamo dati sulle attività online degli utenti e identifichiamo i loro interessi in modo da poter offrire la pubblicità per loro più rilevante. È possibile disattivare le comunicazioni pubblicitarie basate sugli interessi degli utenti inviate da Honeywell, come descritto nella nostra [Informativa sui cookie](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#italian).
* **Programmi di incentivazione finanziaria e di fidelizzazione**. Acquisiamo e utilizziamo i dati personali per mantenere e amministrare i nostri programmi di incentivazione finanziaria e di fidelizzazione. Utilizziamo i dati personali comunicati dall'utente in questi programmi per offrire premi unici, monitorare lo stato del programma e agevolare lo scambio di punti del programma per prodotti, materiali promozionali, laboratori di formazione e altri articoli. Nei limiti consentiti dalla legge, possiamo anche utilizzare qualsiasi dato personale da voi fornito nel contesto di un programma di incentivi finanziari per qualsiasi altro scopo indicato nella presente Informativa sulla privacy. Si raccomanda di esaminare i termini e le condizioni di ciascun programma di incentivi finanziari a cui si desidera registrarsi o partecipare, in quanto tali termini e condizioni possono essere strettamente adattati al programma specifico. Qualora l'utente dia il proprio consenso a partecipare a tali programmi, può revocare tale consenso in qualsiasi momento contattandoci attraverso i dettagli di contatto riportati in calce alla presente Informativa sulla privacy o in conformità con le istruzioni stabilite nei termini e nelle condizioni del programma specifico.
* **Domande d'impiego.** In relazione a una domanda o richiesta di impiego, l'utente può fornirci informazioni su di sé, come per esempio il curriculum vitae, le referenze professionali, le informazioni relative ai titoli di studio e al background lavorativo, le informazioni relative alla formazione professionale e alle certificazioni. Noi e i membri del nostro gruppo possiamo utilizzare tali informazioni allo scopo di prendere in considerazione la possibilità di assunzione, verificarne la veridicità e l'idoneità per l'impiego specifico, e come altrimenti indicato in qualsiasi dichiarazione separata sulla privacy o altro avviso reso disponibile in relazione alla candidatura dell'utente. È possibile utilizzare una terza parte (ad esempio, Recruiter di processo) o la piattaforma dei social media per sollecitare, raccogliere e conservare le domande d'impiego. Per maggiori informazioni, raccomandiamo di prendere visioni della nostra [Informativa sulla privacy dei candidati](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/applicant-privacy-notice#italian).
* **Ricerca e analisi**. Ci riserviamo il diritto di utilizzare le informazioni personali dell'utente per condurre ricerche e analisi sulle sue preferenze di acquisto, individuare i prodotti e i servizi che meglio rispondono alle sue esigenze e misurare l'efficacia dell'offerta pubblicitaria.
* **Applicazione**: Ci riserviamo il diritto di utilizzare i dati personali che raccogliamo per rilevare, prevenire e rispondere a frodi, violazioni della proprietà intellettuale, violazioni dei nostri termini e condizioni, violazioni di leggi o altri usi impropri dei nostri siti.

Ove previsto dalla legge, ci riserviamo il diritto di integrare le informazioni raccolte attraverso i nostri siti con le informazioni relative all'utente già in nostro possesso (come informazioni relative all'utilizzo dei nostri prodotti e servizi) per poter offrire all'utente un'esperienza di livello più elevato durante l'interazione con Honeywell e per altre finalità disposte nella presente Informativa sulla privacy.

**Fondamento giuridico alla base del trattamento dei dati**

Ove previsto dalla legge, garantiremo all'utente una base giuridica per il trattamento dei dati personali. Nella maggior parte dei casi la nostra base giuridica dipenderà dai dati personali trattati e dal contesto specifico di acquisizione.

* **Contratto**: il trattamento è necessario per l'esecuzione dei servizi che forniamo all'utente, o per prendere provvedimenti (su richiesta dell'utente) prima e in previsione dell'esecuzione di tali servizi;
* **Obbligo legale**: il trattamento dei dati è necessario per ottemperare ai nostri obblighi di legge, inclusa la conformità alle leggi e alle normative applicabili, alle richieste di enti governativi e parastatali nonché a ordinanze e citazioni giudiziarie;
* **Consenso**: il trattamento dei dati si basa sul consenso prestato dall'utente al trattamento dei dati personali per uno o più scopi specifici (es. marketing);
* **Interessi legittimi**: il trattamento dei dati è necessario per soddisfare i nostri legittimi interessi, come sviluppare e migliorare i siti Honeywell nonché prodotti e/o servizi offerti a beneficio dei nostri clienti ; o
* **Interessi vitali**: il trattamento è necessario per proteggere gli interessi vitali dell'utente (per esempio, motivi di salute e sicurezza se si partecipa a una riunione in una sede Honeywell).

In caso di domande o necessità di ulteriori informazioni sulla base giuridica su cui raccogliamo e utilizziamo i dati personali, inviate un'e-mail all'indirizzo [HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com)

**Trasformazione in forma anonima dei dati**

Conformemente alla legislazione applicabile, siamo autorizzati a rendere anonimi i dati personali dell'utente affinché non possano più essere utilizzati per identificarlo. I dati resi anonimi non si classificano più come dati personali, pertanto non sono soggetti alla presente Informativa sulla privacy. Ci riserviamo il diritto di acquisire, utilizzare, aggregare e condividere dati in forma anonima per qualsiasi scopo.

**Durata della conservazione dei dati**

Il periodo durante il quale i dati personali dell'utente vengono conservati varia in base allo scopo per cui vengono trattati. Per esempio, conserviamo i dati personali necessari per fornire prodotti e servizi, o per agevolare le transazioni richieste, per tutto il tempo in cui l'utente è cliente di Honeywell o se presenta una domanda di assunzione tramite i nostri siti, conserviamo i dettagli della sua domanda come indicato nell'informativa sulla privacy messa a disposizione dell'utente in relazione alla sua candidatura o come altrimenti previsto a norma di legge. In tutti gli altri casi, Honeywell conserva i dati personali dell'utente per il tempo necessario ad adempiere alle finalità descritte nella presente Informativa sulla privacy. Al termine di tale periodo, i dati saranno resi anonimi (ove consentito dalla legislazione applicabile), eliminati o distrutti.

**Divulgazione dei dati**

Conformemente alla legislazione applicabile, siamo autorizzati a condividere i dati personali dell'utente con terzi selezionati, incluso quanto riportato di seguito:

* **Società del gruppo**. Siamo, inoltre, autorizzati a condividere i dati personali dell'utente con le nostre affiliate e con le società del gruppo Honeywell per le finalità descritte nella presente Informativa sulla privacy.
* **Fornitori di servizi**. Siamo autorizzati a condividere i dati personali dell'utente con le aziende che forniscono servizi per nostro conto, quali hosting di siti web, conduzione di sondaggi, elaborazione delle transazioni, analisi dei nostri siti e conduzione di analisi per migliorare la qualità dell'attività aziendale, dei nostri siti e dei prodotti e servizi offerti. Honeywell richiede a tali fornitori di servizi di tutelare la confidenzialità dei dati personali dell'utente.
* **Distributori e altri partner commerciali di fiducia**. Siamo autorizzati a condividere i dati personali dell'utente con i terzi incaricati della distribuzione dei nostri prodotti e con altri partner commerciali di fiducia per finalità che includono l'invio, da parte di tali terzi, di comunicazioni di marketing all'utente. Tale condivisione dei dati personali dell'utente per scopi di marketing verrà realizzata in conformità alle leggi e alle normative applicabili.
* **Divulgazione correlata alle transazioni**. In relazione a determinate transazioni, possiamo divulgare in parte o interamente i dati personali dell'utente a istituzioni finanziarie, enti governativi e società di spedizione o servizi postali coinvolti nell'adempimento della transazione.
* **Divulgazione in relazione ad acquisizioni o cessioni**. Possono verificarsi circostanze in cui, per ragioni strategiche o per altre ragioni commerciali, Honeywell decide di vendere, acquistare, cedere, fondere o riorganizzare diversamente le attività in alcuni paesi. Honeywell può divulgare i dati dell'utente che essa conserva nella misura necessaria e opportuna a continuare la trattativa o a completare una fusione, un'acquisizione, una cessione o una vendita di tutte le attività di Honeywell o di una loro parte.
* **Divulgazione per altre ragioni**. Ci riserviamo il diritto di divulgare dati personali se richiesto o consentito dalla legge o in caso di buona fede che tale procedura sia necessaria per rispondere a obblighi o procedure di legge, per proteggere e difendere i nostri diritti o proprietà o, in casi urgenti, per difendere la sicurezza personale di un individuo.

**Trasferimenti internazionali**

Honeywell è un'organizzazione globale e i dati personali degli utenti possono essere trasferiti, conservati, memorizzati o utilizzati in varie località del mondo, come gli Stati Uniti, il Messico e l'India, in conformità alle leggi vigenti. Ciò significa che, quando raccogliamo i vostri dati personali, questi possono essere trattati in paesi che possono avere leggi sulla protezione dei dati diverse da quelle del vostro paese. Tuttavia, Honeywell adotterà sempre le misure necessarie per tutelare la tua privacy e per fornire un livello di protezione dei dati personali paragonabile a quello del tuo paese di residenza, il che include l'attuazione delle clausole contrattuali tipo della Commissione europea. Per maggiori informazioni sulle misure di sicurezza appropriate in atto a protezione dei dati personali, contattateci all'indirizzo [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com).

**Sicurezza**

Abbiamo come priorità la tutela della sicurezza dei dati personali. Utilizziamo misure tecniche e organizzative per fornire un livello di sicurezza adeguato al rischio di trattamento dei dati personali. Per maggiori informazioni sulle modalità adottate da Honeywell a tutela dei dati personali, contattateci all'indirizzo [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com)

**Diritti dell'utente**

A seconda della legge applicabile, l'utente può esercitare alcuni diritti in relazione ai propri dati personali.

* Può avere il diritto di **accedere, correggere, aggiornare** o **richiedere la cancellazione** dei propri dati personali.
* Può **opporsi** al trattamento dei propri dati personali, chiederci di **limitare** il trattamento dei propri dati personali o richiederne la **portabilità**.
* Ha il diritto **di non accettare che sia presa una decisione su di lui basata esclusivamente sull'elaborazione automatizzata, compresa la profilazione,** se tale decisione produce effetti giuridici sulla sua persona o la colpisce in modo significativo.
* Allo stesso modo, se abbiamo raccolto ed elaborato i dati personali con il suo consenso, l'utente può **ritirare il proprio consenso in qualsiasi momento**. La revoca del consenso non influirà sulla liceità di qualsiasi trattamento eseguito prima della revoca, né influenzerà il trattamento dei dati personali condotto facendo affidamento su criteri di liceità del trattamento diversi dal consenso.
* L'utente ha il diritto di **opporsi alla vendita dei propri dati personal**i. Honeywell si impegna a non vendere a terzi i dati personali degli utenti a scopo di lucro. Tuttavia, condividiamo o divulghiamo in altro modo i dati personali degli utenti a terze parti in conformità con la presente Informativa sulla privacy e la nostra [Informativa sui cookie](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#italian). Per esempio, ci avvaliamo di società terze per distribuire i nostri prodotti, fornire assistenza tecnica, gestire strumenti e funzioni di analisi del sito web e svolgere attività di marketing e vendita dei nostri prodotti e servizi. Tali attività possono comportare la divulgazione dei dati personali a terzi e possono essere considerate una "vendita" di dati secondo alcune (ma non tutte) le leggi in materia di tutela dei dati.
* L'utente ha il diritto di **presentare reclamo** all'autorità preposta alla tutela dei dati personali, responsabile del controllo del rispetto della legge sulla sicurezza dei dati nella propria giurisdizione, in merito alla nostra acquisizione e all'utilizzo dei propri dati personali, qualora ritenga che il trattamento dei dati personali non sia conforme alla legge sulla loro tutela. Per esempio, gli individui residenti nel SEE hanno il diritto di presentare reclamo all'autorità competente per la protezione dei dati; l'elenco è consultabile all'indirizzo: [https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/board/members\_en](https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/board/members_en). Tuttavia saremmo lieti di avere la possibilità di risolvere direttamente eventuali dubbi, pertanto invitiamo gli utenti a contattarci in relazione a qualsiasi motivo di insoddisfazione. Non opereremo alcuna discriminazione nei confronti degli individui che esercitano i loro diritti in materia di privacy.

Contribuiremo ad agevolare l'esercizio dei diritti dell'utente in conformità con la legge vigente. Tuttavia, anche se i vostri dati personali non sono protetti da una legge sulla tutela dei dati, o altrimenti soggetti a tale legge, possiamo cercare di soddisfare qualsiasi richiesta o istanza che possiate avanzare in merito alle nostre attività di trattamento dei dati. Per domande sui propri diritti o per esercitare i propri diritti, è possibile contattarci all'indirizzo [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com) o inviare domande sulla privacy tramite il nostro modulo web interattivo disponibile al seguente link:

**Informazioni sui minori**

I nostri siti non sono destinati a, e non dovrebbero essere utilizzati da, soggetti di età inferiore ai sedici (16) anni, né noi acquisiamo, utilizziamo o vendiamo intenzionalmente informazioni su tali soggetti. Se sei un minore come inteso dalle leggi del tuo paese, ti preghiamo di non inviare nessun dato personale attraverso i nostri siti.

**Collegamenti ad altri siti web**

I nostri siti potrebbero contenere collegamenti a siti web, prodotti e servizi di terze parti. Honeywell declina ogni responsabilità relativa a tali siti web, prodotti e servizi e alla relative politiche o modalità di acquisizione e trattamento dei dati personali dell'utente. Le prassi di tali terze parti sono disciplinate dalle proprie politiche sulla privacy. Invitiamo l'utente a informarsi riguardo alle politiche in materia di privacy adottate da tali terzi.

**Contattateci**

Se avete domande sulla presente Informativa sulla privacy o sulla gestione dei vostri dati personali, se desiderate presentare un reclamo o se volete contattare il nostro Responsabile della protezione dei dati, contattateci utilizzando le informazioni di contatto elencate di seguito. Esamineremo sollecitamente il vostro problema e cercheremo di raggiungere una risoluzione soddisfacente.

Modulo web interattivo:  

E-mail:  

Indirizzo postale:  
Privacy Honeywell  
4D5  
115 Tabor Road  
Morris Plains, NJ 07950

Numero verde gratuito:  

**Modifiche alla presente Informativa sulla Privacy**

Ci riserviamo il diritto di aggiornare periodicamente la presente Informativa sulla privacy. In tal caso, modificheremo la data dell'"ultimo aggiornamento" all'inizio dell'Informativa sulla privacy e adotteremo eventuali ulteriori misure secondo quanto disposto dalla legge.

**Ultimo aggiornamento in data: 11 giugno 2021**

Japanese

**最終更新日：2024年4月29日**

**はじめに**

Honeywell International Inc.（「**ハネウェル**」、「**我々**」、「**弊社**」、あるいは「**当社**」）は、お客様が本個人情報保護方針にリンクされている当社のWebサイト（以下、総称して当社「**サイト**」）にアクセスしたとき、または製品、サービスおよびアプリケーションを使用したときに当社がお客様について収集する個人情報の「データ管理者」です。本個人情報保護方針では、当社がこのようにして収集したお客様の個人情報を収集、共有、使用する方法、およびお客様がプライバシーの権利を行使する方法について説明しています。

当社がお客様とやり取りする場合、当社は、特定の処理活動に関する追加のプライバシー通知をお客様に提供するか、またはハネウェルが特定の時点でお客様の個人情報を処理する方法について追加の選択肢を提供する場合があります。  

 関心のあるセクションに移動するには、以下の該当するリンクをクリックしてください。

**当社による情報の収集**

* **お客様から直接収集された情報**。 当社はサービスを提供するため、またはお客様から要求された取引を実行するために、個人情報の提供をお願いする場合があります。また、お客様は、(コメント、お問い合わせ、カスタマー サポート要求、サイト訪問などを通じて) 当社に連絡するか当社とやり取りをする際に当社に個人情報を提供したり、当社サイトを利用するためにアカウントに登録したりすることもできます。この個人情報には以下が含まれます。
    * **身元データ。** お客様の名前、役職、会社/組織名、電子メール アドレス、電話番号、ファックス番号、住所（番地、市、州、郵便番号、国を含む）など。      
    * **登録データ、**お客様が当社サイトを利用するためにアカウントに登録する際に提供する情報（ユーザー名とパスワードを含む）など。  
        
    * **採用データ** 。 求職またはお問い合わせに関連して提出された情報（以下に記載）を含みます。 
    * **業務連絡先データ**。第三者組織（企業、会社、パートナーシップ、個人事業主、非営利団体、政府機関など）の他の従業員、所有者、取締役、役員または請負業者に関連する情報など。
    * **生体認証データ**。健康、安全、セキュリティスクリーニングおよびその他の管理機能のための顔認識スキャンなど。
    * **マーケティングおよびコミュニケーションデータ。** お客様のマーケティングの好みや当社の発行物へのサブスクリプションを含みます。  
        
    * **財務情報。** 当社サイトで利用可能な当社の製品およびサービスの購入処理を円滑に進めることができるようにするための、クレジットカードまたはその他の金融口座の情報を含みます。  
        
    * **輸出管理情報。** 国籍、市民権、居住国など。これにより、当社はお客様が輸出管理規制の下で特定の技術に関する情報を受け取る資格を有しているかどうかを判断できます。  
        
    * **取引データ。** 当社の製品およびサービスに関するお問い合わせと注文、ならびにお客様との間の支払いの詳細（発注履歴、支払い取引の円滑化に必要な情報など）を含みます。   
        
    * **イベント登録情報。** お客様が電子登録フォームに記入するときに提供する情報を含みます。  
        
    * **お客様からのフィードバック。** 当社サイトならびに当社の製品およびサービス全般に関する、お客様からのアンケート回答、推奨事項またはその他のフィードバックを含みます。

お客様が要求された情報を提供されない場合、当社は要求されたサービスを提供したり、取引を完了したりできないことがあります。

* **当社がお客様に関して自動的に収集する情報**。 当社は、クッキーおよび類似の追跡技術を使用して、当社サイトへのお客様の訪問に関する特定の情報を収集します。当社は、お客様が有し得る、当社のこの行為を阻止する法的権利を常に尊重します。この方法で収集されるデータには以下が含まれます。
    * **利用状況データ。** お客様が当社サイトをどのように利用しているか、表示したページ、転送バイト数、クリックしたリンク、アクセスした資料、当社サイトへのアクセス日時、いずれかの当社サイトへのリンク元のWebサイト、および当社サイト内で行われたその他のアクションに関する情報を含みます。  
        
    * **技術データ。** インターネット プロトコル (IP) アドレス、ブラウザーの種類と機能、言語、オペレーティング システムなど。

当社サイトで当社が使用するクッキーおよびその他の類似の追跡技術については、当社の[クッキーに関する通知](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice)を参照してください。

* **位置情報**。特定の当社サイトでは、お客様から同意を得たうえで、ハンディデバイスの正確なリアルタイムの位置 (つまり、地理的位置) を収集する場合があります。この情報は、お客様による本サイトの利用を促進する目的でのみ使用し、当社に代わってサービスを提供することに関連してこの情報を処理する可能性のある当社のサービスプロバイダーによる場合もあります。同意された場合は、ハンディデバイスの設定を通じて位置情報サービスの設定を管理することで、この同意を調整できます。
* **第三者から収集された情報**。当社は、適用法に従い、ソーシャルメディアの Webサイトとアプリケーションなどの第三者からお客様に関する個人情報を収集し、この情報を当社が既に保有している情報と組合せ、お客様の好みに合わせて当社サイトを改善およびカスタマイズし、または本個人情報保護方針に記載されているその他の目的を果たします。また、お客様の雇用主またはその他の第三者から業務連絡先情報を収集する場合があり、これにより従来のビジネス活動や同様の管理事項を円滑に進める、またはその他の方法で実施します。

**当社による情報の使用**

当社は、当社サイトを通じて収集された個人情報、またはお客様が以下のような目的で当社に連絡された際に収集された個人情報を使用する場合があります。

* **業務連絡先データ**。ハネウェルは、製品もしくはサービスに関するデューデリジェンスの実施、または製品やサービスの提供もしくは受領を含め、連絡または取引を行うために、業務連絡先データを収集および使用します。たとえば、ハネウェルは、注文、契約、保証、保守および同様の職務を円滑に進めたり管理したりするため、信用分析および収集を実施するため、当社内のコンプライアンスおよび法的要件を支援するため、ならびに（必要に応じて）当社の利益と主張を防御するために、この業務連絡先データを収集および使用することがあります。
* **サービスおよび取引。** 当社は、お客様にサービスを提供したり、お客様から要求された取引（お客様が購入または利用した当社の製品またはサービスに関する情報の提供、購入した製品の登録、製品の注文処理、保証請求への対応、製品マニュアルの交換、カスタマー サービス要求への回答、当社サイトの利用の円滑化を含むがこれらに限定されない）を実行したりするために、お客様の個人情報を使用することがあります。
* **当社のビジネスと当社サイトの管理および保護。** 当社は、当社のビジネスと当社サイトを管理および保護（トラブルシューティング、システム メンテナンス、サポート、レポート、データのホスティングを含む）するために、お客様の個人情報を使用することがあります。
* **当社サイト、当社のビジネス、製品およびサービスの改善。** 当社は、ビジネス分析を実行するため、または当社サイト、当社のビジネス、製品およびサービス（新しい製品およびサービスを含む）を開発し、その品質を改善するのに役立つその他の目的（当社サイトをお客様の特定の好みまたは関心に合わせてカスタマイズする、など）のために、お客様の個人情報を使用することがあります。
* **マーケティング。** 当社は、適用される法律および規制に従って、お客様が関心を持ちそうな製品またはサービスをお客様に通知するため、ならびにその他の方法でサービス、イベントやニュース、アンケート、特別オファーおよび関連トピックについてお客様にお知らせするため、お客様の個人情報を使用することがあります。お客様は、当社から受け取った電子メールの宣伝用資料の「登録解除」リンクを使用するか、本個人情報保護方針に記載されている連絡先情報を使用して当社に連絡することにより、いつでも無料で電子メールで送信されるマーケティング コミュニケーションをオプトアウトできます。居住国によっては、他の種類のマーケティング コミュニケーションをオプトアウトすることもできます。詳細については、個人情報保護方針に記載されている連絡先情報を使用して当社までお問い合わせください。一部の法域では、個人 (カリフォルニア州居住者など) に、第三者のダイレクト マーケティング目的で当社が個人情報を第三者に開示することに関して特定の情報を要求する権利が付与されています。マーケティング目的でのデータ開示に関する慣行の詳細については、下記の指示に従って当社までお問い合わせください。
* **興味関心連動型広告。**当社は、お客様に最も関連性の高い広告を提供できるよう、お客様のオンライン活動に関するデータを収集してお客様の関心を特定します。お客様は、当社の[クッキーに関する通知](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice)で定めるとおり、ハネウェルからの興味関心連動型広告の配信をオプトアウトすることができます。
* **報奨金およびロイヤルティ プログラム**。当社は、報奨金およびロイヤルティ プログラムを維持および管理するために、個人情報を収集して使用します。これらのプログラムにおいて、お客様から提供された個人情報を使用して、独自の報酬を提供したり、プログラムのステータスを追跡したり、製品、販売促進資料、トレーニングワークショップなどに対するプログラムポイントの交換を円滑に進めたりします。法律により認められる範囲で、当社は、本個人情報保護方針に記載されている他の目的のために、報奨金プログラムに関連してお客様から提供される個人情報を使用する場合もあります。登録または参加を希望する各報奨金プログラムの利用規約は、該当するプログラムに合わせて細かく調整されている場合があるため、確認するようお願いいたします。お客様は、これらのプログラムへの参加に同意された場合、本個人情報保護方針の最後にある連絡先の詳細を使用して、または該当するプログラムの利用規約に記載されている指示に従って、いつでもその同意を撤回することができます。
* **求職。** お客様は、求職やそのお問い合わせに関連して、履歴書、推薦状、学歴や職歴に関する情報、職業訓練や認定に関する情報など、自身に関する情報を当社に提供する場合があります。当社とそのグループ会社は、雇用の検討、経歴調査および雇用資格を目的として、別途の個人情報保護方針または求職に関連して提供されるその他の通知に記載されているように、この情報を使用することがあります。当社は、求職を勧誘、募集、および雇用申込書を保持するために、第三者 (職業紹介事業者など) またはソーシャルメディアプラットフォームを使用する場合があります。詳細については、[応募者のプライバシーに関する通知](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/applicant-privacy-notice)をお読みください。
* **研究および分析。** 当社は、お客様の購入傾向の分析、お客様のニーズに最適な製品やサービスの特定、およびお客様に提供する広告の効果測定に役立てるため、お客様の個人情報を使用して調査および分析を行うことがあります。
* **執行：** 当社は、詐欺、知的財産権の侵害、当社の利用規約の違反、法律の違反、または当社サイトのその他の誤用を検出、防止し、それらに対応するために、収集した個人情報を使用することがあります。

法律で認められている場合、当社は、お客様とのやり取りの際に、または本個人情報保護方針に記載されているその他の目的で、顧客体験を改善して一貫したものを提供するために、当社サイトを通じて収集した情報と、お客様に関して保持している他の情報 (当社の製品やサービスの利用に関する情報など) を組み合わせることがあります。

**当社が情報を処理する法的根拠**

法律で求められている場合、当社は、お客様の個人情報を処理する法的根拠があることを保証します。ほとんどの場合、当社の法的根拠は、当該個人情報と、それを収集する特定の状況により異なります。

* **契約：**処理は、当社がお客様に提供するサービスの実施のために、またはそうしたサービスの実施前に、その実施を見込んで (お客様の要求に応じて) 措置を講じるために必要です。
* **法的義務：**処理は、適用される法律、規制、政府および準政府の要求、裁判所命令または召喚状の遵守を含め、当社の法的義務を遵守するために必要です。
* **同意：**処理は、1 つ以上の特定の目的 (マーケティングなど) での個人情報の処理に対するお客様の同意に基づいています。
* **正当な利益：**処理は、当社の顧客の利益のために当社サイト、製品やサービスを開発および改善するなど、当社の正当な利益を満たすために必要です。
* **重大な利益：**処理は、お客様の重大な利益を保護するために必要です（例えば、ハネウェルの事業所での会議に出席する場合、安全衛生上の理由）。

当社がお客様の個人情報を収集および使用する法的根拠についてご質問がある場合、または詳細情報が必要な場合は、[HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com)までEメールでお問い合わせください。

**情報の匿名化**

適用法に従って、当社はお客様の個人情報を匿名化し、お客様の識別に使用できないようにする場合があります。匿名化された情報は個人情報とはみなされないため、本個人情報保護方針の対象ではありません。当社は、目的を問わず匿名化された情報を収集、使用、集約および共有することがあります。

**当社が情報を保持する期間**

当社がお客様の個人情報を保存する期間は、処理の目的によって異なります。例えば、当社は、お客様がハネウェルの顧客である限り、またはお客様が当社サイトを通して求人応募の申請を提出している限り、製品やサービスの提供または要請された取引を円滑に進めるために必要な個人情報を保存します。当社はお客様の申請に関連して、お客様が利用できるプライバシー通知に記載されているとおり、または法律で義務付けられているとおり、お客様による申請の詳細を保持します。その他すべての場合、当社は、このプライバシーに関する声明に記載されている目的を達成するために必要な場合に限り、お客様の個人情報を保存し、その目的の達成後、匿名化 (適用される法律で認められている場合)、削除または破棄します。

**情報の開示。**

当社は、下記を含め、適用される法律に従って、一部の第三者とお客様の個人情報を共有する場合があります。

* **当社のグループ会社**。本個人情報保護方針に記載されている目的のために合理的に必要な場合、当社はお客様の個人情報を当社の関連会社およびグループ会社と共有することがあります。
* **サービスプロバイダー。** 当社は、Webサイトのホスティング、アンケートの実施、取引の処理、当社サイトの分析、当社サイト、当社のビジネス、製品およびサービスの品質改善を目的とした分析の実施など、当社に代わってサービスを提供する契約を結んでいる企業とお客様の個人情報を共有する場合があります。当社は、これらのサービスプロバイダーに、お客様の個人情報の機密を保護するよう求めます。
* **販売代理店およびその他の信頼できるビジネスパートナー**。当社は、当社の製品を販売する第三者およびその他の信頼できるビジネスパートナーと、マーケティングコミュニケーションをお客様に送信することを当該第三者に許可するなどの目的で、お客様の個人情報を共有する場合があります。このようなマーケティング目的での個人情報の共有は、適用される法律および規制に従って行われます。
* **取引に関連する開示**。当社は、特定の取引に関連して、お客様の個人情報の一部またはすべてを、取引の履行に関係する金融機関、政府機関、および輸送会社または郵便サービス業者に開示する場合があります。
* **買収または売却に関連する開示**。戦略的またはその他のビジネス上の理由により、ハネウェルが一部の国で事業を売却、買収、処分、合併またはその他の方法で再編成することを決定した場合、開示が必要な状況が発生する場合があります。当社は、ハネウェルの資産の全部または一部の合併、買収、処分または売却の交渉または履行を進めるために合理的に必要な範囲で、お客様に関して保持している情報を開示することがあります。
* **他の理由による開示**。当社は、法律で求められているか認められている場合、または法的要件や当社に適用される法的手続きを遵守するため、当社の権利や財産を保護および防御するため、もしくは緊急事態において個人の安全を守るために、かかる行為が必要であるという誠実な信念を有している場合、個人情報を開示することがあります。

**国際的な転送**

ハネウェルはグローバルな組織であり、お客様の個人情報は、適用法に従って、米国、メキシコ、インド、その他の国など、世界中のさまざまな場所にて転送、保持、保存、または使用される場合があります。これにより、当社があなたの個人情報を収集すると、お客様の国の法律とは異なるデータ保護法がある国で処理される場合があります。ただし、ハネウェルは、お客様のプライバシーを保護し、お客様の居住国に相当する程度の個人情報保護を提供するために、合理的な措置を講じます。お客様の個人情報を保護するための適切な保護対策の詳細については、[Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com)までお問い合わせください。

**生体認証データに関する方針（イリノイ州居住者のみ）**

ハネウェルは、健康、安全、セキュリティ、その他の管理機能のために生体認証データを収集および使用する場合があります。例えば、当社施設でのウェルネスおよび健康のスクリーニングの実施、時間管理プログラムの実施、ハネウェルのコンピュータおよびその他の技術リソースに関する認証およびアクセス制御の実施、生体認証対応機能を備えたビデオ監視などのセキュリティ対策の実施などです。本個人情報保護方針にこれと異なる規定があっても、該当する個人と当社との間の最後のやり取りから1年以内に生体認証データを保持することがハネウェル方針です。ただし、当社は、適用される法律、または管轄権を有する裁判所が発行した有効な令状、召喚状、または命令を遵守するため、またはハネウェルが法的請求を確立、行使、または防御するために、許可されている、または別途要求されている場合、同じことを満たすために必要な最小限の期間、かかる生体認証データを保持することを条件に、この保持期間を超えてかかる生体認証データを保持する場合があります。ハネウェルは、その機密性を意図的に損なわない方法で、生体認証データを永久に破棄または廃棄するための商業的に合理的なプロトコルを導入し、維持しています。なお、本項は、ハネウェル従業員、請負業者、または臨時雇用者に関する生体認証データまたはその他の個人データの処理に関連するハネウェルの社内方針、手順、または記録の機密性を破棄するものではなく、また破棄することを意図するものでもありません。本項は、米国イリノイ州に居住し、ハネウェルに生体認証データを提供する個人にのみ適用されます。

**ワシントン在住者の場合**

あなたの個人データの処理およびプライバシー権に関する追加情報については[、ワシントン州消費者健康データプライバシー方針](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/washington-consumer-health-data-privacy-policy)をお読みください。 

**セキュリティ**

当社は個人情報のセキュリティ保護に努めています。当社は、個人情報を処理するリスクに適切なレベルのセキュリティを提供するために、技術的および組織的な措置を講じています。 ハネウェルの個人情保護の方法の詳細については、[Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com)までお問い合わせください。

**お客様の権利**

適用法によっては、個人情報に関する特定の権利があなたに付与される場合があります。

* あなたはご自身の個人情報に対し**アクセス、コピーの要求、修正、更新**または**削除の要求**をする権利を有します。
* お客様は、ご自身の個人情報の処理に**異議**を唱えること、個人情報の処理を**制限**するよう当社に依頼したり、個人情報の**ポータビリティ**を要求したりすることができます。
* 意思決定があなたに法的影響を与える場合、またはあなたに重大な影響を与える場合、**あなたについての説明を求める権利およびプロファイリングを含め、自動処理のみに基づいた意思決定を受け入れない**権利を有します。
* 同様に、当社がお客様の同意を得てお客様の個人情報を収集および処理した場合、**お客様はいつでも同意を撤回することができます**。同意の撤回は、撤回前に当社が行った処理の合法性に影響せず、同意以外の合法的な処理根拠に従って行われた個人情報の処理にも影響しません。
* お客様は、**お客様の個人情報の販売をオプトアウト**する権利を有します。ハネウェルは、お客様の個人情報を営利目的で第三者に販売することはありません。ただし、本個人情報保護方針と当社の[クッキーに関する通知](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice)に従って、お客様の個人情報を第三者と共有またはその他の方法で第三者に開示します。たとえば、当社は第三者と連携して当社の製品を販売したり、お客様に技術支援を提供したり、Webサイトの分析ツールと機能を運用したり、当社の製品とサービスのマーケティングと販売に従事したりします。こうした活動は、お客様の個人情報の第三者への開示が伴う場合があり、特定の (ただし、すべてではない) データ保護に関する法律の下でデータの「販売」とみなされる場合があります。
* お客様は、当社によるお客様の個人情報の処理がデータ保護法に準拠していないと考える場合、お客様の法域におけるデータ保護法の遵守について監督責任を負うデータ保護機関に、当社によるお客様の個人情報の収集および使用について**苦情を申し立てる**権利を有します。たとえば、EEAの個人には、管轄のデータ保護当局に苦情を申し立てる権利があります。データ保護当局のリストについては、[https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/board/members\_en](https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/board/members_en) を参照してください。 ただし、当社にお客様の懸念に対処する機会をいただければ幸いです。苦情がございましたら、お気軽に当社までお問い合わせください。 当社は、データプライバシー権を行使したことによって個人を差別することはありません。

当社は、適用される法律に従って、お客様に適用される権利が円滑に行使されるようにします。ただし、お客様の個人情報がデータ保護に関する法律に基づいて保護されていない場合、またはその他データ保護に関する法律の対象となっていない場合でも、当社のデータ処理活動に関するお客様からの要求やお問い合わせに対応するよう努めることがあります。ご自身の権利について質問がある場合、または権利の行使を希望される場合は、[Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com)までご連絡いただくか、以下のリンクにあるインタラクティブなWebフォームからプライバシーに関する質問を提出できます。  

**子供の情報**

当社サイトは、16歳未満の子供を対象としておらず、かかる子供が使用すべきではありません。当社は、かかる個人からそうと知りながら情報を収集、使用、販売することはありません。居住国の法律により未成年とみなされる方は、当社サイトを通じて個人情報を送信しないでください。

**他のWebサイトへのリンク**

当社サイトには、第三者のWebサイト、製品およびサービスへのリンクが含まれている場合があります。これらの Webサイト、製品およびサービス、当該Webサイトのポリシー、またはお客様の個人情報の収集もしくはその他の処理について、当社は一切責任を負いません。これらの第三者の慣行には、それぞれのプライバシーに関する方針適用されます。これらの第三者のプライバシーに関する方針を確認することをお勧めします。

**お問い合わせ**

本個人情報保護方針またはお客様の個人情報の取り扱いに関して質問がある場合、苦情を申し立てる場合、または当社にデータ保護責任者に問い合わせる場合は、下記の連絡先情報を使用して当社までお問い合わせください。当社は、お客様の懸念に速やかに対応し、満足する解決策に到達するよう努めます。 

インタラクティブなWebフォーム:   
  
Eメールアドレス：   
  
住所:   
ハネウェルのプライバシー   
4D5   
115 Tabor Road   
Morris Plains, NJ 07950  
  
米国内フリーダイヤル番号：   

**本個人情報保護方針の変更**

当社は、折に触れて本個人情報保護方針を更新する場合があります。その際、個人情報保護方針の冒頭にある「最終更新日」を変更し、法律で求められる場合は該当する追加措置を講じます。

**最終更新日：2024年4月29日**

Korean

**최종 개정일: 2021년 6월 11일**

**소개**

Honeywell International Inc.(“**Honeywell**”, “**당사**”, “**당사의**”, 또는 “**당사를**”)는 이용자가 당사 웹사이트 중 하나를 방문 또는 이용하거나, 본 개인정보 보호 정책에 연결되어 있는 제품, 서비스 및 애플리케이션(총칭 당사의 “사이트”)을 사용하는 경우 이용자에 관해 당사가 수집하는 개인 정보에 대한 "데이터 관리자"입니다. 본 개인정보 보호 정책에서는 당사가 이러한 방법으로 이용자의 개인 정보를 어떻게 수집, 공유 및 사용하며, 이용자는 어떻게 본인의 개인정보 보호 권리를 행사할 수 있는지에 대해 설명합니다.

당사는 이용자와 상호작용할 때 이용자에게 구체적인 처리 활동에 관한 추가적인 개인정보 보호 고지를 제공하거나, 특정 시점에 Honeywell이 이용자의 개인 정보를 처리하는 방법에 관해 추가적인 선택권을 제시합니다.

원하는 섹션으로 이동하려면 아래 링크 중 하나를 클릭하십시오.

**당사의 정보 수집**

* **이용자로부터 직접 수집하는 정보**. 당사는 이용자가 요청한 서비스를 제공하거나 트랜잭션을 수행하기 위해 개인 정보를 요청할 수 있습니다. 또한 이용자가 당사에 문의 또는 소통(예: 의견 제시, 문의, 고객 지원 요청, 사이트 방문자 등)하는 경우 또는 당사 사이트에서 계정을 등록할 때에도 당사에 개인 정보를 제공하게 될 수 있습니다. 이러한 개인 정보에는 다음 정보가 포함될 수 있습니다.
    * **신분 데이터,** 예를 들어 본인 이름, 직책, 회사/조직명, 이메일 주소, 전화번호 및 우편 주소(국가, 우편번호, 주/도, 시 및/또는 도로명 포함) 등.
    * **등록 데이터,** 사용자 이름과 암호를 포함해 이용자가 당사 사이트 이용을 위해 계정을 등록할 때 입력하는 정보.
    * **채용 데이터,** 입사 지원서 또는 문의와 관련해 제출하는 정보 포함(아래 설명 참조).
    * **업무상 연락처 데이터,** 다른 직원, 오너, 이사, 임원 또는 외부 조직(예: 기업, 회사, 파트너십, 자영업자, 비영리 또는 정부 기관)의 하청업체 등과 관련한 정보 등.
    * **마케팅 및 커뮤니케이션 데이터,** 이용자의 마케팅 설정 선택 및 당사 간행물에 대한 이용자의 구독 정보 포함.
    * **금융 정보,** 당사가 당사 사이트에서 판매될 수 있는 당사 제품 및 서비스에 대한 이용자 구매를 원활하게 진행하고자 하는 목적으로 수집하는 신용 카드 및 기타 금융 기관 계좌 정보 포함.
    * **수출 통제 정보,** 이용자의 국적, 시민권 및 거주 국가 등, 당사가 수출 통제 규정에 따라 특정 기술에 관한 정보를 받을 수 있는 이용자 적격성 여부를 판단하는 데 필요한 정보.
    * **트랜잭션 데이터,** 당사 제품 및 서비스에 관한 정보 및 주문 관련 문의, 이용자에 대한 대금 지급 및 이용자의 대금 결제에 관한 상세 정보(구매 주문 이력 및 결제 트랜잭션을 원활하게 진행하는 데 필요한 정보 포함) 포함.
    * **이벤트 등록 정보,** 이용자가 온라인 등록 양식을 작성하는 과정에서 입력하는 정보 포함. 그리고,
    * **이용자 피드백,** 당사 사이트 및 전반적으로 당사 제품과 서비스에 관한 이용자의 설문조사 응답, 추천 및 기타 피드백.

이용자가 요청하는 정보를 제공하지 않는 경우 당사는 요청 대상 서비스를 제공하거나 해당 트랜잭션을 완료하지 못할 수 있습니다.

* **당사가 이용자에 관해 자동으로 수집하는 정보**. 당사는 쿠키 및 유사 추적 기술을 사용해 이용자의 당사 사이트 방문에 관한 특정 정보를 수집합니다. 당사는 이러한 당사의 수집을 막을 수 있는 이용자의 법적 권리를 항상 존중할 것입니다. 이러한 방식으로 수집되는 데이터는 다음과 같습니다.
    * **사용 데이터,** 당사 사이트 사용 방법에 대한 정보를 포함하여 조회한 페이지, 전송된 바이트 수, 클릭한 링크, 액세스한 자료, 사이트에 액세스한 날짜 및 시간, 당사 사이트로 오기 위해 경유한 웹 사이트 및 해당 사이트 내에서 수행한 기타 작업 등. 그리고,
    * **기술 데이터,** 인터넷 프로토콜(IP) 주소, 브라우저 유형, 용량, 언어 및 운영 체제 등.

당사가 당사 사이트에서 사용하는 쿠키 및 기타 유사 추적 기술에 관한 정보는 당사의 [쿠키 고지](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#korean)를 참조하시기 바랍니다.

* **지리적 위치 정보**. 특정 사이트의 경우, 당사는 이용자의 동의 하에 이용자가 사용하는 모바일 기기의 정밀한 실시간 위치 정보(즉, 지리적 위치 정보)를 수집할 수 있습니다. 이러한 정보는 당사를 대신한 서비스 제공과 관련해 이러한 정보를 처리할 수 있는 당사 서비스 제공자에 의한 것을 포함해 이용자의 당사 사이트 이용을 원활하기 하는 목적에 한해 사용됩니다. 동의한 경우 이용자는 모바일 기기의 설정을 통해 본인의 위치 서비스(Location Service) 설정 선택을 이용해 이러한 동의를 변경할 수 있습니다.
* **제3자로부터 수집되는 정보**. 당사는 관련 법률에 따라, 당사 사이트를 이용자의 선호도에 맞게 개선 및 맞춤화 하거나 본 개인정보 보호 정책에서 정하는 기타 목적을 위해 소셜 미디어 웹사이트 및 애플리케이션 등 제3자로부터 이용자에 대한 개인 정보를 수집해 당사가 이미 보유하고 있는 정보와 결합할 수 있습니다. 당사는 또한 이용자의 직장 또는 그 외 제3자로부터 이용자의 업무상 연락 정보를 수집하거나 그 외에 기존 방식의 비즈니스 활동 및 유사 행정관리 업무를 진행할 수 있습니다.

**당사의 정보 사용**

당사는 당사 사이트에서, 또는 이용자가 다음과 같은 목적으로 당사에 문의할 때 수집된 개인 정보를 사용할 수 있습니다.

* **업무상 연락처 데이터**. Honeywell은 제품 또는 서비스와 관련한 실사를 실시하거나 제품 또는 서비스를 제공 또는 수령하는 것을 포함해 커뮤니케이션이나 트랜잭션을 실행하기 위해 업무상 연락처 데이터를 수집해 사용합니다. 예를 들어, Honeywell은 주문, 계약, 보증, 유지보수 및 유사한 업무상 기능을 실행 및 관리하기 위해, 신용 분석 및 수집 목적으로, 당사의 내부적 준수 및 법적 요건을 지원하기 위해, 그리고 (필요한 경우) 당사의 이해 관계 및 주장을 변호하기 위해 이러한 업무상 연락처 데이터를 수집 및 사용할 수 있습니다.
* **서비스 및 트랜잭션**.당사는 이용자의 개인 정보를 사용하여 서비스를 제공하거나 이용자가 요청한 트랜잭션을 수행합니다. 여기에는 이용자가 구입하거나 달리 사용하는 회사 제품이나 서비스에 대한 정보 제공, 구입한 제품 등록, 제품 주문 처리, 보증 클레임 처리, 제품 설명서 교체, 고객 서비스 요청 답변, 사이트 이용 활성화 등이 포함되나 이에 국한되지 않습니다.
* **당사 비즈니스 및 사이트 관리 및 보호**. 당사는 문제 해결, 시스템 유지 보수, 지원, 보고 및 데이터 호스팅과 같이 당사 비즈니스 및 사이트를 관리하고 보호하기 위해 이용자의 개인 정보를 사용할 수 있습니다.
* **당사 비즈니스, 사이트, 제품 및 서비스 개선**. 당사는 당사 사이트를 사용자의 특정한 기본 설정이나 관심사에 맞게 맞춤 설정함으로써 비즈니스 분석을 수행하거나, 비즈니스, 사이트, 제품 및 서비스(신제품이나 신규 서비스 포함)의 질을 개선하기 위한 기타 목적으로 이용자의 개인 정보를 사용할 수 있습니다.
* **마케팅**. 당사는 관련법 및 규정에 따라 이용자의 개인 정보를 사용하여 이용자가 관심을 가질 만한 제품 또는 서비스를 알리고, 제품, 이벤트 및 뉴스, 설문 조사, 특별 제안 및 관련 주제에 관해 이용자와 소통할 수 있습니다. 이용자는 당사에서 제공하는 이메일 마케팅 자료의 "수신 거부" 링크를 사용하거나 본 개인정보 보호 정책에 나와 있는 연락처 정보로 당사에 문의하여 언제든지 이메일을 통해 무료로 전송되는 마케팅 커뮤니케이션을 구독 거부할 수 있습니다. 이용자의 거주 국가에 따라 다른 유형의 마케팅 연락에 대해 옵트아웃(수신 동의 철회)할 수도 있습니다. 자세한 사항은 본 개인정보 보호 정책에 나와 있는 연락처 정보를 이용해 당사에 문의해 주시기 바랍니다. 사법 관할 지역에 따라 제3자의 직접 마케팅 목적으로 당사가 제3자에 개인 정보를 제공하는 것과 관련해 개인(예: 캘리포니아 주 주민)에게 특정 정보를 요청할 권리를 부여하는 곳도 있습니다. 당사의 마케팅 목적에 따른 데이터 제공 방식에 관한 자세한 정보는 아래에 나와 있는 안내에 따라 당사에 문의해 주시기 바랍니다.
* **관심 기반 광고**. 당사는 이용자에게 가장 관련성 있는 광고를 제공할 수 있도록 이용자의 온라인 활동에 관한 데이터를 수집하고 이용자의 관심 사항을 파악합니다. 이용자는 당사 [쿠키 고지](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#korean)에서 정하는 바에 따라 Honeywell이 보내는 관심 기반 광고 수신을 옵트아웃(수신 동의 철회)할 수 있습니다.
* **금전적 인센티브 및 상용고객 프로그램**. 당사는 당사의 금전적 인센티브와 상용고객 프로그램을 유지 및 실시하기 위해 개인 정보를 수집 및 사용합니다. 당사는 고유한 보상을 제공하고, 이용자의 프로그램 상태를 추적하고, 프로그램 포인트를 제품, 프로모션 자료, 교육 워크샵 및 기타 항목으로 교환 사용하는 것을 촉진하기 위해 이러한 프로그램에서 이용자가 제공하는 개인 정보를 이용합니다. 또한 당사는 법률이 허용하는 범위 내에서 본 개인정보 보호 정책에서 정하는 모든 다른 목적으로 금전적 인센티브 프로그램 맥락에서 이용자가 제공하는 개인 정보를 사용할 수 있습니다. 프로그램의 약관은 해당 프로그램에 맞춰 범위가 좁게 설정되어 있을 수 있는 만큼, 등록 또는 참여하고자 하는 각 금전적 인센티브 프로그램의 약관을 자세히 살펴보시기 바랍니다. 이러한 프로그램에 참여하는 데 동의하시는 경우, 본 개인정보 보호 정책의 끝 부분에 나와 있는 연락처 정보를 이용해 당사에 연락하거나 해당 프로그램의 약관에서 정하는 방법에 따라 언제든지 그러한 동의를 철회하실 수 있습니다.
* **입사 지원**. 이용자는 입사 지원이나 문의와 관련해 이력서, 추천인, 학력 및 경력 관련 정보, 직업적 교육 및 자격증 관련 정보 등, 자신에 관한 정보를 당사에 제공할 수 있습니다. 당사와 당사 그룹 계열사는 채용 심사, 신원 조회 및 채용 적격성 확인 목적, 그리고 별도의 개인정보 보호 정책 또는 그 외에 입사 지원과 관련해 확인 가능한 기타 고지에서 정하는 바에 따라 이러한 정보를 사용할 수 있습니다. 당사는 입사 지원을 요청, 수집 및 보관하기 위해 제3자(예: 채용업체) 또는 소셜 미디어 플랫폼을 이용할 수 있습니다. 자세한 사항은 당사의 [지원자 개인정보 보호 고지](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/applicant-privacy-notice#korean)를 참고하시기 바랍니다.
* **조사 및 분석**. 당사는 이용자의 개인 정보를 토대로 조사 및 분석을 실시하여 사용자의 구매 기본 설정을 분석하고, 이용자의 요구에 가장 잘 맞는 제품 및 서비스를 파악하고, 당사가 이용자에게 제공하는 광고의 효과를 측정할 수 있습니다.
* **법 집행**: 당사는 수집한 개인 정보를 사기, 지적재산권 침해, 당사의 약관 위반, 법률 위반, 당사 사이트의 악용을 탐지하고 방지하며 대응하기 위해 사용할 수 있습니다.

법률이 허용하는 한, 당사가 사이트를 통해 수집한 정보와 이용자에 대해 보유하고 있는 기타 정보(예: 당사 제품 및 서비스 이용에 대한 정보)를 결합하여 당사와 상호 작용할 때 또는 본 개인정보 보호 정책에 기술된 다른 용도를 위해 더 우수하고 일관된 고객 경험을 제공할 수 있습니다.

**당사가 정보를 처리하는 법적 근거**

법률에서 요구하는 경우, 당사는 이용자의 개인 정보 처리를 위한 법적 근거가 있음을 보장합니다. 대부분의 경우 당사의 법적 근거는 해당 개인 정보 및 당사가 그 정보를 수집하는 구체적인 맥락 상황에 따라 결정됩니다.

* **계약**: 당사가 이용자에게 제공하는 서비스의 수행을 위해, 또는 그러한 서비스의 수행 이전에, 그러한 서비스를 예상하고 (이용자의 요청에 따라) 조치를 취하기 위해서는 처리가 필요합니다.
* **법적 의무**: 관련 법률, 규정, 정부 및 준정부 요청, 법원 명령 또는 소환장 이행 등 당사의 법적 의무를 준수하기 위해 개인 정보를 처리해야 합니다.
* **동의**: 하나 이상의 지정된 목적(예: 마케팅)을 위해 처리하며 이용자의 개인 정보 처리에 대한 본인 동의를 근거로 처리합니다.
* **합법적 이해 관계**: 고객의 이익을 위해 당사 사이트, 제품 및/또는 서비스를 개발 및 개선하는 것과 같이 당사의 합법적인 이해 관계를 충족하기 위해 개인 정보 처리가 필요합니다. 또는,
* **생명에 직결되는 이해 관계**: 이용자의 생명에 직결되는 이해 관계를 보호하는 데 처리가 필요합니다(예를 들어, 이용자가 Honeywell 사업장에서 열리는 미팅에 참석하는 경우 건강 및 안전상의 이유로).

당사가 귀하의 개인 정보를 수집 및 사용하는 법적 근거와 관련해 궁금한 사항이 있거나 추가적인 정보가 필요하신 경우 [HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com)으로 이메일을 보내주시기 바랍니다.

**정보의 익명화**

해당 법률에 따라 이용자의 개인 정보를 익명화 하여 더 이상 이용자 신원을 확인하는 데 사용할 수 없도록 할 수 있습니다. 익명화된 정보는 개인 정보로 간주되지 않으며, 따라서 본 개인정보 보호 정책의 대상이 아닙니다. 당사는 익명의 정보를 모든 용도로 수집, 사용, 취합 및 공유할 수 있습니다.

**당사가 정보를 보유하는 기간**

당사가 이용자의 개인 정보를 보관하는 기간은 처리 목적에 따라 다릅니다. 예를 들어, 당사는 이용자가 Honeywell 고객으로 있는 한, 이용자에게 제품 및 서비스를 제공하거나 이용자가 요청한 트랜잭션을 원활하게 진행하기 위해 필요한 개인 정보를 보관하며, 이용자가 당사 사이트를 통해 입사 지원서를 제출하는 경우 해당 지원서와 관련해 이용자에게 제공되는 개인정보 고지에서 정하고 있거나 그 외 법률에서 정하는 요건에 따라 이용자의 지원서 세부 정보를 보관합니다. 그 외 다른 모든 경우 당사는 본 개인정보 보호 정책에 명시된 목적을 달성하는 데 필요한 기간 동안 이용자의 개인 정보를 보관하며 그 후에는 (관련법률에서 허용하는 경우) 익명화 하거나 삭제 또는 폐기합니다.

**정보의 공개**

당사는 아래에 명시된 내용을 포함하여 관련 법률에 따라 이용자의 개인 정보를 선택된 제3자와 공유할 수 있습니다.

* **당사 그룹 계열사**. 당사는 본 개인정보 보호 정책에 명시된 목적을 위해 합리적으로 필요한 경우 이용자의 개인 정보를 당사 계열사 및 그룹사와 공유할 수 있습니다.
* **서비스 제공업체**. 당사는 웹 사이트 호스팅, 설문 조사 수행, 트랜잭션 처리, 당사 사이트 분석 및 당사의 비즈니스, 사이트, 제품 및 서비스의 질을 향상하기 위한 분석 수행과 같이 당사를 대신하여 해당 서비스를 제공하기로 계약한 회사와 사용자의 개인 정보를 공유할 수 있습니다. 당사는 해당 서비스 제공업체에게 이용자의 개인 정보 기밀을 보호하도록 요구합니다.
* **유통사 및 기타 신뢰할 수 있는 비즈니스 파트너**. 당사는 제3자가 이용자에게 마케팅 커뮤니케이션을 보내는 것을 허용하는 목적으로 당사 제품을 유통하는 제3자 및 기타 신뢰할 수 있는 비즈니스 파트너와 이용자의 개인 정보를 공유할 수 있습니다. 마케팅 목적으로 개인 정보를 공유하는 경우 적용 가능한 법률 및 규정에 따라 수행됩니다.
* **트랜잭션과 관련한 공개**. 특정 트랜잭션과 관련하여 당사는 이용자의 개인 정보의 일부 또는 전부를 트랜잭션 이행에 연관된 금융 기관, 정부 기관, 운송 회사 또는 우편 서비스에 공개할 수 있습니다.
* **인수 또는 매각과 관련한 공개**. 전략적 이유 또는 그 외 사업상 이유로 Honeywell이 일부 국가에서 사업체를 매각, 인수, 처분, 합병 또는 그 외 다른 방법으로 조직 개편하는 상황이 발생할 수 있습니다. 당사는 Honeywell 자산의 전체 또는 일부에 대한 협상을 진행하거나 합병, 인수, 처분 또는 매각을 완료하기 위해 합리적으로 필요한 범위까지 당사가 보유하고 있는 이용자의 정보를 공개할 수 있습니다.
* **기타 사유에 따른 공개**. 당사는 법에서 요구하거나 허가하는 경우, 또는 법적 요건이나 당사에 적용된 법적 절차를 준수하기 위해 필요한 경우, 당사의 권리 또는 재산을 보호하고 변호하기 위해, 또는 비상시 개인의 안전을 보호하기 위해 정보 공개가 필요하다는 선의의 확신이 드는 경우 개인 정보를 공개할 수 있습니다.

**국가 간 이전**

Honeywell은 글로벌 조직이며, 이용자의 정보는 관련 법에 따라 미국, 멕시코, 인도 등 전 세계 다양한 장소에 걸쳐 이전, 보유, 저장 또는 사용될 수 있습니다. 따라서 당사가 이용자의 개인 정보를 수집했을 때 그 정보가 이용자 국가의 데이터 보호 법률과는 법률이 다른 국가에서 처리될 수 있다는 뜻입니다. 그러나 Honeywell은 항상 이용자의 개인 정보를 보호하고, 유럽 집행위원회(European Commission)의 표준 계약 조항(Standard Contractual Clauses)을 실시하는 것을 포함해, 이용자 거주 국가와 유사한 수준의 개인 정보 보호를 제공하기 위해 항상 합당한 조치를 취할 것입니다. 귀하의 개인 정보 보호를 위해 마련되어 있는 적절한 안전 장치에 관한 자세한 정보는 [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com)으로 문의해 주시기 바랍니다.

**보안**

당사는 이용자의 개인 정보 보안을 유지하기 위해 최선을 다합니다. 당사는 이용자의 개인 정보 처리에 따른 위험에 적합한 수준의 보안을 제공하기 위해 기술적 조치 및 조직 차원의 조치를 취하고 있습니다. Honeywell이 이용자의 개인 정보를 보호하는 방법에 관한 자세한 정보는 [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com)으로 문의해 주시기 바랍니다.

**이용자의 권리**

관련 법률에 따라 이용자에게는 본인의 개인 정보와 관련해 특정한 권리가 있을 수 있습니다.

* 이용자에게는 자신의 개인 정보에 대해 **열람, 정정, 수정** 또는 **삭제 요청**할 수 있는 권리가 있을 수 있습니다.
* 이용자는 자신의 개인 정보 처리에 **반대**하거나, 당사에 자신의 개인 정보 처리를 **제한**해 줄 것을 요청하거나, 본인 개인 정보의 **이동성**을 요청할 수 있습니다.
* 이용자에게는 자신에 대해 법적 효과를 갖거나 상당한 영향을 미치는 결정인 경우 **프로파일링을 포함해, 전적으로 자동 처리를 바탕으로 자신에 대해 그러한 결정이 이루어지지 않도록 할** 권리가 있습니다.
* 마찬가지로, 당사가 이용자의 동의 하에 이용자의 개인 정보를 수집 및 처리한 경우 **이용자는 언제든지 자신의 동의를 철회할 수 있습니다**. 동의를 철회하더라도 철회 전에 당사가 수행한 처리의 합법성에는 아무런 영향을 미치지 않으며, 동의를 제외한 합법적 처리 근거에 따라 수행한 이용자의 개인 정보 처리에도 영향을 미치지 않습니다.
* 이용자에게는 **자신의 개인 정보 판매에 대해 옵트아웃할 권리가 있을 수 있습니다**. Honeywell은 영리 목적으로 이용자의 개인 정보를 제3자에게 판매하지 않습니다. 그러나, 당사는 본 개인정보 보호 정책 및 당사의 [쿠키 고지](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#korean)에 따라 제3자와 이용자의 개인 정보를 공유하거나 그 외 다른 방법으로 제공합니다. 예를 들어, 당사는 당사 제품을 유통시키고, 이용자에게 기술 지원을 제공하며, 웹사이트 분석 도구 및 기능을 실행하고, 당사 제품 및 서비스의 마케팅 및 판매 활동을 수행하기 위해 제3자와 계약을 맺을 수 있습니다. 그러한 활동 과정에서 제3자에 대한 이용자의 개인 정보 제공이 발생할 수 있으며, 이는 (모두 그런 것은 아니지만) 특정 데이터 보호 법률에 따라 데이터 "판매"로 간주될 수 있습니다.
* 이용자에게는 당사에 의한 자신의 개인 정보 처리가 데이터 보호 법률에 부합되지 않는다고 판단되는 경우 당사의 개인 정보 수집 및 사용에 관해 자신이 속한 사법 관할권 내 데이터 보호 법률의 준수를 관할하는 데이터 보호 당국에 **민원을 제기**할 수 있습니다. 예를 들어, EEA(유럽경제지역) 내에 거주하는 개인의 경우 관할 데이터 보호 기관(Data Protection Authority)에 민원을 제기할 권리가 있으며, 데이터 보호 기관의 목록은 [https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/board/members\_en](https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/board/members_en)에서 확인할 수 있습니다. 하지만 우려되는 부분이 있으신 경우 당사가 해결해 드릴 수 있기를 바라며, 불만 사항이 있으시면 언제든지 당사에 직접 연락해 주시기 바랍니다. 당사는 자신이 가진 데이터 프라이버시 권리를 행사하는 개인을 차별하지 않습니다.

당사는 관련 법률에 따라 사용자에게 적용되는 권리 행사를 촉진합니다. 그러나 개인 정보가 데이터 보호 법률에 따른 보호 대상 또는 적용 대상이 아니라 하더라도 당사는 당사의 데이터 처리 활동과 관련한 이용자의 요청 또는 문의 사항을 수용하고자 할 수 있습니다. 본인의 권리에 관해 궁금한 사항이 있거나 본인이 가진 권리를 행사하고자 하시는 경우 [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com)으로 당사에 연락하시거나, 다음 링크를 이용해 당사의 대화형 웹 양식을 통해 개인정보 보호 관련 질문을 제출해 주시기 바랍니다.

**아동청소년의 정보**

당사 사이트는 십육(16) 세 미만 아동청소년을 대상으로 하지 않고 그러한 아동청소년이 사용해서는 안 되며, 그러한 아동청소년으로부터 의도적으로 정보를 수집해 사용하거나 판매해서는 안 됩니다. 귀하가 본인 국가의 법률 상 미성년자에 해당되는 경우 절대 당사 사이트를 통해 개인 정보를 제출해서는 안 됩니다.

**타 웹사이트 링크**

당사 사이트에는 제3자 웹사이트, 제품 및 서비스에 대한 링크가 포함될 수 있습니다. 당사는 제3자 웹사이트, 제품 및 서비스, 제3자 정책, 또는 제3자의 사용자 개인 정보 수집 또는 기타 처리에 대해 일체 책임지지 않습니다. 그러한 제3자의 정보 취급 방식에는 자체적인 개인정보 보호 정책이 적용됩니다. 이용자는 그러한 제3자의 개인정보 보호 정책에 대해 자세히 알아두는 것을 권장합니다.

**연락처**

본 개인정보 보호 정책 또는 당사의 이용자 개인 정보 처리와 관련하여 궁금한 사항이 있거나, 불만 사항을 제기하고자 하거나, 당사의 데이터 보호 담당자에게 문의하고자 하시는 경우 아래에 나와 있는 연락처 정보를 이용해 당사에 문의해 주시기 바랍니다. 당사는 지체 없이 우려 사항에 대응하고 만족스러운 해결책을 찾기 위해 노력할 것입니다.

대화형 웹 양식:  

이메일:  

우편 주소:  
Honeywell Privacy  
4D5  
115 Tabor Road  
Morris Plains, NJ 07950

무료 전화:  

**본 개인정보 보호 정책의 변경**

당사는 때때로 본 개인정보 보호 정책을 업데이트할 수 있습니다. 업데이트하는 경우 당사는 개인정보 보호 정책의 상단과 하단에 있는 "최종 수정일" 날짜를 수정하고, 법에서 정하고 있는 추가적 조치가 있는 경우 해당 조치를 취할 것입니다.

**최종 개정일: 2021년 6월 11일**

Norwegian

**Sist oppdatert 11. juni 2021**

**Introduksjon**

Honeywell International Inc. ("**Honeywell**", "**våre**", "**oss**" eller "**vi**”), er "behandlingsansvarlig" for personopplysningene vi samler inn om deg når du besøker eller bruker noen av våre nettsteder, eller bruker produkter, tjenester og programmer som er koblet til denne personvernerklæringen (samlet våre "**nettsteder**"). Denne personvernerklæringen forklarer hvordan vi samler inn, deler og bruker personopplysningene dine som er samlet inn på denne måten, og hvordan du kan utøve dine personvernrettigheter.

Når vi kommuniserer med deg, kan vi også gi deg ytterligere personvernerklæringer om spesifikke behandlingsaktiviteter eller tilby deg flere valg om hvordan Honeywell behandler personopplysningene dine på det aktuelle tidspunktet.

Klikk på en av koblingene nedenfor for å gå til avsnittet som du er interessert i:

**Vår innhenting av opplysninger**

* **Informasjon som samles inn direkte fra deg**. Vi kan be deg om personopplysninger for å yte en tjeneste eller utføre en transaksjon som du har bedt om. Du kan også gi oss personopplysninger når du tar kontakt med oss eller samhandler med oss (for eksempel med en kommentar, forespørsel eller kundesupportforespørsel, besøkende på nettsteder) eller registrerer deg for en konto for å bruke våre nettsteder. Disse personopplysningene kan omfatte:
    * **Identitetsdata,** for eksempel navn, tittel, firma/organisasjonsnavn, e-postadresse, telefonnummer og fysisk adresse (inkludert gate, by, postnummer og/eller land);
    * **Registreringsdata,** for eksempel informasjon gitt av deg når du registrerer deg for en konto for å bruke våre nettsteder, inkludert brukernavn og passord;
    * **Rekrutteringsopplysninger,** blant annet informasjon sendt inn i forbindelse med en søknad eller spørsmål om jobb (som beskrevet nedenfor);
    * **Bedriftskontaktdata,** for eksempel informasjon relatert til andre ansatte, eiere, styremedlemmer, funksjonærer eller leverandører i en tredjepartsorganisasjon (f.eks. virksomhet, selskap, partnerskap, enkeltmannsforetak, ideell organisasjon eller offentlig etat).
    * **Markedsførings- og kommunikasjonsdata,** inkludert markedsføringspreferanser og abonnementene i våre publikasjoner;
    * **Finansiell informasjon,** inkludert kredittkort eller annen finansiell kontoinformasjon, med det formål å gjøre det mulig for oss å legge til rette for kjøp av selskapets produkter og tjenester som kan være tilgjengelige på våre nettsteder;
    * **Informasjon om eksportkontroll,** for eksempel nasjonalitet, statsborgerskap og bostedsland, som gjør det mulig for oss å fastslå at du er kvalifisert under eksportkontrollforskrifter for å motta informasjon om visse teknologier;
    * **Transaksjonsdata,** blant annet henvendelser om og bestillinger for våre produkter og tjenester og detaljer om betalinger til og fra deg, inkludert innkjøpsordrehistorikk og informasjon som er nødvendig for å gjennomføre betalingstransaksjoner;
    * **Informasjon i forbindelse med hendelsesregistrering,** inkludert informasjon som du oppgir når du fyller ut e-registreringsskjemaer; og
    * **Din tilbakemelding,** inkludert tilbakemelding fra deg om nettstedet våre, samt produktene og tjenestene generelt.

Når du ikke oppgir forespurt informasjon, kan det hende vi ikke kan levere den tjenesten du ber om, eller utføre transaksjonen din.

* **Informasjon vi samler inn automatisk om deg**. Vi samler inn bestemt informasjon om ditt besøk på våre nettsteder ved hjelp av informasjonskapsler og lignende sporingsteknologier. Vi vil alltid respektere eventuelle juridiske rettigheter du måtte ha for å forhindre at vi gjør dette. Data som samles inn på denne måten, inkluderer:
    * **Bruksdata,** inkludert informasjon om hvordan du bruker våre nettsteder, hvilke sider du viser, antall byte som overføres, lenkene du klikker på, materialene du har tilgang til, datoen og klokkeslettet du får tilgang til nettstedet, nettstedet som du koblet videre til et av våre nettsteder fra, og andre handlinger på nettstedet; og
    * **Tekniske data,** for eksempel din IP-adresse, nettlesertype og -funksjoner og språk og operativsystem.

For informasjon om informasjonskapslene og andre lignende sporingsteknologier vi bruker på nettstedene våre, kan du se vår [merknad om informasjonskapsler](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#norwegian).

* **Geolokasjonsinformasjon**. For bestemte nettsteder kan vi med uttrykkelig samtykke fra deg samle inn nøyaktige posisjonsopplysninger i sanntid (dvs. geolokasjon) for mobilenheten din. Denne informasjonen brukes bare for å lette din bruk av nettstedene, inkludert av tjenesteleverandørene våre som kan behandle denne informasjonen i forbindelse med å tilby tjenester på våre vegne. Hvis du har gitt det, kan du justere dette samtykket ved å administrere preferansene dine for posisjonstjenester gjennom innstillingene på mobilenheten din.
* **Informasjon samlet inn fra tredjeparter**. I samsvar med gjeldende lov kan vi samle inn personopplysninger om deg fra tredjeparter, for eksempel nettsteder og apper på sosiale medier, og kombinere dem med informasjon vi allerede har, for å hjelpe oss med å forbedre og tilpasse nettstedene dine etter dine preferanser og for andre formål som er angitt i denne personvernerklæringen. Vi kan også samle virksomhetens kontaktinformasjon fra arbeidsgiveren din eller andre tredjeparter for å legge til rette for eller på annen måte delta i tradisjonelle forretningsaktiviteter og lignende administrative spørsmål.

**Vår bruk av opplysninger**

Vi kan bruke den personlige informasjonen som er samlet inn via våre nettsteder, eller når du kontakter oss for formål som inkluderer:

* **Forretningskontaktdata**. Honeywell samler inn og bruker forretningskontaktdata for å delta i kommunikasjon eller transaksjoner, inkludert for å utføre due diligence om, eller levere eller motta, et produkt eller en tjeneste. For eksempel kan Honeywell samle inn og bruke disse forretningskontaktopplysningene for å tilrettelegge for og administrere bestillinger, kontrakter, garantier, vedlikehold og lignende forretningsfunksjoner, for kredittanalyse- og innkrevingsformål, for å bistå med vårt eget interne samsvar og juridiske krav, og (om nødvendig) for å forsvare våre interesser og krav.
* **Tjenester og transaksjoner**. Vi kan bruke personopplysningene dine til å levere deg tjenester og utføre transaksjoner du har bedt om, inklusiv, men ikke begrenset til, å gi informasjon om selskapets produkter, eller tjenester som du har kjøpt eller på annen måte bruker, registrere kjøpte produkter, behandle produktbestillinger, behandle garantikrav, erstatte produkthåndbøker, svare på kundeservicehenvendelser og forenkle bruken av nettstedene våre.
* **Administrere og beskytte vår virksomhet og nettsteder**. Vi kan bruke dine personlige opplysninger til å administrere og beskytte vår virksomhet og våre nettsteder, inkludert feilsøking, systemvedlikehold, brukerstøtte, rapportering og hosting av data.
* **Forbedre vår forretningsvirksomhet, nettsteder, produkter og tjenester**. Vi kan bruke dine personlige opplysninger til å utføre forretningsanalyser eller til andre formål som hjelper oss med å utvikle og forbedre kvaliteten på virksomheten vår, nettsteder, produkter og tjenester (inkludert nye produkter og tjenester), for eksempel ved å tilpasse våre nettsteder til dine spesielle preferanser eller interesser.
* **Markedsføring**. I samsvar med gjeldende lover og forskrifter kan vi bruke dine personopplysninger til å informere deg om produkter eller tjenester som kan være av interesse for deg, og ellers kommunisere med deg om tilbud, hendelser og nyheter, undersøkelser, spesialtilbud og relaterte emner. Du kan når som helst melde deg fra markedsføringskommunikasjon sendt via e-post, gratis ved å bruke "unsubscribe"-lenken i e-postmarkedsføringsmateriell du mottar fra oss, eller ved å kontakte oss ved å bruke kontaktopplysningene som er oppført i denne personvernerklæringen. Avhengig av bostedsland kan du også velge bort andre typer markedsføringskommunikasjon; kontakt oss ved hjelp av kontaktinformasjonen som er oppført i personvernerklæringen for mer informasjon. Noen jurisdiksjoner gir enkeltpersoner (for eksempel innbyggere i California) rett til å be om bestemt informasjon om vår utlevering av personopplysninger til tredjeparter for tredjepartens direkte markedsføringsformål. For mer informasjon om vår datapubliseringspraksis for markedsføringsformål kan du kontakte oss i samsvar med instruksjonene som er oppført nedenfor.
* **Interessebasert reklame**. Vi samler inn data om aktivitetene dine på nettet og identifiserer interessene dine slik at vi kan tilby reklame som er mest relevant for deg. Du kan velge å motta interessebasert reklame fra Honeywell som beskrevet i vår [merknad om informasjonskapsler](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#norwegian).
* **Programmer for økonomisk insentiv og lojalitet**. Vi samler inn og bruker personopplysninger for å opprettholde og administrere våre programmer for økonomisk insentiv og lojalitet. Vi bruker personopplysningene du oppgir i disse programmene for å tilby unike belønninger, spore programstatusen din og for å tilrettelegge for utvekslingen av programpoeng i produkter, reklamemateriell, treningsverksteder og andre ting. I den grad loven tillater det, kan vi også bruke alle personopplysninger som du oppgir i forbindelse med et økonomisk insentivprogram til ethvert annet formål som er angitt i denne personvernerklæringen. Se gjennom vilkårene og betingelsene for hvert økonomisk insentivprogram du ønsker å registrere deg for eller delta i, ettersom slike vilkår kan være smalt tilpasset det aktuelle programmet. Hvis du samtykker i å delta i disse programmene, kan du når som helst trekke tilbake samtykket ved å kontakte oss ved å bruke kontaktinformasjonen på slutten av denne personvernerklæringen eller i samsvar med instruksjonene i det aktuelle programmets vilkår og betingelser.
* **Jobbsøknader**. I forbindelse med en jobbsøknad eller henvendelse kan du gi oss informasjon om deg selv, for eksempel CV, fagreferanser, informasjon om utdanning og jobbbakgrunn, og informasjon om fagopplæring og sertifiseringer. Vi og medlemmer av vår gruppe kan bruke denne informasjonen for å vurdere ansettelser, bakgrunnskontroll og ansettelseskvalifikasjon, og som det ellers er angitt i en hvilken som helst separat personvernerklæring eller annen merknad som er gjort tilgjengelig i forbindelse med søknaden din. Vi kan bruke en tredjepart (f.eks. rekrutteringsbyrå) eller plattform for sosiale medier for å be om, samle inn og beholde jobbsøknader. For mer informasjon kan du lese vår [Personvernerklæring for søkere](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/applicant-privacy-notice#norwegian).
* **Undersøkelser og analyser**. Vi kan bruke dine personopplysninger til å utføre forskning og analyse for å hjelpe oss med å analysere innkjøpspraksis, identifisere produktene og tjenestene som best passer dine krav, og måle effektiviteten av annonseringen vi leverer til deg.
* **Håndhevelse**: Vi kan bruke personopplysningene vi samler for å oppdage, forhindre og håndtere svindel, brudd på immaterielle rettigheter, brudd på våre vilkår og betingelser, lovbrudd eller annen misbruk av våre nettsteder.

Når loven tillater det, kan vi kombinere informasjonen vi samler inn via våre nettsteder med annen informasjon vi har om deg (for eksempel informasjon om din bruk av våre produkter og tjenester) for å tilby deg en bedre og konsistent kundeopplevelse når du samhandler med oss eller andre formål som er angitt i denne personvernerklæringen.

**Det rettslige grunnlaget for å behandle opplysninger**

Når loven krever det, sørger vi for at det er et rettslig grunnlag for behandlingen av dine personlige opplysninger. I de fleste tilfeller avhenger vårt juridiske grunnlag av de aktuelle personopplysningene og den spesifikke konteksten vi samler dem inn i.

* **Kontrakt**: behandlingen er nødvendig for utførelsen av tjenestene vi tilbyr deg, eller for å ta skritt (på din forespørsel) før utførelse av slike tjenester;
* **Juridisk forpliktelse**: behandlingen er nødvendig for å overholde våre juridiske forpliktelser, herunder overholdelse av gjeldende lover, forskrifter, statlige og kvasi-statlige forespørsler, rettsordre eller stevninger;
* **Samtykke**: behandlingen er basert på ditt samtykke til behandling av din personopplysninger for ett eller flere spesifiserte formål (for eksempel markedsføring);
* **Legitime interesser**: behandlingen er nødvendig for å møte våre legitime interesser, for eksempel for å utvikle og forbedre våre nettsteder, produkter og/eller tjenester til fordel for våre kunder; eller
* **Vitale interesser**: behandlingen er nødvendig for å beskytte dine vitale interesser (for eksempel helse- og sikkerhetsmessige grunner hvis du deltar på et møte på et Honeywell-sted).

Hvis du har spørsmål om eller trenger ytterligere informasjon om det juridiske grunnlaget som vi samler inn og bruker din personlige informasjon på, kan du sende en e-post til [HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com)

**Anonymisering av opplysninger**

I samsvar med gjeldende lov kan vi anonymisere dine personopplysninger slik at de ikke lenger kan brukes til å identifisere deg. Anonymisert informasjon anses ikke som personopplysninger og er derfor ikke underlagt denne personvernerklæringen. Vi kan samle inn, bruke, aggregere og dele anonymisert informasjon til ethvert formål.

**Hvor lenge vi lagrer opplysninger**

Perioden vi lagrer dine personopplysninger varierer avhengig av formålet med behandlingen. For eksempel lagrer vi personopplysninger som er nødvendige for å levere produkter og tjenester til deg, eller for å tilrettelegge for transaksjoner du har bedt om, så lenge du er kunde hos Honeywell, eller hvis du sender inn en jobbsøknad via våre nettsteder, vil vi beholde informasjon om søknaden din som beskrevet i personvernerklæringen som er tilgjengelig for deg i forbindelse med søknaden din eller som ellers kreves av loven. I alle andre tilfeller lagrer vi dine personlige opplysninger så lenge det er nødvendig for å oppfylle formålene som er angitt i denne personvernerklæringen, etter hvilken tid det er enten anonymisert (der det er tillatt ved gjeldende lov), slettet eller ødelagt.

**Utlevering av opplysninger**

Vi kan dele dine personopplysninger med utvalgte tredjeparter i samsvar med gjeldende lov, inkludert som angitt nedenfor:

* **Våre konsernselskaper**. Vi kan dele dine personopplysninger med våre tilknyttede selskaper og konsernselskaper som rimelig nødvendig for de formålene som er angitt i denne personvernerklæringen.
* **Tjenesteleverandører**. Vi kan dele dine personopplysninger med selskaper som vi har utkontraktert til å tilby tjenester på våre vegne, for eksempel hosting av nettsteder, gjennomføring av undersøkelser, behandlingstransaksjoner, analyse av våre nettsteder og utførelse av analyser for å forbedre kvaliteten på vår virksomhet, nettsteder, produkter og tjenester. Vi trenger disse tjenesteleverandørene for å beskytte konfidensialiteten til dine personopplysninger.
* **Distributører og andre pålitelige samarbeidspartnere**. Vi kan dele dine personlige opplysninger med tredjeparter som distribuerer våre produkter og andre pålitelige forretningspartnere til formål som inkluderer at disse tredjepartene kan sende markedsføringskommunikasjon til deg. Slik utveksling av personlig informasjon til markedsføringsformål blir utført i samsvar med gjeldende lover og forskrifter.
* **Utlevering i forbindelse med transaksjoner**. I forbindelse med visse transaksjoner kan det hende vi leverer videre noen av eller alle personopplysningene dine til finansinstitusjoner, myndighetsorganer og transport- eller postselskaper som er involvert i utførelsen av transaksjonen.
* **Opplysninger i forbindelse med oppkjøp eller frasalg**. Det kan oppstå forhold der Honeywell av strategiske eller andre forretningsgrunner bestemmer seg for å selge, kjøpe, selge, slå sammen eller på annen måte omorganisere virksomheter i noen land. Vi kan avsløre informasjon vi har om deg i den grad det er rimelig nødvendig for å fortsette med forhandling eller fullføring av fusjon, oppkjøp, avhendelse eller salg av hele eller deler av Honeywells eiendeler.
* **Utlevering av andre årsaker**. Det kan hende vi offentliggjør personopplysninger hvis nødvendig eller autorisert til å gjøre dette ifølge lov, eller når vi i god tro mener en slik handling er nødvendig for å etterleve juridiske krav, eller opptre riktig i forbindelse med søksmål mot oss, for å beskytte og forsvare våre rettigheter eller vår eiendom, eller for å beskytte den personlige sikkerheten til en person under presserende omstendigheter.

**Internasjonale overføringer**

Honeywell er en global organisasjon, og din personopplysningene dine kan overføres til, oppbevares, lagres eller brukes på forskjellige steder over hele verden som USA, Mexico og India i samsvar med gjeldende lov. Dette betyr at når vi samler inn personopplysningene dine, kan de bli behandlet i land som kan ha databeskyttelseslover som er forskjellige fra lovene i ditt land. Imidlertid vil Honeywell alltid ta rimelige tiltak for å beskytte personvernet ditt og for å gi et nivå av beskyttelse av personopplysninger som er sammenlignbar med den i bostedslandet ditt, inkludert implementering av EU-kommisjonens standardavtaleklausuler. For mer informasjon om hensiktsmessige tiltak for å beskytte personopplysningene dine kan du kontakte oss på [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com).

**Sikkerhet**

Vi er forpliktet til å verne personopplysninger om deg. Vi bruker tekniske og organisatoriske tiltak for å gi et sikkerhetsnivå som passer til risikoen for å behandle personopplysningene dine. For mer informasjon om hvordan Honeywell beskytter personopplysningene dine kan du kontakte oss på [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com)

**Dine rettigheter**

Avhengig av gjeldende lov kan du ha visse rettigheter med hensyn til personopplysningene dine.

* Du kan ha rett til å **få tilgang til, korrigere, oppdatere** eller **be om sletting** av personopplysningene dine.
* Du kan **protestere** mot behandlingen av personopplysningene dine, be oss om å **begrense** behandlingen av personopplysningene dine eller be om **portabilitet** av personopplysningene dine.
* Du kan ha rett **til at det ikke tas en beslutning om deg som bare er basert på automatisert behandling, inkludert profilering,** hvis avgjørelsen gir rettsvirkninger for deg eller påvirker deg betydelig.
* Tilsvarende, hvis vi har samlet inn og behandlet personopplysningene dine med ditt samtykke, **kan du når som helst trekke tilbake samtykket ditt**. Å trekke tilbake samtykket ditt vil ikke påvirke lovligheten av behandling vi har utført før du trakk det tilbake, og det vil heller ikke påvirke behandlingen av personopplysningene dine som er utført på annet lovlig behandlingsgrunnlag enn samtykke.
* Du kan ha rett til **å velge bort salg av personopplysningene dine**. Honeywell selger ikke personopplysningene dine til tredjeparter for fortjeneste. Imidlertid deler vi eller på annen måte avslører personopplysningene dine til tredjeparter i samsvar med denne personvernerklæringen og vår [Merknad om informasjonskapsler](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#norwegian). For eksempel samarbeider vi med tredjeparter for å distribuere våre produkter, gi deg teknisk assistanse, bruke analyseverktøy og -funksjoner på nettstedet og delta i markedsføring og salg av våre produkter og tjenester. Slike aktiviteter kan innebære utlevering av personopplysningene dine til tredjepart og kan betraktes som et "salg" av data under visse (men ikke alle) lover om databeskyttelse.
* Du har rett til å **klage** til en databeskyttelsesmyndighet som er ansvarlig for å overvåke overholdelse av databeskyttelsesloven i din jurisdiksjon om vår innsamling og bruk av personopplysningene dine hvis du mener at behandlingen av personopplysningene dine ikke er i samsvar med databeskyttelsesloven. For eksempel har personer i EØS rett til å inngi en klage til den kompetente datatilsynsmyndigheten. Det finnes en liste over slike myndigheter på: [https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/board/members\_en](https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/board/members_en). Vi vil imidlertid sette pris på muligheten til å løse dine bekymringer, så ikke nøl med å ta kontakt med oss hvis det er noe du vil klage på. Vi vil ikke diskriminere enkeltpersoner for å utøve sine personvernrettigheter.

Vi vil tilrettelegge utøvelsen av rettighetene som gjelder for deg i samsvar med gjeldende lov. Selv om personopplysningene dine ikke er gitt beskyttelse i henhold til eller på annen måte er underlagt en databeskyttelseslov, kan vi imidlertid søke å imøtekomme enhver forespørsel du måtte ha om våre databehandlingsaktiviteter. Hvis du har spørsmål om dine rettigheter eller ønsker å utøve dine rettigheter, kan du kontakte oss på [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com) eller sende personvernspørsmål via vårt interaktive webskjema på følgende lenke:

**Opplysninger fra barn**

Nettstedene våre er ikke rettet mot, og skal ikke brukes av, barn under seksten (16) år, og vi samler inn, bruker eller selger ikke bevisst informasjon fra slike personer. Hvis du er mindreårig i henhold til lovene i ditt land, må du ikke sende inn personopplysninger via våre nettsteder.

**Lenker til andre nettsteder**

Nettstedene våre kan inneholde lenker til tredjeparters nettsteder, produkter og tjenester. Vi har ikke noe erstatningsansvar eller annet ansvar for disse nettstedene, produktene og tjenestene, deres retningslinjer, eller deres samling eller annen behandling av dine personlige opplysninger. Fremgangsmåten til disse tredjepartene styres av deres egne personvernregler. Vi oppfordrer deg til å lære om personvernreglene til disse tredjepartene.

**Kontakt oss**

Hvis du har spørsmål om denne personvernerklæringen eller om vår håndtering av personopplysninger om deg, hvis du ønsker å levere en klage, eller hvis du ønsker å kontakte personvernombudet vårt, kan du kontakte oss via kontaktinformasjonen angitt nedenfor. Vi vil behandle spørsmålet ditt raskt og prøve å finne en tilfredsstillende løsning.

Interaktivt webskjema:  

E-post:  

Mailing Adresse:  
Honeywell Privacy  
4D5  
115 Tabor Road  
Morris Plains, NJ 07950

Grønt nummer:  

**Endringer i denne personvernerklæringen**

Vi kan av og til oppdatere personvernerklæringen. Når vi gjør det, vil vi revidere "sist oppdatert"-datoen øverst i personvernerklæringen og ta ytterligere skritt som kan være påkrevd i henhold til loven.

**Sist oppdatert 11. juni 2021**

Polish

**Ostatnia aktualizacja: 11 czerwca 2021 r.**

**Wprowadzenie**

Honeywell International Inc. („**Honeywell**”, „**nasz**”, “**nas**” lub „**my**”) jest „administratorem danych” osobowych, które gromadzimy na temat użytkownika podczas jego odwiedzin w naszych witrynach internetowych lub korzystania z nich bądź korzystania z produktów, usług i aplikacji powiązanych z niniejszym Oświadczeniem o ochronie prywatności (łącznie nasze „**Witryny**”). W tym Oświadczeniu o ochronie prywatności wyjaśniono, w jaki sposób gromadzimy, udostępniamy i wykorzystujemy zebrane w ten sposób dane osobowe i w jaki sposób użytkownik może korzystać ze swoich praw do ochrony prywatności.

Podczas interakcji z użytkownikiem możemy również przekazywać mu dodatkowe informacje dotyczące ochrony prywatności o określonych działaniach związanych z przetwarzaniem lub zaoferować dodatkowe możliwości wyboru sposobu przetwarzania danych osobowych przez firmę Honeywell w danym momencie.

Należy kliknąć jedno z łączy poniżej w celu przejścia do interesującej użytkownika sekcji:

**Gromadzenie danych**

* **Dane gromadzone bezpośrednio od użytkownika**. Możemy prosić użytkownika o udostępnienie danych osobowych w celu wykonania żądanej usługi lub przeprowadzenia żądanej transakcji. Użytkownik może również udostępniać nam niektóre dane osobowe, kiedy kontaktuje się z nami lub angażuje się w interakcję z nami w inny sposób (np. pisząc komentarz, przesyłając zapytanie lub zgłoszenie do działu pomocy technicznej, odwiedzając witrynę) bądź rejestruje konto w celu korzystania z naszych Witryn. Te dane osobowe mogą obejmować:
    * **dane tożsamości,** takie jak imię i nazwisko, stanowisko, nazwa firmy/organizacji, adres e-mail, numery telefonu i adres pocztowy (zawierający nazwę ulicy, miasto, województwo, kod pocztowy i/lub kraj);
    * **dane rejestracyjne** przekazane przez użytkownika podczas rejestracji konta w celu korzystania z naszych Witryn, w tym nazwy użytkownika i hasła;
    * **dane rekrutacyjne,** w tym informacje przekazywane w związku z podaniem lub zapytaniem o pracę (zgodnie z poniższym opisem);
    * **dane kontaktowe firmy,** takie jak informacje dotyczące innych pracowników, właścicieli, dyrektorów, członków zarządu lub wykonawców innej organizacji (np. firmy, spółki, spółki osobowej, jednoosobowej działalności gospodarczej, organizacji non-profit lub agencji rządowej);
    * **dane marketingowe i komunikacyjne,** w tym preferencje marketingowe i subskrypcje naszych publikacji;
    * **informacje finansowe,** w tym dane karty kredytowej lub innego rachunku finansowego, umożliwiające ułatwianie użytkownikowi dokonywania zakupu produktów i usług firmy, które mogą być dostępne w naszych Witrynach;
    * **dane dotyczące kontroli eksportu,** takie jak narodowość, obywatelstwo i kraj zamieszkania, które pozwalają nam ustalić, czy zgodnie z przepisami dotyczącymi kontroli eksportu użytkownik może otrzymywać informacje o niektórych technologiach;
    * **dane transakcji,** w tym zapytania o nasze produkty i usługi oraz zamówienia na nie, a także dane płatności na rzecz i od użytkownika, łącznie z historią zamówień i informacjami potrzebnymi do umożliwienia transakcji płatniczych;
    * **informacje o rejestracji udziału w określonych wydarzeniach,** w tym informacje podane przez użytkownika przy wypełnianiu formularzy e-rejestracji; oraz
    * **opinie użytkownika,** co obejmuje ankiety, zalecenia lub jego inne opinie dotyczące naszych Witryn, a także ogólnie oferowane przez nas produkty i usługi.

Jeśli użytkownik nie dostarczy nam wymaganych informacji, świadczenie na jego rzecz żądanej usługi lub zrealizowanie danej transakcji może być niemożliwe.

* **Informacje, które gromadzimy automatycznie o użytkowniku**. Gromadzimy pewne informacje o wizycie użytkownika w naszych Witrynach za pomocą plików cookie i podobnych technologii śledzenia. Zawsze będziemy przestrzegać wszelkich praw użytkownika, które mogą nam to uniemożliwiać. Dane gromadzone w ten sposób obejmują:
    * **dane dotyczące użytkowania,** w tym informacje na temat sposobu korzystania przez użytkownika z naszych Witryn i przeglądanych stron, a także liczby przesłanych bajtów, klikniętych łączy, wyświetlonych materiałów, daty i godziny wizyty w danej Witrynie, witryny internetowej, z której uzyskano dostęp do jednej z naszych Witryn, oraz innych działań podjętych w obrębie tych Witryn; oraz
    * **dane techniczne,** takie jak adres IP (Internet Protocol), typ i możliwości przeglądarki oraz język i system operacyjny.

Informacje na temat plików cookie i innych podobnych technologii śledzenia używanych w naszych Witrynach można znaleźć w naszych [Informacjach o plikach cookie](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#polish).

* **Informacje o geolokalizacji**. W niektórych Witrynach mogą być gromadzone w czasie rzeczywistym precyzyjne informacje o lokalizacji (geolokalizacji) urządzenia mobilnego użytkownika po uzyskaniu jego zgody. Informacje te będą wykorzystywane wyłącznie w celu ułatwienia użytkownikowi korzystania z Witryn, w tym przez naszych usługodawców, którzy mogą przetwarzać te dane w związku ze świadczeniem usług w naszym imieniu. Jeśli użytkownik udzieli wspomnianej zgody, może ją zmienić, zarządzając preferencjami usług lokalizacyjnych w ustawieniach urządzenia mobilnego.
* **Informacje zebrane od osób trzecich**. Zgodnie z obowiązującym prawem możemy gromadzić dane osobowe użytkownika od stron trzecich, takich jak witryny i aplikacje mediów społecznościowych, i łączyć je z informacjami, które już mamy, aby ulepszać nasze Witryny i dostosowywać je do preferencji użytkownika, a także w innych celach określonych w niniejszym Oświadczeniu o ochronie prywatności. Możemy również gromadzić dane kontaktowe firmy użytkownika od jego pracodawcy lub innych stron trzecich w celu ułatwienia prowadzenia tradycyjnej działalności gospodarczej i spraw administracyjnych o podobnym charakterze bądź angażowania się w nie w inny sposób.

**Wykorzystywanie danych**

Możemy wykorzystywać dane osobowe zgromadzone za pośrednictwem naszych Witryn lub podczas kontaktu użytkownika z nami w celach obejmujących:

* **Dane kontaktowe firmy**. Honeywell gromadzi i wykorzystuje dane kontaktowe firmy do komunikacji lub przeprowadzania transakcji, w tym w celu przeprowadzenia analizy due diligence w odniesieniu do produktu lub usługi bądź ich dostarczania lub uzyskania. Honeywell może na przykład gromadzić i wykorzystywać dane kontaktowe firmy w celu umożliwienia realizacji zamówień, umów, gwarancji, konserwacji i funkcji biznesowych o podobnym charakterze oraz zarządzania nimi, a także w celach analizy i windykacji kredytowej oraz wsparcia przestrzegania naszych wewnętrznych wymagań dotyczących zgodności z przepisami i wymogów prawnych oraz (jeśli to konieczne) obrony naszych interesów i roszczeń.
* **Usługi i transakcje**. Możemy używać danych osobowych użytkownika w celu dostarczania mu żądanych usług oraz realizacji żądanych transakcji, w tym w celu dostarczania informacji na temat produktów i usług firmy, które użytkownik zakupił lub z których korzysta w jakikolwiek inny sposób, a także rejestracji zakupionych produktów, przetwarzania zamówień, obsługi roszczeń gwarancyjnych, wymiany instrukcji obsługi produktów, odpowiadania na zgłoszenia przesłane do działu obsługi klienta oraz ułatwiania procesu korzystania z naszych Witryn.
* **Zarządzanie naszą działalnością i Witrynami oraz ich ochrona**. Możemy wykorzystywać dane osobowe użytkownika w celu zarządzania naszą działalnością i Witrynami oraz ich ochrony, w tym rozwiązywania problemów, konserwacji systemu, udzielania wsparcia, raportowania i hostingu danych.
* **Usprawnianie działalności oraz doskonalenie Witryn, produktów i usług**. Możemy wykorzystywać dane osobowe użytkownika do przeprowadzania analiz biznesowych lub w innych celach służących usprawnieniu naszej działalności oraz doskonaleniu Witryn, produktów i usług (w tym nowych produktów i usług), na przykład poprzez dostosowanie Witryn do indywidualnych preferencji lub zainteresowań użytkownika.
* **Marketing**. Zgodnie z obowiązującymi przepisami i regulacjami możemy wykorzystywać dane osobowe użytkownika w celu informowania go o produktach i usługach, którymi może być zainteresowany, oraz komunikowania się z nim w jakikolwiek inny sposób w sprawie naszych ofert, wydarzeń, aktualności, ankiet, ofert specjalnych i powiązanych tematów. Użytkownik może w dowolnym momencie bezpłatnie zrezygnować z otrzymywania wysyłanych pocztą e-mail materiałów marketingowych, klikając łącze rezygnacji z subskrypcji zamieszczone w otrzymanych od nas pocztą e-mail materiałach marketingowych lub kontaktując się z nami za pomocą informacji kontaktowych podanych w tym Oświadczeniu o ochronie prywatności. W zależności od kraju zamieszkania użytkownik może również zrezygnować z otrzymywania innych typów materiałów marketingowych; w celu uzyskania dalszych informacji prosimy o kontakt z nami za pomocą danych kontaktowych podanych w Oświadczeniu o ochronie prywatności. W niektórych jurysdykcjach osoby fizyczne (np. mieszkańcy Kalifornii) mają prawo żądać niektórych informacji dotyczących ujawniania danych osobowych osobom trzecim do celów ich marketingu bezpośredniego. Aby uzyskać więcej informacji na temat naszych praktyk w zakresie ujawniania danych w celach marketingowych, prosimy o kontakt z nami zgodnie z poniższymi instrukcjami.
* **Reklama oparta na zainteresowaniach**. Zbieramy dane o działaniach online użytkownika i ustalamy jego zainteresowania, aby móc mu udostępniać najbardziej odpowiednie dla niego reklamy. Użytkownik może zrezygnować z otrzymywania od firmy Honeywell reklam opartych na zainteresowaniach, jak opisano w naszych [Informacjach o plikach cookie](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#polish).
* **Programy zachęt finansowych i programy lojalnościowe**. Gromadzimy i wykorzystujemy dane osobowe w celu prowadzenia programów zachęt finansowych i programów lojalnościowych oraz zarządzania nimi. Wykorzystujemy dane osobowe podawane w tych programach, aby oferować wyjątkowe nagrody, śledzić status programu i umożliwiać wymianę punktów w ramach programów na produkty, materiały promocyjne, warsztaty szkoleniowe i inne elementy. W zakresie dozwolonym przez prawo możemy również wykorzystywać wszelkie dane osobowe podane przez użytkownika w kontekście programu zachęt finansowych w jakimkolwiek innym celu określonym w niniejszym Oświadczeniu o ochronie prywatności. Prosimy o zapoznanie się z warunkami każdego programu zachęt finansowych, w którym użytkownik chce się zarejestrować lub uczestniczyć, ponieważ takie warunki mogą być ściśle dostosowane do danego programu. Jeśli użytkownik wyrazi zgodę na udział w takich programach, może ją wycofać w każdej chwili, kontaktując się z nami za pomocą danych kontaktowych podanych na końcu tego Oświadczenia o ochronie prywatności lub zgodnie z instrukcjami podanymi w warunkach danego programu.
* **Podania o pracę**. W związku z podaniem lub zapytaniem o pracę użytkownik może przekazać nam informacje o sobie, takie jak życiorys (CV), referencje zawodowe, informacje na temat wykształcenia i historii zatrudnienia oraz szkoleń zawodowych i certyfikatów. My i członkowie naszej grupy możemy wykorzystywać te informacje w celu rozpatrywania podań o pracę, weryfikacji historii zatrudnienia i kwalifikowania się użytkownika do zatrudnienia, a także w inny sposób określony w każdym odrębnym oświadczeniu o ochronie prywatności lub innych informacjach udostępnionych w związku z podaniem użytkownika. Możemy korzystać z usług osoby trzeciej (np. agencji rekrutacyjnej) lub platformy mediów społecznościowych w celu pozyskiwania, gromadzenia i przechowywania podań o pracę. Więcej informacji można uzyskać w naszym [Oświadczeniu o ochronie prywatności dla kandydatów do pracy](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/applicant-privacy-notice#polish).
* **Badania i analizy**. Możemy wykorzystywać dane osobowe użytkownika do prowadzenia badań i analiz, które pomogą nam analizować jego preferencje zakupowe, identyfikować produkty i usługi najlepiej odpowiadające jego wymaganiom oraz mierzyć skuteczność wyświetlanych mu reklam.
* **Egzekwowanie**. Możemy wykorzystywać zebrane przez nas dane osobowe w celach wykrywania oszustw, naruszeń praw własności intelektualnej i postanowień naszych warunków, naruszeń prawa lub innych przypadków niewłaściwego korzystania z naszych Witryn, a także zapobiegania takim oszustwom, naruszeniom i niewłaściwemu korzystaniu oraz reagowania na nie.

W zakresie dozwolonym przez prawo możemy łączyć dane gromadzone za pośrednictwem naszych Witryn z naszymi innymi danymi o użytkowniku (takimi jak informacje o korzystaniu przez niego z naszych produktów i usług) w celu zapewnienia mu lepszej i bardziej spójnej obsługi podczas interakcji z nami lub w innych celach określonych w tym Oświadczeniu o ochronie prywatności.

**Podstawa prawna przetwarzania danych**

Jeśli jest to wymagane przez prawo, upewniamy się, że istnieje podstawa prawna przetwarzania danych osobowych użytkownika. W większości przypadków nasza podstawa prawna będzie zależeć od danych osobowych i konkretnego kontekstu, w jakim je gromadzimy.

* **Umowa**: przetwarzanie jest niezbędne w celu świadczenia usług, które realizujemy na rzecz użytkownika, lub w celu podjęcia kroków (na żądanie użytkownika) przed wykonaniem takich usług i przewidując takie wykonanie;
* **Obowiązek prawny**: przetwarzanie danych jest konieczne w celu wypełnienia naszych zobowiązań prawnych, w tym przestrzegania obowiązujących przepisów i regulacji, nakazów rządowych i quasi-rządowych oraz zarządzeń sądu lub wezwań sądowych;
* **Zgoda**: przetwarzanie odbywa się w oparciu o wyrażoną przez użytkownika zgodę na przetwarzanie jego danych osobowych w jednym lub kilku określonych celach (np. marketingowych);
* **Uzasadnione interesy**: przetwarzanie jest konieczne do realizacji naszych uzasadnionych interesów, na przykład w celu rozwoju i doskonalenia naszych Witryn, produktów i/lub usług na rzecz naszych klientów; lub
* **Żywotne interesy**: przetwarzanie jest niezbędne do ochrony żywotnych interesów użytkownika (na przykład ze względu na zdrowie i bezpieczeństwo, jeśli użytkownik uczestniczy w spotkaniu w lokalizacji firmy Honeywell).

W razie jakichkolwiek pytań lub potrzeby uzyskania dalszych informacji na temat podstawy prawnej zbierania i wykorzystywania przez nas danych osobowych prosimy o wysłanie wiadomości e-mail na adres: [HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com)

**Anonimizacja danych**

Zgodnie z obowiązującymi przepisami możemy przeprowadzić anonimizację danych osobowych użytkownika, aby nie mogły być już wykorzystywane do celów jego identyfikacji. Zanonimizowane dane nie są uznawane za dane osobowe i dlatego nie podlegają niniejszemu Oświadczeniu o ochronie prywatności. Możemy gromadzić, wykorzystywać, agregować i udostępniać zanonimizowane dane w dowolnym celu.

**Czas przechowywania danych**

Okres przechowywania danych osobowych użytkownika różni się w zależności od celu przetwarzania. Na przykład przechowujemy dane osobowe niezbędne do dostarczania produktów i świadczenia usług lub ułatwiania realizowania transakcji żądanych przez użytkownika tak długo, jak będzie on klientem firmy Honeywell, lub jeśli złoży on podanie o pracę za pośrednictwem naszych Witryn, zachowamy informacje na temat tego podania przez czas określony w informacji o ochronie prywatności udostępnionej mu w związku z podaniem lub zgodnie z innymi wymogami prawa. We wszystkich innych przypadkach przechowujemy dane osobowe użytkownika tak długo, jak to jest konieczne do realizacji celów określonych w tym Oświadczeniu o ochronie prywatności. Po tym czasie są one anonimizowane (jeśli jest to dozwolone przez obowiązujące prawo), usuwane lub niszczone.

**Ujawnianie danych**

Możemy udostępniać dane osobowe użytkownika wybranym osobom trzecim zgodnie z obowiązującym prawem, w tym w sposób opisany poniżej:

* **Spółki wchodzące w skład naszej grupy**. Możemy udostępniać dane osobowe użytkownika naszym podmiotom stowarzyszonym i firmom należącym do grupy, gdy będzie to w uzasadnionym zakresie niezbędne do celów określonych w tym Oświadczeniu o ochronie prywatności.
* **Usługodawcy**. Możemy udostępniać dane osobowe użytkownika firmom, którym zleciliśmy świadczenie w naszym imieniu takich usług, jak hosting witryn internetowych, przeprowadzanie ankiet, przetwarzanie transakcji, analiza naszych Witryn i przeprowadzanie analiz w celu usprawnienia naszej działalności oraz udoskonalenia Witryn, produktów i usług. Wymagamy od tych usługodawców ochrony poufności danych osobowych użytkownika.
* **Dystrybutorzy i inni zaufani partnerzy biznesowi**. Możemy udostępniać dane osobowe użytkownika osobom trzecim zajmującym się dystrybucją naszych produktów i innym zaufanym partnerom biznesowym w celu umożliwienia im wysyłania materiałów marketingowych do użytkownika. Ten proces udostępniania danych osobowych w celach marketingowych będzie odbywać się zgodnie z obowiązującymi przepisami i regulacjami prawnymi.
* **Ujawnianie danych w związku z transakcjami**. W związku z niektórymi transakcjami możemy ujawniać niektóre lub wszystkie dane osobowe użytkownika instytucjom finansowym, podmiotom rządowym oraz firmom wysyłkowym i poczcie, które biorą udział w realizacji transakcji.
* **Ujawnianie danych związane z transakcjami przejęcia lub zbycia**. W niektórych okolicznościach ze względów strategicznych lub innych powodów biznesowych firma Honeywell może podjąć decyzję o sprzedaży, zakupie, zbyciu, fuzji lub innej reorganizacji działalności w niektórych krajach. Możemy ujawniać przechowywane przez nas dane użytkownika w uzasadnionym zakresie koniecznym do prowadzenia negocjacji lub realizacji fuzji, przejęcia, zbycia lub sprzedaży całości bądź części aktywów firmy Honeywell.
* **Ujawnianie danych z innych powodów**. Możemy ujawniać dane osobowe, gdy wymaga tego prawo lub w dobrej wierze, że takie działanie jest niezbędne w celu przestrzegania wymogów prawnych lub prowadzonych wobec nas procesów prawnych, w celu ochrony i obrony naszych praw lub mienia, bądź w szczególnych okolicznościach w celu ochrony osobistego bezpieczeństwa dowolnej osoby.

**Międzynarodowe transfery danych**

Honeywell jest firmą globalną i dane osobowe użytkownika mogą być przekazywane do różnych krajów na całym świecie, takich jak Stany Zjednoczone, Meksyk i Indie, a także przechowywane lub wykorzystywane w takich krajach zgodnie z obowiązującym prawem. Oznacza to, że gdy gromadzimy dane osobowe użytkownika, mogą być one przetwarzane w krajach, w których mogą obowiązywać przepisy o ochronie danych różniące się od przepisów kraju użytkownika. Firma Honeywell zawsze podejmie jednak uzasadnione kroki w celu ochrony prywatności użytkownika i zapewnienia mu poziomu ochrony danych osobowych porównywalnego z poziomem ochrony w kraju jego zamieszkania, co obejmuje wdrożenie standardowych klauzul umownych Komisji Europejskiej. Aby uzyskać więcej informacji na temat odpowiednich zabezpieczeń stosowanych w celu ochrony danych osobowych, prosimy o skontaktowanie się z nami pod adresem: [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com).

**Bezpieczeństwo**

Zobowiązujemy się do ochrony bezpieczeństwa danych osobowych użytkowników. Stosujemy środki techniczne i organizacyjne, aby zapewnić poziom bezpieczeństwa odpowiedni do ryzyka przetwarzania danych osobowych użytkownika. Aby uzyskać więcej informacji na temat ochrony danych osobowych przez firmę Honeywell, prosimy o skontaktowanie się z nami pod adresem [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com)

**Prawa użytkownika**

W zależności od obowiązujących przepisów użytkownik może mieć określone prawa w odniesieniu do swoich danych osobowych.

* Użytkownik może mieć prawo **dostępu do swoich danych osobowych, ich poprawiania lub aktualizowania** lub **żądania ich usunięcia.**
* Użytkownik może **wyrazić sprzeciw** wobec przetwarzania swoich danych osobowych, zażądać od nas **ograniczenia** przetwarzania jego danych osobowych lub ich **przeniesienia**.
* Użytkownik może mieć prawo **do tego, aby nie podejmowano dotyczącej go decyzji w oparciu o wyłącznie zautomatyzowane przetwarzanie, w tym profilowanie,** jeśli taka decyzja wywołuje skutki prawne dotyczące użytkownika lub znacząco na niego wpływa.
* Podobnie, jeśli dane użytkownika zostały zebrane i są przetwarzane przez nas za jego zgodą, wówczas **może on w każdej chwili wycofać swoją zgodę**. Wycofanie zgody nie będzie miało wpływu na zgodność z prawem przetwarzania prowadzonego wcześniej ani nie wpłynie na przetwarzanie danych osobowych użytkownika w oparciu o zgodne z prawem podstawy przetwarzania inne niż zgoda.
* Użytkownik może mieć prawo do **rezygnacji ze sprzedaży swoich danych osobowych**. Firma Honeywell nie sprzedaje danych osobowych użytkowników osobom trzecim w celach zarobkowych. Udostępniamy jednak lub w inny sposób ujawniamy dane osobowe użytkowników osobom trzecim zgodnie z tym Oświadczeniem o ochronie prywatności i [Informacjami o plikach cookie](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#polish). Na przykład współpracujemy z osobami trzecimi w celu dystrybucji naszych produktów, świadczenia użytkownikom pomocy technicznej, obsługi narzędzi i funkcji analitycznych w witrynie internetowej, a także prowadzenia marketingu i sprzedaży naszych produktów i usług. Takie działania mogą wiązać się z ujawnianiem danych osobowych użytkownika osobom trzecim i zgodnie z niektórymi (ale nie wszystkimi) przepisami o ochronie danych mogą być uznawane za „sprzedaż” danych.
* Użytkownik ma prawo **złożyć skargę** do organu ds. ochrony danych odpowiedzialnego za nadzór nad przestrzeganiem przepisów o ochronie danych w jurysdykcji użytkownika w związku z gromadzeniem i wykorzystywaniem przez nas jego danych osobowych, jeśli uzna, że nie jest ono zgodne z przepisami o ochronie danych. Na przykład osoby fizyczne w EOG mają prawo złożyć skargę do właściwego organu ds. ochrony danych; wykaz takich organów jest dostępny pod adresem: [https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/board/members\_en](https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/board/members_en). Mamy jednak nadzieję, że zanim to nastąpi, użytkownik da nam szansę na rozwiązanie wszelkich zgłoszonych przez niego problemów, dlatego prosimy o kontakt w sprawie jakiejkolwiek ewentualnej skargi. Nie będziemy dyskryminować żadnych osób fizycznych w związku z korzystaniem przez nie z ich praw do ochrony danych.

Ułatwimy użytkownikowi korzystanie z praw, które mają do niego zastosowanie zgodnie z obowiązującym prawem. Jednak nawet jeśli dane osobowe użytkownika nie są chronione na mocy przepisów o ochronie danych lub nie podlegają im z innej przyczyny, możemy postarać się zrealizować wszelkie żądania lub zapytania, jakie użytkownik może mieć w związku z naszymi działaniami dotyczącymi przetwarzania danych. W razie pytań dotyczących praw użytkownika lub chęci ich wykonania prosimy o skontaktowanie się z nami pod adresem [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.co](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com)m lub o przesłanie pytań dotyczących prywatności za pośrednictwem naszego interaktywnego formularza online dostępnego po kliknięciu poniższego łącza:

**Dane dzieci**

Nasze Witryny nie są przeznaczone dla dzieci poniżej szesnastego (16.) roku życia i nie powinny one z nich korzystać, a my świadomie nie gromadzimy, nie wykorzystujemy ani nie sprzedajemy danych takich osób. Jeśli użytkownik jest osobą niepełnoletnią zgodnie z prawem obowiązującym w jego kraju, prosimy o nieprzekazywanie żadnych danych osobowych za pośrednictwem naszych Witryn.

**Łącza do innych witryn internetowych**

Nasze Witryny mogą zawierać łącza do witryn internetowych, produktów i usług osób trzecich. Nie ponosimy żadnej odpowiedzialności za te witryny internetowe, produkty, usługi i obowiązujące w nich zasady ani za gromadzenie w nich lub przetwarzanie w inny sposób danych osobowych użytkownika. Praktyki tych osób trzecich podlegają ich własnym zasadom ochrony prywatności. Zachęcamy do zapoznania się z zasadami ochrony prywatności tych osób trzecich.

**Kontakt z nami**

W razie pytań dotyczących tego Oświadczenia o ochronie prywatności lub naszego postępowania z danymi osobowymi, chęci złożenia skargi lub skontaktowania się z naszym inspektorem ochrony danych należy skontaktować się z nami za pomocą podanych niżej danych kontaktowych. Niezwłocznie odniesiemy się do zgłoszonych kwestii i będziemy dążyć do pomyślnego rozstrzygnięcia sprawy.

Interaktywny formularz online:  

E-mail:  

Adres do korespondencji:  
Honeywell Privacy  
4D5  
115 Tabor Road  
Morris Plains, NJ 07950

Bezpłatna infolinia:  

**Zmiany tego Oświadczenia o ochronie prywatności**

To Oświadczenie o ochronie prywatności może być okresowo aktualizowane. W takim przypadku zmienimy „datę ostatniej aktualizacji” na górze Oświadczenia o ochronie prywatności i podejmiemy wszelkie dodatkowe kroki, jakie mogą być wymagane przez prawo.

**Ostatnia aktualizacja: 11 czerwca 2021 r.**

Portuguese

**Última atualização: 11 de junho de 2021**

**Introdução**

Honeywell International Inc. ("**Honeywell**", "**nosso(a)**" ou "**nós**") é o "controlador de dados" das informações pessoais que recolhemos sobre o utilizador ao visitar ou utilizar qualquer um dos nossos websites, ou utilizar produtos, serviços e aplicações que estão associados à presente Declaração de Privacidade (coletivamente, os nossos "**Sites**"). Esta Declaração de Privacidade explica como recolhemos, partilhamos e utilizamos as suas informações pessoais recolhidas desta forma e como pode exercer os seus direitos de privacidade.

Quando interagimos consigo, podemos também fornecer-lhe avisos de privacidade adicionais sobre atividades de processamento específicas ou fornecer-lhe escolhas adicionais sobre a forma como a Honeywell processa as suas informações pessoais nesse momento específico.

Clique numa das ligações abaixo para aceder à secção que lhe interessa:

**A nossa recolha de informações**

* **Informações recolhidas diretamente do utilizador**. Poderemos pedir-lhe informações pessoais para fornecermos um serviço ou realizarmos uma transação que tenha solicitado. Também poderá fornecer-nos informações pessoais quando nos contacta ou interage connosco (por ex.: através de um comentário, uma consulta ou um pedido de suporte ao cliente, visitantes do site) ou registar uma conta para utilizar os nossos Sites. Estas informações pessoais podem incluir:
    * **Dados de identidade,** como o seu nome, cargo, nome da empresa/organização, endereço de e-mail, números de telefone e endereço físico (rua, cidade, localidade, distrito, código postal e/ou país);
    * **Dados de registo,** fornecidos por si quando regista uma conta para utilizar os nossos Sites, incluindo nomes de utilizador e palavras-passe;
    * **Dados de recrutamento,** incluindo informações fornecidas em associação com uma candidatura a emprego ou consulta (conforme descrito abaixo);
    * **Dados de contacto profissional,** como informações relacionadas com outros funcionários, proprietários, diretores, responsáveis ou contratantes de uma organização externa (por exemplo, empresa, sociedade, parceria, sociedade unipessoal, sem fins lucrativos ou agência governamental).
    * **Dados de marketing e comunicações,** incluindo preferências de marketing e subscrições das nossas publicações;
    * **Informações financeiras,** incluindo informações sobre cartões de crédito ou outras contas financeiras, com a finalidade de nos permitir proporcionar a compra de produtos e serviços da Empresa que poderão estar disponíveis nos nossos Sites;
    * **Informações de controlo de exportações,** como a sua nacionalidade, cidadania e país de residência, que nos permitem determinar a sua elegibilidade para receber informações sobre determinadas tecnologias, de acordo com os regulamentos de controlo de exportações;
    * **Dados de transações,** incluindo consultas e encomendas dos nossos produtos e serviços e detalhes de pagamento, incluindo histórico de ordens de compra e informações necessárias para facilitar as transações de pagamento;
    * **Informações de registo de eventos,** incluindo informações fornecidas por si durante o preenchimento de formulários de registo eletrónicos; e
    * **Os seus comentários,** incluindo inquéritos, recomendações ou outros comentários sobre os nossos Sites e os nossos produtos e serviços, de uma forma geral.

Se não nos fornecer as informações pedidas, poderemos não ser capazes de lhe proporcionar o serviço pedido ou concluir a transação.

* **Informações recolhidas automaticamente sobre o utilizador**. Recolhemos certas informações sobre a sua visita aos nossos Sites utilizando cookies e tecnologias de rastreio semelhantes. Respeitaremos sempre os direitos legais que o utilizador possa ter de nos impedir de fazê-lo. Os dados recolhidos desta forma incluem:
    * **Dados de utilização,** incluindo informações sobre a forma como utiliza os nossos Sites, as páginas visualizadas, o número de bytes transferidos, as ligações clicadas, os materiais acedidos, a data e hora de acesso ao Site, o site a partir do qual acedeu a um dos nossos Sites e outras ações realizadas nos Sites; e
    * **Dados técnicos,** como o seu endereço IP, tipo de browser, capacidades, idioma e sistema operativo.

Para obter informações sobre os cookies e outras tecnologias de rastreio semelhantes que utilizamos nos nossos Sites, consulte o nosso [Aviso de Cookies.](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#portuguese)

* **Informações de localização geográfica**. Para Sites específicos, com o seu consentimento, poderemos recolher a localização exata e em tempo real (ou seja, a localização geográfica) do seu dispositivo móvel. Estas informações serão utilizadas apenas para facilitar a sua utilização dos Sites, incluindo pelos nossos fornecedores de serviços, que poderão processar estas informações em associação com a prestação dos serviços em nosso nome. Se concedido, pode ajustar esta autorização gerindo as preferências dos Serviços de Localização através das definições do dispositivo móvel.
* **Informações recolhidas a partir de terceiros**. De acordo com a legislação aplicável, poderemos recolher informações pessoais suas a partir de terceiros, como aplicações e sites de redes sociais, que poderemos combinar com informações que já possuímos sobre si para nos ajudar a melhorar e personalizar os nossos Sites de acordo com as suas preferências e para outras finalidades dispostas na presente Declaração de Privacidade. Poderemos também recolher informações de contacto profissional do seu empregador ou de terceiros para facilitar ou participar em atividades comerciais tradicionais e assuntos administrativos semelhantes.

**A nossa utilização das informações**

Poderemos utilizar as informações pessoais recolhidas através dos nossos Sites ou quando nos contactar para finalidades que incluem:

* **Dados de contacto profissional**. A Honeywell recolhe e utiliza os dados de contacto profissional para efetuar comunicações ou transações, incluindo para efetuar a devida diligência relativamente a um produto ou serviço, ou para fornecer ou receber um produto ou serviço. Por exemplo, a Honeywell poderá recolher e utilizar estes dados de contacto profissional para facilitar e gerir encomendas, contratos, garantias, manutenção e funções profissionais semelhantes, para efeitos de análise e recolha de crédito, de modo a ajudar na nossa própria conformidade interna e requisitos legais, e (se necessário) para defender os nossos interesses e reivindicações.
* **Serviços e transações**. Poderemos utilizar as suas informações pessoais para lhe proporcionar serviços ou realizar transações que tenha solicitado, incluindo, sem limitações, o fornecimento de informações sobre produtos ou serviços da Empresa que tenha adquirido ou utilizado por qualquer outra forma, o registo de produtos adquiridos, o processamento de encomendas de produtos, o processamento de garantias, a substituição de manuais de produtos, a resposta a pedidos de suporte ao cliente e a utilização dos nossos Sites.
* **Administrar e proteger o nosso negócio e os nossos Sites**. Poderemos utilizar as suas informações pessoais para administrar e proteger o nosso negócio e os nossos Sites, incluindo tarefas de resolução de problemas, manutenção do sistema, suporte, geração de relatórios e alojamento de dados.
* **Melhorar o nosso negócio e os nossos Sites, produtos e serviços**. Poderemos utilizar as suas informações pessoais para realizar análises de negócio ou para outros fins que nos ajudem a desenvolver e melhorar a qualidade do nosso negócio e dos nossos Sites, produtos e serviços (incluindo produtos e serviços novos); por exemplo, personalizando os nossos Sites de acordo com as suas preferências ou interesses específicos.
* **Marketing**. De acordo com as leis e regulamentos aplicáveis, podemos utilizar as suas informações pessoais para informá-lo sobre produtos ou serviços que possam ser do seu interesse e para comunicar consigo sobre ofertas, eventos e notícias, pesquisas, ofertas especiais e tópicos relacionados. Pode cancelar a subscrição das comunicações de marketing enviadas por e-mail a qualquer momento, gratuitamente, através da ligação "Anular a subscrição" existente nos materiais de marketing por e-mail que recebe de nós ou contactando-nos utilizando as informações de contacto listadas na presente Declaração de Privacidade. Dependendo do seu país de residência, também poderá desativar outros tipos de comunicações de marketing; contacte-nos utilizando as informações de contacto listadas na Declaração de Privacidade para obter mais informações. Algumas jurisdições fornecem a pessoas (por exemplo, residentes na Califórnia) o direito de solicitar determinadas informações relativas à nossa divulgação de informações pessoais a terceiros para efeitos de marketing direto do terceiro. Para obter mais informações sobre as nossas práticas de divulgação de dados para efeitos de marketing, queira contactar-nos de acordo com as instruções indicadas abaixo.
* **Publicidade Baseada em Interesses**. Recolhemos dados sobre as suas atividades online e identificamos os seus interesses, para que possamos fornecer-lhe publicidade mais relevante. O utilizador pode optar por não receber publicidade baseada em interesses da Honeywell, conforme descrito no nosso [Aviso de Cookies](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#portuguese).
* **Programas de Fidelidade e Incentivos Financeiros**. Recolhemos e utilizamos informações pessoais para manter e administrar os nossos programas de fidelidade e incentivos financeiros. Utilizamos as informações pessoais que nos fornece nestes programas para proporcionar recompensas únicas, acompanhar o estado do programa e facilitar a troca de pontos do programa por produtos, materiais promocionais, workshops de formação e outros itens. Na extensão permitida por lei, podemos também utilizar quaisquer informações pessoais que nos forneça no contexto de um programa de incentivos financeiros para qualquer outro fim estabelecido na presente Declaração de Privacidade. Consulte os termos e condições de cada programa de incentivos financeiros no qual gostaria de registar-se ou participar, uma vez que esses termos e condições podem ser especificamente adaptados ao programa aplicável. Se consentir em participar nestes programas, poderá retirar esse consentimento em qualquer altura, ao contactar-nos utilizando os dados de contacto no final desta Declaração de Privacidade ou de acordo com as instruções estabelecidas nos termos e condições do programa aplicável.
* **Candidaturas de emprego**. Em associação a uma candidatura de emprego, poderá fornecer-nos informações sobre si, como um currículo, referências profissionais, informações sobre habilitações académicas e antecedentes profissionais e informações sobre formação profissional e certificações. Nós e membros do nosso grupo poderemos utilizar estas informações para efeitos de análise da candidatura, verificação de antecedentes e elegibilidade de emprego, e para outras finalidades dispostas numa declaração de privacidade separada ou noutro aviso disponibilizado em associação à sua candidatura. Poderemos utilizar um terceiro (por exemplo, recrutador de emprego) ou plataforma de rede social para solicitar, recolher e reter candidaturas de emprego. Para obter mais informações, leia o nosso [Aviso de Privacidade do Candidato](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/applicant-privacy-notice#portuguese).
* **Investigação e análise**. Podemos utilizar as suas informações pessoais para conduzir pesquisas e análises que nos ajudem a avaliar as suas preferências de compra, identificar os produtos e serviços que melhor atendam às suas necessidades e medir a eficácia da publicidade que lhe oferecemos.
* **Aplicação**. Poderemos utilizar as informações pessoais recolhidas para detetar, prevenir e reagir a fraude, violação propriedade intelectual, violação dos nossos termos e condições, violação da lei e outra utilização indevida dos nossos Sites.

Onde permitido por lei, poderemos combinar as informações recolhidas através dos nossos Sites com outras informações que tenhamos sobre si (como informações sobre a sua utilização dos nossos produtos e serviços) para lhe proporcionarmos uma experiência de cliente melhorada e consistente quando interage connosco para as finalidades estabelecidas na presente Declaração de Privacidade.

**A base jurídica pela qual processamos as informações**

Quando exigido por lei, garantiremos que existe uma base jurídica para o processamento das suas informações pessoais. Na maioria dos casos, a nossa base jurídica dependerá das informações pessoais em questão e do contexto específico em que as recolhermos.

* **Contrato**: o processamento é necessário para a execução dos serviços que lhe prestamos, ou para tomar medidas (a seu pedido) antes, em antecipação, da execução de tais serviços;
* **Obrigação legal**: o processamento é necessário para o cumprimento das nossas obrigações legais, incluindo o cumprimento das leis, regulamentações, pedidos governamentais e para-governamentais, ordem judicial ou intimação;
* **Consentimento**: o processamento é baseado no seu consentimento do processamento das suas informações pessoais para uma ou mais finalidades especificadas (por ex.: marketing);
* **Interesses legítimos**: o processamento é necessário para satisfazer os nossos interesses legítimos; por exemplo, para desenvolver e melhorar os nossos Sites, produtos e/ou serviços para o benefício dos nossos clientes; ou
* **Interesses vitais**: o processamento é necessário para proteger os seus interesses vitais (por exemplo, motivos de saúde e segurança se participar numa reunião numa localização da Honeywell).

Se tiver dúvidas ou necessitar de mais informações sobre a base jurídica pela qual recolhemos e utilizamos as suas informações pessoais, envie um e-mail para [HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com)

**Anonimização das informações**

De acordo com a legislação aplicável, poderemos anonimizar as suas informações pessoais para que estas não possam ser utilizadas para identificá-lo. As informações anonimizadas não são consideradas informações pessoais e, portanto, não estão sujeitas a esta Declaração de Privacidade. Podemos recolher, utilizar, agregar e partilhar informações anonimizadas para qualquer finalidade.

**Durante quanto tempo mantemos as informações**

O período durante o qual armazenamos as suas informações pessoais varia consoante a finalidade do processamento. Por exemplo, armazenamos as informações pessoais necessárias para lhe fornecer produtos e serviços ou para realizar transações que tenha solicitado enquanto cliente da Honeywell ou se submeter uma candidatura de emprego através dos nossos Sites, iremos reter os detalhes da candidatura conforme estabelecido na presente declaração de privacidade ou noutro aviso disponibilizado em associação à candidatura ou conforme exigido por lei. Em todos os outros casos, armazenamos as suas informações pessoais durante o período de tempo necessário para cumprir as finalidades descritas na presente Declaração de Privacidade, após o qual essas informações serão anonimizadas (quando permitido pela legislação aplicável), eliminadas ou destruídas.

**Divulgação de informações**

Poderemos partilhar as suas informações pessoais com terceiros selecionados, de acordo com a legislação aplicável, incluindo conforme disposto abaixo:

* **Empresas do nosso grupo**. Poderemos partilhar as suas informações pessoais com afiliadas e empresas do nosso grupo, conforme razoavelmente aceitável para as finalidades dispostas na presente Declaração de Privacidade.
* **Fornecedores de serviços**. Poderemos partilhar as suas informações pessoais com empresas que tenhamos contratado para o fornecimento de serviços em nosso nome, como o alojamento de sites, a realização de inquéritos, o processamento de transações, a análise dos nossos Sites e a realização de análise para o melhoramento da qualidade do nosso negócio e dos nossos Sites, produtos e serviços. Exigimos que estes fornecedores de serviços protejam a confidencialidade das suas informações pessoais.
* **Distribuidores e outros parceiros de negócio fidedignos**. Poderemos partilhar as suas informações pessoais com terceiros que distribuem os nossos produtos e outros parceiros de negócio fidedignos para finalidades que incluem permitir que estes terceiros lhe enviem comunicações de marketing. Esta partilha de informações pessoais para fins de marketing será realizada de acordo com as leis e regulamentos aplicáveis.
* **Divulgação associada a transações**. Em associação com determinadas transações, as suas informações pessoais podem ser total ou parcialmente divulgadas a instituições financeiras, entidades do Estado e empresas de transportes ou serviços postais envolvidos na transação.
* **Divulgações associadas a aquisições ou alienações**. Poderão surgir circunstâncias em que, por motivos estratégicos ou outros motivos de negócio, a Honeywell decida vender, comprar, alienar, fundir ou, por qualquer outra forma, reorganizar o negócio em alguns países. Podemos divulgar informações do utilizador na medida do razoavelmente necessário para proceder com a negociação ou conclusão de uma fusão, aquisição, alienação ou venda do total ou de uma parte dos bens da Honeywell.
* **Divulgação por outros motivos**. Poderemos divulgar Informações pessoais se tal for exigido ou autorizado por lei ou em crença de boa-fé de que tal ação é necessária para cumprir com requisitos ou processos legais impostos, para proteger e defender os nossos direitos ou propriedade ou, em circunstâncias urgentes, para proteger a segurança pessoal de qualquer indivíduo.

**Transferências internacionais**

A Honeywell é uma organização global e as suas informações pessoais podem ser transferidas para, mantidas, armazenadas ou utilizadas em várias localizações a nível mundial, tais como os EUA, o México e a Índia, de acordo com a lei aplicável. Isto significa que, quando recolhemos as suas informações pessoais, estas podem ser processadas em países que podem ter leis de proteção de dados diferentes das leis do seu país. No entanto, a Honeywell tomará sempre medidas razoáveis para proteger a sua privacidade e proporcionar um nível de proteção das informações pessoais que seja comparável à do seu país de residência, o que inclui a implementação das Cláusulas Contratuais Padrão da Comissão Europeia. Para obter mais informações sobre as salvaguardas adequadas em vigor para proteger as suas informações pessoais, contacte-nos em [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com).

**Segurança**

Estamos empenhados em proteger a segurança das suas informações pessoais. Utilizamos medidas técnicas e organizacionais para proporcionar um nível de segurança adequado ao risco de processamento das suas informações pessoais. Para obter mais informações sobre a forma como a Honeywell protege as suas informações pessoais, contacte-nos em [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com)

**Os seus direitos**

Dependendo da lei aplicável, poderá ter certos direitos no que diz respeito às suas informações pessoais.

* Pode ter o direito de **aceder, corrigir, atualizar** ou **solicitar a eliminação** das suas informações pessoais.
* Pode **opor-se** ao processamento das suas informações pessoais, solicitar-nos para **restringir** o processamento das suas informações pessoais ou solicitar a **portabilidade** das suas informações pessoais.
* Pode ter o direito **de não se tomar uma decisão sobre si que se baseie unicamente no processamento automatizado, incluindo a criação de perfis,** se essa decisão produzir efeitos legais sobre si ou o afetar significativamente.
* Da mesma forma, se tivermos recolhido e processado as suas informações pessoais com o seu consentimento, então **poderá retirar o seu consentimento em qualquer altura**. A revogação do seu consentimento não afetará a legalidade de qualquer processamento que tenhamos realizado antes da mesma, nem afetará o processamento das suas informações pessoais realizado com base em fundamentos de processamento legais além do consentimento.
* Pode ter o direito de **optar pela exclusão da venda das suas informações pessoais**. A Honeywell não vende as suas informações pessoais a terceiros com fins lucrativos. No entanto, partilhamos ou divulgamos as suas informações pessoais a terceiros, de acordo com a presente Declaração de Privacidade e o nosso [Aviso de Cookies](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#portuguese). Por exemplo, comprometemo-nos com terceiros para distribuir os nossos produtos, fornecer-lhe assistência técnica, operar ferramentas e funcionalidades analíticas do website, e envolver-nos no marketing e na venda dos nossos produtos e serviços. Tais atividades podem envolver a divulgação das suas informações pessoais a terceiros e podem ser consideradas uma "venda" de dados ao abrigo de certas (mas não todas) leis de proteção de dados.
* Tem o direito de **apresentar queixa** a uma autoridade de proteção de dados responsável pela supervisão do cumprimento da lei de proteção de dados na sua jurisdição sobre a nossa recolha e utilização das suas informações pessoais, se considerar que o nosso processamento das suas informações pessoais não cumpre a lei de proteção de dados. Por exemplo, os indivíduos no EEE têm o direito de apresentar uma queixa à Autoridade de Proteção de Dados competente, cuja lista pode ser consultada em: [https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/board/members\_en](https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/board/members_en). No entanto, gostaríamos que nos desse a oportunidade de resolver tais problemas. Portanto, não hesite em contactar-nos em relação a qualquer reclamação que possa ter. Não discriminaremos pessoas pelo exercício dos seus direitos de privacidade de dados.

Facilitaremos o exercício dos direitos que se aplicam a si, de acordo com a legislação aplicável. Contudo, mesmo que as suas informações pessoais não beneficiem de proteção ao abrigo de, ou de outra forma sujeitas a, uma lei de proteção de dados, poderemos procurar acomodar qualquer pedido ou inquérito que possa ter em relação às nossas atividades de processamento de dados. Se tiver quaisquer perguntas sobre os seus direitos, ou caso pretenda exercer os seus direitos, contacte-nos em [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com) ou submeta perguntas relacionadas com a privacidade através do nosso formulário Web interativo no seguinte link:

**Informações de menores**

Os nossos Sites não são dirigidos a, e não devem ser utilizados por, crianças menores de dezasseis (16) anos e não recolhemos, utilizamos ou vendemos intencionalmente informações de tais pessoas. Se for menor de idade, tal como entendido pela legislação do seu país, não submeta quaisquer informações pessoais através dos nossos Sites.

**Ligações para outros sites**

Os nossos Sites poderão conter ligações para sites, produtos e serviços de terceiros. Não temos qualquer responsabilidade relativamente a esses sites, produtos e serviços, às respetivas políticas, nem à recolha ou outro processamento das suas informações pessoais. As práticas destes terceiros são governadas por políticas de privacidade próprias. Encorajamo-lo a conhecer as políticas de privacidade desses terceiros.

**Contacte-nos**

Se tiver quaisquer perguntas relacionadas com a presente Declaração de Privacidade ou com o nosso processamento das suas informações pessoais, ou se quiser apresentar uma reclamação ou contactar o nosso Responsável pela Proteção de Dados, contacte-nos utilizando as informações listadas abaixo. Daremos toda a atenção à sua questão para obtermos uma resolução satisfatória.

Formulário Web interativo:  

E-mail:  

Endereço postal:  
Honeywell Privacy  
4D5  
115 Tabor Road  
Morris Plains, NJ 07950

Número gratuito:  

**Alterações a esta Declaração de Privacidade**

Poderemos ocasionalmente atualizar esta Declaração de Privacidade. Quando o fizermos, iremos rever a data de "última atualização" indicada na parte superior da Declaração de Privacidade e tomaremos os passos adicionais exigidos por lei.

**Última atualização: 11 de junho de 2021**

Romanian

**Ultima actualizare la 11 iunie 2021**

**Introducere**

Honeywell International Inc. („**Honeywell**","**al nostru**", "**noi**", sau"**noi**"), este "controlorul de date" al informațiilor personale pe care le colectăm despre dvs. atunci când vizitați sau utilizați oricare dintre site-urile noastre web sau utilizați produse, servicii și aplicații care sunt legate de această Declarație de confidențialitate (colectiv, site-urile"**noastre**"). Această Declarație de confidențialitate explică modul în care colectăm, împărtășim și folosim informațiile dvs. personale colectate în acest mod și cum vă puteți exercita drepturile de confidențialitate.

Când interacționăm cu dvs., vă putem oferi, de asemenea, notificări de confidențialitate suplimentare despre activități de prelucrare specifice sau vă putem oferi opțiuni suplimentare despre modul în care Honeywell vă procesează informațiile personale în acel moment.

Faceți clic pe unul dintre linkurile de mai jos pentru a accesa secțiunea care vă interesează:

**Colecția noastră de informații**

* **Informații colectate direct de la dvs**. Este posibil să vă solicităm informații personale pentru furnizarea unui serviciu sau efectuarea unei tranzacții solicitate de dumneavoastră. Este posibil, de asemenea, să ne furnizați informații cu caracter personal atunci când ne contactați sau intrați în legătură cu noi (de ex., cu un comentariu, o întrebare sau o solicitare de asistență pentru clienți, vizitatorii site-ului) sau atunci când înregistrați un cont pentru a utiliza Site-urile noastre. Aceste informații personale pot include:
    * **Date referitoare la identitate,** cum ar fi numele dvs., funcția, numele companiei/organizației, adresa de e-mail, numărul de telefon și de fax și adresa fizică (inclusiv strada, orașul, statul, codul poștal și/sau țara);
    * **Datele de înregistrare,** furnizate de dvs. atunci când înregistrați un cont pentru utilizare pe Site-urile noastre, inclusiv numele de utilizator și parolele;
    * **Date privind recrutările,** inclusiv informațiile transmise în legătură cu o candidatură la un job sau o solicitare de informații (după cum se descrie mai jos);
    * **Date de contact despre afaceri,** cum ar fi informații legate de alți angajați, proprietari, directori, ofițeri sau contractori ai unei organizații terțe (de ex., afaceri, companii, parteneriate, întreprinderi individuale, non-profit sau agenții guvernamentale).
    * **Datele de marketing și comunicare,** inclusiv preferințele dvs. de marketing și abonamentele la publicațiile noastre;
    * **Informații financiare,** inclusiv informații despre cardul de credit sau alte informații despre conturi financiare, cu scopul de a ne permite să vă facilităm achiziția de produse și servicii oferite de Companie, care pot fi disponibile pe Site-urile noastre;
    * **Informații pentru controlul exporturilor,** cum ar fi naționalitatea, cetățenia și țara de reședință, care ne vor permite să stabilim eligibilitatea dumneavoastră pentru primirea de informații despre anumite tehnologii, în conformitate cu reglementările privind controlul exporturilor;
    * **Date legate de tranzacție,** inclusiv întrebări despre și comenzi pentru produsele și serviciile noastre și detalii privind plățile către și de la dvs., inclusiv istoricul comenzilor de achiziție și informațiile necesare pentru a facilita tranzacțiile de plată;
    * **Informații privind înregistrările la evenimente,** inclusiv informațiile pe care le furnizați atunci când completați formulare de înregistrare electronică; și
    * **Feedback-ul dumneavoastră,** inclusiv sondaje, recomandări sau alte feedback-uri de la dvs. despre site-urile noastre, precum și despre produsele și serviciile noastre în general.

Atunci când nu furnizați informațiile solicitate, este posibil să nu putem să vă furnizăm serviciul solicitat sau să vă finalizăm tranzacția.

* **Informații pe care le colectăm automat despre dvs**. Colectăm anumite informații despre vizita dvs. pe site-urile noastre utilizând cookie-uri și tehnologii similare de urmărire. Vom respecta întotdeauna orice drepturi legale pe care le aveți pentru a ne împiedica să facem acest lucru. Datele colectate în acest mod includ:
    * **Date despre utilizare,** inclusiv informații despre modul în care utilizați site-urile noastre, ce pagini vedeți, numărul de octeți transferați, linkurile pe care faceți clic, materialele pe care le accesați, data și ora la care accesați site-ul, site-ul web de la care v-ați conectat la unul dintre site-urile noastre și alte acțiuni întreprinse în cadrul Site-urilor; și
    * **Date tehnice,** cum ar fi adresa IP (Protocol internet), tipul și capacitățile browser-ului, limba și sistemul de operare.

Pentru informații despre cookie-uri și alte tehnologii similare de urmărire pe care le folosim pe site-urile noastre, vă rugăm să consultați site-ul nostru [Notificare cookie](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#romanian).

* **Informații de localizare geografică**. Pentru anumite site-uri, cu consimțământul dvs. expres, putem colecta locația exactă, în timp real (adică locația geografică) a dispozitivului dvs. mobil. Aceste informații vor fi utilizate numai în scopul facilitării utilizării de către dvs. a site-urilor, inclusiv de către furnizorii noștri de servicii care pot procesa aceste informații în legătură cu furnizarea de servicii în numele nostru. Dacă vi se oferă, puteți ajusta acest consimțământ gestionând preferințele Serviciilor de localizare prin setările dispozitivului dvs. mobil.
* **Informații colectate de la terțe părți**. În conformitate cu legislația aplicabilă, putem colecta informații personale despre dvs. de la terți, cum ar fi site-uri și aplicații de social media și le putem combina cu informații pe care le deținem deja, pentru a ne ajuta să îmbunătățim și să personalizăm site-urile noastre în funcție de preferințele dvs. și în alte scopuri stabilite în această Declarație de confidențialitate. Putem, de asemenea, să colectăm informațiile de contact ale companiei dvs. de la angajatorul dvs. sau de la alte terțe părți pentru a facilita sau a ne angaja în alt mod în activități comerciale tradiționale și în probleme administrative similare.

**Cum utilizăm informațiile**

Putem să utilizăm informațiile cu caracter personal colectate prin intermediul Site-urilor noastre sau atunci când ne contactați în diferite scopuri, printre care și următoarele:

* **Date de contact pentru afaceri**. Honeywell colectează și folosește date de contact pentru afaceri pentru a se angaja în comunicări sau tranzacții, inclusiv pentru efectuarea diligenței cu privire la sau furnizarea sau primirea unui produs sau serviciu. De exemplu, Honeywell poate colecta și utiliza aceste date de contact ale companiei pentru a facilita și gestiona comenzile, contractele, garanțiile, întreținerea și funcții comerciale similare, în scopuri de analiză și colectare a creditelor, pentru a ne ajuta cu propriile noastre cerințe legale de conformitate și (dacă este necesar) pentru a ne apăra interesele și revendicările.
* **Servicii și tranzacții**. Putem folosi informațiile dumneavoastră cu caracter personale pentru a presta servicii sau pentru a efectua tranzacții pe le-ați solicitat, care includ, dar nu se limitează la, oferirea de informații cu privire la produsele sau serviciile Companiei pe care le-ați achiziționat sau utilizat în alt mod, înregistrarea produselor achiziționate, procesarea comenzilor de produse, gestionarea solicitărilor de garanție, înlocuirea manualelor produselor, răspunsurile la solicitările de reparații ale clienților, facilitarea utilizării Site-urilor noastre.
* **Administrarea și protejarea afacerii și a site-urilor noastre**. Este posibil să utilizăm informațiile cu caracter personal pentru a ne administra și proteja afacerile și Site-urile, inclusiv prin depanare, întreținere de sistem, asistență, raportarea și găzduirea de date.
* **Îmbunătățirea afacerii, site-urilor, produselor și serviciilor noastre**. Este posibil să utilizăm informațiile dumneavoastră cu caracter personal pentru a efectua analize ale activității noastre sau în alte scopuri, care ne ajută să ne dezvoltăm și să ne îmbunătățim calitatea activității, a Site-urilor, produselor și serviciilor (inclusiv produsele și serviciile noi), de exemplu, prin personalizarea Site-urilor noastre în baza preferințelor sau intereselor dumneavoastră.
* **Marketing**. În conformitate cu legile și reglementările în vigoare, este posibil să utilizăm informațiile dumneavoastră cu caracter personal pentru a vă informa cu privire la produse sau servicii de care ați putea fi interesat și pentru a comunica în alte moduri cu dumneavoastră cu privire la evenimente, știri, chestionare, oferte speciale și subiecte asociate. Puteți să refuzați comunicările de marketing trimise prin e-mail în orice moment, gratuit, prin utilizarea linkului de „dezabonare” din materialele de marketing prin e-mail primite de la noi sau contactându-ne folosind informațiile de contact menționate în această Declarație de confidențialitate. În funcție de țara de reședință, este posibil să puteți renunța la alte tipuri de comunicări de marketing; vă rugăm să ne contactați folosind informațiile de contact enumerate în Declarația de confidențialitate pentru mai multe informații. Unele jurisdicții oferă persoanelor fizice (de exemplu, rezidenții din California) dreptul de a solicita anumite informații cu privire la divulgarea informațiilor personale către terți în scopuri de marketing direct ale terților. Pentru mai multe informații despre practicile noastre de divulgare a datelor în scopuri de marketing, vă rugăm să ne contactați în conformitate cu instrucțiunile enumerate mai jos.
* **Publicitate bazată pe interese**. Colectăm date despre activitățile dvs. online și vă identificăm interesele, astfel încât să vă putem oferi reclame care sunt cele mai relevante pentru dvs. Puteți renunța la primirea publicității bazate pe interese de la Honeywell așa cum este descris în documentul nostru [Notificare cookie](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#romanian).
* **Programele de stimulare financiară și de loialitate**. Colectăm și folosim informații personale pentru a menține și administra programele noastre de stimulare financiară și loialitate. Folosim informațiile personale pe care le furnizați în aceste programe pentru a oferi recompense unice, pentru a urmări starea programului dvs. și pentru a facilita schimbul de puncte de program pentru produse, materiale promoționale, ateliere de instruire și alte articole. În măsura permisă de lege, putem folosi, de asemenea, orice informație personală pe care o furnizați în contextul unui program de stimulare financiară pentru orice alt scop stabilit în această declarație de confidențialitate. Vă rugăm să consultați termenii și condițiile fiecărui program de stimulare financiară în care doriți să vă înregistrați sau să participați, deoarece astfel de termeni și condiții pot fi strict adaptate la programul aplicabil. Dacă sunteți de acord să participați la aceste programe, vă puteți retrage consimțământul în orice moment contactându-ne folosind datele de contact de la sfârșitul acestei Declarații de confidențialitate sau în conformitate cu instrucțiunile stabilite în termenii și condițiile programului aplicabil.
* **Cereri de angajare**. În legătură cu o cerere sau o solicitare de loc de muncă, ne puteți furniza informații despre dvs., cum ar fi un CV/curriculum vitae, referințe profesionale, informații despre educație și experiența profesională și informații despre pregătirea profesională și certificări. Noi și membrii grupului nostru putem folosi aceste informații în scopul luării în considerare a angajării, a face verificări de fond și eligibilitatea pentru angajare și, după cum se prevede în orice declarație de confidențialitate separată sau în altă notificare pusă la dispoziție în legătură cu cererea dvs. Putem folosi un terț (de exemplu, un recrutor de locuri de muncă) sau o platformă de socializare pentru a solicita, colecta și păstra cererile de angajare. Pentru mai multe informații, vă rugăm să citiți [Notificarea de confidențialitate a solicitantului](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/applicant-privacy-notice#romanian) .
* **Cercetare și analize**. Putem folosi informațiile dvs. personale pentru a efectua cercetări și analize care să ne ajute să analizăm preferințele dvs. de cumpărare, să identificăm produsele și serviciile care îndeplinesc cel mai bine cerințele dvs. și să măsurăm eficacitatea publicității pe care v-o servim.
* **Executare**: Este posibil să folosim informațiile cu caracter personal colectate pentru a detecta, preveni și reacționa la cazuri de fraudă, încălcări ale drepturilor de proprietate intelectuală, încălcări ale termenilor și condițiilor noastre sau ale legii, sau alte tipuri de utilizare abuzivă a Site-urilor.

Atunci când legea ne-o permite, este posibil să combinăm informațiile colectate prin Site-urile noastre cu alte informații pe care le deținem despre dumneavoastră (cum ar fi informațiile despre utilizarea produselor și serviciilor noastre) pentru a vă oferi o experiență îmbunătățită și constantă atunci când interacționați cu noi sau în alte scopuri prevăzute în această Declarație de confidențialitate.

**Temeiul juridic în baza căruia prelucrăm informațiile**

Atunci când legea o impune, ne vom asigura că există o bază legală pentru procesarea informațiilor dumneavoastră cu caracter personal. În majoritatea cazurilor, baza noastră juridică va depinde de informațiile personale în cauză și de contextul specific în care le colectăm.

* **Contract**: Prelucrarea este necesară pentru prestarea serviciilor pe care vi le oferim sau pentru a lua măsuri (la cererea dvs.) înainte și în anticiparea efectuării acestor servicii;
* **Obligație legală**: procesarea este necesară pentru a ne conforma cu obligațiile noastre legale, inclusiv conformitatea cu legile, reglementările, solicitărilor guvernamentale și cvasi-guvernamentale, ordinele judecătorești sau citațiile aplicabile;
* **Consimțământ**: procesarea se bazează pe consimțământul dumneavoastră pentru procesarea informațiilor cu caracter personal pentru unul sau mai multe scopuri specificate (de ex. marketing);
* **Interese legitime**: procesarea este necesară pentru interesele noastre legitime, de exemplu pentru dezvoltarea și îmbunătățirea Site-urilor, produselor și/sau serviciilor în beneficiul clienților; sau
* **Interese vitale**: prelucrarea este necesară pentru a vă proteja interesele vitale (de ex., motive de sănătate și siguranță dacă participați la o întâlnire într-o locație Honeywell).

Dacă aveți întrebări sau aveți nevoie de informații suplimentare cu privire la baza legală pe baza căreia colectăm și folosim informațiile dvs. personale, vă rugăm să trimiteți un e-mail la [HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com)

**Anonimizarea informațiilor**

În conformitate cu legile în vigoare, este posibil să anonimizăm informațiile dumneavoastră cu caracter personal, astfel încât să nu mai poată fi utilizate pentru identificare. Informațiile anonimizate nu sunt considerate informații cu caracter personal și, prin urmare, nu se supun acestei Declarații de confidențialitate. Este posibil să colectăm, să utilizăm, să agregăm și să distribuim informațiile anonimizate în orice scop.

**Cât timp păstrăm informațiile**

Perioada de păstrare a informațiilor dumneavoastră cu caracter personal depinde de scopul procesării. De exemplu, stocăm informațiile personale necesare pentru a vă oferi produse și servicii sau pentru a facilita tranzacțiile pe care le-ați solicitat, atâta timp cât sunteți client al Honeywell sau dacă trimiteți o cerere de angajare prin intermediul site-urilor noastre, vom păstra detalii despre cererea dvs. așa cum este stabilit în notificarea de confidențialitate care vă este pusă la dispoziție în legătură cu cererea dvs. sau după cum se impune altfel prin lege. În toate celelalte cazuri, stocăm informațiile dumneavoastră cu caracter personal atât timp cât este necesar pentru a îndeplini scopurile menționate în această declarație de confidențialitate, după care nu sunt nici anonimizate (acolo unde o permite legea în vigoare), nici șterse și nici distruse.

**Divulgarea informațiilor**

Este posibil să distribuim informațiile dumneavoastră cu caracter personal în conformitate cu legile în vigoare, inclusiv după cum se prevede mai jos:

* **Companiile din grupul nostru**. Este posibil să distribuim informațiile dumneavoastră cu caracter personal companiilor din grupul nostru, după cum este necesar în mod rezonabil pentru scopurile prevăzute în această Declarație de confidențialitate.
* **Prestatori de servicii**. Este posibil să distribuim informațiile dumneavoastră cu caracter personal companiilor contractate de noi, pentru ca acestea să presteze servicii în numele nostru, de exemplu pentru găzduirea site-urilor web, realizarea de sondaje, procesarea tranzacțiilor, analizarea Site-urilor noastre și efectuarea analizelor cu scopul de a îmbunătăți calitatea activității, Site-urilor și produselor și serviciilor noastre. Impunem acestor furnizori de servicii să protejeze confidențialitatea informațiilor dumneavoastră cu caracter personal.
* **Distribuitori și alți parteneri de afaceri de încredere**. Este posibil să distribuim informațiile dumneavoastră cu caracter personal terților care distribuie produsele noastre și altor parteneri de afaceri de încredere în scopuri care includ acordarea permisiunii respectivilor terți pentru a vă trimite comunicări de marketing. O astfel de distribuire a informațiilor dumneavoastră cu caracter personal va fi executată în conformitate cu legile și reglementările în vigoare.
* **Divulgarea în legătură cu tranzacțiile**. În contextul anumitor tranzacții, este posibil să divulgăm parțial sau în totalitate informațiile dumneavoastră cu caracter personal unor instituții financiare, entități guvernamentale și companii de expediere sau de servicii poștale implicate în ducerea la îndeplinire a tranzacției.
* **Dezvăluiri în legătură cu achiziții sau reducerea activelor**. Pot apărea circumstanțe în care, din motive strategice sau de altă natură, Honeywell decide să vândă, să cumpere, să cedeze, să fuzioneze sau să reorganizeze în alt mod afacerile din unele țări. Este posibil să divulgăm informații stocate cu privire la dvs., în măsura considerată rezonabilă și necesară pentru a avansa cu negocierile sau cu procedura de fuziune, achiziție, vânzare parțială sau totală a activelor Honeywell.
* **Dezvăluire din alte motive**. Este posibil să divulgăm informații cu caracter personal dacă acest lucru este impus sau autorizat prin lege, sau în situații în care considerăm, de bună-credință, că acest lucru este necesar pentru a respecta cerințele legale sau procedurile legale intentate împotriva noastră, pentru a ne proteja și apăra drepturile sau proprietățile sau, în situații urgente, pentru a proteja siguranța personală a oricărui individ.

**Transferuri internaționale**

Honeywell este o organizație globală, iar informațiile dvs. personale pot fi transferate, păstrate, stocate sau utilizate în diferite locații din întreaga lume, cum ar fi SUA, Mexic și India, în conformitate cu legislația aplicabilă. Aceasta înseamnă că, atunci când colectăm informațiile dvs. personale, acestea pot fi prelucrate în țări care pot avea legi privind protecția datelor care sunt diferite de legile țării dvs. Cu toate acestea, Honeywell va lua întotdeauna măsuri rezonabile pentru a vă proteja confidențialitatea și pentru a oferi un nivel de protecție a informațiilor personale care este comparabil cu cel al țării dvs. de reședință, care include punerea în aplicare a clauzelor contractuale standard ale Comisiei Europene. Pentru mai multe informații despre măsurile de protecție adecvate pentru a vă proteja informațiile personale, vă rugăm să ne contactați la [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com).

**Securitate**

Ne angajăm să protejăm securitatea informațiilor dvs. personale. Folosim măsuri tehnice și organizaționale pentru a oferi un nivel de securitate adecvat riscului de prelucrare a informațiilor dvs. personale. Pentru mai multe informații despre modul în care Honeywell vă protejează informațiile personale, vă rugăm să ne contactați la [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com)

**Drepturile dvs.**

În funcție de legislația aplicabilă, este posibil să aveți anumite drepturi cu privire la informațiile dvs. personale.

* Este posibil să aveți dreptul să **accesați, corectați, actualizați** sau **să solicitați ștergere**a informațiilor dvs. personale.
* Puteți **obiecta** la prelucrarea informațiilor dvs. personale, să ne cereți să **restricționăm** prelucrarea informațiilor dvs. personale sau să cereți **portabilitatea** informațiilor dvs. personale.
* Este posibil să aveți dreptul **să solicitați să nu se ia o decizie despre dvs. care se bazează exclusiv pe prelucrarea automată, inclusiv profilarea** dacă acea decizie produce efecte juridice despre dvs. sau vă afectează semnificativ.
* În mod similar, dacă am colectat și procesat informațiile dvs. personale cu acordul dvs., atunci **vă puteți retrage consimțământul în orice moment**. Retragerea consimțământului dvs. nu va afecta legalitatea oricărei prelucrări pe care am efectuat-o înainte de retragerea dvs. și nici nu va afecta prelucrarea informațiilor dvs. personale efectuate în baza unor motive de prelucrare legale, altele decât consimțământul.
* Este posibil să aveți dreptul să **renunțați la vânzarea informațiilor dvs. personale**. Honeywell nu vinde informațiile dvs. personale unor terțe părți pentru profit. Cu toate acestea, împărtășim sau dezvăluim informațiile dvs. personale unor terțe părți în conformitate cu această Declarație de confidențialitate și cu [Notificarea noastră cu privire la cookie](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#romanian). De exemplu, ne angajăm cu terțe părți pentru a distribui produsele noastre, pentru a vă oferi asistență tehnică, pentru a opera instrumente și caracteristici de analiză a site-ului web și pentru a ne angaja în marketing și vânzări ale produselor și serviciilor noastre. Aceste activități pot implica dezvăluirea informațiilor dvs. personale către terți și pot fi considerate o „vânzare” a datelor în conformitate cu anumite legi (dar nu toate) privind protecția datelor.
* Aveți dreptul să **vă plângeți** la o autoritate de protecție a datelor responsabilă cu supravegherea conformității cu legea privind protecția datelor din jurisdicția dvs. cu privire la colectarea și utilizarea informațiilor dvs. personale în cazul în care considerați că prelucrarea informațiilor dvs. personale nu este conformă cu legea privind protecția datelor. De exemplu, persoanele din SEE au dreptul de a depune o plângere la autoritatea competentă pentru protecția datelor, o listă care poate fi accesată la: [https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/board/members\_en](https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/board/members_en). Am aprecia, totuși, să ne dați șansa de a rezolva problemele dumneavoastră, de aceea vă rugăm să ne contactați oricând cu privire la orice plângere. Nu vom discrimina persoanele care își exercită drepturile de confidențialitate a datelor.

Vă vom facilita exercitarea drepturilor care vi se aplică, în conformitate cu legile în vigoare. Cu toate acestea, chiar dacă informațiile dvs. personale nu beneficiază de protecție în temeiul sau în orice alt mod supus unei legi de protecție a datelor, noi am putea dori să ne ocupăm de orice solicitare sau anchetă pe care o aveți cu privire la activitățile noastre de prelucrare a datelor. Dacă aveți întrebări cu privire la drepturile dvs. sau doriți să vă exercitați drepturile, ne puteți contacta la [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com) sau trimiteți întrebări despre confidențialitate prin intermediul formularului nostru web interactiv la următorul link:

**Informații despre copii**

Site-urile noastre nu sunt direcționate către și nu ar trebui să fie utilizate de copiii cu vârsta sub șaisprezece ani (16) și nu colectăm, folosim sau vindem cu bună știință informații de la astfel de persoane. Dacă sunteți minor, așa cum reglementează legile din țara dvs., vă rugăm să nu trimiteți informații personale prin intermediul site-urilor noastre.

**Linkuri către alte site-uri**

Site-urile noastre pot conține linkuri către site-uri web, produse și servicii ale unor terțe părți. Nu acceptăm nicio responsabilitate pentru site-urile web, produsele și serviciile respective, pentru politicile acestora sau pentru colectarea sau procesarea în alt mod de către acestea a informațiilor dumneavoastră cu caracter personal. Practicile acelor terțe părți sunt guvernate de propriile lor politici de confidențialitate. Vă încurajăm să vă informați în legătură cu politicile de confidențialitate ale respectivilor terți.

**Contactați-ne**

Dacă aveți întrebări cu privire la această declarație de confidențialitate sau manipularea de către noi datelor dvs. personale, dacă doriți să depuneți o plângere sau doriți să contactați responsabilul nostru cu protecția datelor, vă rugăm să ne contactați utilizând informațiile de contact enumerate mai jos. Vom acorda imediat atenție problemei dumneavoastră și vom face eforturi pentru a ajunge la o soluție satisfăcătoare.

Formular web interactiv:  

Email:  

Adresa poștală:  
Honeywell Privacy  
4D5  
115 Tabor Road  
Morris Plains, NJ 07950

Număr gratuit:  

**Modificări la această Declarație de confidențialitate**

Vom actualiza ocazional această Declarație de confidențialitate. Când facem acest lucru, revizuim data ultimei actualizări din partea de sus și de jos a Declarației de confidențialitate și luăm toate măsurile necesare impuse de lege.

Russian

**Последнее обновление: 11 июня 2021 г.**

**Введение**

Компания Honeywell International Inc. (далее **Honeywell**, **мы**, **нас** или **нам**) является контроллером персональных данных, собираемых во время посещения или использования вами любых из наших веб-сайтов или использования наших продуктов, сервисов и приложений, связанных с настоящим Заявлением о конфиденциальности (далее в совокупности **веб-сайты**). В настоящем Заявлении о конфиденциальности объясняется, как мы собираем, передаем и используем ваши персональные данные, собранные указанным образом, и как вы можете реализовывать свои права на конфиденциальность.

При взаимодействии с вами мы также можем предоставлять вам дополнительные уведомления о конфиденциальности в отношении конкретных действий по обработке данных или предлагать вам дополнительные варианты того, как Honeywell будет обрабатывать ваши персональные данные в конкретный момент времени.

Щелкните одну из приведенных ниже ссылок, чтобы перейти в интересующий вас раздел.

**Сбор данных**

* **Данные, которые мы получаем непосредственно от вас**. Мы можем попросить вас сообщить персональные данные, чтобы предоставить запрошенную услугу или совершить необходимую операцию. Некоторую информацию вы также можете предоставить при обращении к нам или взаимодействии с нами (например, оставив комментарий, запрос или обращение в службу поддержки клиентов, либо в качестве посетителя веб-сайта) или при регистрации учетной записи на наших веб-сайтах. Эти персональные данные могут включать в себя следующие данные.
    * **Идентификационные данные,** такие как ваше имя, должность, название компании или организации, адрес электронной почты, номера телефона и физический адрес (улица, город, область, почтовый индекс и (или) страна).
    * **Регистрационные данные,** предоставленные во время регистрации учетной записи для использования наших веб-сайтов, включая имена пользователей и пароли.
    * **Данные, связанные с трудоустройством,** включая информацию, предоставленную в связи с заявкой соискателя вакансии или запросом (см. определение, приведенное далее).
    * **Деловая контактная информация,** например информация, относящаяся к другим сотрудникам, владельцам, директорам, должностным лицам или подрядчикам сторонней организации (например к бизнесу, компании, партнерству, индивидуальному предпринимателю, некоммерческому или государственному учреждению).
    * **Маркетинговые и коммуникационные данные,** включая настройки рекламных рассылок и подписки на наши публикации.
    * **Финансовая информация,** включая данные о кредитных картах или другие финансовые данные, которые используются для упрощения процесса приобретения продуктов и услуг Компании, доступных на наших сайтах.
    * **Сведения для экспортного контроля,** такие как ваша национальность, гражданство и страна проживания, что позволяет нам определить, соответствуете ли вы требованиям нормативно-правовых актов о контроле экспорта для получения информации о тех или иных технологиях.
    * **Данные о сделках,** включая запросы и заказы наших продуктов и услуг, а также сведения о платежах, произведенных или полученных вами, включая историю заказов на покупки и сведения, необходимые для выполнения платежей.
    * **Сведения о регистрации на участие в мероприятиях,** включая информацию, предоставляемую при заполнении форм электронной регистрации.
    * **Ваши отзывы,** включая обзоры, рекомендации и другие отзывы о наших сайтах и продукции и услугах в целом.

Если вы не предоставите требуемую информацию, мы не сможем предоставить вам необходимые услуги или совершить сделку для выполнения вашего заказа.

* **Ваши данные, которые мы собираем автоматически**. Мы собираем определенную информацию о вашем посещении наших веб-сайтов с помощью файлов cookie и других технологий отслеживания. Мы всегда будем уважать все ваши законные права, позволяющие вам препятствовать нам в сборе данных. Собранные таким образом данные включают следующие данные.
    * **Данные об использовании**, включая информацию том, как вы используете наши сайты, просматриваемые вами страницы, количество переданных байтов, нажимаемые вами ссылки, просматриваемые вами материалы, дата и время доступа к сайту, веб-сайты, с которых вы перешли на наши сайты и другие действия, выполняемые вами на наших сайтах.
    * **Технические данные**, такие как IP-адрес, возможности и тип браузера, язык и операционная система.

Сведения о файлах cookie и других технологиях отслеживания, которые мы используем на наших веб-сайтах, см. в разделе [Уведомление о файлах cookie](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#russian).

* **Сведения геолокации**. С вашего явного согласия для определенных веб-сайтов мы можем производить сбор данных о точном местоположении в реальном времени (т. е. производить геолокацию) вашего мобильного устройства. Данная информация будет использоваться только для облегчения пользования нашими веб-сайтами, в том числе может быть предоставлена нашим поставщиками услуг, которые могут обрабатывать эту информацию в рамках предоставления услуг от нашего имени. Предоставив свое соглашение, вы можете изменить его, управляя службами геолокации с помощью настроек мобильного устройства.
* **Данные, полученные от третьих лиц**. В соответствии с применимым законодательством мы можем выполнять сбор персональных данных от третьих лиц, таких как веб-сайты и приложения социальных сетей. Эти данные мы можем объединять с уже имеющейся у нас информацией, чтобы оптимизировать и настраивать наши сайты с учетом ваших предпочтений, а также для других целей, указанных в настоящем Заявлении о конфиденциальности. Мы также можем получать вашу деловую контактную информацию от вашего работодателя или других третьих лиц, чтобы облегчить или иным образом вести традиционную деловую деятельность и решать иные подобные административные вопросы.

**Использование данных**

Мы можем использовать персональные данные, собранные при посещении наших веб-сайтов или при обращении к нам, которые могут включать следующие сведения.

* **Деловая контактная информация**. Компания Honeywell собирает и использует деловую контактную информацию для поддержания связи или транзакций, в том числе для проведения комплексных проверок в связи с предоставлением или получением продукта или услуги. Например, компания Honeywell может собирать и использовать деловую контактную информацию для оформления заказов и контрактов и управления ими, для предоставления гарантий, технического обслуживания и других подобных услуг, для анализа кредитоспособности, для обеспечения соответствия нашим собственным внутренним требованиям и требованиям законодательства, а также (при необходимости) для защиты наших интересов и претензий.
* **Услуги и сделки**. Мы можем использовать ваши персональные данные, чтобы предоставлять вам услуги или выполнять сделки, о совершении которых вы запрашивали, включая, помимо прочего, предоставление информации о продуктах или услугах Компании, которые вы приобрели или использовали иным образом, регистрацию купленных продуктов, обработку заказов на продукты, обработку гарантийных рекламаций, замену руководства по эксплуатации приобретенного продукта, ответы на запросы в службу поддержки клиентов и оптимизацию использования наших сайтов.
* **Администрирование и защита нашей коммерческой деятельности и сайтов**. Мы можем использовать персональные данные для администрирования и защиты нашей коммерческой деятельности и наших сайтов, включая поиск и устранение неполадок, обслуживание системы, поддержку, ведение отчетности и размещение данных.
* **Оптимизация работы нашей компании, сайтов и улучшение наших продуктов и услуг**. Мы можем использовать ваши персональные данные для выполнения бизнес-анализа или других целей, чтобы развивать наш бизнес и повышать качество нашей работы, сайтов, продуктов и услуг (включая новые продукты и услуги), например, настраивая сайт с учетом ваших предпочтений и интересов.
* **Маркетинг**. Согласно действующими законам и нормативам мы можем использовать ваши персональные данные, чтобы информировать вас о продуктах и услугах, в которых вы можете быть заинтересованы, а также отправлять вам предложения, анонсы событий, новости, опросные листы, специальные предложения и другие материалы. Вы в любое время можете бесплатно отказаться от рекламной рассылки по электронной почте. Для этого перейдите по ссылке «отписаться», указанной в любом полученном от нас сообщении с рекламными материалами, или свяжитесь с нами, используя контактные данные, указанные в Заявлении о конфиденциальности. В зависимости от страны проживания вы также можете отказаться от других типов рекламных рассылок. Для получения дополнительных сведений свяжитесь с нами, используя контактные данные, указанные в Заявлении о конфиденциальности. Некоторые юрисдикции предоставляют физическим лицам (например резидентам Калифорнии) право запрашивать определенную информацию, касающуюся раскрытия нами персональных данных третьим лицам для использования в целях прямого маркетинга. Для получения дополнительной информации о наших методах раскрытия данных в маркетинговых целях свяжитесь с нами в соответствии с приведенными далее инструкциями.
* **Реклама на основе интересов**. Мы собираем данные о ваших действиях в Интернете и определяем ваши интересы, чтобы предоставлять вам наиболее релевантную рекламу. Вы можете отказаться от получения рекламы на основе интересов от Honeywell, как описано в нашем [Уведомлении о файлах cookie](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#russian).
* **Программы финансового стимулирования и лояльности.** Мы собираем и используем персональные данные для реализации наших программ финансового стимулирования и лояльности и управления ими. Мы используем персональные данные, которые вы предоставляете в этих программах, чтобы предлагать уникальные вознаграждения, отслеживать статус вашей программы и содействовать обмену баллов программы на продукты, рекламные материалы, учебные семинары и другие предложения. В той степени, в которой это разрешено законодательством, мы также можем использовать любые персональные данные, которые вы предоставляете в контексте программы финансового стимулирования, для любых других целях, указанных в данном Заявлении о конфиденциальности. Ознакомьтесь с положениями и условиями каждой программы финансового стимулирования, в которой вы хотели бы зарегистрироваться или принять участие. Если вы даете согласие на участие в этих программах, вы можете отозвать свое согласие в любое время. Для этого свяжитесь с нами, используя контактные данные, указанные в конце настоящего Заявления о конфиденциальности, или в соответствии с инструкциями, изложенными в положениях и условиях соответствующей программы.
* **Заявление о приеме на работу**. В связи с подачей заявки на вакансию или запроса о наличии вакансии вы можете предоставить нам персональные данные, включая резюме и биографические данные, профессиональные рекомендации, сведения об образовании и опыте работы, а также информацию о профессиональной подготовке и сертификации. Мы и члены нашей группы можем использовать эту информацию для рассмотрения вопроса о приеме на работу, проверки биографических данных и определения права на трудоустройство, а также в иных случаях, указанных в отдельных заявлениях о конфиденциальности или других уведомлениях, применимых к данной ситуации. Мы можем прибегать к помощи третьих лиц (например агентства по трудоустройству) или пользоваться социальными сетями для запрашивания, сбора и хранения заявлений о приеме на работу. Дополнительные сведения см. в [Уведомлении о конфиденциальности данных кандидата](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/applicant-privacy-notice#russian).
* **Исследования и анализ**. Мы можем использовать ваши личные данные для проведения исследований и анализа, которые помогут нам проанализировать ваши предпочтения в покупках, определить продукты и услуги, максимально отвечающие вашим требованиям, и оценить эффективность рекламы, которую мы вам показываем.
* **Правоприменительные меры**. Мы можем использовать собранные персональные данные с целью выявления, предотвращения и реагирования на мошеннические действия, нарушение прав интеллектуальной собственности, неисполнение наших правил и условий, несоблюдение законов и другого неправомерного использования наших сайтов.

В случаях, разрешенных законом, мы можем объединять данные, собранные нами на наших сайтах, с другой имеющейся у нас информацией (такой как информация об использовании вами наших продуктов и услуг), чтобы повысить качество обслуживания клиентов, а также для других целей, указанных в настоящем Заявлении о конфиденциальности.

**Правовые основания для обработки данных**

В случаях, предусмотренных законом, мы обеспечим юридические основания для обработки ваших персональных данных. В большинстве случаев правовые основания будут зависеть от соответствующих персональных данных и конкретного контекста, в котором мы их собираем.

* **Договор**: обработка необходима для предоставления вам услуг или для принятия мер (по вашему запросу) до предоставления таких услуг.
* **Правовые обязательства**: обработка необходима для исполнения наших правовых обязательств, включая соблюдение применимых законов, нормативов, запросов государственных и иных органов, судебных распоряжений или вызовов в суд.
* **Согласие**: обработка выполняется по вашему разрешению на обработку персональных данных в одной или нескольких указанных целях (например для рекламы).
* **Законные интересы**: обработка необходима для удовлетворения наших законных интересов, например для разработки и оптимизации наших сайтов, продуктов и (или) услуг в интересах наших клиентов.
* **Жизненно важные интересы**: обработка необходима для защиты ваших жизненно важных интересов (например по соображениям здоровья и безопасности, если вы присутствуете на совещании в офисе компании Honeywell).

Если у вас есть какие-либо вопросы или вам нужна дополнительная информация о правовых основаниях, на которых мы собираем и используем ваши персональные данные, отправьте электронное письмо по адресу [HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com).

**Анонимизация данных**

В соответствии с применимым законодательством мы можем обеспечивать анонимность персональных данных, чтобы их невозможно было использовать для идентификации личности. Анонимизированные данные не считаются персональными данными и поэтому не попадают под действие настоящего Заявления о конфиденциальности. Мы можем собирать, использовать, объединять и передавать анонимную информацию в любых целях.

**Сроки хранения данных**

Период хранения персональных данных зависит от цели обработки. Например, мы храним персональные данные, необходимые для предоставления вам продуктов и услуг или для выполнения запрашиваемых вами транзакций, пока вы являетесь клиентом компании Honeywell. Если вы подаете заявление о приеме на работу через наши веб-сайты, мы будем хранить информацию о вашем заявлении, как указано в уведомлении о конфиденциальности, предоставленном вам в связи с вашим заявлением, или в соответствии с требованиями закона. Во всех других случаях мы храним персональные данные до тех пор, пока они необходимы для наших целей, изложенных в настоящем Заявлении о конфиденциальности, после чего мы либо анонимизируем данные (если это разрешено применимым законодательством), либо удаляем, либо уничтожаем их.

**Раскрытие данных**

Мы можем передавать ваши персональные данные выбранным третьим лицам в соответствии с применимым законодательством, в том числе, как указано ниже.

* **Наша группа компаний**. Мы также можем предоставлять ваши персональные данные своим аффилированным лицам и компаниям из нашей группы, когда это оправдано необходимо в целях, описанных в этом Заявлении о конфиденциальности.
* **Поставщики услуг**. Мы можем предоставлять персональные данные другим компаниям, с которыми у нас заключены договоры на предоставление услуг от нашего имени, таких как хостинг веб-сайтов, проведение опросов, обработка операций, анализ наших сайтов и выполнение анализа для улучшения качества нашей работы, сайтов, продуктов и услуг. Мы требуем, чтобы эти поставщики услуг обеспечивали конфиденциальность ваших персональных данных.
* **Дистрибьюторы и другие доверенные деловые партнеры**. Мы можем передавать ваши персональные данные третьим лицам, которые распространяют наши продукты, и другим доверенным деловым партнерам в целях, позволяющих этим третьим лицам отправлять вам рекламные материалы. Предоставление персональных данных в маркетинговых целях осуществляется в соответствии с применимыми законами и нормами.
* **Предоставление информации в связи со сделками**. В связи с некоторыми сделками мы можем сообщить некоторую часть или все ваши персональные данные финансовым учреждениям, правительственным организациям и транспортным компаниям, а также почтовым службам, привлеченным к осуществлению сделки.
* **Разглашение в связи с приобретением или ликвидацией компании**. В связи с обстоятельствами в стратегических целях или по иным деловым соображениям корпорация Honeywell может решить продать, купить, разделить, объединить посредством слияния или иначе реорганизовать свои предприятия в некоторых странах. Мы можем раскрыть имеющуюся о вас информацию до степени, достаточной для продолжения переговоров или завершения слияния, приобретения, разделения или продажи всех или части активов компании Honeywell.
* **Разглашение информации по другим причинам**. Мы можем раскрыть персональные данные, если это требуется или разрешено по закону или исходя из добросовестного предположения, что такое действие необходимо для соблюдения законных требований или врученного нам постановления суда, для защиты наших прав и имущества или в чрезвычайных обстоятельствах для защиты личной безопасности того или иного физического лица.

**Передача данных в другие страны**

Компания Honeywell является глобальной организацией, и ваши персональные данные могут передаваться, находиться, храниться или использоваться в различных регионах по всему миру, например в США, Мексике и Индии, в соответствии с действующим законодательством. Это означает, что когда мы собираем ваши персональные данные, они могут обрабатываться в странах, в которых законы о защите данных могут отличаться от законов вашей страны. Тем не менее, компания Honeywell всегда будет принимать разумные меры для защиты вашей конфиденциальности и обеспечения уровня защиты персональных данных, сопоставимого с уровнем защиты в вашей стране проживания, включая выполнение Стандартных договорных положений, утвержденных Европейской комиссией. Чтобы получить дополнительную информацию о соответствующих мерах защиты ваших персональных данных, свяжитесь с нами по адресу [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com).

**Безопасность**

Мы стремимся предпринять все возможные действия для защиты ваших персональных данных. Мы принимаем технические и организационные меры для обеспечения уровня безопасности, соответствующего риску, связанному с обработкой ваших персональных данных. Для получения дополнительной информации о том, как Honeywell защищает ваши персональные данные, свяжитесь с нами по адресу [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com).

**Ваши права**

В зависимости от применимого законодательства у вас могут быть определенные права в отношении ваших персональных данных.

* Вы можете иметь право **на доступ, исправление, обновление** или **удаление** ваших персональных данных.
* Вы можете **возражать** против обработки ваших персональных данных, просить нас **ограничит**ь обработку ваших персональных данных или требовать переноса ваших персональных данных.
* Вы можете иметь право **на то, чтобы в отношении вас не принимались решения, основанные исключительно на автоматической обработке, включая профилирование,** если эти решения создают для вас юридические последствия или оказывают иное значительное влияние на вас.
* Также, если мы собираем и обрабатываем ваши персональные данные с вашего согласия, **вы можете отозвать свое согласие в любое время**. Отзыв вашего согласия не повлияет на законность обработки, которую мы выполняли до отзыва согласия, а также не повлияет на обработку ваших персональных данных, проводимую на законных основаниях, отличных от согласия.
* Вы можете иметь право **отказаться от продажи ваших персональных данных**. Компания Honeywell не продает ваши персональные данные третьим лицам с целью получения прибыли. Однако мы передаем или иным образом раскрываем ваши персональные данные третьим лицам в соответствии с настоящим Заявлением о конфиденциальности и нашим [Уведомлением о файлах cookie](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#russian). Например, мы взаимодействуем с третьими лицами для распространения наших продуктов, предоставления вам технической помощи, использования аналитических инструментов и функций веб-сайта, а также маркетинга и продаж наших продуктов и услуг. Такие действия могут включать раскрытие ваших персональных данных третьим лицам и могут рассматриваться как «продажа» данных в соответствии с некоторыми (но не всеми) законами о защите данных.
* Вы имеете право **подавать жалобы** в органы власти, контролирующие соблюдение законов о защите данных в вашей юрисдикции, в отношении сбора и использования ваших персональных данных, если вы считаете, что обработка нами ваших персональных данных не соответствует закону о защите данных. Например, лица в ЕЭЗ имеют право подать жалобу в компетентный орган по защите данных, список которых можно найти по адресу: [https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/board/members\_en](https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/board/members_en). Тем не менее мы будет рады помочь вам решить ваши вопросы, поэтому не стесняйтесь обращаться к нам с любой жалобой. Мы не будем дискриминировать кого-либо за осуществление прав на конфиденциальность данных.

Мы будем обеспечивать соблюдение ваших прав в соответствии с применимым законодательством. Однако, даже если ваши персональные данные не защищены законом о защите данных или каким-либо иным образом не подпадают под его действие, мы будем стараться удовлетворить любой ваш запрос или требование в отношении нашей деятельности по обработке данных. Если у вас есть вопросы о ваших правах или вы хотите воспользоваться своими правами, свяжитесь с нами по адресу [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com) или отправьте вопросы о конфиденциальности через нашу интерактивную веб-форму по следующей ссылке:

**Персональные данные детей**

Наши веб-сайты не предназначены для детей младше шестнадцати (16) лет и не должны использоваться ими, и мы не собираем, не используем и не продаем данные таких лиц. Если вы являетесь несовершеннолетним в соответствии с законами вашей страны, пожалуйста, не сообщайте какие-либо персональные данные на наших веб-сайтах.

**Ссылки на другие веб-сайты**

Наши веб-сайты могут содержать ссылки на сторонние веб-сайты, продукты и услуги. Мы не несем ответственности за эти веб-сайты, продукты и услуги, их политику, условия сбора или обработки ваших персональных данных. Действия этих третьих лиц регулируются их собственными политиками конфиденциальности. Мы рекомендуем вам знакомиться с политиками конфиденциальности этих третьих лиц.

**Контакты**

Если у вас есть вопросы относительно настоящего Заявления о конфиденциальности или правил обработки ваших персональных данных, если вы хотите подать жалобу или обратиться к нашему специалисту по защите персональных данных, свяжитесь с нами, используя контактную информацию, указанную ниже. Мы незамедлительно изучим ваш вопрос и приложим усилия, чтобы найти удовлетворительное решение.

Интерактивная веб-форма:  

Электронная почта:  

Почтовый адрес:  
Honeywell Privacy  
4D5  
115 Tabor Road  
Morris Plains, NJ 07950.

Номер для бесплатных звонков:  
[844 774 8634](tel:8447748634).

**Изменения в этом Заявлении о конфиденциальности**

Мы вправе время от времени вносить изменения в настоящее Заявление о конфиденциальности. В случае внесения изменений мы исправим дату последнего обновления, указанную в верхней части Заявления о конфиденциальности, и предпримем дополнительные меры, предусмотренные законом.

**Последнее обновление: 11 июня 2021 г.**

Slovak

**Posledná aktualizácia 11. júna 2021**

**Úvod**

Spoločnosť Honeywell International Inc. („**Honeywell**“, „**náš**“, „**nás**“ alebo „**my**“) je „správcom údajov“ osobných údajov, ktoré o vás zhromažďujeme, keď navštívite alebo použijete niektorú z našich webových lokalít alebo použijete produkty, služby a aplikácie, ktoré sú prepojené s týmto vyhlásením o ochrane osobných údajov (ďalej spoločne „**webové lokality**“). Toto vyhlásenie o ochrane osobných údajov vysvetľuje, ako zhromažďujeme, zdieľame a používame vaše osobné údaje zhromaždené týmto spôsobom a ako môžete uplatniť svoje práva na ochranu osobných údajov.

Keď s vami komunikujeme, môžeme vám tiež poskytnúť ďalšie oznámenia o ochrane osobných údajov týkajúce sa konkrétnych činností spracovania alebo vám ponúknuť ďalšie možnosti týkajúce sa spôsobu, akým spoločnosť Honeywell spracúva vaše osobné údaje v danom konkrétnom okamihu.

Kliknutím na jedno z nasledujúcich prepojení prejdite na časť, ktorá vás zaujíma:

**Zhromažďovanie údajov**

* **Údaje zhromaždené priamo od vás**. Môžeme vás požiadať o osobné údaje, aby sme vám mohli poskytnúť požadovanú službu alebo vykonať požadovanú transakciu. Osobné údaje nám môžete poskytnúť aj vtedy, keď nás kontaktujete alebo sa s nami spojíte (napr. keď nám pošlete komentár, otázku alebo žiadosť o zákaznícku podporu, návštevníkov) alebo keď si zaregistrujete konto na používanie našich webových lokalít. Tieto osobné údaje môžu obsahovať:
    * **údaje o identite,** ako napríklad vaše meno, titul, názov spoločnosti alebo organizácie, e-mailovú adresu, telefónne čísla a poštovú adresu (vrátane ulice, mesta, kraja, PSČ a/alebo krajiny);
    * **registračné údaje,** ktoré zadáte pri registrácii konta na používanie našich webových lokalít, vrátane mien používateľov a hesiel;
    * **náborové údaje** vrátane údajov poskytnutých v súvislosti so žiadosťou o zamestnanie alebo súvisiacou otázkou (v súlade s opisom uvedeným nižšie);
    * **Obchodné kontaktné údaje,** ako napríklad údaje týkajúce sa ďalších zamestnancov, vlastníkov, riaditeľov, riadiacich pracovníkov alebo zmluvných pracovníkov organizácie tretej strany (napr. podnik, spoločnosť, partnerstvo, živnostenský podnik, nezisková organizácia alebo vládna agentúra).
    * **marketingové a komunikačné údaje** vrátane vašich marketingových predvolieb a prihlásení na odber našich publikácií,
    * **finančné údaje** vrátane údajov o kreditných kartách alebo iných peňažných účtoch, aby sme vám mohli uľahčiť nákup našich produktov a služieb, ktoré sú dostupné na našich webových lokalitách;
    * **údaje na kontrolu vývozu,** ako napríklad údaje o vašej národnosti, občianstve a krajine trvalého pobytu, ktoré nám umožnia určiť, či ste podľa nariadení o kontrole vývozu oprávnení dostávať informácie o určitých technológiách;
    * **údaje o transakciách** vrátane objednávok a otázok týkajúcich sa našich produktov a služieb a podrobností o prichádzajúcich a odchádzajúcich platbách vrátane histórie nákupných objednávok a údajov potrebných na umožnenie platobných transakcií;
    * **údaje o registrácii** v rámci rôznych podujatí vrátane údajov, ktoré poskytnete pri vypĺňaní elektronických registračných formulárov; a
    * **vaše názory** vrátane prieskumov, odporúčaní a ďalšieho názoru na naše webové lokality, produkty a služby všeobecne.

Ak neposkytnete požadované údaje, môže sa stať, že vám nebudeme môcť poskytnúť požadovanú službu alebo vykonať požadovanú transakciu.

* **Údaje, ktoré o vás zhromažďujeme automaticky**. Pomocou súborov cookie a podobných technológií sledovania zhromažďujeme určité informácie o vašej návšteve našich webových lokalít. Vždy budeme rešpektovať všetky zákonné práva, ktorými nám môžete zabrániť tak urobiť. Údaje zhromaždené týmto spôsobom zahŕňajú:
    * **údaje o používaní** vrátane údajov o spôsobe používania našich webových lokalít, prezeraných webových stránkach, počte prenesených bajtov, prepojeniach, na ktoré kliknete, materiáloch, ku ktorým pristupujete, dátume a čase vášho prístupu k danej webovej lokalite, externej webovej lokalite, z ktorej ste prešli prostredníctvom prepojenia na jednu z našich webových lokalít, ako aj o ďalších činnostiach vykonávaných na našich webových lokalitách; a
    * **technické údaje,** ako napríklad údaje o adrese internetového protokolu (IP), type a možnostiach vášho prehliadača, nastavenom jazyku a používanom operačnom systéme.

Informácie o súboroch cookie a ďalších podobných technológiách sledovania, ktoré používame na našich webových lokalitách, nájdete v našom [oznámení o súboroch cookie](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#slovak).

* **Údaje o zemepisnej polohe**. Na niektorých webových lokalitách môžeme s vaším výslovným súhlasom zhromažďovať údaje o presnej aktuálnej polohe (t. j. zemepisnej polohe) vášho mobilného zariadenia. Tieto údaje budú použité iba na účely uľahčenia vášho používania webových lokalít, a to aj prostredníctvom našich poskytovateľov služieb, ktorí môžu tieto údaje spracovávať v súvislosti s poskytovaním služieb v našom mene. Ak bude udelený, svoj súhlas môžete neskôr zmeniť prostredníctvom predvolieb lokalizačných služieb, ktoré sú k dispozícii v nastaveniach mobilného zariadenia.
* **Údaje zhromaždené od tretích strán**. V súlade s platnými právnymi predpismi môžeme zhromažďovať vaše osobné údaje od tretích strán, ako sú napríklad webové lokality a aplikácie sociálnych médií, a kombinovať ich s údajmi, ktoré už máme, aby nám pomohli zlepšiť a prispôsobiť naše webové lokality vašim predvoľbám a na ďalšie účely uvedené v tomto vyhlásení o ochrane osobných údajov. Môžeme tiež zhromažďovať vaše obchodné kontaktné údaje od zamestnávateľa alebo iných tretích strán, aby sme umožnili alebo sa inak zapojili do tradičných obchodných činností a podobných administratívnych záležitostí.

**Používanie údajov**

Osobné údaje zhromaždené prostredníctvom našich webových lokalít alebo osobné údaje, ktoré nám poskytnete, keď nás kontaktujete, môžeme používať na nasledujúce účely:

* **Obchodné kontaktné údaje**. Spoločnosť Honeywell zhromažďuje a používa obchodné kontaktné údaje na zapojenie sa do komunikácií alebo transakcií a aj na vykonanie povinnej kontroly týkajúcej sa produktu alebo služby alebo ich poskytnutia či prijatia. Spoločnosť Honeywell môže napríklad zhromažďovať a používať tieto obchodné kontaktné údaje s cieľom umožniť a spravovať objednávky, zmluvy, záruky, údržby a podobné obchodné funkcie, na účely úverovej analýzy a zhromažďovania, na pomoc s našimi vlastnými internými zmluvnými a zákonnými požiadavkami a (ak je to potrebné) na obranu našich záujmov a nárokov.
* **Služby a transakcie**. Vaše osobné údaje môžeme používať na poskytovanie služieb pre vás alebo na vykonávanie transakcií, o ktoré požiadate, okrem iného napríklad na poskytovanie informácií o zakúpených alebo inak používaných produktoch či službách našej spoločnosti, registráciu zakúpených produktov, spracúvanie objednávok produktov, vybavovanie reklamácií, poskytovanie náhradných príručiek k produktom, vybavovanie žiadostí v rámci služieb zákazníkom a uľahčovanie používania našich webových lokalít.
* **Spravovanie a ochrana nášho podnikania a našich webových lokalít**. Vaše osobné údaje môžeme používať na spravovanie a ochranu nášho podnikania a našich webových lokalít vrátane riešenia problémov, údržby systémov, poskytovania podpory, poskytovania výkazov a hosťovania údajov.
* **Zlepšovanie nášho podnikania, webových lokalít, produktov a služieb**. Vaše osobné údaje môžeme používať na vykonávanie obchodných analýz a na iné účely, ktoré nám pomáhajú rozvíjať a zlepšovať kvalitu nášho podnikania a našich webových lokalít, produktov a služieb (vrátane nových produktov a služieb), napríklad prispôsobovaním našich webových lokalít vašim predvoľbám alebo záujmom.
* **Marketing**. V súlade s platnými právnymi predpismi a nariadeniami môžeme vaše osobné údaje používať na to, aby sme vás informovali o výrobkoch alebo službách, ktoré by vás mohli zaujímať, alebo na to, aby sme vás inými formami informovali o ponukách, podujatiach alebo novinkách, prieskumoch, osobitných ponukách a súvisiacich témach. Marketingovú komunikáciu zasielanú e-mailom môžete kedykoľvek bezplatne zrušiť prostredníctvom prepojenia na zrušenie jej odberu vo všetkých e-mailových marketingových materiáloch, ktoré od nás dostávate, prípadne nás môžete v tejto súvislosti kontaktovať prostredníctvom kontaktných údajov uvedených v tomto vyhlásení o ochrane osobných údajov. V závislosti od vašej krajiny pobytu môžete byť tiež schopní odhlásiť sa z iných typov marketingovej komunikácie. Pre viac informácií nás kontaktujte pomocou kontaktných údajov uvedených vo vyhlásení o ochrane osobných údajov. Niektoré jurisdikcie poskytujú jednotlivcom (napr. obyvateľom Kalifornie) právo požadovať určité informácie týkajúce sa nášho zverejňovania osobných údajov tretím stranám na účely priameho marketingu tretích strán. Ak chcete získať viac informácií o našich postupoch zverejňovania údajov na marketingové účely, kontaktujte nás v súlade s pokynmi uvedenými nižšie.
* **Záujmovo orientovaná reklama**. Zhromažďujeme údaje o vašich online aktivitách a identifikujeme vaše záujmy, aby sme mohli poskytovať reklamu, ktorá je pre vás najrelevantnejšia. Môžete sa odhlásiť z prijímania záujmovo orientovanej reklamy od spoločnosti Honeywell, ako je uvedené v našom [oznámení o súboroch cookie](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#slovak).
* **Finančné stimuly a vernostné programy**. Zhromažďujeme a používame osobné údaje na udržiavanie a spravovanie našich finančných stimulov a vernostných programov. Osobné údaje, ktoré poskytujete v týchto programoch, používame na ponúkanie jedinečných odmien, sledovanie stavu vášho programu a na umožnenie výmeny bodov programu za produkty, propagačné materiály, školiace semináre a ďalšie položky. V rozsahu povolenom právnymi predpismi môžeme tiež použiť akékoľvek osobné údaje, ktoré poskytnete v súvislosti s programom finančných stimulov, na akýkoľvek iný účel stanovený v tomto vyhlásení o ochrane osobných údajov. Prečítajte si podmienky každého programu finančných stimulov, do ktorého sa chcete zaregistrovať alebo sa ho zúčastniť, pretože tieto podmienky môžu byť úzko prispôsobené príslušnému programu. Ak súhlasíte s účasťou na týchto programoch, môžete tento súhlas kedykoľvek odvolať tak, že nás kontaktujete pomocou kontaktných údajov na konci tohto vyhlásenia o ochrane osobných údajov alebo v súlade s pokynmi uvedenými v podmienkach príslušného programu.
* **Žiadosti o zamestnanie**. V súvislosti so žiadosťou o zamestnanie alebo s požiadavkou na zamestnanie nám môžete poskytnúť informácie o sebe, ako napríklad životopis, profesijné referencie, informácie o vzdelaní a zamestnaní a informácie o odborných školeniach a certifikáciách. Naša spoločnosť a členovia našej skupiny môžu používať tieto údaje na účely zváženia zamestnania, previerok osoby a oprávnenosti na zamestnanie a iné účely stanovené v samostatnom vyhlásení o ochrane osobných údajov alebo v inom oznámení, ktoré je sprístupnené v súvislosti s vašou žiadosťou. Na vyžadovanie, zhromažďovanie a uchovávanie žiadostí o zamestnanie môžeme použiť tretiu stranu (napr. náborového pracovníka) alebo platformu sociálnych médií. Ďalšie informácie nájdete v našom dokumente [Oznámenie o ochrane osobných údajov žiadateľa](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/applicant-privacy-notice#slovak) .
* **Prieskum a analýza**. Vaše osobné údaje môžeme používať na vykonávanie prieskumov a analýz, ktoré nám pomáhajú analyzovať vaše nákupné predvoľby, identifikovať produkty a služby, ktoré najlepšie vyhovujú vašim požiadavkám, a merať efektívnosť zobrazovanej reklamy.
* **Presadzovanie právnych predpisov**: Zhromaždené osobné údaje môžeme používať na odhaľovanie, prevenciu a riešenie podvodov, porušení práv duševného vlastníctva, porušení našich podmienok, porušení právnych predpisov alebo iného zneužívania našich webových lokalít.

Ak to povoľujú platné právne predpisy, údaje zhromaždené prostredníctvom našich webových lokalít môžeme kombinovať s ostatnými údajmi, ktoré o vás evidujeme (napríklad s údajmi o tom, ako používate naše produkty a služby), aby sme vám mohli poskytovať lepšie a konzistentné možnosti pri interakciách s nami alebo na iné účely stanovené v tomto vyhlásení o ochrane osobných údajov.

**Právny základ nášho spracúvania údajov**

Ak to vyžadujú právne predpisy, budeme zaručovať, aby sa spracúvanie vašich osobných údajov vykonávalo na právnom základe. Náš právny základ bude vo väčšine prípadov závisieť od dotknutých osobných údajov a konkrétneho kontextu, v ktorom ich zhromažďujeme.

* **Zmluva**: spracovanie je nevyhnutné na výkon služieb, ktoré vám poskytujeme, alebo na účely podniknutia krokov (na vašu žiadosť) pred vykonaním a očakávaním týchto služieb;
* **Zákonná povinnosť**: spracúvanie je nevyhnutné na to, aby sme dodržiavali naše zákonné povinnosti vrátane dodržiavania platných právnych predpisov, nariadení, štátnych a obdobných požiadaviek, súdnych rozhodnutí alebo predvolaní;
* **Súhlas**: spracúvanie je založené na vašom súhlase so spracúvaním vašich osobných údajov na jeden alebo viacero zo stanovených účelov (napr. marketing);
* **Oprávnené záujmy**: spracúvanie je nevyhnutné na splnenie našich oprávnených záujmov, napríklad na vývoj a zdokonaľovanie našich webových lokalít, produktov a/alebo služieb v prospech našich zákazníkov; alebo
* **Životne dôležité záujmy**: spracúvanie je nevyhnutné na ochranu vašich životne dôležitých záujmov (napríklad z dôvodu ochrany zdravia a bezpečnosti, ak sa zúčastňujete stretnutia v sídle spoločnosti Honeywell).

Ak máte akékoľvek otázky alebo potrebujete ďalšie informácie týkajúce sa právneho základu, na ktorom zhromažďujeme a používame vaše osobné údaje, pošlite e-mail na adresu [HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com)

**Anonymizácia údajov**

V súlade s platnými právnymi predpismi môžeme anonymizovať vaše osobné údaje tak, aby ich nebolo možné použiť na vašu identifikáciu. Anonymizované údaje sa nepovažujú za osobné údaje, a preto sa na ne nevzťahuje toto vyhlásenie o ochrane osobných údajov. Anonymizované údaje môžeme zhromažďovať, používať, agregovať a zdieľať na akýkoľvek účel.

**Ako dlho uchovávame údaje**

Doba uchovávania vašich osobných údajov sa líši v závislosti od účelu ich spracúvania. Napríklad osobné údaje potrebné na to, aby sme vám mohli poskytovať produkty a služby alebo umožňovať vykonávanie požadovaných transakcií, uchovávame tak dlho, kým budete zákazníkmi spoločnosti Honeywell, alebo ak prostredníctvom našich webových lokalít podáte žiadosť o zamestnanie, podrobné informácie o vašej žiadosti budeme uchovávať po dobu stanovenú v tomto oznámení o ochrane osobných údajov, ktoré vám poskytneme v súvislosti s vašou žiadosťou alebo inak v súlade s právnymi predpismi. Vo všetkých ostatných prípadoch uchovávame vaše osobné údaje dovtedy, kým to bude potrebné na splnenie účelov uvedených v tomto vyhlásení o ochrane osobných údajov. Po uplynutí tejto doby budú buď anonymizované (ak to umožňujú platné právne predpisy), odstránené, alebo zničené.

**Zverejňovanie údajov**

Vaše osobné údaje môžeme zdieľať s vybratými tretími stranami v súlade s platnými právnymi predpismi vrátane podmienok stanovených nižšie:

* **Spoločnosti z našej skupiny**. Vaše osobné údaje môžeme zdieľať s našimi pridruženými spoločnosťami a spoločnosťami z našej skupiny, ak na to existujú primerané účely, ktoré sú stanovené v tomto vyhlásení o ochrane osobných údajov.
* **Poskytovatelia služieb**. Vaše osobné údaje môžeme zdieľať so spoločnosťami, s ktorými máme uzatvorenú zmluvu o poskytovaní služieb v našom mene, ako sú napríklad služby hosťovania webových lokalít, vykonávanie prieskumov, spracúvanie transakcií, analyzovanie našich webových lokalít a vykonávanie analýz na zlepšovanie kvality nášho podnikania, našich webových lokalít, produktov a služieb. Od týchto poskytovateľov služieb vyžadujeme, aby vaše osobné údaje chránili ako dôverné.
* **Distribútori a ďalší dôveryhodní obchodní partneri**. Vaše osobné údaje môžeme zdieľať s tretími stranami, ktoré distribuujú naše produkty, ako aj s ďalšími dôveryhodnými obchodnými partnermi, aby sme im umožnili napríklad posielať vám marketingové oznámenia. Takéto zdieľanie osobných údajov na marketingové účely sa bude vykonávať v súlade s platnými právnymi predpismi a nariadeniami.
* **Zverejňovanie v súvislosti s transakciami**. V spojení s určitými transakciami môžeme zverejniť časť alebo všetky osobné údaje finančným inštitúciám, štátnym subjektom, zásielkovým spoločnostiam alebo poštovým službám s cieľom uskutočnenia transakcie.
* **Zverejňovania v súvislosti s akvizíciami alebo odpredajmi**. Naša spoločnosť Honeywell sa za určitých okolností môže zo strategických alebo iných obchodných dôvodov rozhodnúť v niektorých krajinách predať, kúpiť, odpredať, vykonať zlúčenie alebo iným spôsobom reorganizovať svoje podniky. Informácie, ktoré o vás uchovávame, môžeme zverejniť v primeranom rozsahu potrebnom na vyjednanie alebo realizáciu zlúčenia, akvizície, odpredaja alebo predaja všetkého majetku spoločnosti Honeywell alebo jeho časti.
* **Zverejňovanie z iných dôvodov**. Osobné údaje môžeme zverejniť, ak to vyžadujú alebo ak nás k tomu oprávňujú právne predpisy, alebo ak to urobíme v dobrej viere, že je to nutné na splnenie zákonných požiadaviek alebo právneho procesu vedenému voči nám, na ochranu a obranu našich práv alebo majetku alebo v naliehavých prípadoch na ochranu bezpečnosti osôb.

**Medzinárodné prenosy**

Spoločnosť Honeywell je globálna organizácia a vaše osobné údaje môžu byť v súlade s platnými právnymi predpismi prenášané, uchovávané, ukladané alebo používané na rôznych miestach po celom svete, ako sú napríklad USA, Mexiko a India. To znamená, že keď zhromažďujeme vaše osobné údaje, môžu byť spracované v krajinách, ktorých právne predpisy o ochrane údajov sa môžu líšiť od právnych predpisov vo vašej krajine. Spoločnosť Honeywell však vždy podnikne primerané kroky na ochranu vášho súkromia a na zabezpečenie úrovne ochrany osobných údajov, ktorá je porovnateľná s úrovňou vo vašej krajine pobytu, ktoré zahŕňajú implementáciu štandardných zmluvných doložiek Európskej komisie. Ak chcete získať ďalšie informácie o príslušných uplatnených bezpečnostných opatreniach na ochranu vašich osobných údajov, kontaktujte nás na adrese [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com).

**Zabezpečenie**

Zaväzujeme sa chrániť vaše osobné údaje, aby boli v bezpečí. Používame technické a organizačné opatrenia na zabezpečenie úrovne bezpečnosti zodpovedajúcej riziku spracovania vašich osobných údajov. Ak chcete získať viac informácií o tom, ako spoločnosť Honeywell chráni vaše osobné údaje, kontaktujte nás na adrese [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com)

**Vaše práva**

V závislosti od platných právnych predpisov môžete mať určité práva týkajúce sa vašich osobných údajov.

* Môžete mať právo **pristupovať, kontrolovať, aktualizovať** alebo **požiadať o odstránenie** vašich osobných údajov.
* Môžete **namietať** proti spracovaniu vašich osobných údajov, požiadať nás **obmedziť** spracovanie vašich osobných údajov alebo požiadať **o prenosnosť** vašich osobných údajov.
* Môžete mať právo **nenechať o sebe rozhodovať výlučne na základe automatizovaného spracovania vrátane profilovania,** ak toto rozhodnutie vytvára o vás právne účinky alebo vás výrazne ovplyvňuje.
* Podobne, ak sme zhromaždili a spracovali vaše osobné údaje s vašim súhlasom, potom **svoj súhlas môžete kedykoľvek odvolať**. Odvolanie súhlasu neovplyvní zákonnosť spracovania, ktoré sme vykonali pred vašim odvolaním, ani to neovplyvní spracovanie vašich osobných údajov, ktoré sa vykonáva na základe iných zákonných dôvodov ako je súhlas.
* Môžete mať právo **odhlásiť sa z predaja vašich osobných údajov**. Spoločnosť Honeywell nepredáva vaše osobné údaje tretím stranám pre zisk. Vaše osobné údaje však zdieľame alebo inak poskytujeme tretím stranám v súlade s týmto vyhlásením o ochrane osobných údajov a naším [oznámením o súboroch cookie](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#slovak). S tretími stranami napríklad spolupracujeme pri distribúcii našich produktov, poskytovaní technickej pomoci pre vás, prevádzkovaní analytických nástrojov a funkcií webových lokalít a zaoberáme sa marketingom a predajom našich produktov a služieb. Takéto činnosti môžu zahŕňať zverejňovanie vašich osobných údajov tretím stranám a podľa určitých (ale nie všetkých) právnych predpisov na ochranu údajov sa môžu považovať za „predaj“ údajov.
* Máte právo **sťažovať sa** orgánu na ochranu údajov zodpovednému za dohľad nad dodržiavaním právnych predpisov o ochrane údajov vo vašej jurisdikcii na naše zhromažďovanie a používanie vašich osobných údajov, ak sa domnievate, že spracovanie vašich osobných údajov nie je v súlade s právnymi predpismi o ochrane údajov. Napríklad jednotlivci v EHP majú právo podať sťažnosť kompetentným orgánom na ochranu údajov, ktorých zoznam je dostupný na adrese: [https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/board/members\_en](https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/board/members_en). Veľmi by sme ocenili, keby ste nám umožnili vyriešiť vzniknutý problém, preto nás v prípade akýchkoľvek sťažností kontaktujte. Nebudeme diskriminovať jednotlivcov za uplatňovanie ich práv na ochranu osobných údajov.

Zabezpečíme, aby ste si mohli uplatňovať svoje práva v súlade s platnými právnymi predpismi. Aj keď sa na vaše osobné údaje neposkytuje ochrana podľa právnych predpisov o ochrane údajov alebo sa na ne nevzťahuje iný právny predpis, môžeme sa pokúsiť vyhovieť akejkoľvek žiadosti alebo otázke, ktoré môžete mať v súvislosti s našimi činnosťami v oblasti spracovania údajov. Ak máte otázky týkajúce sa vašich práv alebo ich chcete uplatniť, môžete nás kontaktovať na adrese [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com) alebo podajte otázky týkajúce sa ochrany osobných údajov prostredníctvom nášho interaktívneho webového formulára na nasledujúcom prepojení:

**Údaje detí**

Naše webové lokality nie sú zamerané na deti mladšie ako šestnásť (16) rokov a nemali by ich používať. Vedome nezhromažďujeme, nepoužívame ani nepredávame údaje týchto osôb. Ak ste podľa právnych predpisov vašej krajiny maloletí, nezadávajte žiadne osobné údaje prostredníctvom našich webových lokalít.

**Prepojenia na iné webové lokality**

Naše webové lokality môžu obsahovať prepojenia na webové lokality, produkty a služby tretích strán. Za tieto webové lokality, produkty a služby, ich zásady ani ich zhromažďovanie či iné spracúvanie vašich osobných údajov nenesieme žiadnu zodpovednosť. Postupy týchto tretích strán sa riadia ich vlastnými zásadami o ochrane osobných údajov. Odporúčame vám, aby ste sa oboznámili so zásadami ochrany osobných údajov týchto tretích strán.

**Kontaktujte nás**

Ak máte otázky týkajúce sa tohto vyhlásenia o ochrane osobných údajov alebo nášho spracúvania vašich osobných údajov, chcete podať sťažnosť alebo sa obrátiť na osobu zodpovednú za ochranu údajov, použite kontaktné údaje uvedené nižšie. Riešenie otázky s cieľom dosiahnuť uspokojivý výsledok sa bude hľadať v čo najkratšom čase.

Interaktívny webový formulár:  

E-mail:  

Poštová adresa:  
Ochrana osobných údajov spoločnosti Honeywell  
4D5  
115 Tabor Road  
Morris Plains, NJ 07950

Bezplatné číslo:  

**Zmeny tohto vyhlásenia o ochrane osobných údajov**

Toto vyhlásenie o ochrane osobných údajov môžeme príležitostne aktualizovať. V takom prípade sa zmení aj dátum „Posledná aktualizácia“ uvedený v hornej časti vyhlásenia o ochrane osobných údajov a podnikneme príslušné ďalšie kroky vyžadované platnými právnymi predpismi.

**Posledná aktualizácia 11. júna 2021**

Spanish

**Última actualización: 11 de junio de 2021**

**Introducción**

Honeywell International Inc. ("**Honeywell**", "**nuestro**", "**nosotros**" o "**nos**"), es el "controlador de datos" de la información personal que recopilamos sobre usted cuando visita o utiliza alguno de nuestros sitios web, o usa alguno de nuestros productos, servicios o aplicaciones vinculados a esta declaración de privacidad (en conjunto, nuestros "**Sitios**"). Esta declaración de privacidad explica cómo recopilamos, compartimos y utilizamos su información personal de esta forma y cómo puede ejercer sus derechos de privacidad.

Cuando interactuamos con usted, también podemos proporcionarle avisos de privacidad adicionales sobre actividades de procesamiento específicas u ofrecerle opciones adicionales sobre cómo Honeywell procesa su información personal en ese momento en particular.

Haga clic en uno de los enlaces inferiores para ir a la sección que le interese:

**Cómo recopilamos la información**

* **Recopilamos la información directamente de usted.** Podemos pedirle información personal para prestarle un servicio o llevar a cabo una transacción que haya solicitado. También puede proporcionarnos información personal al contactar o interactuar con nosotros (por ejemplo, con un comentario, consulta o solicitud de atención al cliente cuando visita nuestro sitio web) o al registrar una cuenta para utilizar nuestros Sitios. Esta información personal puede incluir:
    * **Datos de identidad,** como su nombre, cargo, el nombre de su empresa/organización, dirección de correo electrónico, números de teléfono y dirección física (incluidos la calle, la ciudad, la provincia, el código postal y/o el país);
    * **Datos de registro,** proporcionados por usted cuando registra una cuenta para utilizar nuestros Sitios, incluidos los nombres de usuario y las contraseñas;
    * **Datos de contratación,** incluida información enviada en relación con una solicitud de empleo o consulta (como se explica a continuación);
    * **Datos de contacto empresariales,** como información relacionada con otros empleados, propietarios, directores, directivos o contratistas de organizaciones externas (por ejemplo, negocios, empresas, sociedades, propietarios únicos, organizaciones sin ánimo de lucro o agencias gubernamentales).
    * **Datos de marketing y de comunicación,** incluidas sus preferencias de marketing y sus suscripciones a nuestras publicaciones;
    * **Información financiera,** incluida la tarjeta de crédito u otros datos de la cuenta financiera que nos permita facilitarle la compra de productos y servicios de la empresa que puedan estar disponibles en nuestros Sitios;
    * **Información de control de las exportaciones,** como su nacionalidad, ciudadanía y país de residencia, que nos permita determinar su idoneidad bajo la normativa de control de exportaciones para recibir información sobre ciertas tecnologías;
    * **Información de transacciones,** incluidos pedidos y consultas sobre nuestros productos y servicios, así como detalles de pagos enviados y recibidos por usted, incluyendo el historial de órdenes de compra y la información necesaria para facilitar las transacciones de pago;
    * **Información de registro de eventos,** incluida la información que nos proporciona al rellenar formularios de inscripción electrónica; y
    * **Sus comentarios,** incluidas las encuestas, las recomendaciones u otros comentarios sobre nuestros Sitios, así como de nuestros productos y servicios en general.

Si no nos facilita la información solicitada, es posible que no podamos proporcionarle el servicio requerido ni completar su transacción.

* **Información que recopilamos automáticamente sobre usted.** Obtenemos cierta información sobre su visita a nuestros Sitios utilizando cookies y tecnologías de seguimiento similares. Siempre respetaremos cualquier derecho legal que pueda tener para evitar que lo hagamos. La información recopilada de esta forma incluye:
    * **Datos de uso,** incluida información sobre cómo utiliza nuestros Sitios, qué páginas visita, el número de bytes transferidos, los enlaces en los que hace clic, los materiales a los que accede, la fecha y la hora a las que accede al Sitio, el sitio web desde el que enlazó a uno de nuestros Sitios y otras acciones realizadas en los Sitios; y
    * **Datos técnicos,** como su dirección IP (Protocolo de Internet), el tipo, capacidad e idioma del navegador y su sistema operativo.

Para obtener más información sobre las cookies y otras tecnologías de seguimiento similares que utilizamos en nuestro Sitios, consulte nuestro [Aviso de cookies](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#spanish).

* **Información de geolocalización.** En determinados Sitios, con su consentimiento, podríamos recopilar la ubicación precisa y en tiempo real (es decir, la geolocalización) de su dispositivo móvil. Esta información se utilizará únicamente con el fin de facilitarle el uso de los Sitios, incluso por parte de nuestros proveedores de servicio, que podrían procesar esta información en relación con la prestación de servicios en nuestro nombre. Si se da el caso, podría ajustar este consentimiento gestionando sus preferencias de servicios de ubicación a través de la configuración de su dispositivo móvil.
* **Información recopilada por terceros.** De acuerdo con la legislación aplicable, podríamos recopilar información personal sobre usted de terceros, como sitios web y aplicaciones de redes sociales, y combinarla con la información sobre usted de la que ya disponemos para ayudarnos a mejorar y personalizar nuestros Sitios según sus preferencias y para otros fines establecidos en esta declaración de privacidad. También podríamos recopilar su información de contacto empresarial de su compañía o de otros terceros para facilitar o participar en actividades comerciales tradicionales y asuntos administrativos similares.

**Nuestro uso de la información**

Podríamos utilizar la información personal recopilada a través de nuestros Sitios o cuando contacta con nosotros para propósitos que incluyen:

* **Datos de contacto empresariales.** Honeywell recopila y utiliza datos de contacto empresariales para involucrarse en comunicaciones o transacciones, incluso para realizar la debida diligencia con respecto a un producto o servicio, o a su provisión o recepción. Por ejemplo, Honeywell podría recopilar y utilizar estos datos de contacto empresariales para facilitar y gestionar pedidos, contratos, garantías, mantenimiento y funciones comerciales similares, con fines de análisis y cobranza de crédito, para que nos ayuden con nuestros requisitos legales y de cumplimiento, y (si es necesario) para defender nuestros intereses y derechos.
* **Servicios y transacciones.** Podríamos usar su información personal para prestarle servicios o llevar a cabo transacciones que haya solicitado, entre las que se incluyen proporcionarle información sobre productos o servicios de la Empresa que haya adquirido o que utilice, registrar los productos adquiridos, procesar los pedidos de productos, gestionar reclamaciones de garantía, sustituir manuales de productos, responder a solicitudes de atención al cliente y facilitar el uso de nuestros Sitios.
* **Administración y protección de nuestra empresa y nuestros Sitios.** Podríamos utilizar su información personal para administrar y proteger nuestra empresa y nuestros Sitios, incluyendo la resolución de problemas, el mantenimiento del sistema, el servicio de asistencia técnica, las notificaciones y el alojamiento de datos.
* **Mejora de nuestra empresa, Sitios, productos y servicios.** Podríamos utilizar su información personal para llevar a cabo análisis empresariales o para otros fines que nos ayuden a desarrollar y mejorar la calidad de nuestra empresa, Sitios, productos y servicios (incluidos nuevos productos y servicios), por ejemplo, personalizando nuestros Sitios en función de sus preferencias o intereses particulares.
* **Marketing.** De acuerdo con las leyes y normativas aplicables, podríamos utilizar su información personal para informarle acerca de los productos o servicios que pudieran interesarle y para comunicarle ofertas, eventos y noticias, encuestas, ofertas especiales y temas relacionados. Tiene la posibilidad de darse de baja de las comunicaciones de marketing enviadas por correo electrónico en cualquier momento y de forma gratuita utilizando el enlace "Anular suscripción" de cualquier material de marketing que reciba por nuestra parte o bien poniéndose en contacto con nosotros a través de los datos de contacto incluidos en esta declaración de privacidad. En función de su país de residencia, también puede darse de baja de otros tipos de comunicaciones de marketing; póngase en contacto con nosotros utilizando los datos de contacto que se muestran en la declaración de privacidad para obtener más información. Algunas jurisdicciones brindan a las personas (por ejemplo, los residentes de California) el derecho a solicitar determinada información con respecto a nuestra divulgación de información personal a terceros para fines de marketing directo de terceros. Para obtener más información sobre nuestras prácticas de divulgación de datos con fines de marketing, póngase en contacto con nosotros siguiendo las instrucciones que se indican a continuación.
* **Publicidad personalizada.** Recopilamos datos sobre sus actividades en línea e identificamos sus intereses para poder mostrarle los anuncios que sean más relevantes para usted. Puede darse de baja de esta publicidad personalizada de Honeywell tal y como se explica en nuestro [Aviso de cookies](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#spanish).
* **Incentivos económicos y programas de fidelización.** Recopilamos y utilizamos información personal para mantener y administrar nuestros incentivos económicos y nuestros programas de fidelización. Utilizamos la información personal que usted nos facilita en esos programas para ofrecerle recompensas únicas, comprobar el estado de su programa y facilitar el intercambio de puntos del programa por productos, materiales promocionales, talleres de formación y otros artículos. En la medida en que lo permita la ley, también podemos utilizar cualquier información personal que nos facilite dentro del contexto de un programa de incentivo económico para cualquier otro propósito establecido en esta declaración de privacidad. Revise los términos y condiciones de cada programa de incentivo económico en los que quisiera registrarse o participar, ya que dichos términos y condiciones pueden estar estrictamente adaptados al programa correspondiente. Si acepta participar en estos programas, puede retirar ese consentimiento en cualquier momento poniéndose en contacto con nosotros utilizando los datos de contacto al final de esta declaración de privacidad o siguiendo las instrucciones establecidas en los términos y condiciones del programa correspondiente.
* **Solicitudes de empleo.** En relación con una consulta o una solicitud de empleo, puede facilitarnos información sobre usted como, por ejemplo, un currículum vitae, referencias profesionales, información sobre formación y trabajos anteriores, así como información sobre certificados y formación profesional. Nosotros y los miembros de nuestro grupo podríamos utilizar esta información para estudiar su solicitud de empleo, comprobar su experiencia y para la elegibilidad laboral, y como se establezca en cualquier declaración de privacidad independiente u otro aviso disponible en relación a su solicitud. Podríamos utilizar un tercero (por ejemplo, una empresa de selección de personal) o una plataforma de redes sociales para solicitar, recopilar y conservar solicitudes de empleo. Para obtener más información, lea nuestro [Aviso de privacidad del solicitante](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/applicant-privacy-notice#spanish).
* **Investigación y análisis.** Podríamos utilizar su información personal para llevar a cabo estudios y análisis que nos ayuden a analizar sus preferencias de compra, identificar los productos y servicios que mejor satisfagan sus necesidades y medir la eficacia de la publicidad que le ofrecemos.
* **Cumplimiento de normas:** podemos utilizar la información personal que recopilamos para detectar, prevenir y actuar contra el fraude, la vulneración de la propiedad intelectual, las infracciones de nuestros términos y condiciones, las infracciones de la ley u otros usos indebidos de nuestros Sitios.

En la medida en que lo permita la ley, podríamos combinar la información que recopilamos a través de nuestros Sitios con otra información que tengamos sobre usted (por ejemplo, información sobre el uso que hace de nuestros productos y servicios) para ofrecerle una experiencia de cliente mejorada y coherente al interactuar con nosotros o para otros fines establecidos en esta declaración de privacidad.

**La base legal sobre la que procesamos la información**

Si lo requiere la ley, nos aseguraremos de que haya una base legal para el procesamiento de su información personal. En la mayoría de los casos, nuestra base legal dependerá de la información personal en cuestión y del contexto específico en el que la recopilemos.

* **Contrato:** el procesamiento es necesario para el funcionamiento de los servicios que le proporcionamos, o para tomar medidas (si usted lo solicita) antes de, y anticipando, la realización de dichos servicios;
* **Obligación legal:** el procesamiento es necesario para cumplir con nuestras obligaciones legales, incluido el cumplimiento de las leyes, los reglamentos, las solicitudes gubernamentales y cuasi gubernamentales, las órdenes judiciales o las citaciones aplicables;
* **Consentimiento:** el procesamiento se basa en su consentimiento para el procesamiento de la información personal para uno o más propósitos especificados (por ejemplo, marketing);
* **Intereses legítimos:** el procesamiento es necesario para satisfacer nuestros intereses legítimos, por ejemplo, para desarrollar y mejorar nuestros Sitios, productos y/o servicios en beneficio de nuestros clientes; o
* **Intereses vitales:** el procesamiento es necesario para proteger sus intereses vitales (por ejemplo, motivos de salud y seguridad si asiste a una reunión en una ubicación de Honeywell).

Si tiene alguna duda o necesita más información acerca de la base legal sobre la que recopilamos y utilizamos su información personal, envíe un correo electrónico a [HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com)

**Anonimización de la información**

De acuerdo con la ley aplicable, podríamos anonimizar su información personal para que no pueda utilizarse en su identificación. La información anonimizada no se considera información personal y, por lo tanto, no está sujeta a esta declaración de privacidad. Podríamos recopilar, utilizar, agrupar y compartir información anonimizada para cualquier propósito.

**Cuánto tiempo almacenamos la información**

El periodo de tiempo durante el cual almacenamos su información personal puede variar en función de la finalidad del procesamiento. Por ejemplo, almacenamos información personal necesaria para proporcionarle productos y servicios o para facilitar transacciones que haya solicitado, durante tanto tiempo como sea cliente de Honeywell o, si envía una solicitud de empleo a través de nuestros Sitios, mantendremos los datos de su solicitud como se describe en el aviso de privacidad que se pone a su disposición en relación con su solicitud o según lo requiera la ley. En cualquier otro caso, almacenamos la información personal durante tanto tiempo como sea necesario para cumplir con los propósitos descritos en esta declaración de privacidad y, tras este tiempo, se anonimiza (donde lo permita la ley aplicable), se borra o se destruye.

**Divulgación de la información**

Podríamos compartir su información personal con terceros seleccionados de acuerdo con la legislación aplicable, incluyendo lo que se establece a continuación:

* **Empresas de nuestro grupo.** Podemos compartir su información personal con nuestras filiales y empresas del grupo en la medida en que sea razonablemente necesario para los fines establecidos en esta declaración de privacidad.
* **Proveedores de servicios.** Podemos compartir su información personal con empresas que hemos contratado para que presten servicios en nuestro nombre, por ejemplo, para que alojen sitios web, lleven a cabo encuestas, procesen transacciones, analicen nuestros Sitios y lleven a cabo análisis para mejorar la calidad de nuestro negocio, nuestros Sitios, los productos y los servicios. Exigimos a estos proveedores de servicio que protejan la confidencialidad de su información personal.
* **Distribuidores y otros socios empresariales de confianza.** Podemos compartir su información personal con terceros que distribuyen nuestros productos y con otros socios empresariales de confianza para diversos fines, entre los que se incluyen permitir a dichos terceros que le envíen comunicaciones de marketing. Este uso compartido de la información personal para fines de marketing se llevará a cabo de acuerdo con la legislación y reglamentos aplicables.
* **Revelación de información relacionada con las transacciones.** Con respecto a determinadas transacciones, podemos revelar parte o toda su información personal a las instituciones financieras, entidades gubernamentales y empresas de mensajería o servicios postales que participen en la realización de la transacción.
* **Revelación de información relacionada con las adquisiciones o desinversiones.** Pueden surgir circunstancias en las que, por razones estratégicas u otras razones comerciales, Honeywell decida vender, comprar, desinvertir, fusionar o reorganizar de otro modo sus negocios en algunos países. Podríamos divulgar información que conservamos de usted el tiempo que estimemos necesario para proseguir con la negociación o realización de una fusión, adquisición, desinversión o venta de todos o parte de los activos de Honeywell.
* **Revelación por otros motivos.** Podemos revelar su información personal si se nos autoriza o exige por ley o si creemos de buena fe que dicha acción es necesaria para cumplir con los requisitos legales o con procesos legales, para proteger y defender nuestros derechos o propiedades o, en circunstancias urgentes, para proteger la seguridad personal de cualquier persona.

**Transferencias internacionales**

Honeywell es una empresa global y su información personal puede ser transferida, conservada, almacenada y utilizada en diferentes ubicaciones de todo el mundo, como Estados Unidos, México y la India de acuerdo con la ley aplicable. Esto significa que cuando recopilamos su información personal, puede que sea procesada en países que tengan leyes de protección de datos distintas a las leyes de su país. No obstante, Honeywell siempre tomará medidas razonables para proteger su privacidad y para proporcionar un nivel de protección de la información personal que sea comparable a la de su país de residencia, lo que incluye la implementación de las cláusulas contractuales estándar de la Comisión Europea. Para obtener más información sobre los dispositivos de seguridad establecidos para proteger su información personal, contacte con nosotros a través de [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com).

**Seguridad**

Nos comprometemos a proteger la seguridad de su información personal. Utilizamos medidas técnicas y organizativas para proporcionar un nivel de seguridad adecuado al riesgo de procesar su información personal. Para obtener más información sobre cómo Honeywell protege su información personal, contacte con nosotros a través de [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com).

**Sus derechos**

En función de la ley aplicable, puede tener determinados derechos con respecto a su información personal.

* Puede tener derecho a **acceder, corregir, actualizar** o **solicitar la eliminación** de su información personal.
* Puede **oponerse** al procesamiento de su información personal, pedirnos que **restrinjamos** el procesamiento de su información personal o solicitar la **portabilidad** de su información personal.
* Podría tener derecho **a que no se tome una decisión sobre usted que se base únicamente en el procesamiento automatizado, incluida la elaboración de perfiles**, si esa decisión produce efectos legales sobre usted o le afecta significativamente.
* Del mismo modo, si hemos recopilado y procesado su información personal con su consentimiento, entonces **puede retirar su consentimiento en cualquier momento**. Retirar su consentimiento no afectará a la legalidad de ningún procesamiento que hubiéramos llevado a cabo antes de que lo retirara, ni afectará al procesamiento de su información personal que se haya llevado a cabo basándose en motivos legales de procesamiento distintos a los del consentimiento.
* Puede tener derecho a **rechazar la venta de su información personal**. Honeywell no vende su información personal a terceros con fines de lucro. No obstante, sí compartimos o revelamos su información personal a terceros de acuerdo con esta declaración de privacidad y nuestro [Aviso de cookies](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#spanish). Por ejemplo, nos relacionamos con terceros para distribuir nuestros productos, proporcionarle asistencia técnica, operar herramientas y funciones analíticas de sitios web, y participar en el marketing y las ventas de nuestros productos y servicios. Estas actividades pueden implicar la revelación de su información personal a terceros y puedes ser consideradas "ventas" de datos según ciertas (pero no todas) leyes de protección de datos.
* Tiene derecho a **reclamar** ante una autoridad de protección de datos responsable de supervisar el cumplimiento de la ley de protección de datos en su jurisdicción sobre nuestra recopilación y uso de su información personal si cree que nuestro procesamiento de su información personal no cumple con la ley de protección de datos. Por ejemplo, las personas del EEE tienen derecho a presentar una queja ante la autoridad de protección de datos competente, cuya lista se puede consultar en: [https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/board/members\_en](https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/board/members_en). Sin embargo, agradeceríamos la oportunidad de poder atender sus preocupaciones, así que, por favor, no dude en contactar con nosotros en relación con cualquier reclamación que pueda tener. No discriminaremos a las personas por ejercer sus derechos de privacidad de datos.

Le facilitaremos el ejercicio de los derechos que le corresponden de acuerdo con la ley aplicable. No obstante, incluso si su información personal no está protegida, o de otra manera sujeta, a una ley de protección de datos, podemos tratar de atender cualquier solicitud o consulta que pueda tener con respecto a nuestras actividades de procesamiento de datos. Si tiene dudas sobre sus derechos o quiere ejercerlos, puede contactar con nosotros a través de [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com) o enviar dudas relacionadas con la privacidad a través de nuestro formulario web interactivo en el siguiente enlace:

**Información sobre menores**

Nuestros Sitios no están dirigidos y no deberían ser utilizados por menores de dieciséis (16) años y no recopilamos, utilizamos ni vendemos información de dichas personas a sabiendas. Si es menor de edad según lo entienden las leyes de su país, no envíe ninguna información personal a través de nuestros Sitios.

**Enlaces a otros sitios web**

Nuestros Sitios pueden contener enlaces a páginas web, productos o servicios de terceros. No tenemos ninguna obligación o responsabilidad sobre esos sitios web, productos y servicios, sus políticas o su recopilación u otro procesamiento de su información personal. Las prácticas de esos terceros se rigen por sus propias políticas de privacidad. Le recomendamos que se informe sobre las políticas de privacidad de esos terceros.

**Contacte con nosotros**

Si tiene dudas en relación con esta declaración de privacidad o sobre el tratamiento de su información personal, quiere presentar una queja o desea contactar con nuestro delegado de protección de datos, póngase en contacto con nosotros utilizando la información de contacto que verá más abajo. Atenderemos su cuestión de inmediato y haremos todo lo posible por llegar a una resolución satisfactoria.

Formulario web interactivo:  
  
Correo electrónico:  
  
Dirección postal:  
Honeywell Privacy  
4D5  
115 Tabor Road  
Morris Plains, NJ 07950  
  
Número gratuito:  

**Cambios en esta declaración de privacidad**

En ocasiones, podemos actualizar esta declaración de privacidad. Cuando lo hagamos, revisaremos la fecha de "última actualización" del inicio de la declaración de privacidad y tomaremos las medidas adicionales que requiera la ley.

**Última actualización: 11 de junio de 2021**

Swedish

**Senast uppdaterad den 11 juni 2021**

**Introduktion**

Honeywell International Inc. (”**Honeywell**”, ”**vår**”, ”**oss**” eller ”**vi**”) är den ”personuppgiftsansvarige” för den personliga informationen vi samlar in om dig när du besöker eller använder någon av våra webbplatser, eller använder produkter, tjänster och applikationer som är kopplade till denna sekretesspolicy (tillsammans, våra ”**webbplatser**”). Denna sekretesspolicy förklarar hur vi samlar in, delar och använder din personliga information som samlas in på detta sätt och hur du kan utöva dina integritetsrättigheter.

När vi interagerar med dig kan vi också ge dig ytterligare sekretessmeddelanden om specifika behandlingsaktiviteter eller erbjuda ytterligare valmöjligheter gällande hur Honeywell behandlar din personliga information vid den aktuella tidpunkten.

Klicka på någon av länkarna nedan för att gå till det avsnitt som intresserar dig:

**Insamling av information**

* **Information som samlas in direkt från dig.** Vi kan be dig om personlig information för att tillhandahålla en tjänst eller genomföra en transaktion som du har begärt. Du kan också tillhandahålla personlig information till oss när du kontaktar eller interagerar med oss (t.ex. i en kommentar, förfrågan eller kundsupportärende, webbplatsbesökare) eller registrerar ett konto för att använda våra webbplatser. Denna personliga information kan inkludera:
    * **Identitetsinformation,** så som ditt namn, titel, företags-/organisationsnamn, e-postadress, telefonnummer och fysisk adress (inklusive gata, stad, delstat, postnummer och/eller land);
    * **Uppgifter för registrering som** tillhandahålls av dig när du registrerar ett konto för att använda våra webbplatser, inklusive användarnamn och lösenord;
    * **Rekryteringsinformation,** inklusive information lämnad i samband med en jobbansökan eller förfrågan (enligt beskrivningen nedan);
    * **Kontaktuppgifter för företag**, så som information relaterad till andra anställda, ägare, styrelseledamöter, befattningshavare eller entreprenörer från en tredjepartsorganisation (t.ex. verksamhet, företag, partnerskap, enmansföretag, ideell verksamhet eller statlig myndighet).
    * **Marknadsförings- och kommunikationsdata,** inklusive dina marknadsföringspreferenser och dina prenumerationer på våra publikationer;
    * **Ekonomisk information,** inklusive kreditkorts- eller annan finansiell kontoinformation i syfte att göra det möjligt för oss att underlätta ditt köp av företagets produkter och tjänster som kan finnas tillgängliga på våra webbplatser;
    * **Exportkontrollinformation,** så som din nationalitet, medborgarskap och bosättningsland, som gör det möjligt för oss att avgöra din behörighet enligt exportkontrollbestämmelser att få information om vissa tekniker;
    * **Transaktionsdata,** inklusive förfrågningar om och beställningar av våra produkter och tjänster samt information om betalningar till och från dig, inklusive inköpsorderhistorik och information som behövs för att underlätta betalningstransaktioner;
    * **Registreringsinformation för evenemang,** inklusive information som du tillhandahåller när du fyller i registreringsformulär online; och
    * **Din feedback,** inklusive undersökningar, rekommendationer eller annan feedback från dig om våra webbplatser samt våra produkter och tjänster i allmänhet.

När du inte tillhandahåller efterfrågad information kanske vi inte kan tillhandahålla den begärda tjänsten eller genomföra din transaktion.

* **Information vi automatiskt samlar in om dig.** Vi samlar in viss information om ditt besök på våra webbplatser med hjälp av cookies och liknande spårningstekniker. Vi kommer alltid att respektera de rättigheter du har enligt lag att förhindra att vi gör detta. Uppgifter som samlas in på detta sätt inkluderar:
    * **Användningsdata,** inklusive information om hur du använder våra webbplatser, vilka sidor du visar, antalet byte som överförts, länkarna du klickar på, materialet du tillgår, datum och tid när du besöker webbplatsen, webbplatsen från vilken du länkat till någon av våra webbplatser samt andra åtgärder som vidtagits på webbplatserna; och
    * **Tekniska data,** så som din IP-adress (Internet Protocol), din webbläsartyp, dess funktioner, språk och ditt operativsystem.

För information om cookies och andra liknande spårningsteknologier som vi använder på våra webbplatser, se vårt [Meddelande om användning av cookies](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#swedish).

* **Information om geografisk plats.** På vissa webbplatser, med ditt samtycke, kan vi i realtid registrera den exakta platsen (dvs. geografisk plats) din mobila enhet befinner sig på. Denna information kommer endast att användas för att underlätta din användning av webbplatserna, inklusive våra tjänsteleverantörer som kan behandla denna information i samband med att de tillhandahåller tjänster för vår räkning. Om du har gett ditt samtycke kan du ändra detta genom att hantera dina inställningar för platstjänster via inställningarna på din mobila enhet.
* **Information som samlats in från tredje part.** I enlighet med tillämplig lag kan vi samla in personlig information om dig från tredje part, till exempel webbplatser och applikationer för sociala medier och kombinera den med information vi redan har, för att hjälpa oss att förbättra och anpassa våra webbplatser enligt dina preferenser och för andra ändamål som anges i denna sekretesspolicy. Vi kan också samla in din företagskontaktinformation via din arbetsgivare eller andra tredje parter för att underlätta eller på annat sätt delta i traditionell affärsverksamhet och liknande administrativa frågor.

**Användning av information**

Vi kan använda den personliga information som samlas in via våra webbplatser eller när du kontaktar oss för ändamål som inkluderar:

* **Företagskontaktinformation.** Honeywell samlar in och använder företagskontaktinformation för att delta i kommunikation eller transaktioner, inklusive för att vidta skälig aktsamhet avseende, eller vid tillhandahållandet eller mottagandet av, en produkt eller tjänst. Honeywell kan till exempel samla in och använda denna företagskontaktinformation för att underlätta och hantera beställningar, kontrakt, garantier, underhåll och liknande affärsfunktioner, för kreditanalys och insamlingsändamål, för att hjälpa till med vår egen interna efterlevnad och juridiska krav och (om nödvändigt) för att försvara våra intressen och anspråk.
* **Tjänster och transaktioner.** Vi kan använda din personliga information för att leverera tjänster till dig eller genomföra transaktioner du har begärt, inklusive, men inte begränsat till, tillhandahålla information om företagets produkter eller tjänster som du har köpt eller på annat sätt använder, registrera köpta produkter, behandla produktbeställningar, hantera garantianspråk, ersätta produktmanualer, svara på kundtjänstförfrågningar och underlätta användningen av våra webbplatser.
* **Administrera och skydda vår verksamhet och webbplatser.** Vi kan använda din personliga information för att administrera och skydda vår verksamhet och våra webbplatser, inklusive felsökning, systemunderhåll, support, rapportering och datavärdskap.
* **Förbättra vår verksamhet, webbplatser, produkter och tjänster.** Vi kan använda din personliga information för att utföra affärsanalyser eller för andra ändamål som hjälper oss att utveckla och förbättra kvaliteten på vår verksamhet, webbplatser, produkter och tjänster (inklusive nya produkter och tjänster), till exempel genom att anpassa våra webbplatser till dina specifika preferenser eller intressen.
* **Marknadsföring.** I enlighet med tillämpliga lagar och förordningar kan vi använda din personliga information för att informera dig om produkter eller tjänster som kan vara av intresse för dig och för att på annat sätt kommunicera med dig om erbjudanden, evenemang och nyheter, undersökningar, specialerbjudanden och relaterade ämnen. Du kan när som helst och utan kostnad välja bort marknadsföringskommunikation som skickas via e-post genom att använda länken ”avanmälan” i något av det marknadsföringsmaterial du får från oss via e-post, eller genom att kontakta oss med hjälp av kontaktinformationen som anges i denna sekretesspolicy. Beroende på i vilket land du bor kan du också välja bort andra typer av marknadsföringskommunikation; vänligen kontakta oss med hjälp av kontaktinformationen i sekretesspolicyn för mer information. Vissa jurisdiktioner ger individer (t.ex. invånare i Kalifornien) rätten att begära viss information om vår utlämning av personlig information till tredje part för tredje parts direkta marknadsföringsändamål. Kontakta oss enligt instruktionerna nedan för mer information om vår praxis gällande utlämning av uppgifter för marknadsföringsändamål.
* **Intressebaserad annonsering.** Vi samlar in data om dina aktiviteter online och identifierar dina intressen så att vi kan tillhandahålla annonsering som är mest relevant för dig. Du kan välja bort intressebaserad annonsering från Honeywell enligt beskrivningen i vårt [Meddelande om användning av cookies](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#swedish).
* **Ekonomiska incitament och lojalitetsprogram.** Vi samlar in och använder personlig information för att underhålla och administrera våra ekonomiska incitament och lojalitetsprogram. Vi använder den personliga informationen du tillhandahåller i dessa program för att erbjuda unika belöningar, spåra din programstatus och för att underlätta utbytet av programpoäng för produkter, reklammaterial, utbildningsworkshops och andra objekt. I den utsträckning som lagen tillåter kan vi också använda all personlig information som du tillhandahåller i samband med ett program med ekonomiska incitament för något annat syfte som anges i denna sekretesspolicy. Det är viktigt att du läser igenom villkoren för varje program med ekonomiska incitament som du vill registrera dig eller delta i eftersom dessa villkor kan vara mycket specifikt anpassade till det tillämpliga programmet. Om du samtycker till att delta i något av dessa program kan du när som helst dra tillbaka ditt samtycke genom att kontakta oss via kontaktuppgifterna i denna sekretesspolicy eller i enlighet med instruktionerna som anges i de tillämpliga villkoren.
* **Jobbansökningar.** I samband med en jobbansökan eller förfrågan kan du förse oss med information om dig själv, till exempel ett CV/meritförteckning, yrkesreferenser, information om utbildning och arbetsbakgrund samt information om yrkesutbildning och certifieringar. Vi och medlemmar i vår koncern kan använda denna information i syfte att överväga anställning, göra bakgrundskontroller och utvärdera anställningslämplighet och annat som anges i varje separat sekretesspolicy eller annat meddelande som görs tillgängligt i samband med din ansökan. Vi kan använda en tredje part (t.ex. jobbrekryterare) eller sociala medieplattformar för att värva, samla in och behålla jobbansökningar. För mer information, läs vårt [Meddelande om arbetssökandes sekretess](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/applicant-privacy-notice#swedish).
* **Forskning och analys.** Vi kan använda din personliga information för att utföra forskning och analys i syfte att hjälpa oss att analysera dina inköpspreferenser, identifiera de produkter och tjänster som bäst uppfyller dina krav och mäta effektiviteten av den annonsering vi erbjuder dig.
* **Tillämpning:** Vi kan använda den personliga informationen vi samlar in för att upptäcka, förhindra och svara på bedrägerier, intrång i immateriella rättigheter, brott mot våra villkor, överträdelser av lag eller annat missbruk av våra webbplatser.

Där lagen tillåter kan vi kombinera informationen som vi samlar in via våra webbplatser med annan information som vi har om dig (så som information om din användning av våra produkter och tjänster) för att erbjuda dig en förbättrad och konsekvent kundupplevelse när du interagerar med oss eller för andra ändamål som anges i denna sekretesspolicy.

**Den rättsliga grunden på vilken vi behandlar information**

Där det krävs enligt lag kommer vi att se till att det finns en rättslig grund för behandlingen av din personliga information. I de flesta fall beror vår rättsliga grund på berörd personlig information och det specifika sammanhang där vi samlar in den.

* **Kontrakt:** behandlingen är nödvändig för utförandet av de tjänster vi tillhandahåller dig, eller för att vidta åtgärder (på din begäran) före utförandet, och vid förväntan att utföra, sådana tjänster;
* **Juridisk skyldighet:** behandlingen är nödvändig för att uppfylla våra juridiska skyldigheter, inklusive efterlevnad av tillämpliga lagar, förordningar, statliga och kvasistatliga begäranden, domstolsbeslut eller stämningar;
* **Samtycke:** behandlingen baseras på ditt samtycke till behandlingen av din personliga information för ett eller flera specifika ändamål (t.ex. marknadsföring);
* **Legitima intressen:** behandlingen är nödvändig för att tillgodose våra legitima intressen, till exempel för att utveckla och förbättra våra webbplatser, produkter och/eller tjänster till förmån för våra kunder; eller
* **Vitala intressen:** behandlingen är nödvändig för att skydda dina vitala intressen (till exempel hälso- och säkerhetsskäl om du deltar i ett möte på en Honeywell-plats).

Om du har några frågor eller behöver ytterligare information om den rättsliga grund på vilken vi samlar in och använder din personliga information, skicka ett e-postmeddelande till [HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com).

**Anonymisering av information**

I enlighet med tillämplig lag kan vi anonymisera din personliga information så att den inte längre kan användas för att identifiera dig. Anonymiserad information anses inte vara personlig information och omfattas därför inte av denna sekretesspolicy. Vi kan samla in, använda, aggregera och dela anonymiserad information för alla syften.

**Hur länge vi behåller uppgifter**

Perioden under vilken vi lagrar din personliga information varierar beroende på syftet med behandlingen. Vi lagrar till exempel personlig information som behövs för att förse dig med produkter och tjänster, eller för att underlätta transaktioner du har begärt, så länge du är kund hos Honeywell eller om du skickar in en jobbansökan via våra webbplatser kommer vi att behålla information om din ansökan enligt beskrivningen i sekretessmeddelandet som görs tillgängligt för dig i samband med din ansökan eller på annat sätt krävs enligt lag. I alla andra fall lagrar vi din personliga information så länge som behövs för att uppfylla de syften som beskrivs i denna sekretesspolicy, varefter den antingen anonymiseras (där det är tillåtet enligt tillämplig lag), raderas eller förstörs.

**Utlämning av information**

Vi kan dela din personliga information med utvalda tredje parter i enlighet med tillämplig lag, inklusive enligt vad som anges nedan:

* **Våra koncernföretag.** Vi kan dela din personliga information med våra dotterbolag och koncernföretag enligt vad som är rimligt nödvändigt för de ändamål som anges i denna sekretesspolicy.
* **Tjänsteleverantörer.** Vi kan dela din personliga information med företag som vi har ingått avtal med att tillhandahålla tjänster för vår räkning, så som att vara värd för webbplatser, genomföra undersökningar, behandla transaktioner, analysera våra webbplatser och utföra analyser för att förbättra kvaliteten på vår verksamhet, webbplatser, produkter och tjänster. Vi kräver att dessa tjänsteleverantörer skyddar din personliga informations konfidentialitet.
* **Distributörer och andra betrodda affärspartner.** Vi kan dela din personliga information med tredje part som distribuerar våra produkter och andra betrodda affärspartner för ändamål som inkluderar att dessa tredje parter kan skicka marknadsföringskommunikation till dig. Sådan delning av personlig information för marknadsföringsändamål kommer att ske i enlighet med tillämpliga lagar och regler.
* **Utlämning i samband med transaktioner.** I samband med vissa transaktioner kan vi lämna ut någon eller all din personliga information till finansinstitut, statliga enheter och rederier eller posttjänster som är involverade i genomförandet av transaktionen.
* **Utlämningar i samband med förvärv eller avyttringar.** Omständigheter kan uppstå om Honeywell av strategiska eller andra affärsskäl beslutar att sälja, köpa, avyttra, slå samman eller på annat sätt omorganisera företag i vissa länder. Vi kan lämna ut information som vi har om dig i den utsträckning som är rimligt nödvändigt för att fortsätta med förhandlingarna eller slutförandet av en sammanslagning, förvärv, avyttring eller försäljning av hela eller en del av Honeywells tillgångar.
* **Utlämning av andra skäl.** Vi kan lämna ut personlig information om detta krävs eller bemyndigas enligt lag eller i god tro och det är nödvändigt för att följa rättsliga krav eller för en juridisk process som delges oss, för att skydda och försvara våra rättigheter eller egendom, under brådskande omständigheter, för att skydda varje individs personliga säkerhet.

**Internationella överföringar**

Honeywell är en global organisation och din personliga information kan överföras till, förvaras, lagras eller användas över olika platser världen över, så som USA, Mexiko och Indien i enlighet med tillämplig lag. Detta innebär att när vi samlar in din personliga information kan den behandlas i länder som kan ha dataskyddslagar som skiljer sig från lagarna i ditt land. Honeywell kommer dock alltid att vidta rimliga åtgärder för att skydda din integritet och för att tillhandahålla en skyddsnivå för personlig information som är jämförbar med den i ditt bosättningsland, inklusive implementering av Europeiska kommissionens standardavtalsklausuler. För mer information om lämpliga skyddsåtgärder för att skydda din personliga information, vänligen kontakta oss på [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com).

**Säkerhet**

Vi arbetar för att upprätthålla säkerheten för dina personuppgifter. Vi använder tekniska och organisatoriska åtgärder för att tillhandahålla en säkerhetsnivå som är lämplig för behandlingen av din personliga information. För mer information om hur Honeywell skyddar din personliga information, vänligen kontakta oss på [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com).

**Dina rättigheter**

Beroende på tillämplig lag kan du ha vissa rättigheter med avseende på din personliga information.

* Du kan ha rätt att **få tillgång till, korrigera, uppdatera** eller **begära radering** av din personliga information.
* Du kan **motsätta dig** behandlingen av din personliga information, be oss att **begränsa** behandlingen av din personliga information eller begära **flyttbarhet** av din personliga information.
* Du kan ha rätt **att inte få ett beslut fattat om dig som enbart baseras på automatiserad behandling, inklusive profilering** om beslutet i fråga leder till rättsliga effekter för dig eller påverkar dig på något väsentligt sätt.
* På samma sätt, om vi har samlat in och behandlat din personliga information med ditt samtycke, **kan du när som helst dra tillbaka ditt samtycke**. Tillbakadragande av ditt samtycke påverkar inte lagenligheten av all behandling som vi genomfört före ditt tillbakadragande och det kommer inte heller att påverka behandlingen av din personliga information som utförs beroende av andra lagliga behandlingsgrunder än samtycke.
* Du kan ha rätt att **välja bort försäljning av din personliga information**. Honeywell säljer inte din personliga information till tredje part för vinst. Vi delar eller lämnar dock ut din personliga information till tredje part i enlighet med denna sekretesspolicy och vårt [Meddelande om användning av cookies](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#swedish). Till exempel samarbetar vi med tredje part för att distribuera våra produkter, tillhandahålla teknisk hjälp, använda verktyg för analys av webbplatser och funktioner samt bedriva marknadsföring och försäljning av våra produkter och tjänster. Sådana aktiviteter kan innebära att din personliga information lämnas ut till tredje part och kan betraktas som en ”försäljning” av uppgifter enligt vissa (men inte alla) dataskyddslagar.
* Du har rätt att **lämna klagomål** till en dataskyddsmyndighet som ansvarar för att övervaka efterlevnaden av dataskyddslagen i din jurisdiktion gällande vår insamling och användning av din personliga information om du anser att vår behandling av din personliga information inte överensstämmer med dataskyddslagen. Till exempel har enskilda personer inom EES rätt att lämna in ett klagomål till den behöriga dataskyddsmyndigheten, vars lista kan nås på: [https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/board/members\_en](https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/board/members_en). Vi skulle dock uppskatta att få möjligheten att ta itu med dina frågor, så kontakta oss gärna angående eventuella klagomål. Vi diskriminerar inte individer för att de utövar sina dataskyddsrättigheter.

Vi kommer att underlätta ditt utövande av de rättigheter som gäller för dig i enlighet med tillämplig lag. Men även om din personliga information inte ges skydd enligt eller på annat sätt omfattas av en dataskyddslag kan vi försöka tillgodose de krav eller förfrågningar du har om vår databehandling. Om du har frågor om dina rättigheter eller vill utöva dina rättigheter kan du kontakta oss på [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com) eller skicka in dina frågor rörande sekretess via vårt interaktiva webbformulär på följande länk:

**Information för barn**

Våra webbplatser är inte riktade till och bör inte användas av barn under sexton (16) år och vi samlar inte medvetet in, använder eller säljer information från sådana individer. Om du är minderårig enligt lagarna i ditt land, vänligen lämna inte någon personlig information via våra webbplatser.

**Länkar till andra webbplatser**

Våra webbplatser kan innehålla länkar till webbplatser, produkter och tjänster tillhörande tredje part. Vi har ingen skyldighet eller ansvar för dessa webbplatser, produkter och tjänster, deras policyer, deras insamling eller annan behandling av din personliga information. Dessa tredje parters praxis styrs av deras egen sekretesspolicy. Vi uppmuntrar dig att ta reda på vad dessa tredje parter har för sekretesspolicyer.

**Kontakta oss**

Om du har frågor angående denna sekretesspolicy eller vår hantering av din personliga information, vill lämna ett klagomål eller komma i kontakt med vårt dataskyddsombud, kontakta oss med hjälp av kontaktinformationen nedan. Vi kommer omedelbart att ta itu med dina frågor och arbeta för att nå en tillfredsställande lösning.

Interaktivt webbformulär:  
  
E-post:  
  
Postadress:  
Honeywell Privacy  
4D5  
115 Tabor Road  
Morris Plains, NJ 07950  
  
Avgiftsfritt nummer:  

**Ändringar i denna sekretesspolicy**

Vi kan ibland göra uppdateringar i denna sekretesspolicy. När vi gör det kommer vi att revidera det ”senast uppdaterad”-datumet högst upp i sekretesspolicyn och vidta sådana ytterligare åtgärder som kan krävas enligt lag.

**Senast uppdaterad den 11 juni 2021**

Turkish

**Son güncelleme: 11 Haziran 2021**

**Giriş**

Honeywell International Inc. ("**Honeywell**", "**bizim**", "**bize**" veya "**biz**"), web sitelerimizden herhangi birini ziyaret ettiğinizde veya kullandığınızda veya bu Gizlilik Bildirimi ile bağlantılı ürünleri, hizmetleri ve uygulamaları kullandığınızda (topluca "**Siteler**") hakkınızda topladığımız kişisel bilgilerin "veri denetleyicisidir". Bu Gizlilik Bildirimi, bu şekilde toplanan kişisel bilgilerinizi nasıl topladığımızı, paylaştığımızı ve kullandığımızı ve gizlilik haklarınızı nasıl kullanabileceğinizi açıklamaktadır.

Sizinle etkileşim kurduğumuzda, size belirli işleme faaliyetleri hakkında ek gizlilik bildirimleri sağlayabilir veya Honeywell'in belirli bir zamanda kişisel bilgilerinizi nasıl işlediği konusunda size ek seçenekler sunabiliriz.

İstediğiniz bölüme geçmek için aşağıdaki bağlantılardan birine tıklayın:

**Tarafımızdan bilgi toplanması**

* **Doğrudan sizden toplanan bilgiler.** Sitelerimizi ziyaret ettiğinizde talep ettiğiniz bir hizmeti vermek veya bir işlemi gerçekleştirmek için sizden kişisel bilgiler girmenizi isteyebiliriz. Ayrıca bizimle iletişime geçtiğinizde veya etkileşim kurduğunuzda (ör. bir yorum, soru veya müşteri destek talebi, site ziyaretçileri) veya Sitelerimizi kullanmak için bir hesap kaydı yaptığınızda da bize kişisel bilgiler verebilirsiniz. Bu kişisel bilgiler şunları içerebilir:
    * **Kimlik verileri,** isminiz, unvanınız, şirketinizin/kuruluşunuzun ismi, e-posta adresiniz, telefon numaralarınız ve posta adresiniz (sokak, şehir, eyalet, posta kodu veya bölge kodu ve/veya ülke dâhil olmak üzere) gibi veriler;
    * **Kayıt verileri,** Sitelerimizi kullanmak adına bir hesap için kaydolduğunuzda kullanıcı adları ve şifreler dahil olmak üzere sizin tarafınızdan sağlanan veriler;
    * **İşe alım verileri,** İş başvurusu veya işe almayla bağlantılı olarak sunulan bilgiler dahil olmak üzere veriler (aşağıda açıklandığı gibi);
    * **İş iletişim verileri,** bir üçüncü taraf kuruluşun (ör. işletme, şirket, ortaklık, şahıs şirketi, kar amacı gütmeyen kuruluş veya devlet kurumu) diğer çalışanları, sahipleri, yöneticileri, memurları veya yüklenicileriyle ilgili bilgiler gibi.
    * **Pazarlama ve iletişim verileri,** pazarlama konusundaki tercihlerinizi ve yayınlarımıza aboneliklerinizi içeren veriler;
    * **Finansal bilgiler,** Sitelerimizde bulunabilecek Şirket ürünlerini ve hizmetlerini satın almanızı kolaylaştırmamızı sağlamak amacıyla kredi kartı veya diğer banka hesap bilgilerini içeren bilgiler;
    * **İhracat denetleme bilgileri,** uyruğunuz, vatandaşlığınız ve ikamet ettiğiniz ülke gibi, ihracat yönetmelikleri uyarınca belirli teknolojiler hakkında bilgi almaya uygun olup olmadığınızı belirlememizi sağlayan bilgiler;
    * **İşlem verileri,** sipariş formu ve ödeme işlemlerini kolaylaştırmak için gereken bilgiler de dahil olmak üzere ürün ve hizmetlerimizle ilgili sorular ve siparişler ile sizden alınan ve size yapılan ödemelerin ayrıntıları;
    * **Etkinlik kayıt bilgileri,** e-kayıt formlarını doldururken sağladığınız bilgilerin dahil olduğu bilgiler ve
    * **Geri bildiriminiz,** anketler, öneriler veya genel olarak ürünlerimiz ve hizmetlerimizin yanı sıra Sitelerimiz hakkında sizden gelen diğer geri bildirimler.

İstenen bilgiyi sağlamadığınızda size istenen hizmeti sunamayabilir ya da işleminizi tamamlayamayabiliriz.

* **Hakkınızda otomatik olarak topladığımız bilgiler**. Çerezler ve benzer izleme teknolojileri kullanarak Sitelerimizi ziyaretiniz hakkında belirli bilgiler topluyoruz. Bunu yapmamızı engellemeniz konusunda sahip olabileceğiniz yasal haklara her zaman saygı duyarız. Bu şekilde toplanan veriler şunları içerir:
    * **Kullanım verileri,** Sitelerimizi nasıl kullandığınız, hangi sayfaları görüntülediğiniz, aktarılan bayt miktarı, tıkladığınız bağlantılar, eriştiğiniz materyaller, Siteye eriştiğiniz tarih ve saat, bağlantı aracılığıyla sizi Sitemize yönlendiren web sitesi ve Sitelerde gerçekleştirilen diğer eylemler hakkındaki bilgileri içeren veriler ve
    * **Teknik veriler,** İnternet Protokolü (IP) adresiniz, tarayıcınızın türü, yetenekleri ve dili ve işletim sisteminiz gibi veriler.

Sitelerimizde kullandığımız çerezler ve diğer benzer izleme teknolojileri hakkında bilgi için lütfen [Çerez Bildirimi](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#turkish) sayfamıza bakın.

* **Coğrafi konum bilgileri.** Belirli Siteler için, onayınızla birlikte, mobil cihazınızın kesin, gerçek zamanlı konumunu (yani coğrafi konumu) toplayabiliriz. Bu bilgiler yalnızca, bu bilgileri bizim adımıza hizmet sağlamakla bağlantılı olarak işleyebilecek hizmet sağlayıcılarımız da dahil olmak üzere, Siteleri kullanımınızı kolaylaştırmak amacıyla kullanılır. Onay verilmişse, mobil cihazınızın ayarları aracılığıyla Konum Servisleri tercihlerinizi yöneterek bu izni ayarlayabilirsiniz.
* **Üçüncü taraflardan toplanan bilgiler.** Yürürlükteki yasalara uygun olarak, Sitelerimizi tercihlerinize ve bu Gizlilik Bildiriminde belirtilen diğer amaçlara göre iyileştirmemize ve özelleştirmemize yardımcı olmak için sosyal medya web siteleri ve uygulamaları gibi üçüncü taraflardan hakkınızda kişisel bilgiler toplayabilir ve bunları halihazırda elimizde bulunan bilgilerle birleştirebiliriz. Ayrıca, geleneksel ticari faaliyetleri ve benzer idari konuları kolaylaştırmak veya bunlarla ilgilenmek için işvereninizden veya diğer üçüncü taraflardan iş iletişim bilgilerinizi toplayabiliriz.

**Tarafımızdan bilginin kullanılması**

Sitelerimiz aracılığıyla veya bizle iletişime geçtiğinizde toplanan kişisel bilgileri şu amaçlar için kullanabiliriz:

* **İş İletişim Verileri.** Honeywell, bir ürün veya hizmetle ilgili durum tespiti yapmak veya bir ürün veya hizmet sağlamak veya almak da dahil olmak üzere, iletişim veya işlemlerde bulunmak için iş iletişim verilerini toplar ve kullanır. Örneğin, Honeywell bu iş iletişim verilerini siparişleri, sözleşmeleri, garantileri, bakım ve benzeri iş fonksiyonlarını kolaylaştırmak ve yönetmek, kredi analizi ve tahsilat amaçlarıyla, kendi iç uyumumuza ve yasal gereksinimlerimize yardımcı olmak ve (gerekirse) çıkarlarımızı ve iddialarımızı savunmak için toplayabilir ve kullanabilir.
* **Hizmetler ve işlemler.** Kişisel bilgilerinizi, satın aldığınız veya başka şekilde kullandığınız Şirket ürünleri ve hizmetleri hakkında bilgi sağlamak, satın alınan ürünleri kaydetmek, ürün siparişlerini işlemek, teminat taleplerini işlemek, ürün el kitaplarını değiştirmek, müşteri hizmet taleplerine cevap vermek ve Sitelerimizin kullanımını kolaylaştırmak dâhil, ancak bunlarla sınırlı olmamak üzere, talep ettiğiniz hizmetleri vermek veya işlemleri gerçekleştirmek için kullanabiliriz.
* **İşletmemizin ve Sitelerimizin yönetilmesi ve korunması.** Kişisel bilgilerinizi; arıza arama, sistem bakımı, destek, raporlama ve verinin barındırılması dâhil olmak üzere işletmemizi ve Sitelerimizi yönetmek ve korumak için kullanabiliriz.
* **İşimizi, Sitelerimizi ve hizmetlerimizi iyileştirme.** Kişisel bilgilerinizi iş analizleri gerçekleştirmek veya Sitelerimizi belirli tercihlerinize ve ilgilerinize göre özelleştirmek gibi, işimizin, Sitelerimizin, ürünlerimizin ve hizmetlerinizin (yeni ürünler ve hizmetler dâhil) kalitesini geliştirmede ve iyileştirmede bize yardımcı olacak amaçlar için kullanabiliriz.
* **Pazarlama.** Yürürlükteki yasalara ve yönetmeliklere uygun olarak kişisel bilgilerinizi size ilgilenebileceğiniz ürünler ve hizmetler ile ilgili bilgi vermek veya teklifler, etkinlikler ve haberler, anketler, özel teklifler ve alakalı başlıklarla ilgili sizle iletişime geçmek için kullanabiliriz. Gönderdiğimiz e-posta pazarlama malzemelerindeki "aboneliği kaldır" bağlantısını kullanarak veya işbu Gizlilik Bildiriminde listelenen iletişim bilgileri ile bizimle iletişime geçerek e-posta ile gönderilen pazarlama iletişimlerini istediğiniz zaman ücretsiz olarak geri çevirebilirsiniz. İkamet ettiğiniz ülkeye bağlı olarak, diğer pazarlama iletişimi türlerini de devre dışı bırakabilirsiniz; daha fazla bilgi için lütfen Gizlilik Bildiriminde listelenen iletişim bilgilerini kullanarak bizimle iletişime geçin. Bazı yetki alanlarında, bireylere (örneğin, Kaliforniya'da ikamet edenlere) üçüncü tarafların doğrudan pazarlama amaçları için kişisel bilgileri üçüncü taraflara açıklamamızla ilgili belirli bilgileri talep etme hakkı verir. Pazarlama amaçlı veri açıklama uygulamalarımız hakkında daha fazla bilgi için lütfen aşağıda listelenen talimatlara uygun olarak bizimle iletişime geçin.
* **İlgi Alanına Dayalı Reklamcılık.** Sizinle en alakalı reklamları sunabilmemiz için çevrimiçi etkinlikleriniz hakkında veri topluyoruz ve ilgi alanlarınızı belirliyoruz. Honeywell'den ilgi alanına dayalı reklamları almayı [Çerez Bildirimi](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#turkish) sayfamızda açıklandığı şekilde devre dışı bırakabilirsiniz.
* **Finansal Teşvik ve Sadakat Programları.** Mali teşvik ve sadakat programlarımızı korumak ve yönetmek için kişisel bilgileri topluyor ve kullanıyoruz. Bu programlarda verdiğiniz kişisel bilgileri benzersiz ödüller sunmak, program durumunuzu izlemek ve ürünler, promosyon materyalleri, eğitim atölyeleri ve diğer ürünler için program puan değişimini kolaylaştırmak için kullanıyoruz. Yasaların izin verdiği ölçüde, bir finansal teşvik programı bağlamında sağladığınız tüm kişisel bilgileri, bu Gizlilik Bildiriminde belirtilen diğer herhangi bir amaç için de kullanabiliriz. Lütfen kaydolmak veya katılmak istediğiniz her bir finansal teşvik programının şart ve koşullarını gözden geçirin, çünkü bu şartlar ve koşullar geçerli programa hukuken uyacak şekilde uyarlanabilir. Bu programlara katılmayı kabul ederseniz, bu Gizlilik Bildiriminin sonundaki iletişim bilgilerini kullanarak veya geçerli programın hüküm ve koşullarında belirtilen talimatlara uygun olarak bizimle iletişime geçerek bu izni istediğiniz zaman geri çekebilirsiniz.
* **İş başvuruları.** Bir iş başvurusu veya iş aramayla bağlantılı olarak, bize kendiniz hakkında özgeçmiş veya mesleki geçmiş, profesyonel referanslar, eğitim ve kariyer geçmişine dair bilgiler ve mesleki eğitim ve sertifika bilgileri gibi bilgiler verebilirsiniz. Biz ve grubumuzun üyeleri bu bilgiyi işe alımı değerlendirme, geçmişe dönük kontroller ve işe uygunluk amacıyla veya başvurunuzla bağlantılı olarak sunulan herhangi ayrı bir gizlilik bildiriminde ya da diğer bildirimlerde belirtildiği şekilde kullanabiliriz. İş başvurularını istemek, toplamak ve saklamak için üçüncü bir taraf (ör. iş veren) veya sosyal medya platformunu kullanabiliriz. Daha fazla bilgi için, [Başvuru Sahibi Gizlilik Bildirimi](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/applicant-privacy-notice#turkish) sayfamızı okuyun.
* **Araştırma ve analiz.** Kişisel bilgilerinizi, satın alma tercihlerinizi analiz etmede, gereksinimlerinizi en iyi karşılayan ürünleri ve hizmetleri tanımlamada ve size sunduğumuz reklamların etkililiğini ölçmede bize yardımcı olması için araştırma veya analiz yapmak üzere kullanabiliriz.
* **Yürütme:** Topladığımız kişisel bilgileri sahteciliği, fikri mülkiyet haklarının çiğnenmesini, şartlar ve koşullarımızın veya yasaların ihlal edilmesini veya Sitelerimizin başka herhangi bir şekilde kötüye kullanılmasını saptamak, önlemek veya bunlara karşılık vermek için kullanabiliriz.

Yasaların izin verdiği durumlarda, bizle etkileşime geçtiğinizde size iyileştirilmiş ve tutarlı bir müşteri deneyimi sunmak için veya bu Gizlilik Bildiriminde belirtilen diğer amaçlarla, Sitelerimiz aracılığıyla topladığımız bilgileri sizin hakkınızda sahip olduğumuz diğer bilgilerle (ürünlerimizi ve hizmetlerimizi kullanımınız hakkındaki bilgiler gibi) birleştirebiliriz.

**Bilgilerinizi işlememizin yasal dayanağı**

Yasaların gerektirdiği durumlarda kişisel bilginizin işlenmesi için yasal bir dayanak olmasını sağlarız. Çoğu durumda yasal dayanağımız, ilgili kişisel bilgilere ve bunları topladığımız özel bağlama bağlı olur.

* **Sözleşme:** işleme, size sunduğumuz hizmetlerin yerine getirilmesi için veya bu tür hizmetleri gerçekleştirmeden önce ve bu tür hizmetleri gerçekleştirme beklentisiyle (isteğiniz üzerine) adımlar atmak için gereklidir;
* **Yasal zorunluluk:** işlemenin yürürlükteki yasalara, yönetmeliklere, hükümet ve hükümet benzeri kurum taleplerine, mahkeme emirlerine ve celplerine uymak da dahil olmak üzere, yükümlülüklerimize uymak için gereklidir;
* **Onay:** işlemenin belirtilen bir veya daha fazla amaç için (ör. pazarlama) kişisel bilgilerinizin işlenmesine verdiğiniz onaya dayalıdır;
* **Meşru menfaatler:** işlemenin meşru menfaatlerimizi karşılamak için, örneğin Sitelerimizi, ürünlerimizi ve/veya hizmetlerimizi müşterilerimizin yararına geliştirmek ve iyileştirmek için, gereklidir veya
* **Hayati çıkarlar:** işleme, hayati çıkarlarınızı korumak için gereklidir (örneğin, bir Honeywell konumunda bir toplantıya katılmanız durumunda sağlık ve güvenlik nedenleri).

Kişisel bilgilerinizi toplamamızın ve kullanmamızın yasal dayanağı hakkında herhangi bir sorunuz varsa veya daha fazla bilgiye ihtiyacınız varsa, [HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:HoneywellPrivacy@honeywell.com) adresine e-posta gönderin.

**Bilgilerinizin anonimleştirilmesi**

Yürürlükteki yasalara uygun olarak kişisel bilgilerinizi sizi tanımlama amacıyla kullanılamaması için anonim hale getirebiliriz. Anonimleştirilmiş bilgiler kişisel bilgi olarak kabul edilmez ve bu nedenle bu Gizlilik Bildirimine tabi değildir. Anonimleştirilmiş bilgileri herhangi bir amaç için toplayabilir, kullanabilir, bir araya getirebilir ve paylaşabiliriz.

**Bilgilerinizi saklama süremiz**

Kişisel bilgilerinizi depoladığımız süre işlemenin amacına göre değişiklik gösterir. Örneğin, size ürünler veya hizmetler sunmak veya talep ettiğiniz işlemleri gerçekleştirmek için gereken kişisel bilgileri, Honeywell müşterisi olduğunuz süre boyunca depolarız veya Sitelerimiz üzerinden bir iş başvurusu göndermeniz halinde başvurunuzla bağlantılı olarak size sunulan gizlilik bildiriminde veya diğer bildirimlerde belirtildiği şekilde ya da yasaların gerektirdiği başka şekillerde başvurunuzun detaylarını tutarız. Diğer tüm durumlarda kişisel bilgilerinizi bu Gizlilik Bildiriminde belirtilen amaçları karşılamak için gereken süre boyunca depolarız, sonrasında bu bilgiler anonim hale getirilir (yürürlükteki yasaların izin verdiği durumlarda), silinir veya imha edilir.

**Bilgilerin açıklanması**

işisel bilgilerinizi yürürlükteki yasalara uygun olarak ve aşağıda belirtilen biçimlerin dahil olduğu şekillerde seçilmiş üçüncü taraflarla paylaşabiliriz:

* **Grup şirketlerimiz.** Kişisel bilgilerinizi bu Gizlilik Bildiriminde belirtilen amaçlar için makul ölçüde gerekli olduğu şekilde bağlı kuruluşlarımızla veya grup şirketlerimizle paylaşabiliriz.
* **Hizmet sağlayıcılar.** Kişisel bilgilerinizi bizim adımıza web sitelerini barındırma, anket yapma, işlem gerçekleştirme, Sitelerimizi analiz etme ve işimizin, Sitelerimizin, ürünlerimizin ve hizmetlerimizin kalitesini iyileştirmek için analizler gerçekleştirme gibi hizmetler sunmaları için sözleşme yaptığımız şirketlerle paylaşabiliriz. Bu hizmet sağlayıcıların kişisel bilgilerin gizliliğini korumalarını talep ederiz.
* **Dağıtımcılar ve diğer güvenilir iş ortakları.** Kişisel bilgilerinizi ürünlerimizi dağıtan üçünü taraflarla veya diğer güvenilir iş ortaklarıyla söz konusu üçüncü tarafların size pazarlama iletileri göndermesine olanak sağlamayı içeren amaçlarla paylaşabiliriz. Kişisel bilgilerin pazarlama amacıyla bu şekilde paylaşılması yürürlükteki yasalara ve yönetmeliklere uygun olarak gerçekleştirilir.
* **İşlemlerle bağlantılı olarak ifşa.** Belirli işlemlerle bağlantılı olarak kişisel bilgilerinizin bir kısmını veya tamamını işlemin yerine getirilmesinde rol oynayan mali kuruluşlara, kamu tüzel kişiliklerine ve taşımacılık şirketlerine veya posta hizmetlerine ifşa edebiliriz.
* **Satın almalar veya elden çıkarmalarla bağlantılı ifşa.** Honeywell'in stratejik veya diğer ticari nedenlerle bazı ülkelerde işletmeleri satmaya, satın almaya, elden çıkarmaya, birleştirmeye veya başka bir şekilde yeniden düzenlemeye karar verdiği durumlar ortaya çıkabilir. Hakkınızda tuttuğumuz bilgileri bir birleşmenin pazarlıklarının sürmesi veya tamamlanması, Honeywell'in varlıklarının bir kısmının veya tamamının alınması, elden çıkarılması veya satılması için gereken makul düzeyde ifşa edebiliriz.
* **Başka nedenlerle ifşa.** Yasaların zorunlu kılması ya da izin vermesi veya yasal gereklere ya da hakkımızdaki yasal bir sürece uymak, haklarımızı ya da mal ve mülkümüzü korumak ve savunmak veya acil durumlarda herhangi bir kimsenin kişisel emniyetini korumak için bunun gerekli olduğuna art niyetsiz olarak kani olunması durumunda kişisel bilgileri ifşa edebiliriz.

**Uluslararası aktarımlar**

Honeywell küresel bir kuruluştur ve kişisel bilgileriniz yürürlükteki yasalara uygun olarak ABD, Meksika ve Hindistan gibi dünyanın çeşitli yerlerinde aktarılabilir, tutulabilir, saklanabilir veya kullanılabilir. Bu, kişisel bilgilerinizi topladığımızda, ülkenizin yasalarından farklı veri koruma yasalarına sahip olabilecek ülkelerde işlenebileceği anlamına gelir. Ancak Honeywell, gizliliğinizi korumak ve Avrupa Komisyonu'nun Standart Sözleşme Maddelerinin uygulanmasını da içeren ikamet ettiğiniz ülkeyle karşılaştırılabilir düzeyde kişisel bilgilerin korunmasını sağlamak için her zaman makul adımlar atacaktır. Kişisel bilgilerinizi korumaya yönelik uygun önlemler hakkında daha fazla bilgi için lütfen [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com) adresinden bizimle iletişime geçin.

**Güvenlik**

Kişisel bilgilerinizin güvenliğini koruma kararlılığıyla çalışırız. Kişisel bilgilerinizin işlenmesi riskine uygun bir güvenlik düzeyi sağlamak için teknik ve organizasyonel önlemler alıyoruz. Honeywell'in kişisel bilgilerinizi nasıl koruduğu hakkında daha fazla bilgi için [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com) adresinden bizimle iletişime geçin.

**Haklarınız**

Yürürlükteki yasalara bağlı olarak, kişisel bilgilerinizle ilgili belirli haklara sahip olabilirsiniz.

* Kişisel bilgilerinize dair **erişim, düzeltme, güncelleme** veya **silme talebinde bulunma** hakkınız olabilir.
* Kişisel bilgilerinizin işlenmesine **itiraz edebilir**, kişisel bilgilerinizin işlenmesini **kısıtlamamızı** isteyebilir veya kişisel bilgilerinizin **taşınabilirliğini** talep edebilirsiniz.
* Bu kararın sizin hakkınızda yasal sonuçlar doğurması veya sizi önemli ölçüde etkilemesi durumunda, **profil çıkarma da dahil olmak üzere, yalnızca otomatik işlemeye dayalı bir karar vermeme** hakkına sahip olabilirsiniz.
* Benzer şekilde, kişisel bilgilerinizi sizin rızanızla toplamış ve işlemişsek, bu durumda **onayınızı istediğiniz zaman geri çekebilirsiniz**. Onayınızı geri çekmeniz, geri çekmenizden önce gerçekleştirdiğimiz herhangi bir işlemin yasallığını etkilemeyecek ve onay dışındaki yasal işleme gerekçelerine dayanarak yürütülen kişisel bilgilerinizin işlenmesini etkilemeyecektir.
* Kişisel bilgilerinizin satışını **devre dışı bırakma hakkına sahip olabilirsiniz**. Honeywell, kişisel bilgilerinizi kar amacıyla üçüncü taraflara satmaz. Ancak, bu Gizlilik Bildirimi ve [Çerez Bildirimimiz](https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/cookie-notice#turkish) uyarınca kişisel bilgilerinizi üçüncü taraflarla paylaşır veya başka bir şekilde ifşa ederiz. Örneğin, ürünlerimizi dağıtmak, size teknik yardım sağlamak, web sitesi analitik araçlarını ve özelliklerini çalıştırmak ve ürün ve hizmetlerimizin pazarlanması ve satışını yapmak için üçüncü taraflarla etkileşime gireriz. Bu tür faaliyetler, kişisel bilgilerinizin üçüncü taraflara ifşa edilmesini içerebilir ve belirli (ancak hepsi olmamak üzere) veri koruma yasaları uyarınca verilerin "satışı" olarak değerlendirilebilir.
* Kişisel bilgilerinizin işlenmesinin veri koruma yasasına uygun olmadığını düşünüyorsanız, kişisel bilgilerinizi toplamamız ve kullanmamız hakkında yargı bölgenizdeki veri koruma yasasına uyumu denetlemekten sorumlu bir veri koruma yetkilisine **şikayette bulunma** hakkınız vardır. Örneğin, AEA'daki bireyler, yetkili Veri Koruma Kurumu'na şikayette bulunma hakkına sahiptir. Bunların listesine şuradan erişebilirsiniz: [https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/board/members\_en](https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/board/members_en). Bununla birlikte, sorunlarınızın üzerine eğilmek istediğimizden, herhangi bir şikayetinizle ilgili olarak lütfen bizimle iletişime geçmekten çekinmeyin. Veri gizliliği haklarını kullandıkları için bireylere karşı ayrımcılık yapmayacağız.

Yürürlükteki yasalara uygun olarak, sizin için geçerli olan hakları kullanmanızı kolaylaştırırız. Bununla birlikte, kişisel bilgileriniz bir veri koruma yasası kapsamında koruma sağlamasa veya başka bir şekilde korunmasa bile, veri işleme faaliyetlerimizle ilgili olabilecek herhangi bir talep veya sorguyu yerine getirmeye çalışabiliriz. Haklarınızla ilgili sorularınız varsa veya haklarınızı kullanmak istiyorsanız, [Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com](mailto:Honeywellprivacy@honeywell.com) adresinden bizimle iletişime geçebilirsiniz veya aşağıdaki bağlantıdaki interaktif web formumuz aracılığıyla gizliliğe dair sorularınızı gönderebilirsiniz:

**Çocuklarla ilgili bilgiler**

Sitelerimiz on altı (16) yaşın altındaki çocuklara yönelik değildir ve bu çocuklar tarafından kullanılmamalıdır; bu tür bireylerden bilerek bilgi toplamaz, kullanmaz veya satmayız. Ülkenizin yasalarına göre reşit değilseniz, lütfen Sitelerimiz aracılığıyla herhangi bir kişisel bilgi göndermeyin.

**Diğer web sitelerine bağlantılar**

Sitelerimiz üçüncü taraf web sitelerine, ürünlere ve hizmetlere bağlantılar içerebilir. Bu web sitelerine, ürünler ve hizmetlere, bunların politikalarına veya kişisel bilgilerinizi toplamalarına ya da başka şekilde işlemelerine dair hiçbir sorumluluğumuz veya yükümlülüğümüz yoktur. Bu üçüncü tarafların uygulamaları kendi gizlilik politikalarına tabidir. Söz konusu üçüncü tarafların gizlilik politikaları hakkında bilgi edinmenizi öneririz.

**Bize ulaşın**

Bu Gizlilik Bildirimi veya kişisel bilgilerinizin ele alınmasıyla ilgili sorularınız varsa, bir şikayette bulunmak veya Veri Koruma Sorumlumuza başvurmak isterseniz, lütfen aşağıda belirtilen iletişim bilgilerini kullanarak bizimle iletişime geçin. Kaygılarınızı en kısa sürede ortadan kaldırmaya ve tatmin edici bir çözüme ulaşmaya çalışırız.

İnteraktif Web formu:  
  
E-posta:  
  
Posta Adresi:  
Honeywell Privacy  
4D5  
115 Tabor Road  
Morris Plains, NJ 07950  
  
Ücretsiz Hat:  

**İşbu Gizlilik Bildiriminde Yapılacak Değişiklikler**

Bu Gizlilik Bildirimini zaman zaman güncelleyebiliriz. Güncellediğimizde Gizlilik Bildiriminin üstündeki "son güncellenme tarihi"ni gözden geçirerek değiştiririz ve yasaların gerektirebileceği şekilde buna benzer ilave tedbirler alırız.

**Son güncelleme: 11 Haziran 2021**

Businesses

What We Do

INDUSTRIES

Company

News

Careers

Contact Us

FOLLOW US

Copyright © 2024 Honeywell International Inc.
